<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for The GNU C Library -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/the%20gnu%20c%20library/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for The GNU C Library -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-33599|2024-05-06T19:21:54.314Z -- The GNU C Library -- glibc
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33599</link><description>nscd: Stack-based buffer overflow in netgroup cache

If the Name Service Cache Daemon's (nscd) fixed size cache is exhausted
by client requests then a subsequent client request for netgroup data
may result in a stack-based buffer overflow.  This flaw was introduced
in glibc 2.15 when the cache was added to nscd.

This vulnerability is only present in the nscd binary.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33599|2024-05-06T19:21:54.314Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:21:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33602|2024-05-06T19:22:12.383Z -- The GNU C Library -- glibc
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33602</link><description>nscd: netgroup cache assumes NSS callback uses in-buffer strings

The Name Service Cache Daemon's (nscd) netgroup cache can corrupt memory
when the NSS callback does not store all strings in the provided buffer.
The flaw was introduced in glibc 2.15 when the cache was added to nscd.

This vulnerability is only present in the nscd binary.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33602|2024-05-06T19:22:12.383Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:22:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33601|2024-05-06T19:22:07.763Z -- The GNU C Library -- glibc
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33601</link><description>nscd: netgroup cache may terminate daemon on memory allocation failure

The Name Service Cache Daemon's (nscd) netgroup cache uses xmalloc or
xrealloc and these functions may terminate the process due to a memory
allocation failure resulting in a denial of service to the clients.  The
flaw was introduced in glibc 2.15 when the cache was added to nscd.

This vulnerability is only present in the nscd binary.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33601|2024-05-06T19:22:07.763Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33600|2024-05-06T19:22:02.726Z -- The GNU C Library -- glibc
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33600</link><description>nscd: Null pointer crashes after notfound response

If the Name Service Cache Daemon's (nscd) cache fails to add a not-found
netgroup response to the cache, the client request can result in a null
pointer dereference.  This flaw was introduced in glibc 2.15 when the
cache was added to nscd.

This vulnerability is only present in the nscd binary.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33600|2024-05-06T19:22:02.726Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2961|2024-04-17T17:51:03.169Z -- The GNU C Library -- glibc
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2961</link><description>The iconv() function in the GNU C Library versions 2.39 and older may overflow the output buffer passed to it by up to 4 bytes when converting strings to the ISO-2022-CN-EXT character set, which may be used to crash an application or overwrite a neighbouring variable.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2961|2024-04-17T17:51:03.169Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 17:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>