<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for rofl0r -- MacGeiger</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/rofl0r/macgeiger.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for rofl0r -- MacGeiger</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20161|2024-08-05T21:45:25.980Z -- rofl0r -- macgeiger
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20161</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in rofl0r MacGeiger. Affected is the function dump_wlan_at of the file macgeiger.c of the component ESSID Handler. The manipulation leads to injection. Access to the local network is required for this attack to succeed. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The name of the patch is 57f1dd50a4821b8c8e676e8020006ae4bfd3c9cb. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-217188.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in rofl0r MacGeiger entdeckt. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion dump_wlan_at der Datei macgeiger.c der Komponente ESSID Handler. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei im lokalen Netzwerk erfolgen. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie gilt als schwierig auszunutzen. Der Patch wird als 57f1dd50a4821b8c8e676e8020006ae4bfd3c9cb bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20161|2024-08-05T21:45:25.980Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 15:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
