<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Brainstorm Force -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/brainstorm%20force/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Brainstorm Force -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-29768|2024-03-27T13:03:39.274Z -- Brainstorm Force -- Astra
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29768</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Brainstorm Force Astra allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Astra: from n/a through 4.6.4.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29768|2024-03-27T13:03:39.274Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 13:03:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4838|2024-05-16T11:05:27.037Z -- Brainstorm Force -- ConvertPlus
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4838</link><description>The ConvertPlus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.26 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'settings_encoded' attribute of the 'smile_modal' shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4838|2024-05-16T11:05:27.037Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:05:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3828|2024-05-10T06:44:58.424Z -- Brainstorm Force -- Spectra Pro
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3828</link><description>The Spectra Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.5. This is due to the plugin allowing lower-privileged users to create registration forms and set the default role to administrator This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to create administrator-level accounts.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3828|2024-05-10T06:44:58.424Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 06:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3240|2024-05-04T03:31:03.810Z -- Brainstorm Force -- ConvertPlug
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3240</link><description>The ConvertPlug plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.25 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'settings_encoded' attribute of the 'smile_info_bar' shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3240|2024-05-04T03:31:03.810Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 03:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3237|2024-05-04T03:31:03.130Z -- Brainstorm Force -- ConvertPlug
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3237</link><description>The ConvertPlug plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the cp_dismiss_notice() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.25. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary option values to true.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3237|2024-05-04T03:31:03.130Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 03:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>