<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for bdthemes -- Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bdthemes/element%20pack%20elementor%20addons%20%28header%20footer%2C%20template%20library%2C%20dynamic%20grid%20%26%20carousel%2C%20remote%20arrows%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for bdthemes -- Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1429|2024-06-04T18:01:37.023Z -- bdthemes -- element%20pack%20elementor%20addons%20%28header%20footer%2C%20template%20library%2C%20dynamic%20grid%20%26%20carousel%2C%20remote%20arrows%29
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1429</link>
      <description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter Grid) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘tab_link’ attribute of the Panel Slider widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1429|2024-06-04T18:01:37.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 04:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1428|2024-04-06T07:34:54.449Z -- bdthemes -- element%20pack%20elementor%20addons%20%28header%20footer%2C%20template%20library%2C%20dynamic%20grid%20%26%20carousel%2C%20remote%20arrows%29
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1428</link>
      <description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter Grid) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘element_pack_wrapper_link’ attribute of the Trailer Box widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1428|2024-04-06T07:34:54.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 07:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1426|2024-04-18T04:32:58.633Z -- bdthemes -- element%20pack%20elementor%20addons%20%28header%20footer%2C%20template%20library%2C%20dynamic%20grid%20%26%20carousel%2C%20remote%20arrows%29
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1426</link>
      <description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter Grid) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘link’ attribute of the Price List widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1426|2024-04-18T04:32:58.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 04:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0837|2024-04-06T07:34:55.697Z -- bdthemes -- element%20pack%20elementor%20addons%20%28header%20footer%2C%20template%20library%2C%20dynamic%20grid%20%26%20carousel%2C%20remote%20arrows%29
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0837</link>
      <description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter Grid) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the image URL parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0837|2024-04-06T07:34:55.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 07:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3926|2024-05-22T14:32:39.251Z -- bdthemes -- element%20pack%20elementor%20addons%20%28header%20footer%2C%20template%20library%2C%20dynamic%20grid%20%26%20carousel%2C%20remote%20arrows%29
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3926</link>
      <description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the custom_attributes value in widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3926|2024-05-22T14:32:39.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 14:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3927|2024-06-04T17:33:02.846Z -- bdthemes -- element%20pack%20elementor%20addons%20%28header%20footer%2C%20template%20library%2C%20dynamic%20grid%20%26%20carousel%2C%20remote%20arrows%29
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3927</link>
      <description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Form Submission Admin Email Bypass  in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.3. This is due to the plugin not properly checking for all variations of an administrators emails. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the restriction using a +value when submitting the contact form.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3927|2024-06-04T17:33:02.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 06:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2966|2024-04-11T07:31:36.278Z -- bdthemes -- element%20pack%20elementor%20addons%20%28header%20footer%2C%20template%20library%2C%20dynamic%20grid%20%26%20carousel%2C%20remote%20arrows%29
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2966</link>
      <description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.6 via the  element_pack_ajax_search function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including password protected post details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2966|2024-04-11T07:31:36.278Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 07:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
