<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for The Foreman Project -- foreman</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/the%20foreman%20project/foreman.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for The Foreman Project -- foreman</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:23:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8613|2024-08-06T02:27:40.956Z -- the%20foreman%20project -- foreman
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8613</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in foreman 1.5.1. The remote execution plugin runs commands on hosts over SSH from the Foreman web UI. When a job is submitted that contains HTML tags, the console output shown in the web UI does not escape the output causing any HTML or JavaScript to run in the user's browser. The output of the job is stored, making this a stored XSS vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8613|2024-08-06T02:27:40.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8634|2024-08-06T02:27:41.211Z -- the%20foreman%20project -- foreman
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8634</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in foreman 1.14.0. When creating an organization or location in Foreman, if the name contains HTML then the second step of the wizard (/organizations/id/step2) will render the HTML. This occurs in the alertbox on the page. The result is a stored XSS attack if an organization/location with HTML in the name is created, then a user is linked directly to this URL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8634|2024-08-06T02:27:41.211Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8639|2024-08-06T02:27:41.125Z -- the%20foreman%20project -- foreman
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8639</link>
      <description>It was found that foreman before 1.13.0 is vulnerable to a stored XSS via an organization or location name. This could allow an attacker with privileges to set the organization or location name to display arbitrary HTML including scripting code within the web interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8639|2024-08-06T02:27:41.125Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
