<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Accusoft -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/accusoft/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Accusoft -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:24:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21942|2024-09-17T03:27:37.292Z -- accusoft -- imagegear
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21942</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the TIFF YCbCr image parser functionality of Accusoft ImageGear 19.10. A specially-crafted file can lead to remote code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21942|2024-09-17T03:27:37.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 19:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21943|2024-09-17T02:47:56.877Z -- accusoft -- imagegear
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21943</link>
      <description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the XWD parser functionality of Accusoft ImageGear 19.10. A specially-crafted file can lead to code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21943|2024-09-17T02:47:56.877Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 19:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29465|2024-09-17T02:57:35.995Z -- accusoft -- imagegear
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29465</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the PSD Header processing memory allocation functionality of Accusoft ImageGear 20.0. A specially-crafted malformed file can lead to memory corruption. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29465|2024-09-17T02:57:35.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 21:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21938|2024-09-17T02:05:50.758Z -- accusoft -- imagegear
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21938</link>
      <description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Palette box parser functionality of Accusoft ImageGear 19.10. A specially-crafted file can lead to code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21938|2024-09-17T02:05:50.758Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 19:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21945|2024-09-17T00:50:58.802Z -- accusoft -- imagegear
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21945</link>
      <description>Two heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the TIFF parser functionality of Accusoft ImageGear 19.10. A specially-crafted file can lead to a heap buffer overflow. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This heap-based buffer oveflow takes place trying to copy the second 12 bits from local variable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21945|2024-09-17T00:50:58.802Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 19:55:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40398|2024-09-17T03:07:53.698Z -- accusoft -- imagegear
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40398</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the parse_raster_data functionality of Accusoft ImageGear 19.10. A specially-crafted malformed file can lead to memory corruption. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40398|2024-09-17T03:07:53.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 19:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
