<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for OpenC3 -- cosmos</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/openc3/cosmos.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for OpenC3 -- cosmos</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 20:24:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-47529|2024-10-02T19:53:00.936Z -- openc3 -- cosmos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47529</link>
      <description>OpenC3 COSMOS provides the functionality needed to send commands to and receive data from one or more embedded systems. OpenC3 COSMOS stores the password of a user unencrypted in the LocalStorage of a web browser. This makes the user password susceptible to exfiltration via Cross-site scripting (see GHSL-2024-128). This vulnerability is fixed in 5.19.0. This only affects Open Source edition, and not OpenC3 COSMOS Enterprise Edition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-47529|2024-10-02T19:53:00.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-43795|2024-10-02T19:54:35.777Z -- openc3 -- cosmos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43795</link>
      <description>OpenC3 COSMOS provides the functionality needed to send commands to and receive data from one or more embedded systems. The login functionality contains a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.19.0. Note: This CVE only affects Open Source Edition, and not OpenC3 COSMOS Enterprise Edition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-43795|2024-10-02T19:54:35.777Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-46977|2024-10-02T19:53:51.219Z -- openc3 -- cosmos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46977</link>
      <description>OpenC3 COSMOS provides the functionality needed to send commands to and receive data from one or more embedded systems. A path traversal vulnerability inside of LocalMode's open_local_file method allows an authenticated user with adequate permissions to download any .txt via the ScreensController#show on the web server COSMOS is running on (depending on the file permissions). This vulnerability is fixed in 5.19.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-46977|2024-10-02T19:53:51.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
