<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for oznetmaster -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oznetmaster/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for oznetmaster -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 23:22:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-10067|2024-08-06T08:58:26.404Z -- oznetmaster -- ssharpsmartthreadpool
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10067</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in oznetmaster SSharpSmartThreadPool. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file SSharpSmartThreadPool/SmartThreadPool.cs. The manipulation leads to race condition within a thread. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The patch is named 0e58073c831093aad75e077962e9fb55cad0dc5f. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-218463.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in oznetmaster SSharpSmartThreadPool ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei SSharpSmartThreadPool/SmartThreadPool.cs. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine race condition within a thread-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie ist schwierig auszunutzen. Der Patch wird als 0e58073c831093aad75e077962e9fb55cad0dc5f bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-10067|2024-08-06T08:58:26.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
