<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for themeisle -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/themeisle/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for themeisle -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1497|2024-03-13T15:27:11.726Z -- themeisle -- Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1497</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the form widget addr2_width attribute in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1497|2024-03-13T15:27:11.726Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1317|2024-02-20T18:56:46.572Z -- themeisle -- RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1317</link><description>The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘search_key’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1317|2024-02-20T18:56:46.572Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1323|2024-02-27T04:32:17.160Z -- themeisle -- Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1323</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Post Type Grid Widget Title in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1323|2024-02-27T04:32:17.160Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 04:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1499|2024-03-13T15:27:19.793Z -- themeisle -- Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1499</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Pricing Table widget in the  $settings['title_tags'] parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1499|2024-03-13T15:27:19.793Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1047|2024-02-02T05:33:14.536Z -- themeisle -- Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1047</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the register_reference() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.28. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the connected API keys.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1047|2024-02-02T05:33:14.536Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 05:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1092|2024-02-05T21:21:53.970Z -- themeisle -- RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1092</link><description>The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized data modification due to a missing capability check on the feedzy dashboard in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to create, edit or delete feed categories created by them.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1092|2024-02-05T21:21:53.970Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1162|2024-02-02T05:33:15.140Z -- themeisle -- Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1162</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.29. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the register_reference() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers  to update the connected API keys via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1162|2024-02-02T05:33:15.140Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 05:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1318|2024-02-20T18:56:21.078Z -- themeisle -- RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1318</link><description>The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'feedzy_wizard_step_process' and 'import_status' functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor access and above, who are normally restricted to only being able to create posts rather than pages, to draft and publish posts with arbitrary content.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1318|2024-02-20T18:56:21.078Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0508|2024-02-05T21:22:05.610Z -- themeisle -- Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0508</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Pricing Table Elementor Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.27 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the user supplied link URL. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0508|2024-02-05T21:22:05.610Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:22:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4635|2024-05-16T05:33:27.125Z -- themeisle -- Menu Icons by ThemeIsle
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4635</link><description>The Menu Icons by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘add_mime_type’ function in versions up to, and including, 0.13.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4635|2024-05-16T05:33:27.125Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27958|2024-03-17T16:24:47.209Z -- Themeisle -- Visualizer
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27958</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themeisle Visualizer allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Visualizer: from n/a through 3.10.5.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27958|2024-03-17T16:24:47.209Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27951|2024-04-03T11:53:07.134Z -- Themeisle -- Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27951</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Themeisle Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG: from n/a through 3.4.0.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27951|2024-04-03T11:53:07.134Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 11:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30235|2024-03-26T12:20:25.690Z -- Themeisle -- Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30235</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Themeisle Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG.This issue affects Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG: from n/a through 3.4.0.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30235|2024-03-26T12:20:25.690Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 12:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31301|2024-04-12T12:32:01.111Z -- Themeisle -- Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31301</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Themeisle Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG.This issue affects Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG: from n/a through 3.4.0.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31301|2024-04-12T12:32:01.111Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3750|2024-05-16T02:36:48.950Z -- themeisle -- Visualizer: Tables and Charts Manager for WordPress
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3750</link><description>The Visualizer: Tables and Charts Manager for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and retrieval of data due to a missing capability check on the getQueryData() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.15. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to perform arbitrary SQL queries that can be leveraged for privilege escalation among many other actions.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3750|2024-05-16T02:36:48.950Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 02:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3344|2024-04-11T11:03:51.639Z -- themeisle -- Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3344</link><description>The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG file upload in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3344|2024-04-11T11:03:51.639Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 11:03:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3962|2024-04-26T08:29:20.259Z -- themeisle -- Product Addons &amp; Fields for WooCommerce
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3962</link><description>The Product Addons &amp; Fields for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the ppom_upload_file function in all versions up to, and including, 32.0.18. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. Successful exploitation requires the PPOM Pro plugin to be installed along with a WooCommerce product that contains a file upload field to retrieve the correct nonce.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3962|2024-04-26T08:29:20.259Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 08:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3343|2024-04-11T11:03:51.061Z -- themeisle -- Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3343</link><description>The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's block attributes in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3343|2024-04-11T11:03:51.061Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 11:03:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3725|2024-05-02T16:52:40.615Z -- themeisle -- Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3725</link><description>The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Post Grid widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as 'titleTag'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3725|2024-05-02T16:52:40.615Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2126|2024-03-13T15:26:32.648Z -- themeisle -- Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2126</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Registration Form widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.32 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2126|2024-03-13T15:26:32.648Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2226|2024-04-09T18:58:37.731Z -- themeisle -- Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2226</link><description>The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the id parameter in the google-map block in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor access and higher to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2226|2024-04-09T18:58:37.731Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2841|2024-03-29T04:31:34.185Z -- themeisle -- Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2841</link><description>The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as 'id'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2841|2024-03-29T04:31:34.185Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 04:31:34 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>