<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for themeisle -- Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/themeisle/orbit%20fox%20by%20themeisle.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for themeisle -- Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1497|2024-03-13T15:27:11.726Z -- themeisle -- Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1497</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the form widget addr2_width attribute in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1497|2024-03-13T15:27:11.726Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1323|2024-02-27T04:32:17.160Z -- themeisle -- Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1323</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Post Type Grid Widget Title in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1323|2024-02-27T04:32:17.160Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 04:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1499|2024-03-13T15:27:19.793Z -- themeisle -- Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1499</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Pricing Table widget in the  $settings['title_tags'] parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1499|2024-03-13T15:27:19.793Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1047|2024-02-02T05:33:14.536Z -- themeisle -- Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1047</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the register_reference() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.28. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the connected API keys.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1047|2024-02-02T05:33:14.536Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 05:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1162|2024-02-02T05:33:15.140Z -- themeisle -- Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1162</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.29. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the register_reference() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers  to update the connected API keys via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1162|2024-02-02T05:33:15.140Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 05:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0508|2024-02-05T21:22:05.610Z -- themeisle -- Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0508</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Pricing Table Elementor Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.27 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the user supplied link URL. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0508|2024-02-05T21:22:05.610Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:22:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2126|2024-03-13T15:26:32.648Z -- themeisle -- Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2126</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Registration Form widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.32 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2126|2024-03-13T15:26:32.648Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>