<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for themeisle -- Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/themeisle/otter%20blocks%20%E2%80%93%20gutenberg%20blocks%2C%20page%20builder%20for%20gutenberg%20editor%20%26%20fse.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for themeisle -- Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-3344|2024-04-11T11:03:51.639Z -- themeisle -- Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3344</link><description>The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG file upload in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3344|2024-04-11T11:03:51.639Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 11:03:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3343|2024-04-11T11:03:51.061Z -- themeisle -- Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3343</link><description>The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's block attributes in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3343|2024-04-11T11:03:51.061Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 11:03:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3725|2024-05-02T16:52:40.615Z -- themeisle -- Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3725</link><description>The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Post Grid widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as 'titleTag'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3725|2024-05-02T16:52:40.615Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2226|2024-04-09T18:58:37.731Z -- themeisle -- Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2226</link><description>The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the id parameter in the google-map block in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor access and higher to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2226|2024-04-09T18:58:37.731Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2841|2024-03-29T04:31:34.185Z -- themeisle -- Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2841</link><description>The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as 'id'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2841|2024-03-29T04:31:34.185Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 04:31:34 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>