<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for reflectionmedia -- Profile Builder – User Profile &amp; User Registration Forms</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/reflectionmedia/profile%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20user%20profile%20%26%20user%20registration%20forms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for reflectionmedia -- Profile Builder – User Profile &amp; User Registration Forms</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:23:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0814|2024-08-02T05:24:34.384Z -- reflectionmedia -- profile%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20user%20profile%20%26%20user%20registration%20forms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0814</link>
      <description>The Profile Builder – User Profile &amp; User Registration Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to sensitive information disclosure via the [user_meta] shortcode in versions up to, and including 3.9.0. This is due to insufficient restriction on sensitive user meta values that can be called via that shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions, and above to retrieve sensitive user meta that can be used to gain access to a high privileged user account. This does require the Usermeta shortcode be enabled to be exploited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0814|2024-08-02T05:24:34.384Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 01:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2297|2024-08-02T06:19:14.870Z -- reflectionmedia -- profile%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20user%20profile%20%26%20user%20registration%20forms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2297</link>
      <description>The Profile Builder – User Profile &amp; User Registration Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized password resets  in versions up to, and including 3.9.0. This is due to the plugin using native password reset functionality, with insufficient validation on the password reset function (wppb_front_end_password_recovery). The function uses the plaintext value of a password reset key instead of a hashed value which means it can easily be retrieved and subsequently used. An attacker can leverage CVE-2023-0814, or another vulnerability like SQL Injection in another plugin or theme installed on the site to successfully exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2297|2024-08-02T06:19:14.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 23:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
