<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SAP SE -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sap%20se/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SAP SE -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 04:24:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40496|2024-08-04T02:44:10.795Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40496</link>
      <description>SAP Internet Communication framework (ICM) - versions 700, 701, 702, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 785, allows an attacker with logon functionality, to exploit the authentication function by using POST and form field to repeat executions of the initial command by a GET request and exposing sensitive data. This vulnerability is normally exposed over the network and successful exploitation can lead to exposure of data like system details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40496|2024-08-04T02:44:10.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40498|2024-08-04T02:44:10.780Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20successfactors%20mobile%20application%20%28for%20android%20devices%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40498</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SAP SuccessFactors Mobile Application for Android - versions older than 2108, which allows an attacker to prevent legitimate users from accessing a service, either by crashing or flooding the service, which can lead to denial of service. The vulnerability is related to Android implementation methods that are widely used across Android mobile applications, and such methods are embedded into the SAP SuccessFactors mobile application. These Android methods begin executing once the user accesses their profile on the mobile application. While executing, it can also pick up the activities from other Android applications that are running in the background of the users device and are using the same types of methods in the application. Such vulnerability can also lead to phishing attacks that can be used for staging other types of attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40498|2024-08-04T02:44:10.780Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42068|2024-08-04T03:22:25.961Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42068</link>
      <description>When a user opens a manipulated GIF (.gif) file received from untrusted sources in SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer - version 9.0, the application crashes and becomes temporarily unavailable to the user until restart of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42068|2024-08-04T03:22:25.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42066|2024-08-04T03:22:25.756Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42066</link>
      <description>SAP Business One - version 10.0, allows an admin user to view DB password in plain text over the network, which should otherwise be encrypted. For an attacker to discover vulnerable function in-depth application knowledge is required, but once exploited the attacker may be able to completely compromise confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42066|2024-08-04T03:22:25.756Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42069|2024-08-04T03:22:26.029Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42069</link>
      <description>When a user opens manipulated Tagged Image File Format (.tif) file received from untrusted sources in SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer - version 9.0, the application crashes and becomes temporarily unavailable to the user until restart of the application</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42069|2024-08-04T03:22:26.029Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40495|2024-08-04T02:44:10.857Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40495</link>
      <description>There are multiple Denial-of Service vulnerabilities in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755. An unauthorized attacker can use the public SICF service /sap/public/bc/abap to reduce the performance of SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40495|2024-08-04T02:44:10.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38178|2024-08-04T01:37:15.889Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38178</link>
      <description>The software logistics system of SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP and ABAP Platform versions - 700, 701, 702, 710, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, enables a malicious user to transfer ABAP code artifacts or content, by-passing the established quality gates. By this vulnerability malicious code can reach quality and production, and can compromise the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the system and its data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38178|2024-08-04T01:37:15.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42064|2024-08-04T03:22:25.989Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42064</link>
      <description>If configured to use an Oracle database and if a query is created using the flexible search java api with a parameterized "in" clause, SAP Commerce - versions 1905, 2005, 2105, 2011, allows attacker to execute crafted database queries, exposing backend database. The vulnerability is present if the parameterized "in" clause accepts more than 1000 values.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42064|2024-08-04T03:22:25.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42063|2024-08-04T03:22:25.975Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20knowledge%20warehouse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42063</link>
      <description>A security vulnerability has been discovered in the SAP Knowledge Warehouse - versions 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50. The usage of one SAP KW component within a Web browser enables unauthorized attackers to conduct XSS attacks, which might lead to disclose sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42063|2024-08-04T03:22:25.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40503|2024-08-04T02:44:10.837Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20gui%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40503</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in SAP GUI for Windows - versions &lt; 7.60 PL13, 7.70 PL4, which allows an attacker with sufficient privileges on the local client-side PC to obtain an equivalent of the user’s password. With this highly sensitive data leaked, the attacker would be able to logon to the backend system the SAP GUI for Windows was connected to and launch further attacks depending on the authorizations of the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40503|2024-08-04T02:44:10.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38164|2024-08-04T01:37:16.113Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20erp%20financial%20accounting%20%28rfopenposting_fr%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38164</link>
      <description>SAP ERP Financial Accounting (RFOPENPOSTING_FR) versions - SAP_APPL - 600, 602, 603, 604, 605, 606, 616, SAP_FIN - 617, 618, 700, 720, 730, SAPSCORE - 125, S4CORE, 100, 101, 102, 103, 104, 105, allows a registered attacker to invoke certain functions that would otherwise be restricted to specific users. These functions are normally exposed over the network and once exploited the attacker may be able to view and modify financial accounting data that only a specific user should have access to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38164|2024-08-04T01:37:16.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38150|2024-08-04T01:37:16.044Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38150</link>
      <description>When an attacker manages to get access to the local memory, or the memory dump of a victim, for example by a social engineering attack, SAP Business Client versions - 7.0, 7.70, will allow him to read extremely sensitive data, such as credentials. This would allow the attacker to compromise the corresponding backend for which the credentials are valid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38150|2024-08-04T01:37:16.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38180|2024-08-04T01:37:15.903Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38180</link>
      <description>SAP Business One - version 10.0, allows an attacker to inject formulas when exporting data to Excel (CSV injection) due to improper sanitation during the data export. An attacker could thereby execute arbitrary commands on the victim's computer but only if the victim allows to execute macros while opening the file and the security settings of Excel allow for command execution.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38180|2024-08-04T01:37:15.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38176|2024-08-04T01:37:16.300Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20s%2F4hana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38176</link>
      <description>Due to improper input sanitization, an authenticated user with certain specific privileges can remotely call NZDT function modules listed in Solution Section to execute manipulated query or inject ABAP code to gain access to Backend Database. On successful exploitation the threat actor could completely compromise confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38176|2024-08-04T01:37:16.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38182|2024-08-04T01:37:16.116Z -- sap%20se -- kyma
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38182</link>
      <description>Due to insufficient input validation of Kyma, authenticated users can pass a Header of their choice and escalate privileges which can completely compromise the cluster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38182|2024-08-04T01:37:16.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38163|2024-08-04T01:37:16.194Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28visual%20composer%207.0%20rt%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38163</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver (Visual Composer 7.0 RT) versions - 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, without restriction, an attacker authenticated as a non-administrative user can upload a malicious file over a network and trigger its processing, which is capable of running operating system commands with the privilege of the Java Server process. These commands can be used to read or modify any information on the server or shut the server down making it unavailable.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38163|2024-08-04T01:37:16.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-37531|2024-08-04T01:22:59.365Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20knowledge%20management%20xml%20forms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-37531</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Knowledge Management XML Forms versions - 7.10, 7.11, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, contains an XSLT vulnerability which allows a non-administrative authenticated attacker to craft a malicious XSL stylesheet file containing a script with OS-level commands, copy it into a location to be accessed by the system and then create a file which will trigger the XSLT engine to execute the script contained within the malicious XSL file. This can result in a full compromise of the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-37531|2024-08-04T01:22:59.365Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38179|2024-08-04T01:37:16.482Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38179</link>
      <description>Debug function of Admin UI of SAP Business One Integration is enabled by default. This allows Admin User to see the captured packet contents which may include User credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38179|2024-08-04T01:37:16.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38177|2024-08-04T01:37:16.323Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commoncryptolib
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38177</link>
      <description>SAP CommonCryptoLib version 8.5.38 or lower is vulnerable to null pointer dereference vulnerability when an unauthenticated attacker sends crafted malicious data in the HTTP requests over the network, this causes the SAP application to crash and has high impact on the availability of the SAP system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38177|2024-08-04T01:37:16.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40499|2024-08-04T02:44:10.842Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20for%20abap%20%28sap%20cloud%20print%20manager%20and%20sapsprint%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40499</link>
      <description>Client-side printing services SAP Cloud Print Manager and SAPSprint for SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP - versions 7.70, 7.70 PI, 7.70 BYD, allow an attacker to inject code that can be executed by the application. An attacker could thereby control the behavior of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40499|2024-08-04T02:44:10.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-37532|2024-08-04T01:23:01.245Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-37532</link>
      <description>SAP Business One version - 10, due to improper input validation, allows an authenticated User to gain access to directory and view the contents of index in the directory, which would otherwise be restricted to high privileged User.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-37532|2024-08-04T01:23:01.245Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38181|2024-08-04T01:37:15.601Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38181</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 700, 701, 702, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, allows an attacker to prevent legitimate users from accessing a service, either by crashing or flooding the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38181|2024-08-04T01:37:15.601Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38162|2024-08-04T01:37:15.668Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20web%20dispatcher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38162</link>
      <description>SAP Web Dispatcher versions - 7.49, 7.53, 7.77, 7.81, KRNL64NUC - 7.22, 7.22EXT, 7.49, KRNL64UC -7.22, 7.22EXT, 7.49, 7.53, KERNEL - 7.22, 7.49, 7.53, 7.77, 7.81, 7.83 processes allow an unauthenticated attacker to submit a malicious crafted request over a network to a front-end server which may, over several attempts, result in a back-end server confusing the boundaries of malicious and legitimate messages. This can result in the back-end server executing a malicious payload which can be used to read or modify any information on the server or consume server resources making it temporarily unavailable.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38162|2024-08-04T01:37:15.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42061|2024-08-04T03:22:25.820Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42061</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence) - version 420, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This allows a low privileged attacker to retrieve some data from the victim but will never be able to modify the document and publish these modifications to the server. It impacts the "Quick Prompt" workflow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42061|2024-08-04T03:22:25.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42070|2024-08-04T03:22:25.853Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42070</link>
      <description>When a user opens manipulated Jupiter Tessellation (.jt) file received from untrusted sources in SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer - version 9.0, the application crashes and becomes temporarily unavailable to the user until restart of the application</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42070|2024-08-04T03:22:25.853Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40502|2024-08-04T02:44:10.860Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40502</link>
      <description>SAP Commerce - versions 2105.3, 2011.13, 2005.18, 1905.34, does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. Authenticated attackers will be able to access and edit data from b2b units they do not belong to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40502|2024-08-04T02:44:10.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42062|2024-08-04T03:22:25.846Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20erp%20hcm%20portugal
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42062</link>
      <description>SAP ERP HCM Portugal does not perform necessary authorization checks for a report that reads the payroll data of employees in a certain area. Since the affected report only reads the payroll information, the attacker can neither modify any information nor cause availability impacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42062|2024-08-04T03:22:25.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40504|2024-08-04T02:44:10.769Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40504</link>
      <description>A certain template role in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 700, 701, 702, 710, 711, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, contains transport authorizations, which exceed expected display only permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40504|2024-08-04T02:44:10.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40497|2024-08-04T02:44:10.782Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20analysis%2C%20%28edition%20for%20olap%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40497</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Analysis (edition for OLAP) - versions 420, 430, allows an attacker to exploit certain application endpoints to read sensitive data. These endpoints are normally exposed over the network and successful exploitation could lead to exposure of some system specific data like its version.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40497|2024-08-04T02:44:10.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40500|2024-08-04T02:44:10.833Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28crystal%20reports%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40500</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Crystal Reports) - versions 420, 430, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit missing XML validations at endpoints to read sensitive data. These endpoints are normally exposed over the network and successful exploitation can enable the attacker to retrieve arbitrary files from the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40500|2024-08-04T02:44:10.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40501|2024-08-04T02:44:10.848Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20abap%20platform%20kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40501</link>
      <description>SAP ABAP Platform Kernel - versions 7.77, 7.81, 7.85, 7.86, does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated business user, resulting in escalation of privileges. That means this business user is able to read and modify data beyond the vulnerable system. However, the attacker can neither significantly reduce the performance of the system nor stop the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40501|2024-08-04T02:44:10.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38174|2024-08-04T01:37:15.770Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38174</link>
      <description>When a user opens manipulated files received from untrusted sources in SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer version - 9, the application crashes and becomes temporarily unavailable to the user until restart of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38174|2024-08-04T01:37:15.770Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38175|2024-08-04T01:37:16.309Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20analysis%20for%20microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38175</link>
      <description>SAP Analysis for Microsoft Office - version 2.8, allows an attacker with high privileges to read sensitive data over the network, and gather or change information in the current system without user interaction. The attack would not lead to an impact on the availability of the system, but there would be an impact on integrity and confidentiality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38175|2024-08-04T01:37:16.309Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-37535|2024-08-04T01:23:01.156Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20java%20%28jms%20connector%20service%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-37535</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server Java (JMS Connector Service) - versions 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, does not perform necessary authorization checks for user privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-37535|2024-08-04T01:23:01.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42067|2024-08-04T03:22:25.941Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42067</link>
      <description>In SAP NetWeaver AS for ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 701, 702, 711, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 786, an attacker authenticated as a regular user can use the S/4 Hana dashboard to reveal systems and services which they would not normally be allowed to see. No information alteration or denial of service is possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42067|2024-08-04T03:22:25.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 19:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38183|2024-08-04T01:37:16.304Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38183</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver - versions 700, 701, 702, 730, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, allowing an attacker to cause a potential victim to supply a malicious content to a vulnerable web application, which is then reflected to the victim and executed by the web browser, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38183|2024-08-04T01:37:16.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
