<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SAP SE -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sap%20se/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SAP SE -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6308|2024-08-04T08:55:22.240Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20services%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6308</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Services) versions - 410, 420, 430, allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject arbitrary values as CMS parameters to perform lookups on the internal network which is otherwise not accessible externally. On successful exploitation, attacker can scan internal network to determine internal infrastructure and gather information for further attacks like remote file inclusion, retrieve server files, bypass firewall and force the vulnerable server to perform malicious requests, resulting in a Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6308|2024-08-04T08:55:22.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 13:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6178|2024-08-04T08:55:22.177Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20enable%20now
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6178</link>
      <description>SAP Enable Now, before version 1911, sends the Session ID cookie value in URL. This might be stolen from the browser history or log files, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6178|2024-08-04T08:55:22.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6273|2024-08-04T08:55:22.195Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20s%2F4%20hana%20%28fiori%20ui%20for%20general%20ledger%20accounting%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6273</link>
      <description>SAP S/4 HANA (Fiori UI for General Ledger Accounting), versions 103, 104, does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user working with attachment service, allowing the attacker to delete attachments due to Missing Authorization Check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6273|2024-08-04T08:55:22.195Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 13:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0341|2024-08-04T17:44:16.467Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20enable%20now
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0341</link>
      <description>The session cookie used by SAP Enable Now, version 1902, does not have the HttpOnly flag set. If an attacker runs script code in the context of the application, he could get access to the session cookie. The session cookie could then be abused to gain access to the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0341|2024-08-04T17:44:16.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 13:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0248|2024-08-04T17:44:16.209Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20gateway%20of%20abap%20application%20server%28sap_gwfnd%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0248</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP Gateway of ABAP Application Server (fixed in SAP_GWFND 7.5, 7.51, 7.52, 7.53; SAP_BASIS 7.5) allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0248|2024-08-04T17:44:16.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6218|2024-08-04T08:55:22.118Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6218</link>
      <description>Admin tools and Query Builder in SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform, versions 4.1, 4.2, allows an attacker to access information that should otherwise be restricted, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6218|2024-08-04T08:55:22.118Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6375|2024-08-04T09:02:40.215Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6375</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated Right Computer Graphics Metafile (.cgm) file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6375|2024-08-04T09:02:40.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 01:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6318|2024-08-04T08:55:22.456Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28abap%20server%29%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6318</link>
      <description>A Remote Code Execution vulnerability exists in the SAP NetWeaver (ABAP Server, up to release 7.40) and ABAP Platform (&gt; release 7.40).Because of this, an attacker can exploit these products via Code Injection, and potentially enabling to take complete control of the products, including viewing, changing, or deleting data by injecting code into the working memory which is subsequently executed by the application. It can also be used to cause a general fault in the product, causing the products to terminate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6318|2024-08-04T08:55:22.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6310|2024-08-04T08:55:22.287Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28abap%20server%29%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6310</link>
      <description>Improper access control in SOA Configuration Trace component in SAP NetWeaver (ABAP Server) and ABAP Platform, versions - 702, 730, 731, 740, 750, allows any authenticated user to enumerate all SAP users, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6310|2024-08-04T08:55:22.287Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 13:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6320|2024-08-04T08:55:22.241Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20marketing%20%28mobile%20channel%20servlet%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6320</link>
      <description>SAP Marketing (Servlet), version-130,140,150, allows an authenticated attacker to invoke certain functions that are restricted. Limited knowledge of payload is required for an attacker to exploit the vulnerability and perform tasks related to contact and interaction data which impacts Confidentiality and Integrity of data in the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6320|2024-08-04T08:55:22.241Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6305|2024-08-04T08:55:22.450Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20process%20integration%20-%20rest%20adapter%20%28sap_xiaf%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6305</link>
      <description>PI Rest Adapter of SAP Process Integration (update provided in SAP_XIAF 7.31, 7.40, 7.50) does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6305|2024-08-04T08:55:22.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 17:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40496|2024-08-04T02:44:10.795Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40496</link>
      <description>SAP Internet Communication framework (ICM) - versions 700, 701, 702, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 785, allows an attacker with logon functionality, to exploit the authentication function by using POST and form field to repeat executions of the initial command by a GET request and exposing sensitive data. This vulnerability is normally exposed over the network and successful exploitation can lead to exposure of data like system details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40496|2024-08-04T02:44:10.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0254|2024-08-04T17:44:16.378Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20disclosure%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0254</link>
      <description>SAP Disclosure Management (before version 10.1 Stack 1301) does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0254|2024-08-04T17:44:16.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6303|2024-08-04T08:55:22.413Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20disclosure%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6303</link>
      <description>SAP Disclosure Management, before version 10.1, does not validate user input properly in specific use cases leading to Cross-Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6303|2024-08-04T08:55:22.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 17:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0338|2024-08-04T17:44:16.440Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0338</link>
      <description>During an OData V2/V4 request in SAP Gateway, versions 750, 751, 752, 753, the HTTP Header attributes cache-control and pragma were not properly set, allowing an attacker to access restricted information, resulting in Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0338|2024-08-04T17:44:16.440Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 13:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6248|2024-08-04T08:55:22.251Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20adaptive%20server%20enterprise%20%28backup%20server%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6248</link>
      <description>SAP Adaptive Server Enterprise (Backup Server), version 16.0, does not perform the necessary validation checks for an authenticated user while executing DUMP or LOAD command allowing arbitrary code execution or Code Injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6248|2024-08-04T08:55:22.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:50:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6327|2024-08-04T08:55:22.290Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6327</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated 3DM file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6327|2024-08-04T08:55:22.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6348|2024-08-04T09:02:39.054Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6348</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated GIF file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6348|2024-08-04T09:02:39.054Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:52:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6343|2024-08-04T09:02:39.027Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6343</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated EPS file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6343|2024-08-04T09:02:39.027Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6210|2024-08-04T08:55:21.854Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20fiori%20launchpad
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6210</link>
      <description>SAP Fiori Launchpad, versions- 753, 754, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, and hence allowing the attacker to inject the meta tag into the launchpad html using the vulnerable parameter, leading to reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6210|2024-08-04T08:55:21.854Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0333|2024-08-04T17:44:16.500Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0333</link>
      <description>In some situations, when a client cancels a query in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence), versions 4.2, 4.3, the attacker can then query and receive the whole data set instead of just what is part of their authorized security profile, resulting in Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0333|2024-08-04T17:44:16.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 13:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0245|2024-08-04T17:44:15.952Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui%20%28sapscore%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0245</link>
      <description>SAP CRM WebClient UI (fixed in SAPSCORE 1.12; S4FND 1.02; WEBCUIF 7.31, 7.46, 7.47, 7.48, 8.0, 8.01) does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0245|2024-08-04T17:44:15.952Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6252|2024-08-04T08:55:22.304Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20adaptive%20server%20enterprise%20%28cockpit%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6252</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP Adaptive Server Enterprise (Cockpit), version 16.0, allows an attacker with access to local network, to get sensitive and confidential information, leading to Information Disclosure. It can be used to get user account credentials, tamper with system data and impact system availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6252|2024-08-04T08:55:22.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40498|2024-08-04T02:44:10.780Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20successfactors%20mobile%20application%20%28for%20android%20devices%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40498</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SAP SuccessFactors Mobile Application for Android - versions older than 2108, which allows an attacker to prevent legitimate users from accessing a service, either by crashing or flooding the service, which can lead to denial of service. The vulnerability is related to Android implementation methods that are widely used across Android mobile applications, and such methods are embedded into the SAP SuccessFactors mobile application. These Android methods begin executing once the user accesses their profile on the mobile application. While executing, it can also pick up the activities from other Android applications that are running in the background of the users device and are using the same types of methods in the application. Such vulnerability can also lead to phishing attacks that can be used for staging other types of attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40498|2024-08-04T02:44:10.780Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6196|2024-08-04T08:55:22.097Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20mobile%20%28mobilebiservice%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6196</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Mobile (MobileBIService), version 4.2, allows an attacker to generate multiple requests, using which he can block all the threads resulting in a Denial of Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6196|2024-08-04T08:55:22.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0325|2024-08-04T17:44:16.457Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20erp%20hcm%20%28sap_hrces%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0325</link>
      <description>SAP ERP HCM (SAP_HRCES) , version 3, does not perform necessary authorization checks for a report that reads payroll data of employees in a certain area. Due to this under certain conditions, the user that once had authorization to payroll data of an employee, which was later revoked, may retain access to the same data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0325|2024-08-04T17:44:16.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 19:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0268|2024-08-04T17:44:16.566Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28cmc%20module%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0268</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (CMC Module), versions 4.10, 4.20 and 4.30, does not sufficiently validate an XML document accepted from an untrusted source.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0268|2024-08-04T17:44:16.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6300|2024-08-04T08:55:22.278Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28central%20management%20console%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6300</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (Central Management Console), versions- 4.2, 4.3, allows an attacker with administrator rights can use the web application to send malicious code to a different end user (victim), as it does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs for RecycleBin, resulting in Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6300|2024-08-04T08:55:22.278Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 13:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42068|2024-08-04T03:22:25.961Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42068</link>
      <description>When a user opens a manipulated GIF (.gif) file received from untrusted sources in SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer - version 9.0, the application crashes and becomes temporarily unavailable to the user until restart of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42068|2024-08-04T03:22:25.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6324|2024-08-04T08:55:22.441Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20%28bsp%20test%20application%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6324</link>
      <description>SAP Netweaver AS ABAP(BSP Test Application sbspext_table), version-700,701,720,730,731,740,750,751,752,753,754,755, allows an unauthenticated attacker to send polluted URL to the victim, when the victim clicks on this URL, the attacker can read, modify the information available in the victim�s browser leading to Reflected Cross Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6324|2024-08-04T08:55:22.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 13:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0405|2024-08-04T17:51:26.482Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20enable%20now
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0405</link>
      <description>SAP Enable Now, before version 1911, leaks information about the existence of a particular user which can be used to construct a list of users, leading to a user enumeration vulnerability and Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0405|2024-08-04T17:51:26.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 21:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0262|2024-08-04T17:44:16.308Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20webintelligence%20bilaunchpad%20%28enterprise%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0262</link>
      <description>SAP WebIntelligence BILaunchPad, versions 4.10, 4.20, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs in generated HTML reports, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0262|2024-08-04T17:44:16.308Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26817|2024-08-04T16:03:22.767Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26817</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows an user to open manipulated HPGL file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26817|2024-08-04T16:03:22.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26824|2024-08-04T16:03:22.411Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28java%20stack%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26824</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager (JAVA stack), version - 7.20, allows an unauthenticated attacker to compromise the system because of missing authorization checks in the Upgrade Legacy Ports Service, this has an impact to the integrity and availability of the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26824|2024-08-04T16:03:22.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6336|2024-08-04T09:02:39.055Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6336</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated PCX file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6336|2024-08-04T09:02:39.055Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-44233|2024-08-04T04:17:24.884Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20grc%20access%20control
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-44233</link>
      <description>SAP GRC Access Control - versions V1100_700, V1100_731, V1200_750, does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, which could lead to escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-44233|2024-08-04T04:17:24.884Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42066|2024-08-04T03:22:25.756Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42066</link>
      <description>SAP Business One - version 10.0, allows an admin user to view DB password in plain text over the network, which should otherwise be encrypted. For an attacker to discover vulnerable function in-depth application knowledge is required, but once exploited the attacker may be able to completely compromise confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42066|2024-08-04T03:22:25.756Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0330|2024-08-04T17:44:16.508Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20diagnostic%20agent%20%28lm-service%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0330</link>
      <description>The OS Command Plugin in the transaction GPA_ADMIN and the OSCommand Console of SAP Diagnostic Agent (LM-Service), version 7.2, allow an attacker to inject code that can be executed by the application. An attacker could thereby control the behavior of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0330|2024-08-04T17:44:16.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 19:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6264|2024-08-04T08:55:22.245Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6264</link>
      <description>SAP Commerce, versions - 6.7, 1808, 1811, 1905, may allow an attacker to access information under certain conditions which would otherwise be restricted, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6264|2024-08-04T08:55:22.245Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 12:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0350|2024-08-04T17:44:16.493Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20hana%20database
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0350</link>
      <description>SAP HANA Database, versions 1.0, 2.0, allows an unauthorized attacker to send a malformed connection request, which crashes the indexserver of an SAP HANA instance, leading to Denial of Service</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0350|2024-08-04T17:44:16.493Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 14:33:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0340|2024-08-04T17:44:16.515Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20enable%20now
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0340</link>
      <description>The XML parser, which is being used by SAP Enable Now, before version 1902, has not been hardened correctly, leading to Missing XML Validation vulnerability. This issue affects the file upload at multiple locations. An attacker can read local XXE files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0340|2024-08-04T17:44:16.515Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 13:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0241|2024-08-04T17:44:16.098Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20work%20and%20inventory%20manager%20%28agentry_sdk%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0241</link>
      <description>SAP Work and Inventory Manager (Agentry_SDK , before 7.0, 7.1) allows an attacker to prevent legitimate users from accessing a service, either by crashing or flooding the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0241|2024-08-04T17:44:16.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0399|2024-08-04T17:51:26.320Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20portfolio%20and%20project%20management%20%28s4core%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0399</link>
      <description>SAP Portfolio and Project Management, before versions S4CORE 102, 103, EPPM 100 and CPRXRPM 500_702, 600_740, 610_740; unintentionally allows a user to discover accounting information of the Projects in Project dashboard, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0399|2024-08-04T17:51:26.320Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 21:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0376|2024-08-04T17:51:26.103Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0376</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface), before versions 4.2 and 4.3, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs and allows an attacker to save malicious scripts in the publication name, which can be executed later by the victim, resulting in Stored Cross-Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0376|2024-08-04T17:51:26.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:23:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6260|2024-08-04T08:55:22.192Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28trace%20analysis%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6260</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager (Trace Analysis), version 7.20, allows an attacker to inject superflous data that can be displayed by the application, due to Incomplete XML Validation. The application shows additional data that do not actually exist.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6260|2024-08-04T08:55:22.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 12:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6284|2024-08-04T08:55:22.312Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28knowledge%20management%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6284</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver (Knowledge Management), versions - 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, allows the automatic execution of script content in a stored file due to inadequate filtering with the accessing user's privileges. If the accessing user has administrative privileges, then the execution of the script content could result in complete compromise of system confidentiality, integrity and availability, leading to Stored Cross Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6284|2024-08-04T08:55:22.312Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 13:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6233|2024-08-04T08:55:22.311Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20s%2F4%20hana%20%28financial%20products%20subledger%20and%20banking%20services%29%20%28fsappl%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6233</link>
      <description>SAP S/4 HANA (Financial Products Subledger and Banking Services), versions - FSAPPL 400, 450, 500 and S4FPSL 100, allows an authenticated user to run an analysis report due to Missing Authorization Check, resulting in slowing the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6233|2024-08-04T08:55:22.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0244|2024-08-04T17:44:16.026Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui%20%28sapscore%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0244</link>
      <description>SAP CRM WebClient UI (fixed in SAPSCORE 1.12; S4FND 1.02; WEBCUIF 7.31, 7.46, 7.47, 7.48, 8.0, 8.01) does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0244|2024-08-04T17:44:16.026Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6262|2024-08-04T08:55:22.163Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20application%20server%20abap%20%28st-pi%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6262</link>
      <description>Service Data Download in SAP Application Server ABAP (ST-PI, before versions 2008_1_46C, 2008_1_620, 2008_1_640, 2008_1_700, 2008_1_710, 740) allows an attacker to inject code that can be executed by the application. An attacker could thereby control the behavior of the application and the whole ABAP system leading to Code Injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6262|2024-08-04T08:55:22.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0327|2024-08-04T17:44:16.446Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20for%20java%20application%20server%20-%20web%20container%20%28engineapi%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0327</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver for Java Application Server - Web Container, (engineapi, versions 7.1, 7.2, 7.3, 7.31, 7.4 and 7.5), (servercode, versions 7.2, 7.3, 7.31, 7.4, 7.5), allows an attacker to upload files (including script files) without proper file format validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0327|2024-08-04T17:44:16.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 19:09:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6257|2024-08-04T08:55:22.255Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28cmc%20and%20bi%20launchpad%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6257</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (CMC and BI Launchpad) 4.2 does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6257|2024-08-04T08:55:22.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0271|2024-08-04T17:44:16.313Z -- sap%20se -- abap%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0271</link>
      <description>ABAP Server (used in NetWeaver and Suite/ERP) and ABAP Platform does not sufficiently validate an XML document accepted from an untrusted source, leading to an XML External Entity (XEE) vulnerability. Fixed in Kernel 7.21 or 7.22, that is ABAP Server 7.00 to 7.31 and Kernel 7.45, 7.49 or 7.53, that is ABAP Server 7.40 to 7.52 or ABAP Platform. For more recent updates please refer to Security Note 2870067 (which supersedes the solution of Security Note 2736825) in the reference section below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0271|2024-08-04T17:44:16.313Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6212|2024-08-04T08:55:22.053Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20erp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6212</link>
      <description>Egypt localized withholding tax reports Clearing of Liabilities and Remittance Statement and Summary in SAP ERP (versions 618, 730, EAPPLGLO 607) and S/4 HANA (versions 100, 101, 102, 103, 104) do not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, allowing reading or modification of some tax reports, due to Missing Authorization Check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6212|2024-08-04T08:55:22.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 22:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6201|2024-08-04T08:55:22.115Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce%20cloud%20%28testweb%20extension%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6201</link>
      <description>The SAP Commerce (Testweb Extension), versions- 6.6, 6.7, 1808, 1811, 1905, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, due to which certain GET URL parameters are reflected in the HTTP responses without escaping/sanitization, leading to Reflected Cross Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6201|2024-08-04T08:55:22.115Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26832|2024-08-04T16:03:22.474Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20%28sap%20landscape%20transformation%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26832</link>
      <description>SAP AS ABAP (SAP Landscape Transformation), versions - 2011_1_620, 2011_1_640, 2011_1_700, 2011_1_710, 2011_1_730, 2011_1_731, 2011_1_752, 2020 and SAP S4 HANA (SAP Landscape Transformation), versions - 101, 102, 103, 104, 105, allows a high privileged user to execute a RFC function module to which access should be restricted, however due to missing authorization an attacker can get access to some sensitive internal information of vulnerable SAP system or to make vulnerable SAP systems completely unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26832|2024-08-04T16:03:22.474Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 16:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42069|2024-08-04T03:22:26.029Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42069</link>
      <description>When a user opens manipulated Tagged Image File Format (.tif) file received from untrusted sources in SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer - version 9.0, the application crashes and becomes temporarily unavailable to the user until restart of the application</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42069|2024-08-04T03:22:26.029Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0345|2024-08-04T17:44:16.475Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20for%20java%20%28administrator%20system%20overview%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0345</link>
      <description>A remote unauthenticated attacker can abuse a web service in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for Java (Administrator System Overview), versions 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, by sending a specially crafted XML file and trick the application server into leaking authentication credentials for its own SAP Management console, resulting in Server-Side Request Forgery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0345|2024-08-04T17:44:16.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 13:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6306|2024-08-04T08:55:22.446Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20leasing%20%28sap_appl%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6306</link>
      <description>Missing authorization check in a transaction within SAP Leasing (update provided in SAP_APPL 6.18, EA-APPL 6.0, 6.02, 6.03, 6.04, 6.05, 6.06, 6.16 and 6.17).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6306|2024-08-04T08:55:22.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 17:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6281|2024-08-04T08:55:22.197Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28bi%20launchpad%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6281</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (BI Launchpad), version 4.2, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting reflected in Cross-Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6281|2024-08-04T08:55:22.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 12:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6213|2024-08-04T08:55:22.059Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20%28business%20server%20pages%20test%20application%20sbspext_phtmlb%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6213</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP Business Server Pages Test Application SBSPEXT_PHTMLB, versions 700, 701, 702, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, is vulnerable to reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via different URL parameters as it does not sufficiently encode user controlled inputs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6213|2024-08-04T08:55:22.059Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 22:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40495|2024-08-04T02:44:10.857Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40495</link>
      <description>There are multiple Denial-of Service vulnerabilities in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755. An unauthorized attacker can use the public SICF service /sap/public/bc/abap to reduce the performance of SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40495|2024-08-04T02:44:10.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6365|2024-08-04T09:02:39.998Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6365</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS Java, versions - 7.10, 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, Start Page allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to redirect users to a malicious site due to insufficient reverse tabnabbing URL validation. The attacker could execute phishing attacks to steal credentials of the victim or to redirect users to untrusted web pages containing malware or similar malicious exploits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6365|2024-08-04T09:02:39.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 02:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6205|2024-08-04T08:55:21.876Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20abap%20%28smart%20forms%29%20-%20sap_basis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6205</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP Business Server Pages (Smart Forms), SAP_BASIS versions- 7.00, 7.01, 7.02, 7.10, 7.11, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, 7.51, 7.52, 7.53, 7.54; does not sufficiently encode user controlled inputs, allowing an unauthenticated attacker to non-permanently deface or modify displayed content and/or steal authentication information of the user and/or impersonate the user and access all information with the same rights as the target user, leading to Reflected Cross Site Scripting Vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6205|2024-08-04T08:55:21.876Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6246|2024-08-04T08:55:22.287Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20%28business%20server%20pages%20test%20application%20sbspext_table%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6246</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP Business Server Pages Test Application SBSPEXT_TABLE, versions 700, 701, 702, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6246|2024-08-04T08:55:22.287Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 12:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26830|2024-08-04T16:03:22.653Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28user%20experience%20monitoring%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26830</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager 7.2 (User Experience Monitoring), version - 7.2, does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user. Due to inadequate access control, a network attacker authenticated as a regular user can use operations which should be restricted to administrators. These operations can be used to Change the User Experience Monitoring configuration, obtain details about the configured SAP Solution Manager agents, Deploy a malicious User Experience Monitoring script.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26830|2024-08-04T16:03:22.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 16:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0329|2024-08-04T17:44:16.520Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20information%20steward
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0329</link>
      <description>SAP Information Steward, version 4.2, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0329|2024-08-04T17:44:16.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 19:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0307|2024-08-04T17:44:16.441Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%28diagnostics%20agent%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0307</link>
      <description>Diagnostics Agent in Solution Manager, version 7.2, stores several credentials such as SLD user connection as well as Solman user communication in the SAP Secure Storage file which is not encrypted by default. By decoding these credentials, an attacker with admin privileges could gain access to the entire configuration, but no system sensitive information can be gained.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0307|2024-08-04T17:44:16.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 14:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0266|2024-08-04T17:44:16.422Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20hana%20extended%20application%20services%2C%20advanced%20model%20%28xs%20advanced%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0266</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP HANA Extended Application Services, version 1.0, advanced model (XS advanced) writes credentials of platform users to a trace file of the SAP HANA system. Even though this trace file is protected from unauthorized access, the risk of leaking information is increased.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0266|2024-08-04T17:44:16.422Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0283|2024-08-04T17:44:16.378Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20process%20integration%20%28adapter%20engine%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0283</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Process Integration (Adapter Engine), fixed in versions 7.10 to 7.11, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50; is vulnerable to Digital Signature Spoofing. It is possible to spoof XML signatures and send arbitrary requests to the server via PI Axis adapter. These requests will be accepted by the PI Axis adapter even if the payload has been altered, especially when the signed element is the body of the xml document.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0283|2024-08-04T17:44:16.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 20:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6220|2024-08-04T08:55:22.261Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6220</link>
      <description>BI Launchpad and CMC in SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform, versions 4.1, 4.2, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. Exploit is possible only when the bttoken in victim’s session is active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6220|2024-08-04T08:55:22.261Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 19:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6223|2024-08-04T08:55:22.249Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6223</link>
      <description>The open document of SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform, versions 4.1, 4.2, allows an attacker to modify certain error pages to include malicious content. This can misdirect a user who is tricked into accessing these error pages rendered by the application, leading to Content Spoofing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6223|2024-08-04T08:55:22.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6349|2024-08-04T09:02:39.581Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6349</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated GIF file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6349|2024-08-04T09:02:39.581Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:53:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6307|2024-08-04T08:55:22.405Z -- sap%20se -- automated%20note%20search%20tool%20%28sap%20basis%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6307</link>
      <description>Automated Note Search Tool (update provided in SAP Basis 7.0, 7.01, 7.02, 7.31, 7.4, 7.5, 7.51, 7.52, 7.53 and 7.54) does not perform sufficient authorization checks leading to the reading of sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6307|2024-08-04T08:55:22.405Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 17:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6249|2024-08-04T08:55:22.176Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20master%20data%20governance%20%28s4core%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6249</link>
      <description>The use of an admin backend report within SAP Master Data Governance, versions - S4CORE 101, S4FND 102, 103, 104, SAP_BS_FND 748; allows an attacker to execute crafted database queries, exposing the backend database, leading to SQL Injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6249|2024-08-04T08:55:22.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6184|2024-08-04T08:55:22.128Z -- sap%20se -- automated%20note%20search%20tool%20%28sap%20basis%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6184</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, ABAP Online Community in SAP NetWeaver (SAP_BASIS version 7.40) and SAP S/4HANA (SAP_BASIS versions 7.50, 7.51, 7.52, 7.53, 7.54), does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6184|2024-08-04T08:55:22.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 19:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0303|2024-08-04T17:44:16.390Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28administration%20console%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0303</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Administration Console), versions 4.2, 4.3, module BILogon/appService.jsp is reflecting requested parameter errMsg into response content without sanitation. This could be used by an attacker to build a special url that execute custom JavaScript code when the url is accessed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0303|2024-08-04T17:44:16.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 18:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6299|2024-08-04T08:55:22.302Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28abap%20server%29%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6299</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver (ABAP Server) and ABAP Platform, versions - 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, allows a business user to access the list of users in the given system using value help, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6299|2024-08-04T08:55:22.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 13:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0267|2024-08-04T17:44:16.407Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20manufacturing%20integration%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0267</link>
      <description>SAP Manufacturing Integration and Intelligence, versions 15.0, 15.1 and 15.2, (Illuminator Servlet) currently does not provide Anti-XSRF tokens. This might lead to XSRF attacks in case the data is being posted to the Servlet from an external application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0267|2024-08-04T17:44:16.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6329|2024-08-04T08:55:22.242Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6329</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated SKP file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6329|2024-08-04T08:55:22.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6183|2024-08-04T08:55:22.286Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20host%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6183</link>
      <description>SAP Host Agent, version 7.21, allows an unprivileged user to read the shared memory or write to the shared memory by sending request to the main SAPOSCOL process and receive responses that may contain data read with user root privileges e.g. size of any directory, system hardware and OS details, leading to Missing Authorization Check vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6183|2024-08-04T08:55:22.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 19:46:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6271|2024-08-04T08:55:22.314Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28problem%20context%20manager%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6271</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager (Problem Context Manager), version 7.2, does not perform the necessary authentication, allowing an attacker to consume large amounts of memory, causing the system to crash and read restricted data (files visible for technical administration users of the diagnostics agent).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6271|2024-08-04T08:55:22.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 12:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6373|2024-08-04T09:02:39.914Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6373</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated PDF file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6373|2024-08-04T09:02:39.914Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 01:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0352|2024-08-04T17:44:16.501Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28cmc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0352</link>
      <description>In SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform, before versions 4.1, 4.2 and 4.3, some dynamic pages (like jsp) are cached, which leads to an attacker can see the sensitive information via cache and can open the dynamic pages even after logout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0352|2024-08-04T17:44:16.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 16:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0305|2024-08-04T17:44:16.457Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20process%20integration%28sap_xiesr%20and%20sap_xitool%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0305</link>
      <description>Java Server Pages (JSPs) provided by the SAP NetWeaver Process Integration (SAP_XIESR and SAP_XITOOL: 7.10 to 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50) do not restrict or incorrectly restrict frame objects or UI layers that belong to another application or domain, resulting in Clickjacking vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability leads to unwanted modification of user's data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0305|2024-08-04T17:44:16.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 14:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6232|2024-08-04T08:55:22.406Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6232</link>
      <description>SAP Commerce, versions 1811, 1905, does not perform necessary authorization checks for an anonymous user, due to Missing Authorization Check. This affects confidentiality of secure media.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6232|2024-08-04T08:55:22.406Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6350|2024-08-04T09:02:39.060Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6350</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated BMP file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6350|2024-08-04T09:02:39.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6371|2024-08-04T09:02:39.932Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20abap%20%28powl%20test%20application%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6371</link>
      <description>User enumeration vulnerability can be exploited to get a list of user accounts and personal user information can be exposed in SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP (POWL test application) versions - 710, 711, 730, 731, 740, 750, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6371|2024-08-04T09:02:39.932Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 01:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6355|2024-08-04T09:02:40.161Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6355</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated TGA file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6355|2024-08-04T09:02:40.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0379|2024-08-04T17:51:26.085Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20process%20integration%2C%20business-to-business%20add-on
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0379</link>
      <description>SAP Process Integration, business-to-business add-on, versions 1.0, 2.0, does not perform authentication check properly when the default security provider is changed to BouncyCastle (BC), leading to Missing Authentication Check</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0379|2024-08-04T17:51:26.085Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6340|2024-08-04T09:02:39.674Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6340</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated PCX file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6340|2024-08-04T09:02:39.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6191|2024-08-04T08:55:22.096Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20landscape%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6191</link>
      <description>SAP Landscape Management, version 3.0, allows an attacker with admin privileges to execute malicious executables with root privileges in SAP Host Agent via SAP Landscape Management due to Missing Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6191|2024-08-04T08:55:22.096Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 19:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0322|2024-08-04T17:44:16.479Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce%20cloud%20%28ex%20sap%20hybris%20commerce%29%20%28hy_com%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0322</link>
      <description>SAP Commerce Cloud (previously known as SAP Hybris Commerce), (HY_COM, versions 6.3, 6.4, 6.5, 6.6, 6.7, 1808, 1811), allows an attacker to prevent legitimate users from accessing a service, either by crashing or flooding the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0322|2024-08-04T17:44:16.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 19:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38178|2024-08-04T01:37:15.889Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38178</link>
      <description>The software logistics system of SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP and ABAP Platform versions - 700, 701, 702, 710, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, enables a malicious user to transfer ABAP code artifacts or content, by-passing the established quality gates. By this vulnerability malicious code can reach quality and production, and can compromise the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the system and its data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38178|2024-08-04T01:37:15.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6181|2024-08-04T08:55:22.112Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28sap%20basis%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6181</link>
      <description>Under some circumstances the SAML SSO implementation in the SAP NetWeaver (SAP_BASIS versions 702, 730, 731, 740 and SAP ABAP Platform (SAP_BASIS versions 750, 751, 752, 753, 754), allows an attacker to include invalidated data in the HTTP response header sent to a Web user, leading to HTTP Response Splitting vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6181|2024-08-04T08:55:22.112Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 19:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0246|2024-08-04T17:44:16.331Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20cloud%20connector
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0246</link>
      <description>SAP Cloud Connector, before version 2.11.3, does not perform any authentication checks for functionalities that require user identity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0246|2024-08-04T17:44:16.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0259|2024-08-04T17:44:16.377Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20servers%20%28enterprise%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0259</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects, versions 4.2 and 4.3, (Visual Difference) allows an attacker to upload any file (including script files) without proper file format validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0259|2024-08-04T17:44:16.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0386|2024-08-04T17:51:26.373Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20erp%20sales%20%28sap_appl%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0386</link>
      <description>Order processing in SAP ERP Sales (corrected in SAP_APPL 6.0, 6.02, 6.03, 6.04, 6.05, 6.06, 6.16, 6.17, 6.18) and S4HANA Sales (corrected in S4CORE 1.0, 1.01, 1.02, 1.03, 1.04) does not execute the required authorization checks for an authenticated user, which can result in an escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0386|2024-08-04T17:51:26.373Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 22:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6302|2024-08-04T08:55:22.407Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6302</link>
      <description>SAP Commerce versions 6.7, 1808, 1811, 1905, 2005 contains the jSession ID in the backoffice URL when the application is loaded initially. An attacker can get this session ID via shoulder surfing or man in the middle attack and subsequently get access to admin user accounts, leading to Session Fixation and complete compromise of the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6302|2024-08-04T08:55:22.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:52:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6251|2024-08-04T08:55:22.168Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6251</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions or error scenarios SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform, version 4.2, allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6251|2024-08-04T08:55:22.168Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6254|2024-08-04T08:55:22.174Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20enterprise%20threat%20detection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6254</link>
      <description>SAP Enterprise Threat Detection, versions 1.0, 2.0, does not sufficiently encode error response pages in case of errors, allowing XSS payload reflecting in the response, leading to reflected Cross Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6254|2024-08-04T08:55:22.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6342|2024-08-04T09:02:39.655Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6342</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated U3D file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6342|2024-08-04T09:02:39.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0251|2024-08-04T17:44:16.593Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28fiori%20launchpad%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0251</link>
      <description>The Fiori Launchpad of SAP BusinessObjects, before versions 4.2 and 4.3, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0251|2024-08-04T17:44:16.593Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0256|2024-08-04T17:44:16.192Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20one%20mobile%20android%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0256</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP Business One Mobile Android App, version 1.2.12, allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0256|2024-08-04T17:44:16.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6195|2024-08-04T08:55:22.152Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6195</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (CMC), version 4.1, 4.2, shows cleartext password in the response, leading to Information Disclosure. It involves social engineering in order to gain access to system and If password is known, it would give administrative rights to the attacker to read/modify delete the data and rights within the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6195|2024-08-04T08:55:22.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 19:36:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0388|2024-08-04T17:51:26.312Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20ui
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0388</link>
      <description>SAP UI5 HTTP Handler (corrected in SAP_UI versions 7.5, 7.51, 7.52, 7.53, 7.54 and SAP UI_700 version 2.0) allows an attacker to manipulate content due to insufficient URL validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0388|2024-08-04T17:51:26.312Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 22:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42064|2024-08-04T03:22:25.989Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42064</link>
      <description>If configured to use an Oracle database and if a query is created using the flexible search java api with a parameterized "in" clause, SAP Commerce - versions 1905, 2005, 2105, 2011, allows attacker to execute crafted database queries, exposing backend database. The vulnerability is present if the parameterized "in" clause accepts more than 1000 values.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42064|2024-08-04T03:22:25.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0370|2024-08-04T17:51:26.086Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20financial%20consolidation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0370</link>
      <description>Due to missing input validation, SAP Financial Consolidation, before versions 10.0 and 10.1, enables an attacker to use crafted input to interfere with the structure of the surrounding query leading to XPath Injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0370|2024-08-04T17:51:26.086Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42063|2024-08-04T03:22:25.975Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20knowledge%20warehouse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42063</link>
      <description>A security vulnerability has been discovered in the SAP Knowledge Warehouse - versions 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50. The usage of one SAP KW component within a Web browser enables unauthorized attackers to conduct XSS attacks, which might lead to disclose sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42063|2024-08-04T03:22:25.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6228|2024-08-04T08:55:22.286Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6228</link>
      <description>SAP Business Client, versions 6.5, 7.0, does not perform necessary integrity checks which could be exploited by an attacker under certain conditions to modify the installer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6228|2024-08-04T08:55:22.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26816|2024-08-04T16:03:22.694Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java%20%28key%20storage%20service%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26816</link>
      <description>SAP AS JAVA (Key Storage Service), versions - 7.10, 7.11, 7.20 ,7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, has the key material which is stored in the SAP NetWeaver AS Java Key Storage service stored in the database in the DER encoded format and is not encrypted. This enables an attacker who has administrator access to the SAP NetWeaver AS Java to decode the keys because of missing encryption and get some application data and client credentials of adjacent systems. This highly impacts Confidentiality as information disclosed could contain client credentials of adjacent systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26816|2024-08-04T16:03:22.694Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 16:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6341|2024-08-04T09:02:39.060Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6341</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated EPS file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6341|2024-08-04T09:02:39.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6269|2024-08-04T08:55:22.156Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6269</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform, version 4.2, allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6269|2024-08-04T08:55:22.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 12:37:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40503|2024-08-04T02:44:10.837Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20gui%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40503</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in SAP GUI for Windows - versions &lt; 7.60 PL13, 7.70 PL4, which allows an attacker with sufficient privileges on the local client-side PC to obtain an equivalent of the user’s password. With this highly sensitive data leaked, the attacker would be able to logon to the backend system the SAP GUI for Windows was connected to and launch further attacks depending on the authorizations of the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40503|2024-08-04T02:44:10.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6322|2024-08-04T08:55:22.405Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6322</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated 3DM file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6322|2024-08-04T08:55:22.405Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0270|2024-08-04T17:44:16.340Z -- sap%20se -- abap%20platform%20%26%20server%20%28krnl32nuc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0270</link>
      <description>ABAP Server of SAP NetWeaver and ABAP Platform fail to perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. This has been corrected in the following versions: KRNL32NUC 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT, KRNL32UC 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT, KRNL64NUC 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT, 7.49, 7.74, KRNL64UC 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT, 7.49, 7.73, 7.74, 8.04, KERNEL 7.21, 7.45, 7.49, 7.53, 7.73, 7.74, 7.75, 8.04.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0270|2024-08-04T17:44:16.340Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6198|2024-08-04T08:55:22.129Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28diagnostics%20agent%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6198</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager (Diagnostics Agent), version 720, allows unencrypted connections from unauthenticated sources. This allows an attacker to control all remote functions on the Agent due to Missing Authentication Check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6198|2024-08-04T08:55:22.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0365|2024-08-04T17:44:16.488Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20kernel%20%28krnl32nuc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0365</link>
      <description>SAP Kernel (RFC), KRNL32NUC, KRNL32UC and KRNL64NUC before versions 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT, KRNL64UC, before versions 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT, 7.49, 7.73 and KERNEL before versions 7.21, 7.49, 7.53, 7.73, 7.76 SAP GUI for Windows (BC-FES-GUI) before versions 7.5, 7.6, and SAP GUI for Java (BC-FES-JAV) before version 7.5, allow an attacker to prevent legitimate users from accessing a service, either by crashing or flooding the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0365|2024-08-04T17:44:16.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 16:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6335|2024-08-04T09:02:39.561Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6335</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated HPGL file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6335|2024-08-04T09:02:39.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0257|2024-08-04T17:44:16.190Z -- sap%20se -- abap%20platform%28sap%20basis%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0257</link>
      <description>Customizing functionality of SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP Platform (fixed in versions from 7.0 to 7.02, from 7.10 to 7.11, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, from 7.50 to 7.53, from 7.74 to 7.75) does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0257|2024-08-04T17:44:16.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6202|2024-08-04T08:55:21.913Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20java%20%28user%20management%20engine%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6202</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server Java (User Management Engine), versions- 7.10, 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50; does not sufficiently validate the LDAP data source configuration XML document accepted from an untrusted source, leading to Missing XML Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6202|2024-08-04T08:55:21.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0291|2024-08-04T17:44:16.377Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0291</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions Solution Manager, version 7.2, allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0291|2024-08-04T17:44:16.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 20:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0282|2024-08-04T17:44:16.560Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20process%20integration%20%28runtime%20workbench%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0282</link>
      <description>Several web pages in SAP NetWeaver Process Integration (Runtime Workbench), fixed in versions 7.10 to 7.11, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50; can be accessed without user authentication, which might expose internal data like release information, Java package and Java object names which can be misused by the attacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0282|2024-08-04T17:44:16.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 20:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6345|2024-08-04T09:02:39.025Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6345</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated TGA file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6345|2024-08-04T09:02:39.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6328|2024-08-04T08:55:22.331Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6328</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated CGM file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6328|2024-08-04T08:55:22.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6366|2024-08-04T09:02:39.996Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28compare%20systems%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6366</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver (Compare Systems) versions - 7.20, 7.30, 7.40, 7.50, does not sufficiently validate uploaded XML documents. An attacker with administrative privileges can retrieve arbitrary files including files on OS level from the server and/or can execute a denial-of-service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6366|2024-08-04T09:02:39.996Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 13:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6332|2024-08-04T08:55:22.515Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6332</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated HPGL file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6332|2024-08-04T08:55:22.515Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6225|2024-08-04T08:55:22.160Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28knowledge%20management%29%20%28kmc-cm%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6225</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver (Knowledge Management), versions (KMC-CM - 7.00, 7.01, 7.02, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50 and KMC-WPC 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50), does not sufficiently validate path information provided by users, thus characters representing traverse to parent directory are passed through to the file APIs, allowing the attacker to overwrite, delete, or corrupt arbitrary files on the remote server, leading to Path Traversal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6225|2024-08-04T08:55:22.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 19:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38164|2024-08-04T01:37:16.113Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20erp%20financial%20accounting%20%28rfopenposting_fr%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38164</link>
      <description>SAP ERP Financial Accounting (RFOPENPOSTING_FR) versions - SAP_APPL - 600, 602, 603, 604, 605, 606, 616, SAP_FIN - 617, 618, 700, 720, 730, SAPSCORE - 125, S4CORE, 100, 101, 102, 103, 104, 105, allows a registered attacker to invoke certain functions that would otherwise be restricted to specific users. These functions are normally exposed over the network and once exploited the attacker may be able to view and modify financial accounting data that only a specific user should have access to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38164|2024-08-04T01:37:16.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38150|2024-08-04T01:37:16.044Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38150</link>
      <description>When an attacker manages to get access to the local memory, or the memory dump of a victim, for example by a social engineering attack, SAP Business Client versions - 7.0, 7.70, will allow him to read extremely sensitive data, such as credentials. This would allow the attacker to compromise the corresponding backend for which the credentials are valid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38150|2024-08-04T01:37:16.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38180|2024-08-04T01:37:15.903Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38180</link>
      <description>SAP Business One - version 10.0, allows an attacker to inject formulas when exporting data to Excel (CSV injection) due to improper sanitation during the data export. An attacker could thereby execute arbitrary commands on the victim's computer but only if the victim allows to execute macros while opening the file and the security settings of Excel allow for command execution.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38180|2024-08-04T01:37:15.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0377|2024-08-04T17:51:26.707Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0377</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface), before versions 4.2, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs and allows an attacker to store malicious scripts in the input controls, resulting in Stored Cross-Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0377|2024-08-04T17:51:26.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6286|2024-08-04T08:55:22.280Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java%20%28lm%20configuration%20wizard%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6286</link>
      <description>The insufficient input path validation of certain parameter in the web service of SAP NetWeaver AS JAVA (LM Configuration Wizard), versions - 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit a method to download zip files to a specific directory, leading to Path Traversal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6286|2024-08-04T08:55:22.280Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 12:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6361|2024-08-04T09:02:40.171Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6361</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated RLE files received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6361|2024-08-04T09:02:40.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6192|2024-08-04T08:55:22.058Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20landscape%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6192</link>
      <description>SAP Landscape Management, version 3.0, allows an attacker with admin privileges to execute malicious commands with root privileges in SAP Host Agent via SAP Landscape Management.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6192|2024-08-04T08:55:22.058Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 19:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0328|2024-08-04T17:44:16.476Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20process%20integration%20abap%20tests%20%28sap%20basis%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0328</link>
      <description>ABAP Tests Modules (SAP Basis, versions 7.0, 7.1, 7.3, 7.31, 7.4, 7.5) of SAP NetWeaver Process Integration enables an attacker the execution of OS commands with privileged rights. An attacker could thereby impact the integrity and availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0328|2024-08-04T17:44:16.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 19:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6237|2024-08-04T08:55:22.178Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6237</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform, version 4.1, 4.2, dswsbobje web application allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6237|2024-08-04T08:55:22.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6230|2024-08-04T08:55:22.267Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20orientdb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6230</link>
      <description>SAP OrientDB, version 3.0, allows an authenticated attacker with script execute/write permissions to inject code that can be executed by the application and lead to Code Injection. An attacker could thereby control the behavior of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6230|2024-08-04T08:55:22.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0280|2024-08-04T17:44:16.517Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20treasury%20and%20risk%20management%28ea-finserv%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0280</link>
      <description>SAP Treasury and Risk Management (EA-FINSERV 6.0, 6.03, 6.04, 6.05, 6.06, 6.16, 6.17, 6.18 and 8.0; S4CORE 1.01, 1.02 and 1.03), does not perform necessary authorization checks for authorization objects T_DEAL_DP and T_DEAL_PD , resulting in escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0280|2024-08-04T17:44:16.517Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 20:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6357|2024-08-04T09:02:39.941Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6357</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated U3D file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6357|2024-08-04T09:02:39.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6268|2024-08-04T08:55:22.226Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20erp%20%28statutory%20reporting%20for%20insurance%20companies%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6268</link>
      <description>Statutory Reporting for Insurance Companies in SAP ERP (EA-FINSERV versions - 600, 603, 604, 605, 606, 616, 617, 618, 800 and S4CORE versions 101, 102, 103, 104) does not execute the required authorization checks for an authenticated user, allowing an attacker to view and tamper with certain restricted data leading to Missing Authorization Check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6268|2024-08-04T08:55:22.226Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 12:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6231|2024-08-04T08:55:22.155Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6231</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface), version 4.2, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6231|2024-08-04T08:55:22.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38176|2024-08-04T01:37:16.300Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20s%2F4hana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38176</link>
      <description>Due to improper input sanitization, an authenticated user with certain specific privileges can remotely call NZDT function modules listed in Solution Section to execute manipulated query or inject ABAP code to gain access to Backend Database. On successful exploitation the threat actor could completely compromise confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38176|2024-08-04T01:37:16.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0287|2024-08-04T17:44:16.324Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28central%20management%20server%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0287</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence platform (Central Management Server), versions 4.2 and 4.3, allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0287|2024-08-04T17:44:16.324Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 20:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6275|2024-08-04T08:55:22.250Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6275</link>
      <description>SAP Netweaver AS ABAP, versions 700, 701, 702, 710, 711, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, are vulnerable for Server Side Request Forgery Attack where in an attacker can use inappropriate path names containing malicious server names in the import/export of sessions functionality and coerce the web server into authenticating with the malicious server. Furthermore, if NTLM is setup the attacker can compromise confidentiality, integrity and availability of the SAP database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6275|2024-08-04T08:55:22.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 12:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0277|2024-08-04T17:44:16.319Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20hana%20extended%20application%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0277</link>
      <description>SAP HANA extended application services, version 1, advanced does not sufficiently validate an XML document accepted from an authenticated developer with privileges to the SAP space (XML External Entity vulnerability).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0277|2024-08-04T17:44:16.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6258|2024-08-04T08:55:22.209Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20identity%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6258</link>
      <description>SAP Identity Management, version 8.0, does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, allowing the attacker to view certain sensitive information of the victim, leading to Missing Authorization Check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6258|2024-08-04T08:55:22.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0281|2024-08-04T17:44:16.570Z -- sap%20se -- openui5
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0281</link>
      <description>SAPUI5 and OpenUI5, before versions 1.38.39, 1.44.39, 1.52.25, 1.60.6 and 1.63.0, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0281|2024-08-04T17:44:16.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 18:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6253|2024-08-04T08:55:22.324Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20adaptive%20server%20enterprise%20%28web%20services%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6253</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, SAP Adaptive Server Enterprise (Web Services), versions 15.7, 16.0, allows an authenticated user to execute crafted database queries to elevate their privileges, modify database objects, or execute commands they are not otherwise authorized to execute, leading to SQL Injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6253|2024-08-04T08:55:22.324Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0382|2024-08-04T17:51:26.301Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0382</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability exists in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence-Publication related pages); corrected in version 4.2. Privileges are required in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0382|2024-08-04T17:51:26.301Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 21:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6217|2024-08-04T08:55:22.141Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20%28business%20server%20pages%20test%20application%20it05%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6217</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP Business Server Pages Test Application IT00, versions 700, 701, 702, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6217|2024-08-04T08:55:22.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 19:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0243|2024-08-04T17:44:15.938Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20bw%2F4hana%20%28dw4core%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0243</link>
      <description>Under some circumstances, masterdata maintenance in SAP BW/4HANA (fixed in DW4CORE version 1.0 (SP08)) does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0243|2024-08-04T17:44:15.938Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38182|2024-08-04T01:37:16.116Z -- sap%20se -- kyma
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38182</link>
      <description>Due to insufficient input validation of Kyma, authenticated users can pass a Header of their choice and escalate privileges which can completely compromise the cluster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38182|2024-08-04T01:37:16.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6221|2024-08-04T08:55:22.090Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6221</link>
      <description>Web Intelligence HTML interface in SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform, versions 4.1, 4.2, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6221|2024-08-04T08:55:22.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26823|2024-08-04T16:03:22.605Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28java%20stack%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26823</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager (JAVA stack), version - 7.20, allows an unauthenticated attacker to compromise the system because of missing authorization checks in the Upgrade Diagnostics Agent Connection Service, this has an impact to the integrity and availability of the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26823|2024-08-04T16:03:22.605Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0315|2024-08-04T17:44:16.439Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20process%20integration%28sap_xiesr%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0315</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions the PI Integration Builder Web UI of SAP NetWeaver Process Integration (versions: SAP_XIESR: 7.10 to 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, SAP_XITOOL: 7.10 to 7.11, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50 and SAP_XIPCK 7.10 to 7.11, 7.20, 7.30) allows an attacker to access passwords used in FTP channels leading to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0315|2024-08-04T17:44:16.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 16:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6282|2024-08-04T08:55:22.289Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java%20%28iiop%20service%29%20%28servercore%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6282</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS JAVA (IIOP service) (SERVERCORE), versions 7.10, 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, and SAP NetWeaver AS JAVA (IIOP service) (CORE-TOOLS), versions 7.10, 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, allows an attacker to send a crafted request from a vulnerable web application. It is usually used to target internal systems behind firewalls that are normally inaccessible to an attacker from the external network, resulting in a Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6282|2024-08-04T08:55:22.289Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 12:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0384|2024-08-04T17:51:27.032Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20treasury%20and%20risk%20management%20%28s4core%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0384</link>
      <description>Transaction Management in SAP Treasury and Risk Management (corrected in S4CORE versions 1.01, 1.02, 1.03, 1.04 and EA-FINSERV versions 6.0, 6.03, 6.04, 6.05, 6.06, 6.16, 6.17, 6.18, 8.0) does not perform necessary authorization checks for functionalities that require user identity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0384|2024-08-04T17:51:27.032Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 19:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6266|2024-08-04T08:55:22.302Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20fiori%20for%20sap%20s%2F4hana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6266</link>
      <description>SAP Fiori for SAP S/4HANA, versions - 100, 200, 300, 400, allows an attacker to redirect users to a malicious site due to insufficient URL validation, leading to URL Redirection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6266|2024-08-04T08:55:22.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 12:51:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6294|2024-08-04T08:55:22.318Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6294</link>
      <description>Xvfb of SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform, versions - 4.2, 4.3, platform on Unix does not perform any authentication checks for functionalities that require user identity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6294|2024-08-04T08:55:22.318Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 13:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0363|2024-08-04T17:44:16.529Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20hana%20extended%20application%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0363</link>
      <description>Attackers may misuse an HTTP/REST endpoint of SAP HANA Extended Application Services (Advanced model), before version 1.0.118, to overload the server or retrieve information about internal network ports.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0363|2024-08-04T17:44:16.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 16:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0385|2024-08-04T17:51:26.061Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20enable%20now
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0385</link>
      <description>SAP Enable Now, before version 1908, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0385|2024-08-04T17:51:26.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 21:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26821|2024-08-04T16:03:22.410Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28java%20stack%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26821</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager (JAVA stack), version - 7.20, allows an unauthenticated attacker to compromise the system because of missing authorization checks in the SVG Converter Service, this has an impact to the integrity and availability of the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26821|2024-08-04T16:03:22.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0393|2024-08-04T17:51:26.616Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20quality%20management%20%28s4core%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0393</link>
      <description>An SQL Injection vulnerability in SAP Quality Management (corrected in S4CORE versions 1.0, 1.01, 1.02, 1.03) allows an attacker to carry out targeted database queries that can read individual fields of historical inspection results.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0393|2024-08-04T17:51:26.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 21:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0293|2024-08-04T17:44:16.414Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20system%20%28st-pi%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0293</link>
      <description>Read of RFC destination does not always perform necessary authorization checks, resulting in escalation of privileges to access information on RFC destinations on managed systems and SAP Solution Manager system (ST-PI, before versions 2008_1_700, 2008_1_710, and 740).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0293|2024-08-04T17:44:16.414Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 20:21:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26835|2024-08-04T16:03:22.606Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26835</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP, versions - 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754 , does not sufficiently encode URL which allows an attacker to input malicious java script in the URL which could be executed in the browser resulting in Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26835|2024-08-04T16:03:22.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 16:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6177|2024-08-04T08:55:21.591Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20mobile%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6177</link>
      <description>SAP Mobile Platform, version 3.0, does not sufficiently validate an XML document accepted from an untrusted source which could lead to partial denial of service. Since SAP Mobile Platform does not allow External-Entity resolving, there is no issue of leaking content of files on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6177|2024-08-04T08:55:21.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 19:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26815|2024-08-04T16:03:22.733Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20fiori%20launchpad%20%28news%20tile%20application%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26815</link>
      <description>SAP Fiori Launchpad (News tile Application), versions - 750,751,752,753,754,755, allows an unauthorized attacker to send a crafted request to a vulnerable web application. It is usually used to target internal systems behind firewalls that are normally inaccessible to an attacker from the external network to retrieve sensitive / confidential resources which are otherwise restricted for internal usage only, resulting in a Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26815|2024-08-04T16:03:22.733Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6346|2024-08-04T09:02:39.568Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6346</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated BMP file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6346|2024-08-04T09:02:39.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:53:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0331|2024-08-04T17:44:16.543Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28bi%20workspace%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0331</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (BI Workspace), versions 4.1, 4.2, 4.3, allows an attacker to access sensitive data such as directory structure, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0331|2024-08-04T17:44:16.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 13:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0346|2024-08-04T17:44:16.560Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28cmc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0346</link>
      <description>Unencrypted communication error in SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (Central Management Console), version 4.2, leads to disclosure of list of user names and roles imported from SAP NetWeaver BI systems, resulting in Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0346|2024-08-04T17:44:16.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 13:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0369|2024-08-04T17:51:26.111Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20financial%20consolidation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0369</link>
      <description>SAP Financial Consolidation, before versions 10.0 and 10.1, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, which allows an attacker to execute scripts by uploading files containing malicious scripts, leading to reflected cross site scripting vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0369|2024-08-04T17:51:26.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6226|2024-08-04T08:55:22.196Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6226</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface), version 4.2, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6226|2024-08-04T08:55:22.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6313|2024-08-04T08:55:22.450Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java%20%28xml%20forms%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6313</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server JAVA(XML Forms) versions 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50 does not sufficiently encode user controlled inputs, which allows an authenticated User with special roles to store malicious content, that when accessed by a victim, can perform malicious actions by executing JavaScript, leading to Stored Cross-Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6313|2024-08-04T08:55:22.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:43:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6354|2024-08-04T09:02:39.617Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6354</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated SKP file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6354|2024-08-04T09:02:39.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38163|2024-08-04T01:37:16.194Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28visual%20composer%207.0%20rt%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38163</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver (Visual Composer 7.0 RT) versions - 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, without restriction, an attacker authenticated as a non-administrative user can upload a malicious file over a network and trigger its processing, which is capable of running operating system commands with the privilege of the Java Server process. These commands can be used to read or modify any information on the server or shut the server down making it unavailable.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38163|2024-08-04T01:37:16.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0348|2024-08-04T17:44:16.472Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0348</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence), versions 4.1, 4.2, can access database with unencrypted connection, even if the quality of protection should be encrypted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0348|2024-08-04T17:44:16.472Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 13:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-37531|2024-08-04T01:22:59.365Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20knowledge%20management%20xml%20forms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-37531</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Knowledge Management XML Forms versions - 7.10, 7.11, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, contains an XSLT vulnerability which allows a non-administrative authenticated attacker to craft a malicious XSL stylesheet file containing a script with OS-level commands, copy it into a location to be accessed by the system and then create a file which will trigger the XSLT engine to execute the script contained within the malicious XSL file. This can result in a full compromise of the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-37531|2024-08-04T01:22:59.365Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6289|2024-08-04T08:55:22.240Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20disclosure%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6289</link>
      <description>SAP Disclosure Management, version 10.1, had insufficient protection against Cross-Site Request Forgery, which could be used to trick user in to browsing malicious site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6289|2024-08-04T08:55:22.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 12:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38179|2024-08-04T01:37:16.482Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38179</link>
      <description>Debug function of Admin UI of SAP Business One Integration is enabled by default. This allows Admin User to see the captured packet contents which may include User credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38179|2024-08-04T01:37:16.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26807|2024-08-04T16:03:22.746Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20erp%20client%20for%20e-bilanz%201.0
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26807</link>
      <description>SAP ERP Client for E-Bilanz, version - 1.0, installation sets Incorrect default filesystem permissions are set in its installation folder which allows anyone to modify the files in the folder.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26807|2024-08-04T16:03:22.746Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6211|2024-08-04T08:55:22.038Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6211</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (AdminTools), versions 4.1, 4.2, allows an attacker to redirect users to a malicious site due to insufficient URL validation and steal credentials of the victim, leading to URL Redirection vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6211|2024-08-04T08:55:22.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 19:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6214|2024-08-04T08:55:21.977Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20s%2F4hana%20%28financial%20products%20subledger%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6214</link>
      <description>SAP S/4HANA (Financial Products Subledger), version 100, uses an incorrect authorization object in some reports. Although the affected reports are protected with other authorization objects, exploitation of the vulnerability would allow an authenticated attacker to view, change, or delete data, thereby preventing the proper segregation of duties in the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6214|2024-08-04T08:55:21.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38177|2024-08-04T01:37:16.323Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commoncryptolib
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38177</link>
      <description>SAP CommonCryptoLib version 8.5.38 or lower is vulnerable to null pointer dereference vulnerability when an unauthenticated attacker sends crafted malicious data in the HTTP requests over the network, this causes the SAP application to crash and has high impact on the availability of the SAP system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38177|2024-08-04T01:37:16.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6276|2024-08-04T08:55:22.335Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28bipodata%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6276</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (bipodata), version 4.2, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6276|2024-08-04T08:55:22.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 12:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6187|2024-08-04T08:55:21.848Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28guided%20procedures%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6187</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver (Guided Procedures), versions 7.10, 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, does not sufficiently validate an XML document input from a compromised admin, leading to Denial of Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6187|2024-08-04T08:55:21.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 19:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0396|2024-08-04T17:51:26.767Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0396</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface), corrected in versions 4.1 and 4.2, does not sufficiently validate an XML document accepted from an untrusted source. An attacker can craft a message that contains malicious elements that will not be correctly filtered by Web Intelligence HTML interface in some specific workflows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0396|2024-08-04T17:51:26.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 22:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0261|2024-08-04T17:44:16.376Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20hana%20extended%20application%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0261</link>
      <description>Under certain circumstances, SAP HANA Extended Application Services, advanced model (XS advanced) does not perform authentication checks properly for XS advanced platform and business users. Fixed in 1.0.97 to 1.0.99 (running on SAP HANA 1 or SAP HANA 2 SPS0 (second S stands for stack)).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0261|2024-08-04T17:44:16.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6206|2024-08-04T08:55:21.973Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20cloud%20platform%20integration%20for%20data%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6206</link>
      <description>SAP Cloud Platform Integration for Data Services, version 1.0, allows user inputs to be reflected as error or warning massages. This could mislead the victim to follow malicious instructions inserted by external attackers, leading to Cross Site Request Forgery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6206|2024-08-04T08:55:21.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6330|2024-08-04T08:55:22.231Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6330</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated 3DM file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6330|2024-08-04T08:55:22.231Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0381|2024-08-04T17:51:26.765Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20iq
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0381</link>
      <description>A binary planting in SAP SQL Anywhere, before version 17.0, SAP IQ, before version 16.1, and SAP Dynamic Tier, before versions 1.0 and 2.0, can result in the inadvertent access of files located in directories outside of the paths specified by the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0381|2024-08-04T17:51:26.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0344|2024-08-04T17:44:16.517Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce%20cloud%20%28virtualjdbc%20extension%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0344</link>
      <description>Due to unsafe deserialization used in SAP Commerce Cloud (virtualjdbc extension), versions 6.4, 6.5, 6.6, 6.7, 1808, 1811, 1905, it is possible to execute arbitrary code on a target machine with 'Hybris' user rights, resulting in Code Injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0344|2024-08-04T17:44:16.517Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 13:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0326|2024-08-04T17:44:16.440Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20-%20bi%20workspace%20%28enterprise%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0326</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (BI Workspace) (Enterprise), versions 4.1, 4.2, 4.3, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0326|2024-08-04T17:44:16.440Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 19:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40499|2024-08-04T02:44:10.842Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20for%20abap%20%28sap%20cloud%20print%20manager%20and%20sapsprint%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40499</link>
      <description>Client-side printing services SAP Cloud Print Manager and SAPSprint for SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP - versions 7.70, 7.70 PI, 7.70 BYD, allow an attacker to inject code that can be executed by the application. An attacker could thereby control the behavior of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40499|2024-08-04T02:44:10.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6247|2024-08-04T08:55:22.161Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6247</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform, version 4.2, allows an unauthenticated attacker to prevent legitimate users from accessing a service. Using a specially crafted request, the attacker can crash or flood the Central Management Server, thereby impacting system availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6247|2024-08-04T08:55:22.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0275|2024-08-04T17:44:16.521Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20java%20application%20server%20%28j2ee-apps%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0275</link>
      <description>SAML 1.1 SSO Demo Application in SAP NetWeaver Java Application Server (J2EE-APPS), versions 7.10 to 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40 and 7.50, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, which results in cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0275|2024-08-04T17:44:16.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0298|2024-08-04T17:44:16.423Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20e-commerce%20%28sap-crmjav%2C%20sap-crmweb%2C%20sap-shrweb%2C%20sap-shrjav%2C%20sap-crmapp%2C%20sap-shrapp%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0298</link>
      <description>SAP E-Commerce (Business-to-Consumer) application does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. Fixed in the following components SAP-CRMJAV SAP-CRMWEB SAP-SHRWEB SAP-SHRJAV SAP-CRMAPP SAP-SHRAPP, versions 7.30, 7.31, 7.32, 7.33, 7.54.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0298|2024-08-04T17:44:16.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 20:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6326|2024-08-04T08:55:22.326Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28knowledge%20management%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6326</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver (Knowledge Management), version-7.30,7.31,7.40,7.50, allows an authenticated attacker to create malicious links in the UI, when clicked by victim, will execute arbitrary java scripts thus extracting or modifying information otherwise restricted leading to Stored Cross Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6326|2024-08-04T08:55:22.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:47:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0314|2024-08-04T17:44:16.468Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20work%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0314</link>
      <description>SAP Work Manager, versions: 6.3, 6.4, 6.5 and SAP Inventory Manager, version 4.3, allows an attacker to prevent legitimate users from accessing a service, either by crashing or flooding the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0314|2024-08-04T17:44:16.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 16:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-37532|2024-08-04T01:23:01.245Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-37532</link>
      <description>SAP Business One version - 10, due to improper input validation, allows an authenticated User to gain access to directory and view the contents of index in the directory, which would otherwise be restricted to high privileged User.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-37532|2024-08-04T01:23:01.245Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26809|2024-08-04T16:03:22.462Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26809</link>
      <description>SAP Commerce Cloud, versions- 1808,1811,1905,2005, allows an attacker to bypass existing authentication and permission checks via the '/medias' endpoint hence gaining access to Secure Media folders. This folder could contain sensitive files that results in disclosure of sensitive information and impact system configuration confidentiality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26809|2024-08-04T16:03:22.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38181|2024-08-04T01:37:15.601Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38181</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 700, 701, 702, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, allows an attacker to prevent legitimate users from accessing a service, either by crashing or flooding the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38181|2024-08-04T01:37:15.601Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6304|2024-08-04T08:55:22.294Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20internet%20communication%20manager%20%28krnl32nuc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6304</link>
      <description>Improper input validation in SAP NetWeaver Internet Communication Manager (update provided in KRNL32NUC &amp; KRNL32UC 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT KRNL64NUC &amp; KRNL64UC 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT, 7.49 KERNEL 7.21, 7.49, 7.53) allows an attacker to prevent users from accessing its services through a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6304|2024-08-04T08:55:22.294Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 17:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0380|2024-08-04T17:51:26.927Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20landscape%20management%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0380</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, SAP Landscape Management enterprise edition, before version 3.0, allows custom secure parameters’ default values to be part of the application logs leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0380|2024-08-04T17:51:26.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6283|2024-08-04T08:55:22.250Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20fiori%28launchpad%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6283</link>
      <description>SAP Fiori Launchpad does not sufficiently encode user controlled inputs, and hence allowing the attacker to inject the meta tag into the launchpad html using the vulnerable parameter, resulting in reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. With a successful attack, the attacker can steal authentication information of the user, such as data relating to his or her current session.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6283|2024-08-04T08:55:22.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0249|2024-08-04T17:44:16.381Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20landscape%20management%28vcm%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0249</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP Landscape Management (VCM 3.0) allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0249|2024-08-04T17:44:16.381Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0334|2024-08-04T17:44:16.482Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28bi%20workspace%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0334</link>
      <description>When creating a module in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (BI Workspace), versions 4.1, 4.2, 4.3, it is possible to store a malicious script which when executed later could potentially allow a user to escalate privileges via session hijacking. The attacker could also access other sensitive information, leading to Stored Cross Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0334|2024-08-04T17:44:16.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 13:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38162|2024-08-04T01:37:15.668Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20web%20dispatcher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38162</link>
      <description>SAP Web Dispatcher versions - 7.49, 7.53, 7.77, 7.81, KRNL64NUC - 7.22, 7.22EXT, 7.49, KRNL64UC -7.22, 7.22EXT, 7.49, 7.53, KERNEL - 7.22, 7.49, 7.53, 7.77, 7.81, 7.83 processes allow an unauthenticated attacker to submit a malicious crafted request over a network to a front-end server which may, over several attempts, result in a back-end server confusing the boundaries of malicious and legitimate messages. This can result in the back-end server executing a malicious payload which can be used to read or modify any information on the server or consume server resources making it temporarily unavailable.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38162|2024-08-04T01:37:15.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6197|2024-08-04T08:55:22.008Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20enable%20now
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6197</link>
      <description>SAP Enable Now, before version 1908, does not invalidate session tokens in a timely manner. The Insufficient Session Expiration may allow attackers with local access, for instance, to still download the portables.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6197|2024-08-04T08:55:22.008Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0383|2024-08-04T17:51:26.142Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20treasury%20and%20risk%20management%20%28s4core%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0383</link>
      <description>Transaction Management in SAP Treasury and Risk Management (corrected in S4CORE versions 1.01, 1.02, 1.03, 1.04 and EA-FINSERV versions 6.0, 6.03, 6.04, 6.05, 6.06, 6.16, 6.17, 6.18, 8.0) does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0383|2024-08-04T17:51:26.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 19:21:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0391|2024-08-04T17:51:26.799Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0391</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP NetWeaver AS Java (corrected in 7.10, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50) allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0391|2024-08-04T17:51:26.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 22:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0285|2024-08-04T17:44:16.353Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20crystal%20reports%20for%20visual%20studio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0285</link>
      <description>The .NET SDK WebForm Viewer in SAP Crystal Reports for Visual Studio (fixed in version 2010) discloses sensitive database information including credentials which can be misused by the attacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0285|2024-08-04T17:44:16.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 20:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6280|2024-08-04T08:55:22.265Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28abap%20server%29%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6280</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver (ABAP Server) and ABAP Platform, versions 731, 740, 750, allows an attacker with admin privileges to access certain files which should otherwise be restricted, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6280|2024-08-04T08:55:22.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 12:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6290|2024-08-04T08:55:22.403Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20disclosure%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6290</link>
      <description>SAP Disclosure Management, version 10.1, is vulnerable to Session Fixation attacks wherein the attacker tricks the user into using a specific session ID.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6290|2024-08-04T08:55:22.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 12:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0284|2024-08-04T17:44:16.347Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20hana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0284</link>
      <description>SLD Registration in SAP HANA (fixed in versions 1.0, 2.0) does not sufficiently validate an XML document accepted from an untrusted source. The attacker can call SLDREG with an XML file containing a reference to an XML External Entity (XXE). This can cause SLDREG to, for example, continuously loop, read arbitrary files and even send local files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0284|2024-08-04T17:44:16.347Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 20:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0378|2024-08-04T17:51:26.339Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0378</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface), before version 4.2, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs and allows an attacker to store malicious scripts in the file name of the background image resulting in Stored Cross-Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0378|2024-08-04T17:51:26.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6222|2024-08-04T08:55:22.147Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6222</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface), versions 4.1, 4.2, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6222|2024-08-04T08:55:22.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0312|2024-08-04T17:44:16.453Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20process%20integration%28sap_xiesr%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0312</link>
      <description>Several web pages provided SAP NetWeaver Process Integration (versions: SAP_XIESR: 7.10 to 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50 and SAP_XITOOL: 7.10 to 7.11, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50) are not password protected. An attacker could access landscape information like host names, ports or other technical data in the absence of restrictive firewall and port settings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0312|2024-08-04T17:44:16.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 16:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6353|2024-08-04T09:02:39.581Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6353</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated SKP file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6353|2024-08-04T09:02:39.581Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:54:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6234|2024-08-04T08:55:22.159Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20host%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6234</link>
      <description>SAP Host Agent, version 7.21, allows an attacker with admin privileges to use the operation framework to gain root privileges over the underlying operating system, leading to Privilege Escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6234|2024-08-04T08:55:22.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6367|2024-08-04T09:02:39.915Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20composite%20application%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6367</link>
      <description>There is a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Composite Application Framework, versions - 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50. An unauthenticated attacker can trick an unsuspecting authenticated user to click on a malicious link. The end users browser has no way to know that the script should not be trusted, and will execute the script, resulting in sensitive information being disclosed or modified.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6367|2024-08-04T09:02:39.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 13:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6239|2024-08-04T08:55:22.312Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20one%20%28backup%20service%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6239</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP Business One (Backup service), versions 9.3, 10.0, allows an attacker with admin permissions to view SYSTEM user password in clear text, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6239|2024-08-04T08:55:22.312Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 12:33:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0269|2024-08-04T17:44:16.455Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28bi%20workspace%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0269</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (BI Workspace), versions 4.10 and 4.20, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0269|2024-08-04T17:44:16.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0301|2024-08-04T17:44:16.388Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20identity%20management%20%28rest%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0301</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, it is possible to request the modification of role or privilege assignments through SAP Identity Management REST Interface Version 2, which would otherwise be restricted only for viewing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0301|2024-08-04T17:44:16.388Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 20:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6347|2024-08-04T09:02:39.820Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6347</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated HDR file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6347|2024-08-04T09:02:39.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42061|2024-08-04T03:22:25.820Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42061</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence) - version 420, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This allows a low privileged attacker to retrieve some data from the victim but will never be able to modify the document and publish these modifications to the server. It impacts the "Quick Prompt" workflow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42061|2024-08-04T03:22:25.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0361|2024-08-04T17:44:16.592Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20supplier%20relationship%20management%20%28master%20data%20management%20catalog%29%20%28srm_mdm_cat%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0361</link>
      <description>SAP Supplier Relationship Management (Master Data Management Catalog - SRM_MDM_CAT, before versions 3.73, 7.31, 7.32) does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0361|2024-08-04T17:44:16.592Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 16:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0337|2024-08-04T17:44:16.510Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20process%20integration%20%28java%20proxy%20runtime%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0337</link>
      <description>Java Proxy Runtime of SAP NetWeaver Process Integration, versions 7.10, 7.11, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs and allows an attacker to execute malicious scripts in the url thereby resulting in Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0337|2024-08-04T17:44:16.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 13:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6362|2024-08-04T09:02:39.846Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20banking%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6362</link>
      <description>SAP Banking Services version 500, use an incorrect authorization object in some of its reports. Although the affected reports are protected with otherauthorization objects, exploitation of the vulnerability could lead to privilege escalation and violation in segregation of duties, which in turn could lead to Service interruptions and system unavailability for the victim and users of the component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6362|2024-08-04T09:02:39.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 13:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6376|2024-08-04T09:02:40.379Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6376</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated Right Hemisphere Binary (.rh) file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6376|2024-08-04T09:02:40.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 01:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6267|2024-08-04T08:55:22.272Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20disclosure%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6267</link>
      <description>Some sensitive cookies in SAP Disclosure Management, version 10.1, are missing HttpOnly flag, leading to sensitive cookie without Http Only flag.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6267|2024-08-04T08:55:22.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 12:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6270|2024-08-04T08:55:22.334Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20%28banking%20services%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6270</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP (Banking Services), versions - 710, 711, 740, 750, 751, 752, 75A, 75B, 75C, 75D, 75E, does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user due to Missing Authorization Check, allowing wrong and unexpected change of individual conditions by a malicious user leading to wrong prices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6270|2024-08-04T08:55:22.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 12:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0349|2024-08-04T17:44:16.482Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20kernel%20%28krnl32nuc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0349</link>
      <description>SAP Kernel (ABAP Debugger), versions KRNL32NUC 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT, KRNL32UC 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT, KRNL64NUC 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT, 7.49, KRNL64UC 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT, 7.49, 7.73, KERNEL 7.21, 7.49, 7.53, 7.73, 7.75, 7.76, 7.77, allows a user to execute “Go to statement” without possessing the authorization S_DEVELOP DEBUG 02, resulting in Missing Authorization Check</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0349|2024-08-04T17:44:16.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 14:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6351|2024-08-04T09:02:40.186Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6351</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated FBX file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6351|2024-08-04T09:02:40.186Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0247|2024-08-04T17:44:16.249Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20cloud%20connector
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0247</link>
      <description>SAP Cloud Connector, before version 2.11.3, allows an attacker to inject code that can be executed by the application. An attacker could thereby control the behavior of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0247|2024-08-04T17:44:16.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0403|2024-08-04T17:51:26.878Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20enable%20now
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0403</link>
      <description>SAP Enable Now, before version 1911, allows an attacker to input commands into the CSV files, which will be executed when opened, leading to CSV Command Injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0403|2024-08-04T17:51:26.878Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 21:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-44232|2024-08-04T04:17:24.925Z -- sap%20se -- saf-t%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-44232</link>
      <description>SAF-T Framework Transaction SAFTN_G allows an attacker to exploit insufficient validation of path information provided by normal user, leading to full server directory access. The attacker can see the whole filesystem structure but cannot overwrite, delete, or corrupt arbitrary files on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-44232|2024-08-04T04:17:24.925Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0390|2024-08-04T17:51:26.563Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20data%20hub%20%28dh_foundation%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0390</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP Data Hub (corrected in DH_Foundation version 2) allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted. Connection details that are maintained in Connection Manager are visible to users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0390|2024-08-04T17:51:26.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 22:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0351|2024-08-04T17:44:16.464Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20uddi%20server%20%28services%20registry%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0351</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the SAP NetWeaver UDDI Server (Services Registry), versions 7.10, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50. Because of this, an attacker can exploit Services Registry potentially enabling them to take complete control of the product, including viewing, changing, or deleting data by injecting code into the working memory which is subsequently executed by the application. It can also be used to cause a general fault in the product, causing the product to terminate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0351|2024-08-04T17:44:16.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 13:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0402|2024-08-04T17:51:26.083Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20adaptive%20server%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0402</link>
      <description>SAP Adaptive Server Enterprise, before versions 15.7 and 16.0, under certain conditions exposes some sensitive information to the admin, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0402|2024-08-04T17:51:26.083Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 21:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0389|2024-08-04T17:51:26.664Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20java%20%28j2ee-framework%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0389</link>
      <description>An administrator of SAP NetWeaver Application Server Java (J2EE-Framework), (corrected in versions 7.1, 7.2, 7.3, 7.31, 7.4, 7.5), may change privileges for all or some functions in Java Server, and enable users to execute functions, they are not allowed to execute otherwise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0389|2024-08-04T17:51:26.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 21:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0316|2024-08-04T17:44:16.455Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20process%20integration%28sap_xiesr%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0316</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Process Integration, versions: SAP_XIESR: 7.20, SAP_XITOOL: 7.10 to 7.11, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, does not sufficiently validate user-controlled inputs, which allows an attacker possessing admin privileges to read and modify data from the victim’s browser, by injecting malicious scripts in certain servlets, which will be executed when the victim is tricked to click on those malicious links, resulting in reflected Cross Site Scripting vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0316|2024-08-04T17:44:16.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 18:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0398|2024-08-04T17:51:26.079Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28monitoring%20application%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0398</link>
      <description>Due to insufficient CSRF protection, SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Monitoring Application), before versions 4.1, 4.2 and 4.3, may lead to an authenticated user to send unintended request to the web server, leading to Cross Site Request Forgery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0398|2024-08-04T17:51:26.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 21:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-44231|2024-08-04T04:17:24.557Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20abap%20server%20%26%20abap%20platform%20%28translation%20tools%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-44231</link>
      <description>Internally used text extraction reports allow an attacker to inject code that can be executed by the application. An attacker could thereby control the behavior of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-44231|2024-08-04T04:17:24.557Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26829|2024-08-04T16:03:22.449Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java%20%28p2p%20cluster%20communication%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26829</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS JAVA (P2P Cluster Communication), versions - 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, allows arbitrary connections from processes because of missing authentication check, that are outside the cluster and even outside the network segment dedicated for the internal cluster communication. As result, an unauthenticated attacker can invoke certain functions that would otherwise be restricted to system administrators only, including access to system administration functions or shutting down the system completely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26829|2024-08-04T16:03:22.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 16:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6297|2024-08-04T08:55:22.435Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20data%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6297</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions the upgrade of SAP Data Hub 2.7 to SAP Data Intelligence, version - 3.0, allows an attacker to access confidential system configuration information, that should otherwise be restricted, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6297|2024-08-04T08:55:22.435Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 13:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6323|2024-08-04T08:55:22.480Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20enterprise%20portal%20%28fiori%20framework%20page%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6323</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Enterprise Portal (Fiori Framework Page) versions - 7.50, 7.31, 7.40, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs and allows an attacker on a valid session to create an XSS that will be both reflected immediately and also be persisted and returned in further access to the system, resulting in Cross Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6323|2024-08-04T08:55:22.480Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 01:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0318|2024-08-04T17:44:16.482Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20for%20java%20%28startup%20framework%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0318</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP NetWeaver Application Server for Java (Startup Framework), versions 7.21, 7.22, 7.45, 7.49, and 7.53, allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0318|2024-08-04T17:44:16.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 18:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6296|2024-08-04T08:55:22.230Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28abap%20server%29%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6296</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver (ABAP Server) and ABAP Platform, versions - 700, 701, 702, 710, 711, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 753, 755, allows an attacker to inject code that can be executed by the application, leading to Code Injection. An attacker could thereby control the behavior of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6296|2024-08-04T08:55:22.230Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 13:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6364|2024-08-04T09:02:40.251Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28ca%20introscope%20enterprise%20manager%29%20and%20sap%20focused%20run%20%28ca%20introscope%20enterprise%20manager%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6364</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager and SAP Focused Run (update provided in WILY_INTRO_ENTERPRISE 9.7, 10.1, 10.5, 10.7), allows an attacker to modify a cookie in a way that OS commands can be executed and potentially gain control over the host running the CA Introscope Enterprise Manager,leading to Code Injection. With this, the attacker is able to read and modify all system files and also impact system availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6364|2024-08-04T09:02:40.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 01:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-44234|2024-08-04T04:17:24.598Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-44234</link>
      <description>SAP Business One - version 10.0, extended log stores information that can be of a sensitive nature and give valuable guidance to an attacker or expose sensitive user information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-44234|2024-08-04T04:17:24.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 19:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42070|2024-08-04T03:22:25.853Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42070</link>
      <description>When a user opens manipulated Jupiter Tessellation (.jt) file received from untrusted sources in SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer - version 9.0, the application crashes and becomes temporarily unavailable to the user until restart of the application</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42070|2024-08-04T03:22:25.853Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0258|2024-08-04T17:44:16.456Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20disclosure%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0258</link>
      <description>SAP Disclosure Management, version 10.01, does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0258|2024-08-04T17:44:16.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6285|2024-08-04T08:55:22.414Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20-%20xml%20toolkit%20for%20java%20%28engineapi%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6285</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver - XML Toolkit for JAVA (ENGINEAPI) (versions- 7.10, 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50), under certain conditions allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6285|2024-08-04T08:55:22.414Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 12:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6207|2024-08-04T08:55:22.109Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28user%20experience%20monitoring%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6207</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager (User Experience Monitoring), version- 7.2, due to Missing Authentication Check does not perform any authentication for a service resulting in complete compromise of all SMDAgents connected to the Solution Manager.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6207|2024-08-04T08:55:22.109Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6295|2024-08-04T08:55:22.195Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20adaptive%20server%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6295</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions the SAP Adaptive Server Enterprise, version 16.0, allows an attacker to access encrypted sensitive and confidential information through publicly readable installation log files leading to a compromise of the installed Cockpit. This compromise could enable the attacker to view, modify and/or make unavailable any data associated with the Cockpit, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6295|2024-08-04T08:55:22.195Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 13:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6314|2024-08-04T08:55:22.489Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6314</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated HPGL file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6314|2024-08-04T08:55:22.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0276|2024-08-04T17:44:16.230Z -- sap%20se -- banking%20services%20from%20sap%209.0%20%28fsappl%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0276</link>
      <description>Banking services from SAP 9.0 (FSAPPL version 5) and SAP S/4HANA Financial Products Subledger (S4FPSL, version 1) performs an inadequate authorization check for an authenticated user, potentially resulting in escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0276|2024-08-04T17:44:16.230Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40502|2024-08-04T02:44:10.860Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40502</link>
      <description>SAP Commerce - versions 2105.3, 2011.13, 2005.18, 1905.34, does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. Authenticated attackers will be able to access and edit data from b2b units they do not belong to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40502|2024-08-04T02:44:10.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6288|2024-08-04T08:55:22.418Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6288</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface) allows an attacker with edit document rights to upload any file (including script files) without proper file format validation leading to Unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability. The attacker can modify some formulas and display erroneous content. The server is not affected only the current user browser session, that can easily be closed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6288|2024-08-04T08:55:22.418Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6215|2024-08-04T08:55:22.077Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20%28business%20server%20pages%20test%20application%20it00%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6215</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP Business Server Pages Test Application IT00, versions 700, 701, 702, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, allows an attacker to redirect users to a malicious site due to insufficient URL validation and steal credentials of the victim, leading to URL Redirection vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6215|2024-08-04T08:55:22.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6189|2024-08-04T08:55:22.102Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28cmc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6189</link>
      <description>Certain settings page(s) in SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (CMC), version 4.2, generates error messages that can give enterprise private-network related information which would otherwise be restricted leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6189|2024-08-04T08:55:22.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 19:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0321|2024-08-04T17:44:16.476Z -- sap%20se -- abap%20server%20and%20abap%20platform%20%28sap%20basis%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0321</link>
      <description>ABAP Server and ABAP Platform (SAP Basis), versions, 7.31, 7.4, 7.5, do not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0321|2024-08-04T17:44:16.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 18:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6185|2024-08-04T08:55:22.130Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28sap%20basis%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6185</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions ABAP Online Community in SAP NetWeaver (SAP_BASIS version 7.40) and SAP S/4HANA (SAP_BASIS versions 7.50, 7.51, 7.52, 7.53, 7.54), allows an authenticated attacker to store a malicious payload which results in Stored Cross Site Scripting vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6185|2024-08-04T08:55:22.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 19:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6292|2024-08-04T08:55:22.252Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20disclosure%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6292</link>
      <description>Logout mechanism in SAP Disclosure Management, version 10.1, does not invalidate one of the session cookies, leading to Insufficient Session Expiration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6292|2024-08-04T08:55:22.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 12:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6359|2024-08-04T09:02:39.983Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6359</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated PLT file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6359|2024-08-04T09:02:39.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0238|2024-08-04T17:44:15.951Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce%20%28ex.%20sap%20hybris%20commerce%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0238</link>
      <description>SAP Commerce (previously known as SAP Hybris Commerce), before version 6.7, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0238|2024-08-04T17:44:15.951Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6363|2024-08-04T09:02:39.615Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6363</link>
      <description>SAP Commerce Cloud, versions - 1808, 1811, 1905, 2005, exposes several web applications that maintain sessions with a user. These sessions are established after the user has authenticated with username/passphrase credentials. The user can change their own passphrase, but this does not invalidate active sessions that the user may have with SAP Commerce Cloud web applications, which gives an attacker the opportunity to reuse old session credentials, resulting in Insufficient Session Expiration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6363|2024-08-04T09:02:39.615Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 01:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6344|2024-08-04T09:02:39.585Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6344</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated PDF file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6344|2024-08-04T09:02:39.585Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6352|2024-08-04T09:02:39.625Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6352</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated FBX file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6352|2024-08-04T09:02:39.625Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6256|2024-08-04T08:55:22.211Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20master%20data%20governance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6256</link>
      <description>SAP Master Data Governance, versions - 748, 749, 750, 751, 752, 800, 801, 802, 803, 804, allows users to display change request details without having required authorizations, due to Missing Authorization Check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6256|2024-08-04T08:55:22.211Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26820|2024-08-04T16:03:22.700Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26820</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS JAVA, versions - 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, allows an attacker who is authenticated as an administrator to use the administrator console, to expose unauthenticated access to the file system and upload a malicious file. The attacker or another user can then use a separate mechanism to execute OS commands through the uploaded file leading to Privilege Escalation and completely compromise the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the server operating system and any application running on it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26820|2024-08-04T16:03:22.700Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6204|2024-08-04T08:55:22.119Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20treasury%20and%20risk%20management%20%28transaction%20management%29%20%28ea-finserv%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6204</link>
      <description>The selection query in SAP Treasury and Risk Management (Transaction Management) (EA-FINSERV?versions 600, 603, 604, 605, 606, 616, 617, 618, 800 and S4CORE versions 101, 102, 103, 104) returns more records than it should be when selecting and displaying the contract number, leading to Missing Authorization Check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6204|2024-08-04T08:55:22.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6186|2024-08-04T08:55:21.898Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20host%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6186</link>
      <description>SAP Host Agent, version 7.21, allows an attacker to cause a slowdown in processing of username/password-based authentication requests of the SAP Host Agent, leading to Denial of Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6186|2024-08-04T08:55:21.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 19:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0319|2024-08-04T17:44:16.458Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0319</link>
      <description>The SAP Gateway, versions 7.5, 7.51, 7.52 and 7.53, allows an attacker to inject content which is displayed in the form of an error message. An attacker could thus mislead a user to believe this information is from the legitimate service when it's not.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0319|2024-08-04T17:44:16.458Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 18:51:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0343|2024-08-04T17:44:16.564Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce%20cloud%20%28mediaconversion%20extension%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0343</link>
      <description>SAP Commerce Cloud (Mediaconversion Extension), versions 6.4, 6.5, 6.6, 6.7, 1808, 1811, 1905, allows an authenticated Backoffice/HMC user to inject code that can be executed by the application, leading to Code Injection. An attacker could thereby control the behavior of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0343|2024-08-04T17:44:16.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 13:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6319|2024-08-04T08:55:22.263Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6319</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server Java, versions - 7.10, 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, and 7.50 allows an unauthenticated attacker to include JavaScript blocks in any web page or URL with different symbols which are otherwise not allowed. On successful exploitation an attacker can steal authentication information of the user, such as data relating to his or her current session and limitedly impact confidentiality and integrity of the application, leading to Reflected Cross Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6319|2024-08-04T08:55:22.263Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 01:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42062|2024-08-04T03:22:25.846Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20erp%20hcm%20portugal
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42062</link>
      <description>SAP ERP HCM Portugal does not perform necessary authorization checks for a report that reads the payroll data of employees in a certain area. Since the affected report only reads the payroll information, the attacker can neither modify any information nor cause availability impacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42062|2024-08-04T03:22:25.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6240|2024-08-04T08:55:22.180Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20%28web%20dynpro%20abap%29%20%28sap_ui%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6240</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP (Web Dynpro ABAP), versions (SAP_UI 750, 752, 753, 754 and SAP_BASIS 700, 710, 730, 731, 804) allows an unauthenticated attacker to prevent legitimate users from accessing a service, either by crashing or flooding the service leading to Denial of Service</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6240|2024-08-04T08:55:22.180Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26819|2024-08-04T16:03:23.072Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20%28web%20dynpro%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26819</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP (Web Dynpro), versions - 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 782, allows an authenticated user to access Web Dynpro components, that allows them to read and delete database logfiles because of Improper Access Control.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26819|2024-08-04T16:03:23.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6356|2024-08-04T09:02:39.676Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6356</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated BMP file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6356|2024-08-04T09:02:39.676Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6261|2024-08-04T08:55:22.152Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28trace%20analysis%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6261</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager (Trace Analysis), version 7.20, allows an attacker to perform a log injection into the trace file, due to Incomplete XML Validation. The readability of the trace file is impaired.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6261|2024-08-04T08:55:22.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 12:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6369|2024-08-04T09:02:39.880Z -- sap%20se -- ca%20introscope%20enterprise%20manager%20%28affected%20products%3A%20sap%20solution%20manager%20and%20sap%20focused%20run%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6369</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager and SAP Focused Run (update provided in WILY_INTRO_ENTERPRISE 9.7, 10.1, 10.5, 10.7), allows an unauthenticated attackers to bypass the authentication if the default passwords for Admin and Guest have not been changed by the administrator.This may impact the confidentiality of the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6369|2024-08-04T09:02:39.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 13:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6236|2024-08-04T08:55:22.273Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20landscape%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6236</link>
      <description>SAP Landscape Management, version 3.0, and SAP Adaptive Extensions, version 1.0, allows an attacker with admin_group privileges to change ownership and permissions (including S-user ID bit s-bit) of arbitrary files remotely. This results in the possibility to execute these files as root user from a non-root context, leading to Privilege Escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6236|2024-08-04T08:55:22.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26811|2024-08-04T16:03:22.453Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce%20cloud%20%28accelerator%20payment%20mock%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26811</link>
      <description>SAP Commerce Cloud (Accelerator Payment Mock), versions - 1808, 1811, 1905, 2005, allows an unauthenticated attacker to submit a crafted request over a network to a particular SAP Commerce module URL which will be processed without further interaction, the crafted request leads to Server Side Request Forgery attack which could lead to retrieval of limited pieces of information about the service with no impact on integrity or availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26811|2024-08-04T16:03:22.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40504|2024-08-04T02:44:10.769Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40504</link>
      <description>A certain template role in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 700, 701, 702, 710, 711, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, contains transport authorizations, which exceed expected display only permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40504|2024-08-04T02:44:10.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0306|2024-08-04T17:44:16.483Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20hana%20extended%20application%20services%20%28advanced%20model%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0306</link>
      <description>SAP HANA Extended Application Services (advanced model), version 1, allows authenticated low privileged XS Advanced Platform users such as SpaceAuditors to execute requests to obtain a complete list of SAP HANA user IDs and names.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0306|2024-08-04T17:44:16.483Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 14:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6244|2024-08-04T08:55:22.319Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6244</link>
      <description>SAP Business Client, version 7.0, allows an attacker after a successful social engineering attack to inject malicious code as a DLL file in untrusted directories that can be executed by the application, due to uncontrolled search path element. An attacker could thereby control the behavior of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6244|2024-08-04T08:55:22.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26828|2024-08-04T16:03:22.743Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20disclosure%20management.
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26828</link>
      <description>SAP Disclosure Management, version - 10.1, provides capabilities for authorized users to upload and download content of specific file type. In some file types it is possible to enter formulas which can call external applications or execute scripts. The execution of a payload (script) on target machine could be used to steal and modify the data available in the spreadsheet</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26828|2024-08-04T16:03:22.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 16:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0367|2024-08-04T17:44:16.518Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20process%20integration%20%28b2b%20toolkit%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0367</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Process Integration (B2B Toolkit), before versions 1.0 and 2.0, does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, allowing the import of B2B table content that leads to Missing Authorization Check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0367|2024-08-04T17:44:16.518Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0240|2024-08-04T17:44:16.021Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20mobile%20for%20android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0240</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Mobile for Android (before 6.3.5) application allows an attacker to provide malicious input in the form of a SAP BI link, preventing legitimate users from accessing the application by crashing it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0240|2024-08-04T17:44:16.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6316|2024-08-04T08:55:22.258Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20erp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6316</link>
      <description>SAP ERP and SAP S/4 HANA allows an authenticated user to see cost records to objects to which he has no authorization in PS reporting, leading to Missing Authorization check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6316|2024-08-04T08:55:22.258Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6190|2024-08-04T08:55:21.916Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java%20%28heap%20dump%20application%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6190</link>
      <description>Certain vulnerable endpoints in SAP NetWeaver AS Java (Heap Dump Application), versions 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, provide valuable information about the system like hostname, server node and installation path that could be misused by an attacker leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6190|2024-08-04T08:55:21.916Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 19:46:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40497|2024-08-04T02:44:10.782Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20analysis%2C%20%28edition%20for%20olap%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40497</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Analysis (edition for OLAP) - versions 420, 430, allows an attacker to exploit certain application endpoints to read sensitive data. These endpoints are normally exposed over the network and successful exploitation could lead to exposure of some system specific data like its version.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40497|2024-08-04T02:44:10.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0368|2024-08-04T17:44:16.523Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20customer%20relationship%20management%20%28email%20management%20-%20s4crm%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0368</link>
      <description>SAP Customer Relationship Management (Email Management), versions: S4CRM before 1.0 and 2.0, BBPCRM before 7.0, 7.01, 7.02, 7.12, 7.13 and 7.14, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs within the mail client resulting in Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0368|2024-08-04T17:44:16.523Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:17:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40500|2024-08-04T02:44:10.833Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28crystal%20reports%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40500</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Crystal Reports) - versions 420, 430, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit missing XML validations at endpoints to read sensitive data. These endpoints are normally exposed over the network and successful exploitation can enable the attacker to retrieve arbitrary files from the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40500|2024-08-04T02:44:10.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-44235|2024-08-04T04:17:24.558Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-44235</link>
      <description>Two methods of a utility class in SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP - versions 700, 701, 702, 710, 711, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, allow an attacker with high privileges and has direct access to SAP System, to inject code when executing with a certain transaction class builder. This could allow execution of arbitrary commands on the operating system, that could highly impact the Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-44235|2024-08-04T04:17:24.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6235|2024-08-04T08:55:22.266Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28diagnostics%20agent%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6235</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager (Diagnostics Agent), version 7.2, does not perform the authentication check for the functionalities of the Collector Simulator, leading to Missing Authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6235|2024-08-04T08:55:22.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:36:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26837|2024-08-04T16:03:22.675Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28user%20experience%20monitoring%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26837</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager 7.2 (User Experience Monitoring), version - 7.2, allows an authenticated user to upload a malicious script that can exploit an existing path traversal vulnerability to compromise confidentiality exposing elements of the file system, partially compromise integrity allowing the modification of some configurations and partially compromise availability by making certain services unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26837|2024-08-04T16:03:22.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 16:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6370|2024-08-04T09:02:40.564Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28di%20design%20time%20repository%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6370</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Design Time Repository (DTR), versions - 7.11, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6370|2024-08-04T09:02:40.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 13:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0265|2024-08-04T17:44:16.194Z -- sap%20se -- abap%20platform%20%28krnl32nuc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0265</link>
      <description>SLD Registration of ABAP Platform allows an attacker to prevent legitimate users from accessing a service, either by crashing or flooding the service. Fixed in versions KRNL32NUC 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT,KRNL32UC 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT, KRNL64NUC 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT, 7.49,KRNL64UC 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT, 7.49. 7.73 KERNEL from 7.21 to 7.22, 7.45, 7.49, 7.53, 7.73, 7.75.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0265|2024-08-04T17:44:16.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40501|2024-08-04T02:44:10.848Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20abap%20platform%20kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40501</link>
      <description>SAP ABAP Platform Kernel - versions 7.77, 7.81, 7.85, 7.86, does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated business user, resulting in escalation of privileges. That means this business user is able to read and modify data beyond the vulnerable system. However, the attacker can neither significantly reduce the performance of the system nor stop the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40501|2024-08-04T02:44:10.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6293|2024-08-04T08:55:22.260Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28knowledge%20management%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6293</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver (Knowledge Management), versions - 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, allows an unauthenticated attacker to upload a malicious file and also to access, modify or make unavailable existing files but the impact is limited to the files themselves and is restricted by other policies such as access control lists and other upload file size restrictions, leading to Unrestricted File Upload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6293|2024-08-04T08:55:22.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 13:22:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6242|2024-08-04T08:55:22.174Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28live%20data%20connect%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6242</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (Live Data Connect), versions 1.0, 2.0, 2.1, 2.2, 2.3, allows an attacker to logon on the Central Management Console without password in case of the BIPRWS application server was not protected with some specific certificate, leading to Missing Authentication Check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6242|2024-08-04T08:55:22.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:58:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6317|2024-08-04T08:55:22.364Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20adaptive%20server%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6317</link>
      <description>In certain situations, an attacker with regular user credentials and local access to an ASE cockpit installation can access sensitive information which appears in the installation log files. This information although sensitive is of limited utility and cannot be used to further access, modify or render unavailable any other information in the cockpit or system. This affects SAP Adaptive Server Enterprise, Versions - 15.7, 16.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6317|2024-08-04T08:55:22.364Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 18:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26831|2024-08-04T16:03:22.943Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20bi%20platform%20%28crystal%20report%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26831</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects BI Platform (Crystal Report), versions - 4.1, 4.2, 4.3, does not sufficiently validate uploaded XML entities during crystal report generation due to missing XML validation, An attacker with basic privileges can inject some arbitrary XML entities leading to internal file disclosure, internal directories disclosure, Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) and denial-of-service (DoS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26831|2024-08-04T16:03:22.943Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 16:29:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0395|2024-08-04T17:51:26.239Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28fiori%20bi%20launchpad%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0395</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Fiori BI Launchpad), before version 4.2, allows execution of JavaScript in a text module in Fiori BI Launchpad, leading to Stored Cross Site Scripting vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0395|2024-08-04T17:51:26.239Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 21:34:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6321|2024-08-04T08:55:22.439Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6321</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated U3D file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6321|2024-08-04T08:55:22.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6333|2024-08-04T08:55:22.392Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6333</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated 3DM file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6333|2024-08-04T08:55:22.392Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26838|2024-08-04T16:03:22.812Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20warehouse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26838</link>
      <description>SAP Business Warehouse, versions - 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 782, and SAP BW4HANA, versions - 100, 200 allows an attacker authenticated with (high) developer privileges to submit a crafted request to generate and execute code without requiring any user interaction. It is possible to craft a request which will result in the execution of Operating System commands leading to Code Injection vulnerability which could completely compromise the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the server and any data or other applications running on it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26838|2024-08-04T16:03:22.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 16:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6245|2024-08-04T08:55:22.271Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6245</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform, version 4.2, allows an attacker with access to local instance, to inject file or code that can be executed by the application due to Improper Control of Resource Identifiers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6245|2024-08-04T08:55:22.271Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6200|2024-08-04T08:55:21.904Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce%20cloud%20%28smartedit%20extension%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6200</link>
      <description>The SAP Commerce (SmartEdit Extension), versions- 6.6, 6.7, 1808, 1811, is vulnerable to client-side angularjs template injection, a variant of Cross-Site-Scripting (XSS) that exploits the templating facilities of the angular framework.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6200|2024-08-04T08:55:21.904Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:18:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26818|2024-08-04T16:03:22.370Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20%28web%20dynpro%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26818</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP (Web Dynpro), versions - 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 782, allows an authenticated user to access Web Dynpro components, which reveals sensitive system information that would otherwise be restricted to highly privileged users because of missing authorization, resulting in Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26818|2024-08-04T16:03:22.370Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38174|2024-08-04T01:37:15.770Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38174</link>
      <description>When a user opens manipulated files received from untrusted sources in SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer version - 9, the application crashes and becomes temporarily unavailable to the user until restart of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38174|2024-08-04T01:37:15.770Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6219|2024-08-04T08:55:22.303Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28crystalreports%20webform%20viewer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6219</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (CrystalReports WebForm Viewer), versions 4.1, 4.2, and Crystal Reports for VS version 2010, allows an attacker with basic authorization to perform deserialization attack in the application, leading to service interruptions and denial of service and unauthorized execution of arbitrary commands, leading to Deserialization of Untrusted Data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6219|2024-08-04T08:55:22.303Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0375|2024-08-04T17:51:26.129Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0375</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface), before versions 4.2 and 4.3, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs and allows execution of scripts in the export dialog box of the report name resulting in reflected Cross-Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0375|2024-08-04T17:51:26.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6287|2024-08-04T08:55:22.221Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java%20%28lm%20configuration%20wizard%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6287</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS JAVA (LM Configuration Wizard), versions - 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, does not perform an authentication check which allows an attacker without prior authentication to execute configuration tasks to perform critical actions against the SAP Java system, including the ability to create an administrative user, and therefore compromising Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability of the system, leading to Missing Authentication Check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6287|2024-08-04T08:55:22.221Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 12:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6374|2024-08-04T09:02:39.614Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6374</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated Jupiter Tessallation(.jt) file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6374|2024-08-04T09:02:39.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 01:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26826|2024-08-04T16:03:22.433Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26826</link>
      <description>Process Integration Monitoring of SAP NetWeaver AS JAVA, versions - 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, allows an attacker to upload any file (including script files) without proper file format validation, leading to Unrestricted File Upload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26826|2024-08-04T16:03:22.433Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 16:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0278|2024-08-04T17:44:16.299Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20process%20integration%20%28messaging%20system%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0278</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions the Monitoring Servlet of the SAP NetWeaver Process Integration (Messaging System), fixed in versions 7.10 to 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, allows an attacker to see the names of database tables used by the application, leading to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0278|2024-08-04T17:44:16.299Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 20:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6250|2024-08-04T08:55:22.282Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20adaptive%20server%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6250</link>
      <description>SAP Adaptive Server Enterprise, version 16.0, allows an authenticated attacker to exploit certain misconfigured endpoints exposed over the adjacent network, to read system administrator password leading to Information Disclosure. This could help the attacker to read/write any data and even stop the server like an administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6250|2024-08-04T08:55:22.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6259|2024-08-04T08:55:22.271Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20adaptive%20server%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6259</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP Adaptive Server Enterprise, versions 15.7, 16.0, allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted leading to Missing Authorization Check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6259|2024-08-04T08:55:22.271Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0289|2024-08-04T17:44:16.424Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0289</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence platform (Analysis for OLAP), versions 4.2 and 4.3, allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0289|2024-08-04T17:44:16.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 20:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26810|2024-08-04T16:03:22.387Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce%20cloud%20%28accelerator%20payment%20mock%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26810</link>
      <description>SAP Commerce Cloud (Accelerator Payment Mock), versions - 1808, 1811, 1905, 2005, allows an unauthenticated attacker to submit a crafted request over a network to a particular SAP Commerce module URL which will be processed without further interaction, the crafted request can render the SAP Commerce service itself unavailable leading to Denial of Service with no impact on confidentiality or integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26810|2024-08-04T16:03:22.387Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6209|2024-08-04T08:55:21.962Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20disclosure%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6209</link>
      <description>SAP Disclosure Management, version 10.1, does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, allowing access to administration accounts by a user with no roles, leading to Missing Authorization Check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6209|2024-08-04T08:55:21.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38175|2024-08-04T01:37:16.309Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20analysis%20for%20microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38175</link>
      <description>SAP Analysis for Microsoft Office - version 2.8, allows an attacker with high privileges to read sensitive data over the network, and gather or change information in the current system without user interaction. The attack would not lead to an impact on the availability of the system, but there would be an impact on integrity and confidentiality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38175|2024-08-04T01:37:16.309Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0304|2024-08-04T17:44:16.439Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20platform%28krnl32nuc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0304</link>
      <description>FTP Function of SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP Platform, versions- KRNL32NUC 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT, KRNL32UC 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT, KRNL64NUC 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT, 7.49, KRNL64UC 7.21, 7.21EXT, 7.22, 7.22EXT, 7.49, 7.73, KERNEL 7.21, 7.45, 7.49, 7.53, 7.73, allows an attacker to inject code or specifically manipulated command that can be executed by the application. An attacker could thereby control the behaviour of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0304|2024-08-04T17:44:16.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 14:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6199|2024-08-04T08:55:22.062Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20erp%20%28eappglo%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6199</link>
      <description>The view FIMENAV_COMPCERT in SAP ERP (MENA Certificate Management), EAPPGLO version 607, SAP_FIN versions- 618, 730 and SAP S/4HANA (MENA Certificate Management), S4CORE versions- 100, 101, 102, 103, 104; does not have any authorization check to it due to which an attacker without an authorization group can maintain any company certificate, leading to Missing Authorization Check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6199|2024-08-04T08:55:22.062Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6372|2024-08-04T09:02:40.644Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6372</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated PDF file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6372|2024-08-04T09:02:40.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 01:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0311|2024-08-04T17:44:16.455Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20r%2F3%20enterprise%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0311</link>
      <description>Automotive Dealer Portal in SAP R/3 Enterprise Application (versions: 600, 602, 603, 604, 605, 606, 616, 617) does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, this makes it possible for an attacker to send unwanted scripts to the browser of the victim using unwanted input and execute malicious code there, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0311|2024-08-04T17:44:16.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 16:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6338|2024-08-04T09:02:39.054Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6338</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated RH file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6338|2024-08-04T09:02:39.054Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-37535|2024-08-04T01:23:01.156Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20java%20%28jms%20connector%20service%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-37535</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server Java (JMS Connector Service) - versions 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, does not perform necessary authorization checks for user privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-37535|2024-08-04T01:23:01.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0355|2024-08-04T17:44:16.479Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20for%20java%20%28web%20container%29-engineapi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0355</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server Java Web Container, ENGINEAPI (before versions 7.10, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50) and SAP-JEECOR (before versions 6.40, 7.0, 7.01), allows an attacker to inject code that can be executed by the application. An attacker could thereby control the behaviour of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0355|2024-08-04T17:44:16.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 16:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6278|2024-08-04T08:55:22.330Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28bi%20launchpad%20and%20cmc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6278</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (BI Launchpad and CMC), versions 4.1, 4.2, allows to an attacker to embed malicious scripts in the application while uploading images, which gets executed when the victim opens these files, leading to Stored Cross Site Scripting</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6278|2024-08-04T08:55:22.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 12:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6368|2024-08-04T09:02:40.215Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20planning%20and%20consolidation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6368</link>
      <description>SAP Business Planning and Consolidation, versions - 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 810, 100, 200, can be abused by an attacker, allowing them to modify displayed application content without authorization, and to potentially obtain authentication information from other legitimate users, leading to Cross Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6368|2024-08-04T09:02:40.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 01:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6243|2024-08-04T08:55:22.168Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20adaptive%20server%20enterprise%20%28xp%20server%20on%20windows%20platform%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6243</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, SAP Adaptive Server Enterprise (XP Server on Windows Platform), versions 15.7, 16.0, does not perform the necessary checks for an authenticated user while executing the extended stored procedure, allowing an attacker to read, modify, delete restricted data on connected servers, leading to Code Injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6243|2024-08-04T08:55:22.168Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0274|2024-08-04T17:44:16.199Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20mobile%20platform%20sdk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0274</link>
      <description>SAP Mobile Platform SDK allows an attacker to prevent legitimate users from accessing a service, either by crashing or flooding the service (i.e. denial of service). Fixed in versions 3.1 SP03 PL02, SDK 3.1 SP04, or later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0274|2024-08-04T17:44:16.199Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6265|2024-08-04T08:55:22.177Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6265</link>
      <description>SAP Commerce, versions - 6.7, 1808, 1811, 1905, and SAP Commerce (Data Hub), versions - 6.7, 1808, 1811, 1905, allows an attacker to bypass the authentication and/or authorization that has been configured by the system administrator due to the use of Hardcoded Credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6265|2024-08-04T08:55:22.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 18:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6263|2024-08-04T08:55:22.315Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6263</link>
      <description>Standalone clients connecting to SAP NetWeaver AS Java via P4 Protocol, versions (SAP-JEECOR 7.00, 7.01; SERVERCOR 7.10, 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50; CORE-TOOLS 7.00, 7.01, 7.02, 7.05, 7.10, 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50) do not perform any authentication checks for operations that require user identity leading to Authentication Bypass.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6263|2024-08-04T08:55:22.315Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 12:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42067|2024-08-04T03:22:25.941Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42067</link>
      <description>In SAP NetWeaver AS for ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 701, 702, 711, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 786, an attacker authenticated as a regular user can use the S/4 Hana dashboard to reveal systems and services which they would not normally be allowed to see. No information alteration or denial of service is possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42067|2024-08-04T03:22:25.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 19:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6291|2024-08-04T08:55:22.208Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20disclosure%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6291</link>
      <description>SAP Disclosure Management, version 10.1, session mechanism does not have expiration data set therefore allows unlimited access after authenticating once, leading to Insufficient Session Expiration</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6291|2024-08-04T08:55:22.208Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 12:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6315|2024-08-04T08:55:22.380Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6315</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version 9, allows an attacker to send certain manipulated file to the victim, which can lead to leakage of sensitive information when the victim loads the malicious file into the VE viewer, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6315|2024-08-04T08:55:22.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 13:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6216|2024-08-04T08:55:21.875Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28bi%20launchpad%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6216</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (BI Launchpad), version 4.2, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6216|2024-08-04T08:55:21.875Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6360|2024-08-04T09:02:39.571Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6360</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated DIB file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6360|2024-08-04T09:02:39.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6227|2024-08-04T08:55:22.281Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28cms%20%2F%20auditing%20issues%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6227</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (CMS / Auditing issues), version 4.2, allows attacker to send specially crafted GIOP packets to several services due to Improper Input Validation, allowing to forge additional entries in GLF log files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6227|2024-08-04T08:55:22.281Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6229|2024-08-04T08:55:22.172Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20%28business%20server%20pages%20application%20crm_bsp_frame%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6229</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP (Business Server Pages application CRM_BSP_FRAME), versions 700, 701, 702, 710, 711, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 75A, 75B, 75C, 75D, 75E, does not sufficiently encode user controlled inputs, resulting in reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6229|2024-08-04T08:55:22.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0356|2024-08-04T17:44:16.494Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20process%20integration%20runtime%20workbench%20%E2%80%93%20messaging%20and%20sap_xiaf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0356</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP NetWeaver Process Integration Runtime Workbench – MESSAGING and SAP_XIAF (before versions 7.31, 7.40, 7.50) allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0356|2024-08-04T17:44:16.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 16:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0357|2024-08-04T17:44:16.461Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20hana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0357</link>
      <description>The administrator of SAP HANA database, before versions 1.0 and 2.0, can misuse HANA to execute commands with operating system "root" privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0357|2024-08-04T17:44:16.461Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 16:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0404|2024-08-04T17:51:26.910Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20enable%20now
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0404</link>
      <description>SAP Enable Now, before version 1911, leaks information about network configuration in the server error messages, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0404|2024-08-04T17:51:26.910Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 21:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6358|2024-08-04T09:02:40.474Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6358</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated FBX file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6358|2024-08-04T09:02:40.474Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26808|2024-08-04T16:03:22.579Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20as%20abap%28dmis%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26808</link>
      <description>SAP AS ABAP(DMIS), versions - 2011_1_620, 2011_1_640, 2011_1_700, 2011_1_710, 2011_1_730, 2011_1_731, 2011_1_752, 2020 and SAP S4 HANA(DMIS), versions - 101, 102, 103, 104, 105, allows an authenticated attacker to inject arbitrary code into function module leading to code injection that can be executed in the application which affects the confidentiality, availability and integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26808|2024-08-04T16:03:22.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0364|2024-08-04T17:44:16.544Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20hana%20extended%20application%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0364</link>
      <description>Attackers may misuse an HTTP/REST endpoint of SAP HANA Extended Application Services (Advanced model), before version 1.0.118, to enumerate open ports.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0364|2024-08-04T17:44:16.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 16:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6241|2024-08-04T08:55:22.162Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20adaptive%20server%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6241</link>
      <description>SAP Adaptive Server Enterprise, version 16.0, allows an authenticated user to execute crafted database queries to elevate privileges of users in the system, leading to SQL Injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6241|2024-08-04T08:55:22.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6301|2024-08-04T08:55:22.415Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20erp%20%28hcm%20travel%20management%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6301</link>
      <description>SAP ERP (HCM Travel Management), versions - 600, 602, 603, 604, 605, 606, 607, 608, allows an authenticated but unauthorized attacker to read, modify and settle trips, resulting in escalation of privileges, due to Missing Authorization Check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6301|2024-08-04T08:55:22.415Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 13:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0335|2024-08-04T17:44:16.490Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28cmc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0335</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Central Management Console), versions 4.1, 4.2, 4.3, allows an attacker to store a malicious payload within the description field of a user account. The payload is triggered when the mouse cursor is moved over the description field in the list, when generating the little yellow informational pop up box, resulting in Stored Cross Site Scripting Attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0335|2024-08-04T17:44:16.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 13:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26814|2024-08-04T16:03:22.683Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20process%20integration%20%28pgp%20-%20module%20business-to-business%20add%20on%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26814</link>
      <description>SAP Process Integration (PGP Module - Business-to-Business Add On), version - 1.0, allows an attacker to read PGP Keys under certain conditions in the PGP Module of Business-to-Business Add-On, these keys can then be used to read messages processed by the module leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26814|2024-08-04T16:03:22.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38183|2024-08-04T01:37:16.304Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38183</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver - versions 700, 701, 702, 730, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, allowing an attacker to cause a potential victim to supply a malicious content to a vulnerable web application, which is then reflected to the victim and executed by the web browser, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38183|2024-08-04T01:37:16.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6238|2024-08-04T08:55:22.193Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6238</link>
      <description>SAP Commerce, versions - 6.6, 6.7, 1808, 1811, 1905, does not process XML input securely in the Rest API from Servlet xyformsweb, leading to Missing XML Validation. This affects confidentiality and availability (partially) of SAP Commerce.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6238|2024-08-04T08:55:22.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6208|2024-08-04T08:55:21.925Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28crystal%20reports%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6208</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (Crystal Reports), versions- 4.1, 4.2, allows an attacker with basic authorization to inject code that can be executed by the application and thus allowing the attacker to control the behaviour of the application, leading to Remote Code Execution. Although the mode of attack is only Local, multiple applications can be impacted as a result of the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6208|2024-08-04T08:55:21.925Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0308|2024-08-04T17:44:16.439Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20e-commerce%20%28business-to-consumer%20application%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0308</link>
      <description>An authenticated attacker in SAP E-Commerce (Business-to-Consumer application), versions 7.3, 7.31, 7.32, 7.33, 7.54, can change the price of the product to zero and also checkout, by injecting an HTML code in the application that will be executed whenever the victim logs in to the application even on a different machine, leading to Code Injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0308|2024-08-04T17:44:16.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 14:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6188|2024-08-04T08:55:22.007Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20erp%20%28sap_appl%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6188</link>
      <description>VAT Pro-Rata reports in SAP ERP (SAP_APPL versions 600, 602, 603, 604, 605, 606, 616 and SAP_FIN versions 617, 618, 700, 720, 730) and SAP S/4 HANA (versions 100, 101, 102, 103, 104) do not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user leading to Missing Authorization Check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6188|2024-08-04T08:55:22.007Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 19:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6193|2024-08-04T08:55:22.129Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28knowledge%20management%20ice%20service%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6193</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver (Knowledge Management ICE Service), versions 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute malicious scripts leading to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6193|2024-08-04T08:55:22.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 19:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0279|2024-08-04T17:44:16.179Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20basis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0279</link>
      <description>ABAP BASIS function modules INST_CREATE_R3_RFC_DEST, INST_CREATE_TCPIP_RFCDEST, and INST_CREATE_TCPIP_RFC_DEST in SAP BASIS (fixed in versions 7.0 to 7.02, 7.10 to 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50 to 7.53) do not perform necessary authorization checks in all circumstances for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0279|2024-08-04T17:44:16.179Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 20:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6309|2024-08-04T08:55:22.249Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java%20%28engineapi%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6309</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS JAVA, versions - (ENGINEAPI 7.10; WSRM 7.10, 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50; J2EE-FRMW 7.10, 7.11), does not perform any authentication checks for a web service allowing the attacker to send several payloads and leading to complete denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6309|2024-08-04T08:55:22.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 13:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26836|2024-08-04T16:03:22.578Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28trace%20analysis%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26836</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager (Trace Analysis), version - 720, allows for misuse of a parameter in the application URL leading to Open Redirect vulnerability, an attacker can enter a link to malicious site which could trick the user to enter credentials or download malicious software, as a parameter in the application URL and share it with the end user who could potentially become a victim of the attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26836|2024-08-04T16:03:22.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 16:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6339|2024-08-04T09:02:39.583Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6339</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated BMP file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6339|2024-08-04T09:02:39.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6272|2024-08-04T08:55:22.297Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6272</link>
      <description>SAP Commerce Cloud versions - 1808, 1811, 1905, 2005, does not sufficiently encode user inputs, which allows an authenticated and authorized content manager to inject malicious script into several web CMS components. These can be saved and later triggered, if an affected web page is visited, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6272|2024-08-04T08:55:22.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 01:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6311|2024-08-04T08:55:22.265Z -- sap%20se -- banking%20services%20from%20sap%209.0%28bank%20analyzer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6311</link>
      <description>Banking services from SAP 9.0 (Bank Analyzer), version - 500, and SAP S/4HANA for financial products subledger, version � 100, does not correctly perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user due to Improper Authorization checks, that may cause a system administrator to create incorrect authorization proposals. This may result in privilege escalation and may expose restricted banking data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6311|2024-08-04T08:55:22.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 13:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6298|2024-08-04T08:55:22.280Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20banking%20services%20%28generic%20market%20data%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6298</link>
      <description>SAP Banking Services (Generic Market Data), versions - 400, 450, 500, allows an unauthorized user to display protected Business Partner Generic Market Data (GMD) and change related GMD key figure values, due to Missing Authorization Check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6298|2024-08-04T08:55:22.280Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 13:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6224|2024-08-04T08:55:22.154Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java%20%28http%20service%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6224</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS Java (HTTP Service), versions 7.10, 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50, allows an attacker with administrator privileges to access user sensitive data such as passwords in trace files, when the user logs in and sends request with login credentials, leading to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6224|2024-08-04T08:55:22.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6334|2024-08-04T09:02:39.018Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6334</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated SKP file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6334|2024-08-04T09:02:39.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26822|2024-08-04T16:03:22.328Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28java%20stack%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26822</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager (JAVA stack), version - 7.20, allows an unauthenticated attacker to compromise the system because of missing authorization checks in the Outside Discovery Configuration Service, this has an impact to the integrity and availability of the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26822|2024-08-04T16:03:22.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6337|2024-08-04T09:02:39.029Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6337</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated HDR file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6337|2024-08-04T09:02:39.029Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0332|2024-08-04T17:44:16.487Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28info%20view%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0332</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Info View), versions 4.1, 4.2, 4.3, allows an attacker to give some payload for keyword in the search and it will be executed while search performs its action, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0332|2024-08-04T17:44:16.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26834|2024-08-04T16:03:22.211Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20hana%20database
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26834</link>
      <description>SAP HANA Database, version - 2.0, does not correctly validate the username when performing SAML bearer token-based user authentication. It is possible to manipulate a valid existing SAML bearer token to authenticate as a user whose name is identical to the truncated username for whom the SAML bearer token was issued.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26834|2024-08-04T16:03:22.211Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 16:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6312|2024-08-04T08:55:22.413Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6312</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface), versions - 4.1, 4.2, allows an attacker with a non-administrative user account that can edit certain web page properties, can modify how a browser processes particular page elements, leading to stored Cross Site Scripting. In certain situations, when a user accesses an affected web page element, the attacker will be able to access or modify metadata for which they are not authorized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6312|2024-08-04T08:55:22.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26825|2024-08-04T16:03:22.699Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20fiori%20launchpad%20%28news%20tile%20application%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26825</link>
      <description>SAP Fiori Launchpad (News tile Application), versions - 750,751,752,753,754,755, allows an unauthorized attacker to use SAP Fiori Launchpad News tile Application to send malicious code, to a different end user (victim), because News tile does not sufficiently encode user controlled inputs, resulting in Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. Information maintained in the victim's web browser can be read, modified, and sent to the attacker. The malicious code cannot significantly impact the victim's browser and the victim can easily close the browser tab to terminate it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26825|2024-08-04T16:03:22.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0374|2024-08-04T17:51:26.119Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0374</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface), before versions 4.2 and 4.3, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs and allows execution of scripts in the chart title resulting in reflected Cross-Site Scripting</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0374|2024-08-04T17:51:26.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6203|2024-08-04T08:55:21.879Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20uddi%20server%20%28services%20registry%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6203</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver UDDI Server (Services Registry), versions- 7.10, 7.11, 7.20, 7.30, 7.31, 7.40, 7.50; allows an attacker to exploit insufficient validation of path information provided by users, thus characters representing 'traverse to parent directory' are passed through to the file APIs, leading to Path Traversal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6203|2024-08-04T08:55:21.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0353|2024-08-04T17:44:16.539Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20business%20one%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0353</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP Business One client (B1_ON_HANA, SAP-M-BO), before versions 9.2 and 9.3, allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0353|2024-08-04T17:44:16.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 16:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6331|2024-08-04T08:55:22.405Z -- sap%20se -- sap%203d%20visual%20enterprise%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6331</link>
      <description>SAP 3D Visual Enterprise Viewer, version - 9, allows a user to open manipulated HPGL file received from untrusted sources which results in crashing of the application and becoming temporarily unavailable until the user restarts the application, this is caused due to Improper Input Validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6331|2024-08-04T08:55:22.405Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
