<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SAP SE -- SAP NetWeaver Master Data Management</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sap%20se/sap%20netweaver%20master%20data%20management.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SAP SE -- SAP NetWeaver Master Data Management</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21469|2024-08-03T18:16:22.563Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20master%20data%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21469</link>
      <description>When security guidelines for SAP NetWeaver Master Data Management running on windows have not been thoroughly reviewed, it might be possible for an external operator to try and set custom paths in the MDS server configuration. When no adequate protection has been enforced on any level (e.g., MDS Server password not set, network and OS configuration not properly secured, etc.), a malicious user might define UNC paths which could then be exploited to put the system at risk using a so-called SMB relay attack and obtain highly sensitive data, which leads to Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21469|2024-08-03T18:16:22.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 14:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21482|2024-08-03T18:16:22.607Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20netweaver%20master%20data%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21482</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Master Data Management, versions - 710, 710.750, allows a malicious unauthorized user with access to the MDM Server subnet to find the password using a brute force method. If successful, the attacker could obtain access to highly sensitive data and MDM administrative privileges leading to information disclosure vulnerability thereby affecting the confidentiality and integrity of the application. This happens when security guidelines and recommendations concerning administrative accounts of an SAP NetWeaver Master Data Management installation have not been thoroughly reviewed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21482|2024-08-03T18:16:22.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 18:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
