<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SAP SE -- SAP Commerce Cloud</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sap%20se/sap%20commerce%20cloud.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SAP SE -- SAP Commerce Cloud</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26809|2024-08-04T16:03:22.462Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26809</link>
      <description>SAP Commerce Cloud, versions- 1808,1811,1905,2005, allows an attacker to bypass existing authentication and permission checks via the '/medias' endpoint hence gaining access to Secure Media folders. This folder could contain sensitive files that results in disclosure of sensitive information and impact system configuration confidentiality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26809|2024-08-04T16:03:22.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6363|2024-08-04T09:02:39.615Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6363</link>
      <description>SAP Commerce Cloud, versions - 1808, 1811, 1905, 2005, exposes several web applications that maintain sessions with a user. These sessions are established after the user has authenticated with username/passphrase credentials. The user can change their own passphrase, but this does not invalidate active sessions that the user may have with SAP Commerce Cloud web applications, which gives an attacker the opportunity to reuse old session credentials, resulting in Insufficient Session Expiration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6363|2024-08-04T09:02:39.615Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 01:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6272|2024-08-04T08:55:22.297Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20commerce%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6272</link>
      <description>SAP Commerce Cloud versions - 1808, 1811, 1905, 2005, does not sufficiently encode user inputs, which allows an authenticated and authorized content manager to inject malicious script into several web CMS components. These can be saved and later triggered, if an affected web page is visited, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6272|2024-08-04T08:55:22.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 01:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
