<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SAP SE -- SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sap%20se/sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SAP SE -- SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 18:24:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0376|2024-08-04T17:51:26.103Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0376</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface), before versions 4.2 and 4.3, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs and allows an attacker to save malicious scripts in the publication name, which can be executed later by the victim, resulting in Stored Cross-Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0376|2024-08-04T17:51:26.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:23:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0377|2024-08-04T17:51:26.707Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0377</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface), before versions 4.2, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs and allows an attacker to store malicious scripts in the input controls, resulting in Stored Cross-Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0377|2024-08-04T17:51:26.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0396|2024-08-04T17:51:26.767Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0396</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface), corrected in versions 4.1 and 4.2, does not sufficiently validate an XML document accepted from an untrusted source. An attacker can craft a message that contains malicious elements that will not be correctly filtered by Web Intelligence HTML interface in some specific workflows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0396|2024-08-04T17:51:26.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 22:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0378|2024-08-04T17:51:26.339Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0378</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface), before version 4.2, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs and allows an attacker to store malicious scripts in the file name of the background image resulting in Stored Cross-Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0378|2024-08-04T17:51:26.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6222|2024-08-04T08:55:22.147Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6222</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface), versions 4.1, 4.2, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6222|2024-08-04T08:55:22.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0375|2024-08-04T17:51:26.129Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0375</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface), before versions 4.2 and 4.3, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs and allows execution of scripts in the export dialog box of the report name resulting in reflected Cross-Site Scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0375|2024-08-04T17:51:26.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6312|2024-08-04T08:55:22.413Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6312</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface), versions - 4.1, 4.2, allows an attacker with a non-administrative user account that can edit certain web page properties, can modify how a browser processes particular page elements, leading to stored Cross Site Scripting. In certain situations, when a user accesses an affected web page element, the attacker will be able to access or modify metadata for which they are not authorized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6312|2024-08-04T08:55:22.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0374|2024-08-04T17:51:26.119Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%20html%20interface%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0374</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence HTML interface), before versions 4.2 and 4.3, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs and allows execution of scripts in the chart title resulting in reflected Cross-Site Scripting</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0374|2024-08-04T17:51:26.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
