<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SAP SE -- SAP Solution Manager (User Experience Monitoring)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sap%20se/sap%20solution%20manager%20%28user%20experience%20monitoring%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SAP SE -- SAP Solution Manager (User Experience Monitoring)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26830|2024-08-04T16:03:22.653Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28user%20experience%20monitoring%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26830</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager 7.2 (User Experience Monitoring), version - 7.2, does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user. Due to inadequate access control, a network attacker authenticated as a regular user can use operations which should be restricted to administrators. These operations can be used to Change the User Experience Monitoring configuration, obtain details about the configured SAP Solution Manager agents, Deploy a malicious User Experience Monitoring script.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26830|2024-08-04T16:03:22.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 16:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6207|2024-08-04T08:55:22.109Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28user%20experience%20monitoring%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6207</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager (User Experience Monitoring), version- 7.2, due to Missing Authentication Check does not perform any authentication for a service resulting in complete compromise of all SMDAgents connected to the Solution Manager.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6207|2024-08-04T08:55:22.109Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26837|2024-08-04T16:03:22.675Z -- sap%20se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28user%20experience%20monitoring%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26837</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager 7.2 (User Experience Monitoring), version - 7.2, allows an authenticated user to upload a malicious script that can exploit an existing path traversal vulnerability to compromise confidentiality exposing elements of the file system, partially compromise integrity allowing the modification of some configurations and partially compromise availability by making certain services unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26837|2024-08-04T16:03:22.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 16:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
