<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for indico -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/indico/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for indico -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 19:21:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37901|2024-10-10T18:58:39.624Z -- indico -- indico
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37901</link>
      <description>Indico is an open source a general-purpose, web based event management tool. There is a Cross-Site-Scripting vulnerability in confirmation prompts commonly used when deleting content from Indico. Exploitation requires someone with at least submission privileges (such as a speaker) and then someone else to attempt to delete this content. Considering that event organizers may want to delete suspicious-looking content when spotting it, there is a non-negligible risk of such an attack to succeed. The risk of this could be further increased when combined with some some social engineering pointing the victim towards this content. Users need to update to Indico 3.2.6 as soon as possible. See the docs for instructions on how to update. Users who cannot upgrade should only let trustworthy users manage categories, create events or upload materials ("submission" privileges on a contribution/event). This should already be the case in a properly-configured setup when it comes to category/event management. Note that a conference doing a Call for Abstracts actively invites external speakers (who the organizers may not know and thus cannot fully trust) to submit content, hence the need to update to a a fixed version ASAP in particular when using such workflows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37901|2024-10-10T18:58:39.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 18:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-45399|2024-09-04T20:17:38.298Z -- indico -- indico</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45399</link>
      <description>Indico is an event management system that uses Flask-Multipass, a multi-backend authentication system for Flask. In Indico prior to version 3.3.4, corresponding to Flask-Multipass prior to version 0.5.5, there is a Cross-Site-Scripting vulnerability during account creation when redirecting to the `next` URL. Exploitation requires initiating the account creation process with a maliciously crafted link, and then finalizing the signup process. Because of this, it can only target newly created (and thus unprivileged) Indico users. Indico 3.3.4 upgrades the dependency on Flask-Multipass to version 0.5.5, which fixes the issue. Those who build the Indico package themselves and cannot upgrade can update the `flask-multipass` dependency to `&gt;=0.5.5` which fixes the vulnerability. Otherwise one could configure one's web server to disallow requests containing a query string with a `next` parameter that starts with `javascript:`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-45399|2024-09-04T20:17:38.298Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 20:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
