<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for inspireui -- MStore API</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/inspireui/mstore%20api.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for inspireui -- MStore API</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 14:22:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3199|2024-08-02T06:48:07.824Z -- inspireui -- mstore%20api
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3199</link>
      <description>The MStore API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery due to missing nonce validation on the mstore_update_status_order_title function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update status order title via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3199|2024-08-02T06:48:07.824Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 04:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2732|2024-08-02T06:33:05.222Z -- inspireui -- mstore%20api
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2732</link>
      <description>The MStore API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 3.9.2. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being supplied during the add listing REST API request through the plugin. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the user id.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2732|2024-08-02T06:33:05.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 02:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3203|2024-08-02T06:48:07.962Z -- inspireui -- mstore%20api
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3203</link>
      <description>The MStore API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery due to missing nonce validation on the mstore_update_limit_product function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update limit the number of product per category to use cache data in home screen via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3203|2024-08-02T06:48:07.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 01:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2733|2024-08-02T06:33:05.447Z -- inspireui -- mstore%20api
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2733</link>
      <description>The MStore API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 3.9.0. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being supplied during the coupon redemption REST API request through the plugin. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the user id.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2733|2024-08-02T06:33:05.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 02:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3200|2024-08-02T06:48:07.878Z -- inspireui -- mstore%20api
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3200</link>
      <description>The MStore API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery due to missing nonce validation on the mstore_update_new_order_message function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update new order message via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3200|2024-08-02T06:48:07.878Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 01:47:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3277|2024-08-02T06:48:08.451Z -- inspireui -- mstore%20api
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3277</link>
      <description>The MStore API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Unauthorized Account Access and Privilege Escalation in versions up to, and including, 4.10.7 due to improper implementation of the Apple login feature. This allows unauthenticated attackers to log in as any user as long as they know the user's email address. We are disclosing this issue as the developer has not yet released a patch, but continues to release updates and we escalated this issue to the plugin's team 30 days ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3277|2024-08-02T06:48:08.451Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 11:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3201|2024-08-02T06:48:08.352Z -- inspireui -- mstore%20api
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3201</link>
      <description>The MStore API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery due to missing nonce validation on the mstore_update_new_order_title function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update new order title via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3201|2024-08-02T06:48:08.352Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 01:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2734|2024-08-02T06:33:04.325Z -- inspireui -- mstore%20api
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2734</link>
      <description>The MStore API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 3.9.1. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being supplied during the cart sync from mobile REST API request through the plugin. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the user id.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2734|2024-08-02T06:33:04.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 02:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3198|2024-08-02T06:48:07.816Z -- inspireui -- mstore%20api
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3198</link>
      <description>The MStore API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery due to missing nonce validation on the mstore_update_status_order_message function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update status order message via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3198|2024-08-02T06:48:07.816Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 01:47:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3197|2024-08-02T06:48:08.115Z -- inspireui -- mstore%20api
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3197</link>
      <description>The MStore API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Unauthenticated Blind SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in versions up to, and including, 4.0.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameters and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3197|2024-08-02T06:48:08.115Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 02:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3202|2024-08-02T06:48:07.954Z -- inspireui -- mstore%20api
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3202</link>
      <description>The MStore API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery due to missing nonce validation on the mstore_update_firebase_server_key function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the firebase server key to push notification when order status changed via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3202|2024-08-02T06:48:07.954Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 04:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
