<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Segmentio -- is-url</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/segmentio/is-url.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Segmentio -- is-url</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:24:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-25079|2024-08-05T12:33:47.846Z -- segmentio -- is-url
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25079</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Segmentio is-url up to 1.2.2. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file index.js. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.2.3 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 149550935c63a98c11f27f694a7c4a9479e53794. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-220058 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Segmentio is-url bis 1.2.2 ausgemacht. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei index.js. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine inefficient regular expression complexity-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.2.3 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 149550935c63a98c11f27f694a7c4a9479e53794 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-25079|2024-08-05T12:33:47.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 03:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
