<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ethereum -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ethereum/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ethereum -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26265|2024-08-04T15:56:03.493Z -- ethereum -- go-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26265</link>
      <description>Go Ethereum, or "Geth", is the official Golang implementation of the Ethereum protocol. In Geth from version 1.9.4 and before version 1.9.20 a consensus-vulnerability could cause a chain split, where vulnerable versions refuse to accept the canonical chain. The fix was included in the Paragade release version 1.9.20. No individual workaround patches have been made -- all users are recommended to upgrade to a newer version.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26265|2024-08-04T15:56:03.493Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 16:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26264|2024-08-04T15:56:04.248Z -- ethereum -- go-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26264</link>
      <description>Go Ethereum, or "Geth", is the official Golang implementation of the Ethereum protocol. In Geth before version 1.9.25 a denial-of-service vulnerability can make a LES server crash via malicious GetProofsV2 request from a connected LES client. This vulnerability only concerns users explicitly enabling les server; disabling les prevents the exploit. The vulnerability was patched in version 1.9.25.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26264|2024-08-04T15:56:04.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 16:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39137|2024-08-04T01:58:17.913Z -- ethereum -- go-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39137</link>
      <description>go-ethereum is the official Go implementation of the Ethereum protocol. In affected versions a consensus-vulnerability in go-ethereum (Geth) could cause a chain split, where vulnerable versions refuse to accept the canonical chain. Further details about the vulnerability will be disclosed at a later date. A patch is included in the upcoming `v1.10.8` release. No workaround are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39137|2024-08-04T01:58:17.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 16:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41173|2024-08-04T02:59:31.575Z -- ethereum -- go-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41173</link>
      <description>Go Ethereum is the official Golang implementation of the Ethereum protocol. Prior to version 1.10.9, a vulnerable node is susceptible to crash when processing a maliciously crafted message from a peer. Version v1.10.9 contains patches to the vulnerability. There are no known workarounds aside from upgrading.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41173|2024-08-04T02:59:31.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 14:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26241|2024-08-04T15:56:03.871Z -- ethereum -- go-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26241</link>
      <description>Go Ethereum, or "Geth", is the official Golang implementation of the Ethereum protocol. This is a Consensus vulnerability in Geth before version 1.9.17 which can be used to cause a chain-split where vulnerable nodes reject the canonical chain. Geth's pre-compiled dataCopy (at 0x00...04) contract did a shallow copy on invocation. An attacker could deploy a contract that writes X to an EVM memory region R, then calls 0x00..04 with R as an argument, then overwrites R to Y, and finally invokes the RETURNDATACOPY opcode. When this contract is invoked, a consensus-compliant node would push X on the EVM stack, whereas Geth would push Y. This is fixed in version 1.9.17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26241|2024-08-04T15:56:03.871Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 01:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26240|2024-08-04T15:56:04.861Z -- ethereum -- go-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26240</link>
      <description>Go Ethereum, or "Geth", is the official Golang implementation of the Ethereum protocol. An ethash mining DAG generation flaw in Geth before version 1.9.24 could cause miners to erroneously calculate PoW in an upcoming epoch (estimated early January, 2021). This happened on the ETC chain on 2020-11-06. This issue is relevant only for miners, non-mining nodes are unaffected. This issue is fixed as of 1.9.24</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26240|2024-08-04T15:56:04.861Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 01:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26242|2024-08-04T15:56:03.570Z -- ethereum -- go-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26242</link>
      <description>Go Ethereum, or "Geth", is the official Golang implementation of the Ethereum protocol. In Geth before version 1.9.18, there is a Denial-of-service (crash) during block processing. This is fixed in 1.9.18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26242|2024-08-04T15:56:03.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 01:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32972|2024-08-02T02:27:53.323Z -- ethereum -- go-ethereum</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32972</link>
      <description>go-ethereum (geth) is a golang execution layer implementation of the Ethereum protocol. Prior to 1.13.15, a vulnerable node can be made to consume very large amounts of memory when handling specially crafted p2p messages sent from an attacker node. The fix has been included in geth version `1.13.15` and onwards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32972|2024-08-02T02:27:53.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32972|2024-06-04T17:50:49.796Z -- ethereum -- go-ethereum</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32972</link>
      <description>go-ethereum (geth) is a golang execution layer implementation of the Ethereum protocol. Prior to 1.13.15, a vulnerable node can be made to consume very large amounts of memory when handling specially crafted p2p messages sent from an attacker node. The fix has been included in geth version `1.13.15` and onwards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32972|2024-06-04T17:50:49.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
