<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for The QEMU Project -- qemu</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/the%20qemu%20project/qemu.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for The QEMU Project -- qemu</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10717|2024-08-04T11:14:14.837Z -- the%20qemu%20project -- qemu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10717</link>
      <description>A potential DoS flaw was found in the virtio-fs shared file system daemon (virtiofsd) implementation of the QEMU version &gt;= v5.0. Virtio-fs is meant to share a host file system directory with a guest via virtio-fs device. If the guest opens the maximum number of file descriptors under the shared directory, a denial of service may occur. This flaw allows a guest user/process to cause this denial of service on the host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10717|2024-08-04T11:14:14.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10702|2024-08-04T11:06:11.188Z -- the%20qemu%20project -- qemu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10702</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in QEMU in the implementation of the Pointer Authentication (PAuth) support for ARM introduced in version 4.0 and fixed in version 5.0.0. A general failure of the signature generation process caused every PAuth-enforced pointer to be signed with the same signature. A local attacker could obtain the signature of a protected pointer and abuse this flaw to bypass PAuth protection for all programs running on QEMU.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10702|2024-08-04T11:06:11.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 17:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3812|2024-08-04T19:19:18.499Z -- the%20qemu%20project -- qemu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3812</link>
      <description>QEMU, through version 2.10 and through version 3.1.0, is vulnerable to an out-of-bounds read of up to 128 bytes in the hw/i2c/i2c-ddc.c:i2c_ddc() function. A local attacker with permission to execute i2c commands could exploit this to read stack memory of the qemu process on the host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3812|2024-08-04T19:19:18.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
