<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for projectdiscovery -- nuclei</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/projectdiscovery/nuclei.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for projectdiscovery -- nuclei</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37896|2023-08-04T15:34:11.804Z -- projectdiscovery -- nuclei
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37896</link>
      <description>Nuclei is a vulnerability scanner. Prior to version 2.9.9, a security issue in the Nuclei project affected users utilizing Nuclei as Go code (SDK) running custom templates. This issue did not affect CLI users. The problem was related to sanitization issues with payload loading in sandbox mode. There was a potential risk with payloads loading in sandbox mode. The issue occurred due to relative paths not being converted to absolute paths before doing the check for `sandbox` flag allowing arbitrary files to be read on the filesystem in certain cases when using Nuclei from `Go` SDK implementation. 

This issue has been fixed in version 2.9.9. The maintainers have also enabled sandbox by default for filesystem loading. This can be optionally disabled if required. The `-sandbox` option has been deprecated and is now divided into two new options: `-lfa` (allow local file access) which is enabled by default and `-lna` (restrict local network access) which can be enabled by users optionally. The `-lfa` allows file (payload) access anywhere on the system (disabling sandbox effectively), and `-lna` blocks connections to the local/private network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37896|2023-08-04T15:34:11.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 15:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27920|2024-06-04T17:46:39.282Z -- projectdiscovery -- nuclei
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27920</link>
      <description>projectdiscovery/nuclei is a fast and customisable vulnerability scanner based on simple YAML based DSL. A significant security oversight was identified in Nuclei v3, involving the execution of unsigned code templates through workflows. This vulnerability specifically affects users utilizing custom workflows, potentially allowing the execution of malicious code on the user's system. This advisory outlines the impacted users, provides details on the security patch, and suggests mitigation strategies. The vulnerability is addressed in Nuclei v3.2.0. Users are strongly recommended to update to this version to mitigate the security risk. Users should refrain from using custom workflows if unable to upgrade immediately. Only trusted, verified workflows should be executed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27920|2024-06-04T17:46:39.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
