<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Discourse -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/discourse/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Discourse -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:19:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-35227|2024-07-03T18:39:26.390Z -- discourse -- discourse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35227</link>
      <description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta3 on the `tests-passed` branch, Oneboxing against a carefully crafted malicious URL can reduce the availability of a Discourse instance. The problem has been patched in version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta3 on the `tests-passed` branch. There are no known workarounds available for this vulnerability. </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-35227|2024-07-03T18:39:26.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-35234|2024-07-03T18:40:10.254Z -- discourse -- discourse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35234</link>
      <description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta3 on the `tests-passed` branch, an attacker can execute arbitrary JavaScript on users’ browsers by posting a specific URL containing maliciously crafted meta tags. This issue only affects sites with Content Security Polic (CSP) disabled. The problem has been patched in version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta3 on the `tests-passed` branch. As a workaround, ensure CSP is enabled on the forum.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-35234|2024-07-03T18:40:10.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49099|2024-01-12T20:53:53.163Z -- discourse -- discourse</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-49099</link>
      <description>Discourse is a platform for community discussion. Under very specific circumstances, secure upload URLs associated with posts can be accessed by guest users even when login is required. This vulnerability has been patched in 3.2.0.beta4 and 3.1.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49099|2024-01-12T20:53:53.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49098|2024-01-12T20:37:26.516Z -- discourse -- discourse-reactions</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-49098</link>
      <description>Discourse-reactions is a plugin that allows user to add their reactions to the post. Data about a user's reaction notifications could be exposed. This vulnerability was patched in commit 2c26939.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49098|2024-01-12T20:37:26.516Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:37:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-48297|2024-01-12T20:35:02.394Z -- discourse -- discourse</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-48297</link>
      <description>Discourse is a platform for community discussion. The message serializer uses the full list of expanded chat mentions (@all and @here) which can lead to a very long array of users. This issue was patched in versions 3.1.4 and beta 3.2.0.beta5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-48297|2024-01-12T20:35:02.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:35:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46241|2024-02-21T16:08:41.494Z -- discourse -- discourse-microsoft-auth</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-46241</link>
      <description>`discourse-microsoft-auth` is a plugin that enables authentication via Microsoft. On sites with the `discourse-microsoft-auth` plugin enabled, an attack can potentially take control of a victim's Discourse account. Sites that have configured their application's account type to any options other than `Accounts in this organizational directory only (O365 only - Single tenant)` are vulnerable. This vulnerability has been patched in commit c40665f44509724b64938c85def9fb2e79f62ec8 of `discourse-microsoft-auth`. A `microsoft_auth:revoke` rake task has also been added which will deactivate and log out all users that have connected their accounts to Microsoft. User API keys as well as API keys created by those users will also be revoked. The rake task will also remove the connection records to Microsoft for those users. This will allow affected users to re-verify their account emails as well as reconnect their Discourse account to Microsoft for authentication. As a workaround, disable the `discourse-microsoft-auth` plugin by setting the `microsoft_auth_enabled` site setting to `false`. Run the `microsoft_auth:log_out_users` rake task to log out all users with associated Microsoft accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46241|2024-02-21T16:08:41.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28242|2024-06-04T18:03:46.509Z -- discourse -- discourse</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28242</link>
      <description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In affected versions an attacker can learn that secret categories exist when they have backgrounds set. The issue is patched in the latest stable, beta and tests-passed version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should temporarily remove category backgrounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28242|2024-06-04T18:03:46.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26145|2024-02-21T17:19:11.128Z -- discourse -- discourse-calendar</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-26145</link>
      <description>Discourse Calendar adds the ability to create a dynamic calendar in the first post of a topic on Discourse. Uninvited users are able to gain access to private events by crafting a request to update their attendance. This problem is resolved in commit dfc4fa15f340189f177a1d1ab2cc94ffed3c1190. As a workaround, one may use post visibility to limit access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26145|2024-02-21T17:19:11.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 17:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27085|2024-03-15T19:22:46.937Z -- discourse -- discourse</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27085</link>
      <description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In affected versions users that are allowed to invite others can inject arbitrarily large data in parameters used in the invite route. The problem has been patched in the latest version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should disable invites or restrict access to them using the `invite allowed groups` site setting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27085|2024-03-15T19:22:46.937Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27100|2024-06-04T17:46:44.223Z -- discourse -- discourse</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27100</link>
      <description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In affected versions the endpoints for suspending users, silencing users and exporting CSV files weren't enforcing limits on the sizes of the parameters that they accept. This could lead to excessive resource consumption which could render an instance inoperable. A site could be disrupted by either a malicious moderator on the same site or a malicious staff member on another site in the same multisite cluster. This issue is patched in the latest stable, beta and tests-passed versions of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27100|2024-06-04T17:46:44.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23654|2024-02-21T20:28:12.939Z -- discourse -- discourse-ai</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23654</link>
      <description>discourse-ai is the AI plugin for the open-source discussion platform Discourse. Prior to commit 94ba0dadc2cf38e8f81c3936974c167219878edd, interactions with different AI services are vulnerable to admin-initiated SSRF attacks. Versions of the plugin that include commit 94ba0dadc2cf38e8f81c3936974c167219878edd contain a patch. As a workaround, one may disable the discourse-ai plugin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23654|2024-02-21T20:28:12.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:28:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23834|2024-01-30T21:31:35.617Z -- discourse -- discourse</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23834</link>
      <description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Improperly sanitized user input could lead to an XSS vulnerability in some situations. This vulnerability only affects Discourse instances which have disabled the default Content Security Policy. The vulnerability is patched in 3.1.5 and 3.2.0.beta5.  As a workaround, ensure Content Security Policy is enabled and does not include `unsafe-inline`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23834|2024-01-30T21:31:35.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 21:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24748|2024-03-15T19:15:17.121Z -- discourse -- discourse</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24748</link>
      <description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In affected versions an attacker can learn that a secret subcategory exists under a public category which has no public subcategories. The issue is patched in the latest stable, beta and tests-passed version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24748|2024-03-15T19:15:17.121Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24817|2024-02-22T17:45:57.887Z -- discourse -- discourse-calendar</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24817</link>
      <description>Discourse Calendar adds the ability to create a dynamic calendar in the first post of a topic on the open-source discussion platform Discourse. Prior to version 0.4, event invitees created in topics in private categories or PMs (private messages) can be retrieved by anyone, even if they're not logged in. This problem is resolved in version 0.4 of the discourse-calendar plugin. While no known workaround is available, putting the site behind `login_required` will disallow this endpoint to be used by anonymous users, but logged in users can still get the list of invitees in the private topics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24817|2024-02-22T17:45:57.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 17:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24827|2024-03-15T19:13:43.221Z -- discourse -- discourse</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24827</link>
      <description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. Without a rate limit on the POST /uploads endpoint, it makes it easier for an attacker to carry out a DoS attack on the server since creating an upload can be a resource intensive process. Do note that the impact varies from site to site as various site settings like `max_image_size_kb`, `max_attachment_size_kb` and `max_image_megapixels` will determine the amount of resources used when creating an upload. The issue is patched in the latest stable, beta and tests-passed version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should reduce `max_image_size_kb`, `max_attachment_size_kb` and `max_image_megapixels` as smaller uploads require less resources to process. Alternatively, `client_max_body_size` can be reduced in Nginx to prevent large uploads from reaching the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24827|2024-03-15T19:13:43.221Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24755|2024-02-01T22:14:23.064Z -- discourse -- discourse-group-membership-ip-block</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24755</link>
      <description>discourse-group-membership-ip-block is a discourse plugin that adds support for adding users to groups based on their IP address. discourse-group-membership-ip-block was sending all group custom fields to the client, including group custom fields from other plugins which may expect their custom fields to remain secret.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24755|2024-02-01T22:14:23.064Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 22:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21655|2024-01-12T20:46:00.196Z -- discourse -- discourse</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21655</link>
      <description>Discourse is a platform for community discussion. For fields that are client editable, limits on sizes are not imposed. This allows a malicious actor to cause a Discourse instance to use excessive disk space and also often excessive bandwidth. The issue is patched 3.1.4 and 3.2.0.beta4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21655|2024-01-12T20:46:00.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31219|2024-06-04T17:36:49.662Z -- discourse -- discourse-reactions</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31219</link>
      <description>Discourse-reactions is a plugin that allows user to add their reactions to the post. When whispers are enabled on a site via `whispers_allowed_groups` and reactions are made on whispers on public topics, the contents of the whisper and the reaction data are shown on the `/u/:username/activity/reactions` endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31219|2024-06-04T17:36:49.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 18:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-35168|2024-06-11T19:05:34.639Z -- discourse -- wp%20discourse</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-35168</link>
      <description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Discourse WP Discourse.This issue affects WP Discourse: from n/a through 2.5.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-35168|2024-06-11T19:05:34.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 14:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-35227|2024-07-03T17:39:38.293Z -- discourse -- discourse</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35227</link>
      <description>Discourse is an open-source discussion platform. Prior to version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta3 on the `tests-passed` branch, Oneboxing against a carefully crafted malicious URL can reduce the availability of a Discourse instance. The problem has been patched in version 3.2.3 on the `stable` branch and version 3.3.0.beta3 on the `tests-passed` branch. There are no known workarounds available for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-35227|2024-07-03T17:39:38.293Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
