<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Campcodes -- Church Management System</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/campcodes/church%20management%20system.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Campcodes -- Church Management System</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-3536|2024-04-10T03:31:04.604Z -- Campcodes -- Church Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3536</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Church Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/delete_log.php. The manipulation of the argument selector leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259906 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Campcodes Church Management System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /admin/delete_log.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments selector mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3536|2024-04-10T03:31:04.604Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 03:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3541|2024-04-10T05:31:05.183Z -- Campcodes -- Church Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3541</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Campcodes Church Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/admin_user.php. The manipulation of the argument firstname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259911.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Campcodes Church Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /admin/admin_user.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments firstname mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3541|2024-04-10T05:31:05.183Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 05:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3540|2024-04-10T05:00:06.098Z -- Campcodes -- Church Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3540</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Church Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/add_sundaysch.php. The manipulation of the argument Gender leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259910 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Campcodes Church Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /admin/add_sundaysch.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments Gender mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3540|2024-04-10T05:00:06.098Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 05:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3537|2024-04-10T04:00:05.135Z -- Campcodes -- Church Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3537</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Church Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/admin_user.php. The manipulation of the argument firstname leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259907.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Campcodes Church Management System 1.0 gefunden. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /admin/admin_user.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments firstname mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3537|2024-04-10T04:00:05.135Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 04:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3534|2024-04-10T02:31:04.876Z -- Campcodes -- Church Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3534</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Campcodes Church Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument password leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259904.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Campcodes Church Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei login.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3534|2024-04-10T02:31:04.876Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 02:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3538|2024-04-10T04:31:05.223Z -- Campcodes -- Church Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3538</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Church Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/addTithes.php. The manipulation of the argument na leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259908.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Campcodes Church Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /admin/addTithes.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments na mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3538|2024-04-10T04:31:05.223Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 04:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3542|2024-04-10T06:00:05.433Z -- Campcodes -- Church Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3542</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Campcodes Church Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/add_visitor.php. The manipulation of the argument mobile leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259912.
In Campcodes Church Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /admin/add_visitor.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments mobile mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3542|2024-04-10T06:00:05.433Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 06:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3539|2024-04-10T05:00:04.707Z -- Campcodes -- Church Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3539</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Church Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/addgiving.php. The manipulation of the argument amount leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259909 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Campcodes Church Management System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /admin/addgiving.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments amount mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3539|2024-04-10T05:00:04.707Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 05:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3535|2024-04-10T03:00:05.144Z -- Campcodes -- Church Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3535</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes Church Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument password leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259905 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Campcodes Church Management System 1.0 gefunden. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /admin/index.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3535|2024-04-10T03:00:05.144Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>