<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Campcodes -- Online Laundry Management System</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/campcodes/online%20laundry%20management%20system.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Campcodes -- Online Laundry Management System</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-4797|2024-05-12T07:31:04.239Z -- Campcodes -- Online Laundry Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4797</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /ajax.php. The manipulation of the argument name/customer_name/username leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263896.
In Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /ajax.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments name/customer_name/username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4797|2024-05-12T07:31:04.239Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4796|2024-05-12T06:31:04.682Z -- Campcodes -- Online Laundry Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4796</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /manage_inv.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263895.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /manage_inv.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4796|2024-05-12T06:31:04.682Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 06:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4817|2024-05-13T12:31:08.754Z -- Campcodes -- Online Laundry Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4817</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file manage_user.php of the component HTTP Request Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to improper control of resource identifiers. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263938 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei manage_user.php der Komponente HTTP Request Parameter Handler. Durch Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper control of resource identifiers-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4817|2024-05-13T12:31:08.754Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 12:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4818|2024-05-13T13:00:05.975Z -- Campcodes -- Online Laundry Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4818</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument page leads to file inclusion. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263939.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0 gefunden. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei /index.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments page mit unbekannten Daten kann eine file inclusion-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4818|2024-05-13T13:00:05.975Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4793|2024-05-12T03:00:04.373Z -- Campcodes -- Online Laundry Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4793</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /manage_laundry.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263892.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /manage_laundry.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4793|2024-05-12T03:00:04.373Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 03:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4792|2024-05-12T02:00:04.415Z -- Campcodes -- Online Laundry Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4792</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin_class.php. The manipulation of the argument id/delete_category/delete_inv/delete_laundry/delete_supply/delete_user/login/save_inv/save_user leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263891.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /admin_class.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments id/delete_category/delete_inv/delete_laundry/delete_supply/delete_user/login/save_inv/save_user mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4792|2024-05-12T02:00:04.415Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4819|2024-05-13T13:31:04.420Z -- Campcodes -- Online Laundry Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4819</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin_class.php. The manipulation of the argument type with the input 1 leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263940.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei admin_class.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments type mit der Eingabe 1 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper authorization-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4819|2024-05-13T13:31:04.420Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4795|2024-05-12T05:31:03.852Z -- Campcodes -- Online Laundry Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4795</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263894 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei /manage_user.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4795|2024-05-12T05:31:03.852Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 05:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4794|2024-05-12T03:31:03.968Z -- Campcodes -- Online Laundry Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4794</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /manage_receiving.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263893 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Campcodes Online Laundry Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /manage_receiving.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4794|2024-05-12T03:31:03.968Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 03:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>