<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Campcodes -- Online Thesis Archiving System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/campcodes/online%20thesis%20archiving%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Campcodes -- Online Thesis Archiving System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 11:20:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2148|2024-08-02T06:12:20.514Z -- campcodes -- online%20thesis%20archiving%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2148</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Online Thesis Archiving System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/curriculum/view_curriculum.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-226269 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Campcodes Online Thesis Archiving System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /admin/curriculum/view_curriculum.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2148|2024-08-02T06:12:20.514Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 12:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2145|2024-08-02T06:12:20.563Z -- campcodes -- online%20thesis%20archiving%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2145</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Thesis Archiving System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file projects_per_curriculum.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-226266 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Campcodes Online Thesis Archiving System 1.0 ausgemacht. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei projects_per_curriculum.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2145|2024-08-02T06:12:20.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2146|2024-08-02T06:12:20.590Z -- campcodes -- online%20thesis%20archiving%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2146</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Thesis Archiving System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file classes/Master.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-226267.
In Campcodes Online Thesis Archiving System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei classes/Master.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2146|2024-08-02T06:12:20.590Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 11:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2144|2024-08-02T06:12:20.629Z -- campcodes -- online%20thesis%20archiving%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2144</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Thesis Archiving System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/departments/view_department.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-226265 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Campcodes Online Thesis Archiving System 1.0 gefunden. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /admin/departments/view_department.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2144|2024-08-02T06:12:20.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2147|2024-08-02T06:12:20.534Z -- campcodes -- online%20thesis%20archiving%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2147</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Thesis Archiving System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/students/view_details.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-226268.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Campcodes Online Thesis Archiving System 1.0 ausgemacht. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /admin/students/view_details.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2147|2024-08-02T06:12:20.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 11:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2149|2024-08-02T06:12:20.599Z -- campcodes -- online%20thesis%20archiving%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2149</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Campcodes Online Thesis Archiving System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/user/manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-226270 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Campcodes Online Thesis Archiving System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /admin/user/manage_user.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2149|2024-08-02T06:12:20.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 12:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
