<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Campcodes -- Simple Student Information System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/campcodes/simple%20student%20information%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Campcodes -- Simple Student Information System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:23:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5926|2024-08-02T08:14:24.992Z -- campcodes -- simple%20student%20information%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5926</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/students/update_status.php. The manipulation of the argument student_id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-244326 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /admin/students/update_status.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments student_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5926|2024-08-02T08:14:24.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5923|2024-08-02T08:14:25.057Z -- campcodes -- simple%20student%20information%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5923</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244323.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /admin/index.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5923|2024-08-02T08:14:25.057Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 18:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5929|2024-08-02T08:14:24.981Z -- campcodes -- simple%20student%20information%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5929</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/students/manage_academic.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-244329 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /admin/students/manage_academic.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5929|2024-08-02T08:14:24.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 20:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5928|2024-08-02T08:14:25.110Z -- campcodes -- simple%20student%20information%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5928</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/departments/manage_department.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244328.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /admin/departments/manage_department.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5928|2024-08-02T08:14:25.110Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5927|2024-08-02T08:14:24.977Z -- campcodes -- simple%20student%20information%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5927</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/courses/manage_course.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244327.
In Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /admin/courses/manage_course.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5927|2024-08-02T08:14:24.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5930|2024-08-02T08:14:25.122Z -- campcodes -- simple%20student%20information%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5930</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/students/manage_academic.php. The manipulation of the argument student_id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-244330 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /admin/students/manage_academic.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments student_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5930|2024-08-02T08:14:25.122Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 20:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5925|2024-08-02T08:14:25.027Z -- campcodes -- simple%20student%20information%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5925</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /classes/Master.php. The manipulation of the argument f leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-244325 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /classes/Master.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments f mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5925|2024-08-02T08:14:25.027Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5924|2024-08-02T08:14:25.022Z -- campcodes -- simple%20student%20information%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5924</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/courses/view_course.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244324.
In Campcodes Simple Student Information System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /admin/courses/view_course.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5924|2024-08-02T08:14:25.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 18:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
