<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Campcodes -- Video Sharing Website</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/campcodes/video%20sharing%20website.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Campcodes -- Video Sharing Website</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:20:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2036|2024-08-02T06:12:19.896Z -- campcodes -- video%20sharing%20website
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2036</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Video Sharing Website 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file upload.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-225914 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Campcodes Video Sharing Website 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei upload.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2036|2024-08-02T06:12:19.896Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 07:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2035|2024-08-02T06:12:20.062Z -- campcodes -- video%20sharing%20website
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2035</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Video Sharing Website 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file signup.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-225913 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Campcodes Video Sharing Website 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei signup.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2035|2024-08-02T06:12:20.062Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 06:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2038|2024-08-02T06:12:19.876Z -- campcodes -- video%20sharing%20website
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2038</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Video Sharing Website 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file admin_class.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-225916.
In Campcodes Video Sharing Website 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei admin_class.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments email mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2038|2024-08-02T06:12:19.876Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 07:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2037|2024-08-02T06:12:19.951Z -- campcodes -- video%20sharing%20website
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2037</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Video Sharing Website 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file watch.php. The manipulation of the argument code leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-225915.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Campcodes Video Sharing Website 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei watch.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments code mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2037|2024-08-02T06:12:19.951Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 07:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
