<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for silverstripe -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/silverstripe/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for silverstripe -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:21:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29885|2024-07-17T20:55:01.983Z -- silverstripe -- silverstripe-reports
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29885</link>
      <description>silverstripe/reports is an API for creating backend reports in the Silverstripe Framework. In affected versions reports can be accessed by their direct URL by any user who has access to view the reports admin section, even if the `canView()` method for that report returns `false`. This issue has been addressed in version 5.2.3. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29885|2024-07-17T20:55:01.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 19:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49783|2024-01-23T13:54:51.301Z -- silverstripe -- silverstripe-admin</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-49783</link>
      <description>Silverstripe Admin provides a basic management interface for the Silverstripe Framework. In versions on the 1.x branch prior to 1.13.19 and on the 2.x branch prior to 2.1.8, users who don't have edit or delete permissions for records exposed in a `ModelAdmin` can still edit or delete records using the CSV import form, provided they have create permissions. The likelihood of a user having create permissions but not having edit or delete permissions is low, but it is possible. Note that this doesn't affect any `ModelAdmin` which has had the import form disabled via the `showImportForm` public property. Versions 1.13.19 and 2.1.8 contain a patch for the issue. Those who have a custom implementation of `BulkLoader` should update their implementations to respect permissions when the return value of `getCheckPermissions()` is true. Those who use any `BulkLoader` in their own project logic, or maintain a module which uses it, should consider passing `true` to `setCheckPermissions()` if the data is provided by users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49783|2024-01-23T13:54:51.301Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:54:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-48714|2024-01-23T13:49:27.350Z -- silverstripe -- silverstripe-framework</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-48714</link>
      <description>Silverstripe Framework is the framework that forms the base of the Silverstripe content management system. Prior to versions 4.13.39 and 5.1.11, if a user should not be able to see a record, but that record can be added to a `GridField` using the `GridFieldAddExistingAutocompleter` component, the record's title can be accessed by that user. Versions 4.13.39 and 5.1.11 contain a fix for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-48714|2024-01-23T13:49:27.350Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44401|2024-01-23T13:08:34.055Z -- silverstripe -- silverstripe-graphql</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44401</link>
      <description>The Silverstripe CMS GraphQL Server serves Silverstripe data as GraphQL representations. In versions 4.0.0 prior to 4.3.7 and 5.0.0 prior to 5.1.3, `canView` permission checks are bypassed for ORM data in paginated GraphQL query results where the total number of records is greater than the number of records per page. Note that this also affects GraphQL queries which have a limit applied, even if the query isn’t paginated per se. This has been fixed in versions 4.3.7 and 5.1.3 by ensuring no new records are pulled in from the database after performing `canView` permission checks for each page of results. This may result in some pages in the query results having less than the maximum number of records per page even when there are more pages of results. This behavior is consistent with how pagination works in other areas of Silverstripe CMS, such as in `GridField`, and is a result of having to perform permission checks in PHP rather than in the database directly. One may disable these permission checks by disabling the `CanViewPermission` plugin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44401|2024-01-23T13:08:34.055Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29885|2024-07-17T19:35:58.914Z -- silverstripe -- silverstripe-reports</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29885</link>
      <description>silverstripe/reports is an API for creating backend reports in the Silverstripe Framework. In affected versions reports can be accessed by their direct URL by any user who has access to view the reports admin section, even if the `canView()` method for that report returns `false`. This issue has been addressed in version 5.2.3. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29885|2024-07-17T19:35:58.914Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 19:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32981|2024-07-17T19:36:00.563Z -- silverstripe -- silverstripe-framework</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32981</link>
      <description>Silverstripe framework is the PHP framework forming the base for the Silverstripe CMS. In affected versions a bad actor with access to edit content in the CMS could add send a specifically crafted encoded payload to the server, which could be used to inject a JavaScript payload on the front end of the site. The payload would be sanitised on the client-side, but server-side sanitisation doesn't catch it. The server-side sanitisation logic has been updated to sanitise against this type of attack in version 5.2.16. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32981|2024-07-17T19:36:00.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 19:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
