<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for jegtheme -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/jegtheme/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for jegtheme -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 14:21:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3819|2024-07-07T13:53:18.411Z -- jegtheme -- jeg%20elementor%20kit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3819</link>
      <description>The Jeg Elementor Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's JKit - Banner widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3819|2024-07-07T13:53:18.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1327|2024-06-04T18:01:20.930Z -- jegtheme -- jeg%20elementor%20kit</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1327</link>
      <description>The Jeg Elementor Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's image box widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1327|2024-06-04T18:01:20.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 02:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1326|2024-03-12T23:33:52.349Z -- jegtheme -- jeg%20elementor%20kit</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1326</link>
      <description>The Jeg Elementor Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HTML Tag attributes in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1326|2024-03-12T23:33:52.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 23:33:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0334|2024-06-04T17:58:47.035Z -- jegtheme -- jeg%20elementor%20kit</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0334</link>
      <description>The Jeg Elementor Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the custom attribute of a link in several Elementor widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0334|2024-06-04T17:58:47.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29101|2024-06-04T17:58:13.766Z -- jegtheme -- jeg%20elementor%20kit</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29101</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jegtheme Jeg Elementor Kit allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Jeg Elementor Kit: from n/a through 2.6.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29101|2024-06-04T17:58:13.766Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32721|2024-04-24T10:09:51.279Z -- jegtheme -- jeg%20elementor%20kit</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32721</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jegtheme Jeg Elementor Kit allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Jeg Elementor Kit: from n/a through 2.6.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32721|2024-04-24T10:09:51.279Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:09:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3161|2024-06-04T17:33:02.023Z -- jegtheme -- jeg%20elementor%20kit</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3161</link>
      <description>The Jeg Elementor Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the countdown widget's attributes in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3161|2024-06-04T17:33:02.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3819|2024-05-02T16:52:01.563Z -- jegtheme -- jeg%20elementor%20kit</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3819</link>
      <description>The Jeg Elementor Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's JKit - Banner widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3819|2024-05-02T16:52:01.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3162|2024-06-04T17:31:20.102Z -- jegtheme -- jeg%20elementor%20kit</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3162</link>
      <description>The Jeg Elementor Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Testimonial Widget Attributes in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3162|2024-06-04T17:31:20.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 02:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4479|2024-06-17T13:59:30.627Z -- jegtheme -- jeg%20elementor%20kit</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4479</link>
      <description>The Jeg Elementor Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the sg_general_toggle_tab_enable and sg_accordion_style attributes within the plugin's JKit - Tabs and JKit - Accordion widget, respectively, in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4479|2024-06-17T13:59:30.627Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
