<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Mitsubishi Electric Corporation -- GOT2000 series GT27, GT25, and GT23</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mitsubishi%20electric%20corporation/got2000%20series%20gt27%2C%20gt25%2C%20and%20gt23.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Mitsubishi Electric Corporation -- GOT2000 series GT27, GT25, and GT23</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 11:20:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5596|2024-08-04T08:30:24.615Z -- mitsubishi%20electric%20corporation -- got2000%20series%20gt27%2C%20gt25%2C%20and%20gt23
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5596</link>
      <description>TCP/IP function included in the firmware of Mitsubishi Electric GOT2000 series (CoreOS with version -Y and earlier installed in GT27 Model, GT25 Model, and GT23 Model) does not properly manage sessions, which may allow a remote attacker to stop the network functions of the products or execute a malicious program via a specially crafted packet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5596|2024-08-04T08:30:24.615Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 08:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5599|2024-08-04T08:30:24.627Z -- mitsubishi%20electric%20corporation -- got2000%20series%20gt27%2C%20gt25%2C%20and%20gt23
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5599</link>
      <description>TCP/IP function included in the firmware of Mitsubishi Electric GOT2000 series (CoreOS with version -Y and earlier installed in GT27 Model, GT25 Model, and GT23 Model) contains an improper neutralization of argument delimiters in a command ('Argument Injection') vulnerability, which may allow a remote attacker to stop the network functions of the products or execute a malicious program via a specially crafted packet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5599|2024-08-04T08:30:24.627Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 08:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5595|2024-08-04T08:30:24.610Z -- mitsubishi%20electric%20corporation -- got2000%20series%20gt27%2C%20gt25%2C%20and%20gt23
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5595</link>
      <description>TCP/IP function included in the firmware of Mitsubishi Electric GOT2000 series (CoreOS with version -Y and earlier installed in GT27 Model, GT25 Model, and GT23 Model) contains a buffer overflow vulnerability, which may allow a remote attacker to stop the network functions of the products or execute a malicious program via a specially crafted packet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5595|2024-08-04T08:30:24.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 08:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5597|2024-08-04T08:30:24.631Z -- mitsubishi%20electric%20corporation -- got2000%20series%20gt27%2C%20gt25%2C%20and%20gt23
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5597</link>
      <description>TCP/IP function included in the firmware of Mitsubishi Electric GOT2000 series (CoreOS with version -Y and earlier installed in GT27 Model, GT25 Model, and GT23 Model) contains a null pointer dereference vulnerability, which may allow a remote attacker to stop the network functions of the products or execute a malicious program via a specially crafted packet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5597|2024-08-04T08:30:24.631Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 08:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5600|2024-08-04T08:30:24.613Z -- mitsubishi%20electric%20corporation -- got2000%20series%20gt27%2C%20gt25%2C%20and%20gt23
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5600</link>
      <description>TCP/IP function included in the firmware of Mitsubishi Electric GOT2000 series (CoreOS with version -Y and earlier installed in GT27 Model, GT25 Model, and GT23 Model) contains a resource management error vulnerability, which may allow a remote attacker to stop the network functions of the products or execute a malicious program via a specially crafted packet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5600|2024-08-04T08:30:24.613Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 08:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5598|2024-08-04T08:30:24.545Z -- mitsubishi%20electric%20corporation -- got2000%20series%20gt27%2C%20gt25%2C%20and%20gt23
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5598</link>
      <description>TCP/IP function included in the firmware of Mitsubishi Electric GOT2000 series (CoreOS with version -Y and earlier installed in GT27 Model, GT25 Model, and GT23 Model) contains an improper access control vulnerability, which may which may allow a remote attacker tobypass access restriction and stop the network functions of the products or execute a malicious program via a specially crafted packet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5598|2024-08-04T08:30:24.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 08:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
