<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Mitsubishi Electric Corporation -- GOT2000 Series GT27 model</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mitsubishi%20electric%20corporation/got2000%20series%20gt27%20model.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Mitsubishi Electric Corporation -- GOT2000 Series GT27 model</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:22:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40268|2024-08-03T12:14:40.024Z -- mitsubishi%20electric%20corporation -- got2000%20series%20gt27%20model
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40268</link>
      <description>Improper Restriction of Rendered UI Layers or Frames vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation GOT2000 Series GT27 model versions 01.14.000 to 01.47.000, Mitsubishi Electric Corporation GOT2000 Series GT25 model versions 01.14.000 to 01.47.000 and Mitsubishi Electric Corporation GT SoftGOT2000 versions 1.265B to 1.285X allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to lead legitimate users to perform unintended operations through clickjacking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40268|2024-08-03T12:14:40.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 07:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40269|2024-08-03T12:14:40.021Z -- mitsubishi%20electric%20corporation -- got2000%20series%20gt27%20model
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40269</link>
      <description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation GOT2000 Series GT27 model versions 01.14.000 to 01.47.000, Mitsubishi Electric Corporation GOT2000 Series GT25 model versions 01.14.000 to 01.47.000 and Mitsubishi Electric Corporation GT SoftGOT2000 versions 1.265B to 1.285X allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to disclose sensitive information from users' browsers or spoof legitimate users by abusing inappropriate HTML attributes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40269|2024-08-03T12:14:40.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 07:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
