<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Mitsubishi Electric Corporation -- GX Works3</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mitsubishi%20electric%20corporation/gx%20works3.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Mitsubishi Electric Corporation -- GX Works3</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5247|2023-11-30T03:57:30.083Z -- mitsubishi%20electric%20corporation -- gx%20works3
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5247</link>
      <description>Malicious Code Execution Vulnerability due to External Control of File Name or Path in multiple Mitsubishi Electric FA Engineering Software Products allows a malicious attacker to execute a malicious code by having legitimate users open a specially crafted project file, which could result in information disclosure, tampering and deletion, or a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5247|2023-11-30T03:57:30.083Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 03:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4088|2023-09-27T23:14:21.617Z -- mitsubishi%20electric%20corporation -- gx%20works3
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4088</link>
      <description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability due to incomplete fix to address CVE-2020-14496 in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation FA engineering software products allows a malicious local attacker to execute a malicious code, which could result in information disclosure, tampering with and deletion, or a denial-of-service (DoS) condition. However, if the mitigated version described in the advisory for CVE-2020-14496 is used and installed in the default installation folder, this vulnerability does not affect the products.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4088|2023-09-27T23:14:21.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 02:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
