<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for WPWeb -- Social Auto Poster</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/wpweb/social%20auto%20poster.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for WPWeb -- Social Auto Poster</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:23:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6755|2024-07-24T14:58:33.607Z -- wpweb -- social%20auto%20poster
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6755</link>
      <description>The Social Auto Poster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the ‘wpw_auto_poster_quick_delete_multiple’ function in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.14. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary posts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6755|2024-07-24T14:58:33.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6753|2024-07-24T13:36:25.304Z -- wpweb -- social%20auto%20poster</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6753</link>
      <description>The Social Auto Poster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘mapTypes’ parameter in the 'wpw_auto_poster_map_wordpress_post_type' AJAX function in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6753|2024-07-24T13:36:25.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:33:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6756|2024-07-24T13:20:16.533Z -- wpweb -- social%20auto%20poster</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6756</link>
      <description>The Social Auto Poster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'wpw_auto_poster_get_image_path' function in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.14. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level and above permissions, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. An attacker can use CVE-2024-6754 to exploit with subscriber-level access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6756|2024-07-24T13:20:16.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 02:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
