<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Kaspersky Lab -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/kaspersky%20lab/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Kaspersky Lab -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8267|2024-08-04T21:17:31.270Z -- kaspersky%20lab -- ultravnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8267</link>
      <description>UltraVNC revision 1207 has out-of-bounds read vulnerability in VNC client code inside TextChat module, which results in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This attack appears to be exploitable via network connectivity. This vulnerability has been fixed in revision 1208.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8267|2024-08-04T21:17:31.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8275|2024-08-04T21:17:30.848Z -- kaspersky%20lab -- ultravnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8275</link>
      <description>UltraVNC revision 1211 has multiple improper null termination vulnerabilities in VNC server code, which result in out-of-bound data being accessed by remote users. This attack appears to be exploitable via network connectivity. These vulnerabilities have been fixed in revision 1212.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8275|2024-08-04T21:17:30.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8266|2024-08-04T21:17:30.554Z -- kaspersky%20lab -- ultravnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8266</link>
      <description>UltraVNC revision 1207 has multiple out-of-bounds access vulnerabilities connected with improper usage of ClientConnection::Copybuffer function in VNC client code, which can potentially result in code execution. This attack appears to be exploitable via network connectivity. User interaction is required to trigger these vulnerabilities. These vulnerabilities have been fixed in revision 1208.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8266|2024-08-04T21:17:30.554Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8271|2024-08-04T21:17:31.251Z -- kaspersky%20lab -- ultravnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8271</link>
      <description>UltraVNC revision 1211 has a heap buffer overflow vulnerability in VNC server code inside file transfer handler, which can potentially result code execution. This attack appears to be exploitable via network connectivity. This vulnerability has been fixed in revision 1212.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8271|2024-08-04T21:17:31.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8277|2024-08-04T21:17:30.165Z -- kaspersky%20lab -- ultravnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8277</link>
      <description>UltraVNC revision 1211 contains multiple memory leaks (CWE-665) in VNC server code, which allows an attacker to read stack memory and can be abused for information disclosure. Combined with another vulnerability, it can be used to leak stack memory and bypass ASLR. This attack appears to be exploitable via network connectivity. These vulnerabilities have been fixed in revision 1212.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8277|2024-08-04T21:17:30.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8263|2024-08-04T21:17:30.560Z -- kaspersky%20lab -- ultravnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8263</link>
      <description>UltraVNC revision 1205 has stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in VNC client code inside ShowConnInfo routine, which leads to a denial of service (DoS) condition. This attack appear to be exploitable via network connectivity. User interaction is required to trigger this vulnerability. This vulnerability has been fixed in revision 1206.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8263|2024-08-04T21:17:30.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8274|2024-08-04T21:17:30.639Z -- kaspersky%20lab -- ultravnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8274</link>
      <description>UltraVNC revision 1211 has a heap buffer overflow vulnerability in VNC server code inside file transfer offer handler, which can potentially in result code execution. This attack appears to be exploitable via network connectivity. This vulnerability has been fixed in revision 1212.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8274|2024-08-04T21:17:30.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8265|2024-08-04T21:17:30.842Z -- kaspersky%20lab -- ultravnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8265</link>
      <description>UltraVNC revision 1207 has multiple out-of-bounds access vulnerabilities connected with improper usage of SETPIXELS macro in VNC client code, which can potentially result in code execution. This attack appears to be exploitable via network connectivity. These vulnerabilities have been fixed in revision 1208.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8265|2024-08-04T21:17:30.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8276|2024-08-04T21:17:30.806Z -- kaspersky%20lab -- ultravnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8276</link>
      <description>UltraVNC revision 1211 has a stack buffer overflow vulnerability in VNC server code inside file transfer request handler, which can result in Denial of Service (DoS). This attack appears to be exploitable via network connectivity. This vulnerability has been fixed in revision 1212.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8276|2024-08-04T21:17:30.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8270|2024-08-04T21:17:31.273Z -- kaspersky%20lab -- ultravnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8270</link>
      <description>UltraVNC revision 1210 has out-of-bounds read vulnerability in VNC client code inside Ultra decoder, which results in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This attack appear to be exploitable via network connectivity. This vulnerability has been fixed in revision 1211.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8270|2024-08-04T21:17:31.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8272|2024-08-04T21:17:30.483Z -- kaspersky%20lab -- ultravnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8272</link>
      <description>UltraVNC revision 1211 has multiple off-by-one vulnerabilities in VNC server code, which can potentially result in code execution. This attack appears to be exploitable via network connectivity. These vulnerabilities have been fixed in revision 1212.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8272|2024-08-04T21:17:30.483Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8273|2024-08-04T21:17:31.298Z -- kaspersky%20lab -- ultravnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8273</link>
      <description>UltraVNC revision 1211 has a heap buffer overflow vulnerability in VNC server code inside file transfer request handler, which can potentially result in code execution. This attack appears to be exploitable via network connectivity. This vulnerability has been fixed in revision 1212.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8273|2024-08-04T21:17:31.298Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8278|2024-08-04T21:17:31.152Z -- kaspersky%20lab -- invision%20power%20board
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8278</link>
      <description>Stored XSS in Invision Power Board versions 3.3.1 - 3.4.8 leads to Remote Code Execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8278|2024-08-04T21:17:31.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8264|2024-08-04T21:17:30.529Z -- kaspersky%20lab -- ultravnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8264</link>
      <description>UltraVNC revision 1203 has out-of-bounds access vulnerability in VNC client inside Ultra2 decoder, which can potentially result in code execution. This attack appears to be exploitable via network connectivity. This vulnerability has been fixed in revision 1204.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8264|2024-08-04T21:17:30.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8280|2024-08-04T21:17:30.735Z -- kaspersky%20lab -- ultravnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8280</link>
      <description>UltraVNC revision 1203 has out-of-bounds access vulnerability in VNC client inside RAW decoder, which can potentially result code execution. This attack appear to be exploitable via network connectivity. This vulnerability has been fixed in revision 1204.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8280|2024-08-04T21:17:30.735Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8268|2024-08-04T21:17:30.455Z -- kaspersky%20lab -- ultravnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8268</link>
      <description>UltraVNC revision 1206 has multiple off-by-one vulnerabilities in VNC client code connected with improper usage of ClientConnection::ReadString function, which can potentially result code execution. This attack appears to be exploitable via network connectivity. These vulnerabilities have been fixed in revision 1207.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8268|2024-08-04T21:17:30.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8279|2024-08-04T21:17:30.787Z -- kaspersky%20lab -- vanilla%20forums
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8279</link>
      <description>Multiple stored XSS in Vanilla Forums before 2.5 allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary JavaScript code into any message on forum.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8279|2024-08-04T21:17:30.787Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8269|2024-08-04T21:17:30.516Z -- kaspersky%20lab -- ultravnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8269</link>
      <description>UltraVNC revision 1206 has stack-based Buffer overflow vulnerability in VNC client code inside FileTransfer module, which leads to a denial of service (DoS) condition. This attack appear to be exploitable via network connectivity. This vulnerability has been fixed in revision 1207.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8269|2024-08-04T21:17:30.516Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
