<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for themehunk -- Easy Mega Menu Plugin for WordPress – ThemeHunk</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/themehunk/easy%20mega%20menu%20plugin%20for%20wordpress%20%E2%80%93%20themehunk.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for themehunk -- Easy Mega Menu Plugin for WordPress – ThemeHunk</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 10:23:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8433|2024-10-08T09:33:14.205Z -- themehunk -- easy%20mega%20menu%20plugin%20for%20wordpress%20%E2%80%93%20themehunk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8433</link>
      <description>The Easy Mega Menu Plugin for WordPress – ThemeHunk plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘themehunk_megamenu_bg_image' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Please note that this was partially fixed in 1.1.0 due to the missing authorization protection that was added.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8433|2024-10-08T09:33:14.205Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 09:33:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8434|2024-09-25T13:30:29.959Z -- themehunk -- easy%20mega%20menu%20plugin%20for%20wordpress%20%E2%80%93%20themehunk</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8434</link>
      <description>The Easy Mega Menu Plugin for WordPress – ThemeHunk plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on several functions hooked via AJAX in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to perform actions like updating plugin settings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8434|2024-09-25T13:30:29.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 02:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
