<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ITarian -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/itarian/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ITarian -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 17:22:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-25152|2024-08-06T12:32:40.482Z -- itarian -- itarian%20platform%20%28saas%20%2F%20on-premise%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25152</link>
      <description>The ITarian platform (SAAS / on-premise) offers the possibility to run code on agents via a function called procedures. It is possible to require a mandatory approval process. Due to a vulnerability in the approval process, present in any version prior to 6.35.37347.20040, a malicious actor (with a valid session token) can create a procedure, bypass approval, and execute the procedure. This results in the ability for any user with a valid session token to perform arbitrary code execution and full system take-over on all agents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-25152|2024-08-06T12:32:40.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-25153|2024-08-06T12:32:39.628Z -- itarian -- endpoint%20manager%20communication%20client%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25153</link>
      <description>The ITarian Endpoint Manage Communication Client, prior to version 6.43.41148.21120, is compiled using insecure OpenSSL settings. Due to this setting, a malicious actor with low privileges access to a system can escalate his privileges to SYSTEM abusing an insecure openssl.conf lookup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-25153|2024-08-06T12:32:39.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-25151|2024-08-06T12:32:38.901Z -- itarian -- itarian%20saas%20platform%20%2F%20on-premise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25151</link>
      <description>Within the Service Desk module of the ITarian platform (SAAS and on-premise), a remote attacker can obtain sensitive information, caused by the failure to set the HTTP Only flag. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to gain access to the management interface by using this vulnerability in combination with a successful Cross-Site Scripting attack on a user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-25151|2024-08-06T12:32:38.901Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
