<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Delta Electronics -- DOPSoft</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/delta%20electronics/dopsoft.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Delta Electronics -- DOPSoft</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:22:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5944|2024-08-02T08:14:25.147Z -- delta%20electronics -- dopsoft
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5944</link>
      <description>
Delta Electronics DOPSoft is vulnerable to a stack-based buffer overflow, which may allow for arbitrary code execution if an attacker can lead a legitimate user to execute a specially crafted file.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5944|2024-08-02T08:14:25.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43819|2024-08-02T19:52:11.465Z -- delta%20electronics -- dopsoft
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43819</link>
      <description>A stack based buffer overflow exists in Delta Electronics Delta Industrial Automation DOPSoft when parsing the InitialMacroLen field of a DPS file. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability by enticing a user to open a specially crafted DPS file to achieve remote code execution.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43819|2024-08-02T19:52:11.465Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 21:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43817|2024-08-02T19:52:11.320Z -- delta%20electronics -- dopsoft
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43817</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow exists in Delta Electronics Delta Industrial Automation DOPSoft version 2 when parsing the wMailContentLen field of a DPS file. An anonymous attacker can exploit this vulnerability by enticing a user to open a specially crafted DPS file to achieve code execution.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43817|2024-08-02T19:52:11.320Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 21:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43815|2024-08-02T19:52:11.322Z -- delta%20electronics -- dopsoft
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43815</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Delta Electronics Delta Industrial Automation DOPSoft version 2 when parsing the wScreenDESCTextLen field of a DPS file. An anonymous attacker can exploit this vulnerability by enticing a user to open a specially crafted DPS file to achieve code execution.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43815|2024-08-02T19:52:11.322Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 21:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43818|2024-08-02T19:52:11.326Z -- delta%20electronics -- dopsoft
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43818</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow exists in Delta Electronics Delta Industrial Automation DOPSoft. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability by enticing a user to open a specially crafted DPS file to achieve remote code execution.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43818|2024-08-02T19:52:11.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 21:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43823|2024-08-02T19:52:11.377Z -- delta%20electronics -- dopsoft
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43823</link>
      <description>A stack based buffer overflow exists in Delta Electronics Delta Industrial Automation DOPSoft when parsing the wTTitleLen field of a DPS file. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability by enticing a user to open a specially crafted DPS file to achieve remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43823|2024-08-02T19:52:11.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 21:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43822|2024-08-02T19:52:11.405Z -- delta%20electronics -- dopsoft
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43822</link>
      <description>A stack based buffer overflow exists in Delta Electronics Delta Industrial Automation DOPSoft when parsing the wLogTitlesTimeLen field of a DPS file. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability by enticing a user to open a specially crafted DPS file to achieve remote code execution.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43822|2024-08-02T19:52:11.405Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 21:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43816|2024-08-02T19:52:11.411Z -- delta%20electronics -- dopsoft
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43816</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Delta Electronics Delta Industrial Automation DOPSoft version 2 when parsing the wKPFStringLen field of a DPS file. An anonymous attacker can exploit this vulnerability by enticing a user to open a specially crafted DPS file to achieve code execution.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43816|2024-08-02T19:52:11.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 21:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43821|2024-08-02T19:52:11.313Z -- delta%20electronics -- dopsoft
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43821</link>
      <description>A stack based buffer overflow exists in Delta Electronics Delta Industrial Automation DOPSoft when parsing the wLogTitlesActionLen field of a DPS file. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability by enticing a user to open a specially crafted DPS file to achieve remote code execution.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43821|2024-08-02T19:52:11.313Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 21:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43820|2024-08-02T19:52:11.345Z -- delta%20electronics -- dopsoft
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43820</link>
      <description>A stack based buffer overflow exists in Delta Electronics Delta Industrial Automation DOPSoft when parsing the wLogTitlesPrevValueLen field of a DPS file. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability by enticing a user to open a specially crafted DPS file to achieve remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43820|2024-08-02T19:52:11.345Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 21:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43824|2024-08-02T19:52:11.869Z -- delta%20electronics -- dopsoft
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43824</link>
      <description>A stack based buffer overflow exists in Delta Electronics Delta Industrial Automation DOPSoft when parsing the wTitleTextLen field of a DPS file. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability by enticing a user to open a specially crafted DPS file to achieve remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43824|2024-08-02T19:52:11.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 21:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
