<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for themeum -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/themeum/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for themeum -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:25:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3553|2024-05-02T16:52:53.256Z -- themeum -- tutor%20lms%20%E2%80%93%20elearning%20and%20online%20course%20solution</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3553</link>
      <description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the hide_notices function in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable user registration on sites that may have it disabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3553|2024-05-02T16:52:53.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4279|2024-06-06T19:47:56.372Z -- themeum -- tutor%20lms%20%E2%80%93%20elearning%20and%20online%20course%20solution</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4279</link>
      <description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference to Arbitrary Course Deletion in versions up to, and including, 2.7.0 via the 'tutor_course_delete' function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This can allow authenticated attackers, with Instructor-level permissions and above, to delete any course.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4279|2024-06-06T19:47:56.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4902|2024-06-07T04:33:25.127Z -- themeum -- tutor%20lms%20%E2%80%93%20elearning%20and%20online%20course%20solution</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4902</link>
      <description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘course_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with admin access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4902|2024-06-07T04:33:25.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 04:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
