<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for themeum -- Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/themeum/tutor%20lms%20%E2%80%93%20elearning%20and%20online%20course%20solution.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for themeum -- Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1751|2024-03-13T15:27:26.103Z -- themeum -- Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1751</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the question_id parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber/student access or higher, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1751|2024-03-13T15:27:26.103Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1503|2024-03-12T23:33:49.090Z -- themeum -- Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1503</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the erase_tutor_data() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to deactivate the plugin and erase all data via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. This requires the "Erase upon uninstallation" option to be enabled.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1503|2024-03-12T23:33:49.090Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 23:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1128|2024-02-20T18:56:22.265Z -- themeum -- Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1128</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to HTML Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.0. This is due to insufficient sanitization of HTML input in the Q&amp;A functionality. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Student access and above, to inject arbitrary HTML onto a site, though it does not allow Cross-Site Scripting</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1128|2024-02-20T18:56:22.265Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1133|2024-02-20T18:56:49.287Z -- themeum -- Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1133</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of restricted Q&amp;A content due to a missing capability check when interacting with questions in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access or higher, to interact with questions in courses in which they are not enrolled including private courses.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1133|2024-02-20T18:56:49.287Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1502|2024-03-12T23:33:50.040Z -- themeum -- Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1502</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the tutor_delete_announcement() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary posts.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1502|2024-03-12T23:33:50.040Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 23:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4318|2024-05-16T05:33:27.607Z -- themeum -- Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4318</link><description>The Tutor LMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘question_id’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 2.7.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Instructor-level permissions and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4318|2024-05-16T05:33:27.607Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4279|2024-05-16T05:33:25.813Z -- themeum -- Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4279</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference to Arbitrary Course Deletion in versions up to, and including, 2.7.0 via the 'tutor_course_delete' function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This can allow authenticated attackers, with Instructor-level permissions and above, to delete any course.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4279|2024-05-16T05:33:25.813Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4223|2024-05-16T08:32:50.538Z -- themeum -- Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4223</link><description>The Tutor LMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data, modification of data, loss of data due to a missing capability check on multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add, modify, or delete data.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4223|2024-05-16T08:32:50.538Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 08:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3994|2024-04-25T09:29:58.460Z -- themeum -- Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3994</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tutor_instructor_list' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3994|2024-04-25T09:29:58.460Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 09:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3553|2024-05-02T16:52:53.256Z -- themeum -- Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3553</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the hide_notices function in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable user registration on sites that may have it disabled.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3553|2024-05-02T16:52:53.256Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>