<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for xmldom -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/xmldom/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for xmldom -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39353|2024-08-03T12:00:44.144Z -- xmldom -- xmldom
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39353</link>
      <description>xmldom is a pure JavaScript W3C standard-based (XML DOM Level 2 Core) `DOMParser` and `XMLSerializer` module. xmldom parses XML that is not well-formed because it contains multiple top level elements, and adds all root nodes to the `childNodes` collection of the `Document`, without reporting any error or throwing. This breaks the assumption that there is only a single root node in the tree, which led to issuance of CVE-2022-39299 as it is a potential issue for dependents. Update to @xmldom/xmldom@~0.7.7, @xmldom/xmldom@~0.8.4 (dist-tag latest) or @xmldom/xmldom@&gt;=0.9.0-beta.4 (dist-tag next). As a workaround, please one of the following approaches depending on your use case: instead of searching for elements in the whole DOM, only search in the `documentElement`or reject a document with a document that has more then 1 `childNode`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39353|2024-08-03T12:00:44.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21366|2024-08-03T18:09:16.000Z -- xmldom -- xmldom
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21366</link>
      <description>xmldom is a pure JavaScript W3C standard-based (XML DOM Level 2 Core) DOMParser and XMLSerializer module. xmldom versions 0.4.0 and older do not correctly preserve system identifiers, FPIs or namespaces when repeatedly parsing and serializing maliciously crafted documents. This may lead to unexpected syntactic changes during XML processing in some downstream applications. This is fixed in version 0.5.0. As a workaround downstream applications can validate the input and reject the maliciously crafted documents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21366|2024-08-03T18:09:16.000Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
