<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Triangle MicroWorks -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/triangle%20microworks/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Triangle MicroWorks -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 14:22:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2187|2024-08-02T06:12:20.539Z -- triangle%20microworks -- scada%20data%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2187</link>
      <description>On Triangle MicroWorks' SCADA Data Gateway version &lt;= v5.01.03, an unauthenticated attacker can send broadcast events to any user via the WebMonitor.An unauthenticated user can use this vulnerability to forcefully log out of any currently logged-in user by sending a "password change event". Furthermore, an attacker could use this vulnerability to spam the logged-in user with false events.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2187|2024-08-02T06:12:20.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 06:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2186|2024-08-02T06:12:20.659Z -- triangle%20microworks -- scada%20data%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2186</link>
      <description>On Triangle MicroWorks' SCADA Data Gateway version &lt;= v5.01.03, an unauthenticated attacker can send a specially crafted broadcast message including format string characters to the SCADA Data Gateway to perform unrestricted memory reads.An unauthenticated user can use this format string vulnerability to repeatedly crash the GTWWebMonitor.exe process to DoS the Web Monitor.  Furthermore, an authenticated user can leverage this vulnerability to leak memory from the GTWWebMonitor.exe process. This could be leveraged in an exploit chain to gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2186|2024-08-02T06:12:20.659Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 06:37:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39466|2024-07-23T17:15:39.965Z -- triangle%20microworks -- scada%20data%20gateway</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39466</link>
      <description>Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway get_config Missing Authentication Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the get_config endpoint. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose sensitive information. Was ZDI-CAN-20797.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39466|2024-07-23T17:15:39.965Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-0369|2024-07-23T17:09:35.862Z -- triangle%20microworks -- scada%20data%20gateway</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-0369</link>
      <description>Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway Restore Workspace Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the Restore Workspace feature. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-17227.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-0369|2024-07-23T17:09:35.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39467|2024-06-04T17:26:51.263Z -- triangle%20microworks -- scada%20data%20gateway</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39467</link>
      <description>Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway certificate Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of certificate web directory. The issue results from the exposure of sensitive information in the application webroot. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose sensitive information. Was ZDI-CAN-20798.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39467|2024-06-04T17:26:51.263Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39466|2024-05-03T01:59:28.811Z -- triangle%20microworks -- scada%20data%20gateway</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39466</link>
      <description>Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway get_config Missing Authentication Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the get_config endpoint. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose sensitive information. Was ZDI-CAN-20797.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39466|2024-05-03T01:59:28.811Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39457|2024-06-04T17:26:56.761Z -- triangle%20microworks -- scada%20data%20gateway</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39457</link>
      <description>Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway Missing Authentication Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists due to the lack of user authentication. The issue results from missing authentication in the default system configuration. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20501.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39457|2024-06-04T17:26:56.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39461|2024-06-04T17:26:58.048Z -- triangle%20microworks -- scada%20data%20gateway</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39461</link>
      <description>Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway Event Log Improper Output Neutralization For Logs Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to write arbitrary files on affected installations of Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of event logs. The issue results from improper sanitization of log output. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20535.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39461|2024-06-04T17:26:58.048Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39460|2024-06-04T17:26:58.471Z -- triangle%20microworks -- scada%20data%20gateway</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39460</link>
      <description>Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway Event Log Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Creation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create arbitrary files on affected installations of Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the creation of event logs. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20534.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39460|2024-06-04T17:26:58.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39463|2024-06-04T17:27:02.325Z -- triangle%20microworks -- scada%20data%20gateway</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39463</link>
      <description>Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway Trusted Certification Unrestricted Upload of File Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the trusted certification feature. The issue lies in the handling of the OpcUaSecurityCertificateAuthorityTrustDir variable, which allows an arbitrary file write with attacker-controlled data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20537.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39463|2024-06-04T17:27:02.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39459|2024-06-04T17:27:02.754Z -- triangle%20microworks -- scada%20data%20gateway</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39459</link>
      <description>Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Creation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create arbitrary files on affected installations of Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of workspace files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create files in the context of Administrator. Was ZDI-CAN-20531.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39459|2024-06-04T17:27:02.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39458|2024-06-04T17:27:03.174Z -- triangle%20microworks -- scada%20data%20gateway</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39458</link>
      <description>Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway Use of Hard-coded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of certificates. The service uses a hard-coded default SSL certificate. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-20509.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39458|2024-06-04T17:27:03.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39462|2024-06-04T17:27:04.040Z -- triangle%20microworks -- scada%20data%20gateway</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39462</link>
      <description>Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway Workspace Unrestricted Upload Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to upload arbitrary files on affected installations of Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of workspace files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can allow the upload of arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilitites to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20536.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39462|2024-06-04T17:27:04.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39465|2024-06-04T17:27:05.297Z -- triangle%20microworks -- scada%20data%20gateway</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39465</link>
      <description>Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway Use of Hard-coded Cryptograhic Key Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the TmwCrypto class. The issue results from the usage of a hard-coded cryptograhic key and the usage of a hard-coded certificate. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose sensitive information. Was ZDI-CAN-20615.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39465|2024-06-04T17:27:05.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39468|2024-06-04T17:27:09.598Z -- triangle%20microworks -- scada%20data%20gateway</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39468</link>
      <description>Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway DbasSectorFileToExecuteOnReset Exposed Dangerous Function Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of DbasSectorFileToExecuteOnReset parameter. The issue results from an exposed dangerous function. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20799.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39468|2024-06-04T17:27:09.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39464|2024-06-04T17:27:11.296Z -- triangle%20microworks -- scada%20data%20gateway</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39464</link>
      <description>Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway GTWWebMonitorService Unquoted Search Path Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute code on affected installations of Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of the GTWWebMonitorService service. The path to the service executable contains spaces not surrounded by quotations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20538.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39464|2024-06-04T17:27:11.296Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
