<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for geoserver -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/geoserver/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for geoserver -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 22:22:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5786|2024-06-28T19:58:51.677Z -- geoserver -- geowebcache
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5786</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in GeoServer GeoWebCache up to 1.15.1. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /geoserver/gwc/rest.html. The manipulation leads to direct request. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243592.
In GeoServer GeoWebCache bis 1.15.1 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /geoserver/gwc/rest.html. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine direct request-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5786|2024-06-28T19:58:51.677Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41877|2024-03-20T14:27:34.308Z -- geoserver -- geoserver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41877</link>
      <description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. A path traversal vulnerability in versions 2.23.4 and prior requires GeoServer Administrator with access to the admin console to misconfigure the Global Settings for log file location to an arbitrary location. The admin console GeoServer Logs page provides a preview of these contents. As this issue requires GeoServer administrators access, often representing a trusted party, the vulnerability has not received a patch as of time of publication. As a workaround, a system administrator responsible for running GeoServer can use the `GEOSERVER_LOG_FILE` setting to override any configuration option provided by the Global Settings page. The `GEOSERVER_LOG_LOCATION` parameter can be set as system property, environment variables, or servlet context parameters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41877|2024-03-20T14:27:34.308Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51444|2024-03-20T15:07:29.869Z -- geoserver -- geoserver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51444</link>
      <description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. An arbitrary file upload vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.23.4 and 2.24.1 that enables an authenticated administrator with permissions to modify coverage stores through the REST Coverage Store API to upload arbitrary file contents to arbitrary file locations which can lead to remote code execution. Coverage stores that are configured using relative paths use a GeoServer Resource implementation that has validation to prevent path traversal but coverage stores that are configured using absolute paths use a different Resource implementation that does not prevent path traversal. This vulnerability can lead to executing arbitrary code. An administrator with limited privileges could also potentially exploit this to overwrite GeoServer security files and obtain full administrator privileges. Versions 2.23.4 and 2.24.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51444|2024-03-20T15:07:29.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:07:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51445|2024-03-20T15:14:49.682Z -- geoserver -- geoserver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51445</link>
      <description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.23.3 and 2.24.0 that enables an authenticated administrator with workspace-level privileges to store a JavaScript payload in uploaded style/legend resources that will execute in the context of another administrator's browser when viewed in the REST Resources API.  Access to the REST Resources API is limited to full administrators by default and granting non-administrators access to this endpoint should be carefully considered as it may allow access to files containing sensitive information. Versions 2.23.3 and 2.24.0 contain a patch for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51445|2024-03-20T15:14:49.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23642|2024-06-04T17:46:05.167Z -- geoserver -- geoserver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23642</link>
      <description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.23.4 and 2.24.1 that enables an authenticated administrator with workspace-level privileges to store a JavaScript payload in the GeoServer catalog that will execute in the context of another user's browser when viewed in the WMS GetMap SVG Output Format when the Simple SVG renderer is enabled. Access to the WMS SVG Format is available to all users by default although data and service security may limit users' ability to trigger the XSS. Versions 2.23.4 and 2.24.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23642|2024-06-04T17:46:05.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:44:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23818|2024-03-20T17:57:38.893Z -- geoserver -- geoserver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23818</link>
      <description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.23.3 and 2.24.1 that enables an authenticated administrator with workspace-level privileges to store a JavaScript payload in the GeoServer catalog that will execute in the context of another user's browser when viewed in the WMS GetMap OpenLayers Output Format.  Access to the WMS OpenLayers Format is available to all users by default although data and service security may limit users' ability to trigger the XSS. Versions 2.23.3 and 2.24.1 contain a patch for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23818|2024-03-20T17:57:38.893Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23634|2024-06-04T17:46:00.499Z -- geoserver -- geoserver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23634</link>
      <description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. An arbitrary file renaming vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.23.5 and 2.24.2 that enables an authenticated administrator with permissions to modify stores through the REST Coverage Store or Data Store API to rename arbitrary files and directories with a name that does not end in `.zip`. Store file uploads rename zip files to have a `.zip` extension if it doesn't already have one before unzipping the file.  This is fine for file and url upload methods where the files will be in a specific subdirectory of the data directory but, when using the external upload method, this allows arbitrary files and directories to be renamed. Renaming GeoServer files will most likely result in a denial of service, either completely preventing GeoServer from running or effectively deleting specific resources (such as a workspace, layer or style).  In some cases, renaming GeoServer files could revert to the default settings for that file which could be relatively harmless like removing contact information or have more serious consequences like allowing users to make OGC requests that the customized settings would have prevented them from making. The impact of renaming non-GeoServer files depends on the specific environment although some sort of denial of service is a likely outcome. Versions 2.23.5 and 2.24.2 contain a fix for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23634|2024-06-04T17:46:00.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:22:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23819|2024-06-04T17:46:00.113Z -- geoserver -- geoserver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23819</link>
      <description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.23.4 and 2.24.1 that enables an authenticated administrator with workspace-level privileges to store a JavaScript payload in the GeoServer catalog that will execute in the context of another user's browser when viewed in the MapML HTML Page. The MapML extension must be installed and access to the MapML HTML Page is available to all users although data security may limit users' ability to trigger the XSS. Versions 2.23.4 and 2.24.1 contain a patch for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23819|2024-06-04T17:46:00.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 18:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23643|2024-06-11T17:15:17.108Z -- geoserver -- geoserver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23643</link>
      <description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.23.2 and 2.24.1 that enables an authenticated administrator with workspace-level privileges to store a JavaScript payload in the GeoServer catalog that will execute in the context of another administrator’s browser when viewed in the GWC Seed Form. Access to the GWC Seed Form is limited to full administrators by default and granting non-administrators access to this endpoint is not recommended. Versions 2.23.2 and 2.24.1 contain a fix for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23643|2024-06-11T17:15:17.108Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23640|2024-06-04T17:45:55.450Z -- geoserver -- geoserver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23640</link>
      <description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.23.3 and 2.24.0 that enables an authenticated administrator with workspace-level privileges to store a JavaScript payload in uploaded style/legend resources or in a specially crafted datastore file that will execute in the context of another user's browser when viewed in the Style Publisher. Access to the Style Publisher is available to all users although data security may limit users' ability to trigger the XSS. Versions 2.23.3 and 2.24.0 contain a fix for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23640|2024-06-04T17:45:55.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23821|2024-06-04T17:45:50.116Z -- geoserver -- geoserver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23821</link>
      <description>GeoServer is an open source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 2.23.4 and 2.24.1 that enables an authenticated administrator with workspace-level privileges to store a JavaScript payload in the GeoServer catalog that will execute in the context of another user's browser when viewed in the GWC Demos Page.  Access to the GWC Demos Page is available to all users although data security may limit users' ability to trigger the XSS. Versions 2.23.4 and 2.24.1 contain a patch for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23821|2024-06-04T17:45:50.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 18:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
