<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Amazon -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/amazon/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Amazon -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 17:22:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8901|2024-10-22T16:01:52.200Z -- amazon -- aws%20alb%20route%20directive%20adapter%20for%20istio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8901</link>
      <description>The  AWS ALB Route Directive Adapter For Istio repo https://github.com/awslabs/aws-alb-route-directive-adapter-for-istio/tree/master  provides an OIDC authentication mechanism that was integrated into the open source Kubeflow project. The adapter uses JWT for authentication, but lacks proper signer and issuer validation. In uncommon deployments of ALB, wherein endpoints are exposed to internet traffic, an actor can provide a JWT signed by an untrusted entity in order to spoof OIDC-federated sessions and successfully bypass authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8901|2024-10-22T16:01:52.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 23:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10125|2024-10-22T14:33:10.780Z -- amazon -- amazon.applicationloadbalancer.identity.aspnetcore%20middleware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10125</link>
      <description>The  Amazon.ApplicationLoadBalancer.Identity.AspNetCore repo https://github.com/awslabs/aws-alb-identity-aspnetcore#validatetokensignature  contains Middleware that can be used in conjunction with the Application Load Balancer (ALB) OpenId Connect integration and can be used in any  ASP.NET http://asp.net/  Core deployment scenario, including Fargate, EKS, ECS, EC2, and Lambda. In the JWT handling code, it performs signature validation but fails to validate the JWT issuer and signer identity. The signer omission, if combined with a scenario where the infrastructure owner allows internet traffic to the ALB targets (not a recommended configuration), can allow for JWT signing by an untrusted entity and an actor may be able to mimic valid OIDC-federated sessions to the ALB targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-10125|2024-10-22T14:33:10.780Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 23:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
