<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for docCMS -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/doccms/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for docCMS -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3187|2024-08-05T14:16:28.217Z -- doccms -- administration%20panel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3187</link>
      <description>The dotCMS administration panel, versions 3.7.1 and earlier, are vulnerable to cross-site request forgery. The dotCMS administrator panel contains a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability. An attacker can perform actions with the same permissions as a victim user, provided the victim has an active session and is induced to trigger the malicious request. An unauthenticated remote attacker may perform actions with the dotCMS administrator panel with the same permissions of a victim user or execute arbitrary system commands with the permissions of the user running the dotCMS application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3187|2024-08-05T14:16:28.217Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3189|2024-08-05T14:16:28.234Z -- doccms -- administration%20panel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3189</link>
      <description>The dotCMS administration panel, versions 3.7.1 and earlier, "Push Publishing" feature in Enterprise Pro is vulnerable to arbitrary file upload. When "Bundle" tar.gz archives uploaded to the Push Publishing feature are decompressed, there are no checks on the types of files which the bundle contains. This vulnerability combined with the path traversal vulnerability (CVE-2017-3188) can lead to remote command execution with the permissions of the user running the dotCMS application. An unauthenticated remote attacker may perform actions with the dotCMS administrator panel with the same permissions of a victim user or execute arbitrary system commands with the permissions of the user running the dotCMS application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3189|2024-08-05T14:16:28.234Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3188|2024-08-05T14:16:28.240Z -- doccms -- administration%20panel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3188</link>
      <description>The dotCMS administration panel, versions 3.7.1 and earlier, "Push Publishing" feature in Enterprise Pro is vulnerable to path traversal. When "Bundle" tar.gz archives uploaded to the Push Publishing feature are decompressed, the filenames of its contents are not properly checked, allowing for writing files to arbitrary directories on the file system. These archives may be uploaded directly via the administrator panel, or using the CSRF vulnerability (CVE-2017-3187). An unauthenticated remote attacker may perform actions with the dotCMS administrator panel with the same permissions of a victim user or execute arbitrary system commands with the permissions of the user running the dotCMS application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3188|2024-08-05T14:16:28.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
