<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for PHPGurukul -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/phpgurukul/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for PHPGurukul -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 22:23:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3605|2024-10-15T18:33:35.103Z -- phpgurukul -- online%20shopping%20portal
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3605</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Registration Page. The manipulation leads to improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts. The attack can be launched remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-233467.
In PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Komponente Registration Page. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3605|2024-10-15T18:33:35.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-9326|2024-09-30T19:38:58.076Z -- phpgurukul -- online%20shopping%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9326</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /shopping/admin/index.php of the component Admin Panel. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
In PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /shopping/admin/index.php der Komponente Admin Panel. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-9326|2024-09-30T19:38:58.076Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 08:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8472|2024-09-05T13:28:45.886Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8472</link>
      <description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability, whereby user-controlled input is not sufficiently encrypted. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to retrieve the session details of an authenticated user through multiple parameters in /jobportal/index.php.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8472|2024-09-05T13:28:45.886Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 13:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8464|2024-09-05T13:24:06.728Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8464</link>
      <description>SQL injection vulnerability, by which an attacker could send a specially designed query through JOBREGID parameter in /jobportal/admin/applicants/controller.php, and retrieve all the information stored in it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8464|2024-09-05T13:24:06.728Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:54:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8471|2024-09-05T13:29:09.863Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8471</link>
      <description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability, whereby user-controlled input is not sufficiently encrypted. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to retrieve the session details of an authenticated user through JOBID and USERNAME parameters in /jobportal/process.php.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8471|2024-09-05T13:29:09.863Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 13:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8468|2024-09-05T13:15:13.688Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8468</link>
      <description>SQL injection vulnerability, by which an attacker could send a specially designed query through search parameter in /jobportal/index.php, and retrieve all the information stored in it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8468|2024-09-05T13:15:13.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8473|2024-09-05T13:27:17.329Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8473</link>
      <description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability, whereby user-controlled input is not sufficiently encrypted. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to retrieve the session details of an authenticated user through user_email parameter in /jobportal/admin/login.php.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8473|2024-09-05T13:27:17.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 13:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8466|2024-09-05T13:21:56.302Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8466</link>
      <description>SQL injection vulnerability, by which an attacker could send a specially designed query through CATEGORY parameter in /jobportal/admin/category/controller.php, and retrieve all the information stored in it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8466|2024-09-05T13:21:56.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:54:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8463|2024-09-05T13:25:59.317Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8463</link>
      <description>File upload restriction bypass vulnerability in PHPGurukul Job Portal 1.0, the exploitation of which could allow an authenticated user to execute an RCE via webshell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8463|2024-09-05T13:25:59.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8467|2024-09-05T13:18:18.565Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8467</link>
      <description>SQL injection vulnerability, by which an attacker could send a specially designed query through id parameter in /jobportal/admin/category/index.php, and retrieve all the information stored in it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8467|2024-09-05T13:18:18.565Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8470|2024-09-05T13:12:37.209Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8470</link>
      <description>SQL injection vulnerability, by which an attacker could send a specially designed query through CATEGORY parameter in /jobportal/admin/vacancy/controller.php, and retrieve all the information stored in it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8470|2024-09-05T13:12:37.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8469|2024-09-05T13:13:56.901Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8469</link>
      <description>SQL injection vulnerability, by which an attacker could send a specially designed query through id parameter in /jobportal/admin/employee/index.php, and retrieve all the information stored in it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8469|2024-09-05T13:13:56.901Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8465|2024-09-05T13:22:57.789Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8465</link>
      <description>SQL injection vulnerability, by which an attacker could send a specially designed query through user_id parameter in /jobportal/admin/user/controller.php, and retrieve all the information stored in it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8465|2024-09-05T13:22:57.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4294|2024-08-01T20:33:53.078Z -- phpgurukul -- doctor%20appointment%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4294</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /doctor/view-appointment-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to improper control of resource identifiers. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-262226 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /doctor/view-appointment-detail.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments editid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper control of resource identifiers-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4294|2024-08-01T20:33:53.078Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 22:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4293|2024-08-01T20:33:53.191Z -- phpgurukul -- doctor%20appointment%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file appointment-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-262225 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei appointment-bwdates-reports-details.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments fromdate/todate mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4293|2024-08-01T20:33:53.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 21:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5361|2024-07-18T18:40:13.455Z -- phpgurukul -- zoo%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/normal-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266273 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /admin/normal-bwdates-reports-details.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments fromdate mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5361|2024-07-18T18:40:13.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5135|2024-07-18T18:30:35.386Z -- phpgurukul -- directory%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5135</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Directory Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-265211.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Directory Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /admin/index.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5135|2024-07-18T18:30:35.386Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 08:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5358|2024-06-04T18:02:44.330Z -- phpgurukul -- zoo%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5358</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/normal-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266270 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /admin/normal-search.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments searchdata mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5358|2024-06-04T18:02:44.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 09:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5135|2024-05-20T08:31:03.784Z -- phpgurukul -- directory%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5135</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Directory Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-265211.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Directory Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /admin/index.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5135|2024-05-20T08:31:03.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 08:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5359|2024-06-04T18:02:23.883Z -- phpgurukul -- zoo%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5359</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/foreigner-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266271.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /admin/foreigner-search.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments searchdata mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5359|2024-06-04T18:02:23.883Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 10:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5066|2024-05-17T20:00:06.464Z -- phpgurukul -- online%20course%20registration%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5066</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /pincode-verification.php. The manipulation of the argument pincode leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-264925 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /pincode-verification.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments pincode mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5066|2024-05-17T20:00:06.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5360|2024-05-26T10:31:07.466Z -- phpgurukul -- zoo%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5360</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/foreigner-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266272.
In PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /admin/foreigner-bwdates-reports-details.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments fromdate mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5360|2024-05-26T10:31:07.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 10:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5136|2024-06-04T18:02:18.974Z -- phpgurukul -- directory%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5136</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPGurukul Directory Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/search-directory.php.. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-265212.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Directory Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /admin/search-directory.php.. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5136|2024-06-04T18:02:18.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 09:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5065|2024-06-04T18:02:18.155Z -- phpgurukul -- online%20course%20registration%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5065</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /onlinecourse/. The manipulation of the argument regno leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-264924.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /onlinecourse/. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments regno mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5065|2024-06-04T18:02:18.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5357|2024-06-07T19:56:04.156Z -- phpgurukul -- zoo%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5357</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266269 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /admin/forgot-password.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments email mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5357|2024-06-07T19:56:04.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 08:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5064|2024-06-04T18:02:06.755Z -- phpgurukul -- online%20course%20registration%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5064</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file news-details.php. The manipulation of the argument nid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-264923.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei news-details.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments nid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5064|2024-06-04T18:02:06.755Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 18:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5137|2024-06-04T18:02:03.083Z -- phpgurukul -- directory%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5137</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in PHPGurukul Directory Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin-profile.php of the component Searchbar. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-265213 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPGurukul Directory Management System 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /admin/admin-profile.php der Komponente Searchbar. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5137|2024-06-04T18:02:03.083Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 09:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5361|2024-05-26T11:00:07.645Z -- phpgurukul -- zoo%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/normal-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266273 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /admin/normal-bwdates-reports-details.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments fromdate mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5361|2024-05-26T11:00:07.645Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5063|2024-06-04T18:01:51.039Z -- phpgurukul -- online%20course%20registration%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5063</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-264922 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /admin/index.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments username/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5063|2024-06-04T18:01:51.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 18:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4294|2024-06-04T17:56:36.044Z -- phpgurukul -- doctor%20appointment%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4294</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /doctor/view-appointment-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to improper control of resource identifiers. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-262226 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /doctor/view-appointment-detail.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments editid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper control of resource identifiers-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4294|2024-06-04T17:56:36.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 22:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4293|2024-06-04T17:55:05.654Z -- phpgurukul -- doctor%20appointment%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file appointment-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-262225 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei appointment-bwdates-reports-details.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments fromdate/todate mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4293|2024-06-04T17:55:05.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 21:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5136|2024-08-01T21:03:10.643Z -- phpgurukul -- directory%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5136</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPGurukul Directory Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/search-directory.php.. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-265212.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Directory Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /admin/search-directory.php.. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5136|2024-08-01T21:03:10.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 09:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5361|2024-08-01T21:11:12.554Z -- phpgurukul -- zoo%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/normal-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266273 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /admin/normal-bwdates-reports-details.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments fromdate mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5361|2024-08-01T21:11:12.554Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5063|2024-08-01T21:03:10.441Z -- phpgurukul -- online%20course%20registration%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5063</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-264922 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /admin/index.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments username/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5063|2024-08-01T21:03:10.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 18:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5357|2024-08-01T21:11:12.500Z -- phpgurukul -- zoo%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5357</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266269 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /admin/forgot-password.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments email mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5357|2024-08-01T21:11:12.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 08:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5065|2024-08-01T21:03:10.474Z -- phpgurukul -- online%20course%20registration%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5065</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /onlinecourse/. The manipulation of the argument regno leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-264924.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /onlinecourse/. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments regno mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5065|2024-08-01T21:03:10.474Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5137|2024-08-01T21:03:10.745Z -- phpgurukul -- directory%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5137</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in PHPGurukul Directory Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin-profile.php of the component Searchbar. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-265213 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPGurukul Directory Management System 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /admin/admin-profile.php der Komponente Searchbar. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5137|2024-08-01T21:03:10.745Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 09:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5064|2024-08-01T21:03:10.496Z -- phpgurukul -- online%20course%20registration%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5064</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file news-details.php. The manipulation of the argument nid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-264923.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei news-details.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments nid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5064|2024-08-01T21:03:10.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 18:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5066|2024-08-01T21:03:10.629Z -- phpgurukul -- online%20course%20registration%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5066</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /pincode-verification.php. The manipulation of the argument pincode leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-264925 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /pincode-verification.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments pincode mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5066|2024-08-01T21:03:10.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5358|2024-08-01T21:11:12.464Z -- phpgurukul -- zoo%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5358</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/normal-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266270 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /admin/normal-search.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments searchdata mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5358|2024-08-01T21:11:12.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 09:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5360|2024-08-01T21:11:12.498Z -- phpgurukul -- zoo%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5360</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/foreigner-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266272.
In PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /admin/foreigner-bwdates-reports-details.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments fromdate mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5360|2024-08-01T21:11:12.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 10:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5135|2024-08-01T21:03:10.981Z -- phpgurukul -- directory%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5135</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Directory Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-265211.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Directory Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /admin/index.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5135|2024-08-01T21:03:10.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 08:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5359|2024-08-01T21:11:12.443Z -- phpgurukul -- zoo%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5359</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/foreigner-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266271.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /admin/foreigner-search.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments searchdata mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5359|2024-08-01T21:11:12.443Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 10:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5066|2024-08-08T14:37:56.667Z -- phpgurukul -- online%20course%20registration%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5066</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /pincode-verification.php. The manipulation of the argument pincode leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-264925 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /pincode-verification.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments pincode mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5066|2024-08-08T14:37:56.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5360|2024-09-03T15:26:24.956Z -- phpgurukul -- zoo%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5360</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/foreigner-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266272.
In PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /admin/foreigner-bwdates-reports-details.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments fromdate mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5360|2024-09-03T15:26:24.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 10:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8465|2024-09-05T12:54:34.307Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8465</link>
      <description>SQL injection vulnerability, by which an attacker could send a specially designed query through user_id parameter in /jobportal/admin/user/controller.php, and retrieve all the information stored in it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8465|2024-09-05T12:54:34.307Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8469|2024-09-05T12:55:44.603Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8469</link>
      <description>SQL injection vulnerability, by which an attacker could send a specially designed query through id parameter in /jobportal/admin/employee/index.php, and retrieve all the information stored in it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8469|2024-09-05T12:55:44.603Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8470|2024-09-05T12:56:02.047Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8470</link>
      <description>SQL injection vulnerability, by which an attacker could send a specially designed query through CATEGORY parameter in /jobportal/admin/vacancy/controller.php, and retrieve all the information stored in it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8470|2024-09-05T12:56:02.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8467|2024-09-05T12:55:09.389Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8467</link>
      <description>SQL injection vulnerability, by which an attacker could send a specially designed query through id parameter in /jobportal/admin/category/index.php, and retrieve all the information stored in it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8467|2024-09-05T12:55:09.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8463|2024-09-05T12:49:52.618Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8463</link>
      <description>File upload restriction bypass vulnerability in PHPGurukul Job Portal 1.0, the exploitation of which could allow an authenticated user to execute an RCE via webshell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8463|2024-09-05T12:49:52.618Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8466|2024-09-05T12:54:49.671Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8466</link>
      <description>SQL injection vulnerability, by which an attacker could send a specially designed query through CATEGORY parameter in /jobportal/admin/category/controller.php, and retrieve all the information stored in it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8466|2024-09-05T12:54:49.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:54:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8468|2024-09-05T12:55:28.534Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8468</link>
      <description>SQL injection vulnerability, by which an attacker could send a specially designed query through search parameter in /jobportal/index.php, and retrieve all the information stored in it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8468|2024-09-05T12:55:28.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8464|2024-09-05T12:54:15.421Z -- phpgurukul -- job%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8464</link>
      <description>SQL injection vulnerability, by which an attacker could send a specially designed query through JOBREGID parameter in /jobportal/admin/applicants/controller.php, and retrieve all the information stored in it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8464|2024-09-05T12:54:15.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 12:54:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-9326|2024-09-29T08:00:09.100Z -- phpgurukul -- online%20shopping%20portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9326</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /shopping/admin/index.php of the component Admin Panel. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
In PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /shopping/admin/index.php der Komponente Admin Panel. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-9326|2024-09-29T08:00:09.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 08:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
