<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for PHPGurukul -- Bank Locker Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/phpgurukul/bank%20locker%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for PHPGurukul -- Bank Locker Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:25:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0563|2024-08-02T05:17:49.691Z -- phpgurukul -- bank%20locker%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0563</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file add-locker-form.php of the component Assign Locker. The manipulation of the argument ahname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-219717 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei add-locker-form.php der Komponente Assign Locker. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments ahname mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0563|2024-08-02T05:17:49.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 22:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0562|2024-08-02T05:17:49.900Z -- phpgurukul -- bank%20locker%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0562</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-219716.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei index.php der Komponente Login. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0562|2024-08-02T05:17:49.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 22:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1964|2024-08-02T06:05:27.069Z -- phpgurukul -- bank%20locker%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1964</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file recovery.php of the component Password Reset. The manipulation of the argument uname/mobile leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-225360.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei recovery.php der Komponente Password Reset. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments uname/mobile mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1964|2024-08-02T06:05:27.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 08:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1963|2024-08-02T06:05:27.077Z -- phpgurukul -- bank%20locker%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1963</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file index.php of the component Search. The manipulation of the argument searchinput leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-225359.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei index.php der Komponente Search. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments searchinput mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1963|2024-08-02T06:05:27.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 08:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
