<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for PHPGurukul -- Boat Booking System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/phpgurukul/boat%20booking%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for PHPGurukul -- Boat Booking System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 19:20:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10153|2024-10-19T18:00:09.081Z -- phpgurukul -- boat%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10153</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file book-boat.php?bid=1 of the component Book a Boat Page. The manipulation of the argument nopeople leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
In PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei book-boat.php?bid=1 der Komponente Book a Boat Page. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments nopeople mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-10153|2024-10-19T18:00:09.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 18:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10154|2024-10-19T18:31:05.394Z -- phpgurukul -- boat%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10154</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file status.php of the component Check Booking Status Page. The manipulation of the argument emailid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei status.php der Komponente Check Booking Status Page. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments emailid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-10154|2024-10-19T18:31:05.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 18:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
