<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for PHPGurukul -- Boat Booking System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/phpgurukul/boat%20booking%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for PHPGurukul -- Boat Booking System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 16:24:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10156|2024-10-21T15:35:26.016Z -- phpgurukul -- boat%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10156</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/index.php of the component Sign In Page. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
In PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /admin/index.php der Komponente Sign In Page. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-10156|2024-10-21T15:35:26.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 21:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10191|2024-10-20T05:31:05.194Z -- phpgurukul -- boat%20booking%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10191</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/book-details.php of the component Booking Details Page. The manipulation of the argument Official Remark leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 gefunden. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /admin/book-details.php der Komponente Booking Details Page. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments Official Remark mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-10191|2024-10-20T05:31:05.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 05:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10158|2024-10-19T23:00:07.132Z -- phpgurukul -- boat%20booking%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10158</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0. Affected is the function session_start. The manipulation leads to session fixiation. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion session_start. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine session fixiation-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-10158|2024-10-19T23:00:07.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 23:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10157|2024-10-19T22:31:05.359Z -- phpgurukul -- boat%20booking%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10157</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/password-recovery.php of the component Reset Your Password Page. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /admin/password-recovery.php der Komponente Reset Your Password Page. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-10157|2024-10-19T22:31:05.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 22:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10153|2024-10-19T18:00:09.081Z -- phpgurukul -- boat%20booking%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10153</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file book-boat.php?bid=1 of the component Book a Boat Page. The manipulation of the argument nopeople leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
In PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei book-boat.php?bid=1 der Komponente Book a Boat Page. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments nopeople mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-10153|2024-10-19T18:00:09.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 18:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10154|2024-10-19T18:31:05.394Z -- phpgurukul -- boat%20booking%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10154</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file status.php of the component Check Booking Status Page. The manipulation of the argument emailid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei status.php der Komponente Check Booking Status Page. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments emailid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-10154|2024-10-19T18:31:05.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 18:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10155|2024-10-19T20:31:05.591Z -- phpgurukul -- boat%20booking%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10155</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file book-boat.php?bid=1 of the component Book a Boat Page. The manipulation of the argument phone_number leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei book-boat.php?bid=1 der Komponente Book a Boat Page. Dank Manipulation des Arguments phone_number mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-10155|2024-10-19T20:31:05.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 20:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10156|2024-10-19T21:00:08.643Z -- phpgurukul -- boat%20booking%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10156</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/index.php of the component Sign In Page. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
In PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /admin/index.php der Komponente Sign In Page. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-10156|2024-10-19T21:00:08.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 21:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10161|2024-10-20T00:31:05.138Z -- phpgurukul -- boat%20booking%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10161</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file change-image.php of the component Update Boat Image Page. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 gefunden. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei change-image.php der Komponente Update Boat Image Page. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments image mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-10161|2024-10-20T00:31:05.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 00:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10162|2024-10-20T01:00:08.694Z -- phpgurukul -- boat%20booking%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10162</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit-subadmin.php of the component Edit Subdomain Details Page. The manipulation of the argument sadminusername/fullname/emailid/mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "mobilenumber" to be affected. But it must be assumed that other parameters are affected as well.
In PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /admin/edit-subadmin.php der Komponente Edit Subdomain Details Page. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments sadminusername/fullname/emailid/mobilenumber mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-10162|2024-10-20T01:00:08.694Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 01:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10155|2024-10-21T13:50:50.542Z -- phpgurukul -- boat%20booking%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10155</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file book-boat.php?bid=1 of the component Book a Boat Page. The manipulation of the argument phone_number leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei book-boat.php?bid=1 der Komponente Book a Boat Page. Dank Manipulation des Arguments phone_number mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-10155|2024-10-21T13:50:50.542Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 20:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10154|2024-10-21T13:51:58.477Z -- phpgurukul -- boat%20booking%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10154</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file status.php of the component Check Booking Status Page. The manipulation of the argument emailid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei status.php der Komponente Check Booking Status Page. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments emailid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-10154|2024-10-21T13:51:58.477Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 18:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10153|2024-10-21T13:52:48.825Z -- phpgurukul -- boat%20booking%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10153</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file book-boat.php?bid=1 of the component Book a Boat Page. The manipulation of the argument nopeople leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
In PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei book-boat.php?bid=1 der Komponente Book a Boat Page. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments nopeople mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-10153|2024-10-21T13:52:48.825Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 18:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
