<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for PHPGurukul -- BP Monitoring Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/phpgurukul/bp%20monitoring%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for PHPGurukul -- BP Monitoring Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:19:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1950|2024-08-02T06:05:27.090Z -- phpgurukul -- bp%20monitoring%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1950</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul BP Monitoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file password-recovery.php of the component Password Recovery. The manipulation of the argument emailid/contactno leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-225337 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPGurukul BP Monitoring Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei password-recovery.php der Komponente Password Recovery. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments emailid/contactno mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1950|2024-08-02T06:05:27.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 07:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1909|2024-08-02T06:05:26.850Z -- phpgurukul -- bp%20monitoring%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1909</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul BP Monitoring Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file profile.php of the component User Profile Update Handler. The manipulation of the argument name/mobno leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-225318 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul BP Monitoring Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei profile.php der Komponente User Profile Update Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments name/mobno mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1909|2024-08-02T06:05:26.850Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1948|2024-08-02T06:05:27.088Z -- phpgurukul -- bp%20monitoring%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1948</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in PHPGurukul BP Monitoring Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file add-family-member.php of the component Add New Family Member Handler. The manipulation of the argument Member Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-225335.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul BP Monitoring Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei add-family-member.php der Komponente Add New Family Member Handler. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments Member Name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1948|2024-08-02T06:05:27.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 06:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1949|2024-08-02T06:05:27.081Z -- phpgurukul -- bp%20monitoring%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1949</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul BP Monitoring Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file change-password.php of the component Change Password Handler. The manipulation of the argument password leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-225336.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul BP Monitoring Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei change-password.php der Komponente Change Password Handler. Dank Manipulation des Arguments password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1949|2024-08-02T06:05:27.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 07:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
