<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for PHPGurukul -- Hospital Management System</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/phpgurukul/hospital%20management%20system.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for PHPGurukul -- Hospital Management System</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-0361|2024-01-10T02:00:05.367Z -- PHPGurukul -- Hospital Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0361</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin/contact.php. The manipulation of the argument mobnum leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250128.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei admin/contact.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments mobnum mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0361|2024-01-10T02:00:05.367Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0286|2024-01-07T17:31:04.014Z -- PHPGurukul -- Hospital Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0286</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file index.php#contact_us of the component Contact Form. The manipulation of the argument Name/Email/Message leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249843.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 1.0 gefunden. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei index.php#contact_us der Komponente Contact Form. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments Name/Email/Message mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0286|2024-01-07T17:31:04.014Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0360|2024-01-10T01:31:05.270Z -- PHPGurukul -- Hospital Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0360</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/edit-doctor-specialization.php. The manipulation of the argument doctorspecilization leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250127.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei admin/edit-doctor-specialization.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments doctorspecilization mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0360|2024-01-10T01:31:05.270Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 01:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0363|2024-01-10T02:31:03.318Z -- PHPGurukul -- Hospital Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0363</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/patient-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250130 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei admin/patient-search.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments searchdata mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0363|2024-01-10T02:31:03.318Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 02:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0362|2024-01-10T02:00:06.459Z -- PHPGurukul -- Hospital Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0362</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/change-password.php. The manipulation of the argument cpass leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250129 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei admin/change-password.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments cpass mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0362|2024-01-10T02:00:06.459Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 02:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0364|2024-01-10T03:00:05.400Z -- PHPGurukul -- Hospital Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0364</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file admin/query-details.php. The manipulation of the argument adminremark leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250131.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 1.0 gefunden. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei admin/query-details.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments adminremark mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0364|2024-01-10T03:00:05.400Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>