<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for PHPGurukul -- Online Course Registration System</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/phpgurukul/online%20course%20registration%20system.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for PHPGurukul -- Online Course Registration System</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-5066|2024-05-17T20:00:06.464Z -- PHPGurukul -- Online Course Registration System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5066</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /pincode-verification.php. The manipulation of the argument pincode leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-264925 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /pincode-verification.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments pincode mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5066|2024-05-17T20:00:06.464Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5065|2024-05-17T20:00:04.992Z -- PHPGurukul -- Online Course Registration System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5065</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /onlinecourse/. The manipulation of the argument regno leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-264924.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /onlinecourse/. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments regno mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5065|2024-05-17T20:00:04.992Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5064|2024-05-17T18:31:06.286Z -- PHPGurukul -- Online Course Registration System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5064</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file news-details.php. The manipulation of the argument nid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-264923.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei news-details.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments nid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5064|2024-05-17T18:31:06.286Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 18:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5063|2024-05-17T18:31:04.690Z -- PHPGurukul -- Online Course Registration System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5063</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-264922 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPGurukul Online Course Registration System 3.1 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /admin/index.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments username/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5063|2024-05-17T18:31:04.690Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 18:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>