<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for PHPGurukul -- Restaurant Table Booking System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/phpgurukul/restaurant%20table%20booking%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for PHPGurukul -- Restaurant Table Booking System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:25:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6074|2024-08-02T08:21:17.250Z -- phpgurukul -- restaurant%20table%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6074</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file check-status.php of the component Booking Reservation Handler. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244943.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei check-status.php der Komponente Booking Reservation Handler. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6074|2024-08-02T08:21:17.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 14:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6075|2024-08-02T08:21:17.315Z -- phpgurukul -- restaurant%20table%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6075</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file index.php of the component Reservation Request Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244944.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei index.php der Komponente Reservation Request Handler. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6075|2024-08-02T08:21:17.315Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6076|2024-08-02T08:21:17.386Z -- phpgurukul -- restaurant%20table%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6076</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file booking-details.php of the component Reservation Status Handler. The manipulation of the argument bid leads to information disclosure. The attack can be launched remotely. The identifier VDB-244945 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei booking-details.php der Komponente Reservation Status Handler. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments bid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6076|2024-08-02T08:21:17.386Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7100|2024-08-02T08:50:08.228Z -- phpgurukul -- restaurant%20table%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7100</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/bwdates-report-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fdate leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248952.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /admin/bwdates-report-details.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments fdate mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7100|2024-08-02T08:50:08.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
