<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for PHPGurukul -- Teacher Subject Allocation Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/phpgurukul/teacher%20subject%20allocation%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for PHPGurukul -- Teacher Subject Allocation Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 20:21:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6766|2024-10-08T14:26:33.964Z -- phpgurukul -- teacher%20subject%20allocation%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6766</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/course.php of the component Delete Course Handler. The manipulation of the argument delid leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-247896.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /admin/course.php der Komponente Delete Course Handler. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments delid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross-site request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6766|2024-10-08T14:26:33.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 17:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
