<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for PHPGurukul -- Teacher Subject Allocation Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/phpgurukul/teacher%20subject%20allocation%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for PHPGurukul -- Teacher Subject Allocation Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:24:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6653|2024-08-02T08:35:14.888Z -- phpgurukul -- teacher%20subject%20allocation%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6653</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/subject.php of the component Create a new Subject. The manipulation of the argument cid leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-247346 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /admin/subject.php der Komponente Create a new Subject. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments cid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross-site request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6653|2024-08-02T08:35:14.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 12:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6649|2024-08-02T08:35:14.915Z -- phpgurukul -- teacher%20subject%20allocation%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6649</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata with the input &lt;script&gt;alert(5)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-247342 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei index.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments searchdata mit der Eingabe &lt;script&gt;alert(5)&lt;/script&gt; mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6649|2024-08-02T08:35:14.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 10:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6766|2024-08-02T08:42:07.825Z -- phpgurukul -- teacher%20subject%20allocation%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6766</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/course.php of the component Delete Course Handler. The manipulation of the argument delid leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-247896.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /admin/course.php der Komponente Delete Course Handler. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments delid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross-site request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6766|2024-08-02T08:42:07.825Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 17:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
