<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for PHPGurukul -- Zoo Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/phpgurukul/zoo%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for PHPGurukul -- Zoo Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5358|2024-06-04T18:02:44.330Z -- phpgurukul -- zoo%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5358</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/normal-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266270 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /admin/normal-search.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments searchdata mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5358|2024-06-04T18:02:44.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 09:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5359|2024-06-04T18:02:23.883Z -- phpgurukul -- zoo%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5359</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/foreigner-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266271.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /admin/foreigner-search.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments searchdata mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5359|2024-06-04T18:02:23.883Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 10:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5360|2024-05-26T10:31:07.466Z -- phpgurukul -- zoo%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5360</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/foreigner-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266272.
In PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /admin/foreigner-bwdates-reports-details.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments fromdate mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5360|2024-05-26T10:31:07.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 10:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5357|2024-06-07T19:56:04.156Z -- phpgurukul -- zoo%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5357</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266269 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /admin/forgot-password.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments email mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5357|2024-06-07T19:56:04.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 08:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5361|2024-05-26T11:00:07.645Z -- phpgurukul -- zoo%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/normal-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266273 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /admin/normal-bwdates-reports-details.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments fromdate mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5361|2024-05-26T11:00:07.645Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
