<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Netentsec -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/netentsec/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Netentsec -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 21:21:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2644|2024-06-05T20:00:21.067Z -- netentsec -- ns-asg%20application%20security%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2644</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /protocol/firewall/addfirewall.php. The manipulation of the argument FireWallTableArray leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257282 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3 ausgemacht. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /protocol/firewall/addfirewall.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments FireWallTableArray mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2644|2024-06-05T20:00:21.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 22:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2021|2024-02-29T23:31:04.361Z -- netentsec -- ns-asg%20application%20security%20gateway</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2021</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/list_localuser.php. The manipulation of the argument ResId leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255300. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Netentsec NS-ASG Application Security Gateway 6.3 ausgemacht. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /admin/list_localuser.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments ResId mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2021|2024-02-29T23:31:04.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 23:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
