<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Guangdong -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/guangdong/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Guangdong -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:23:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3035|2024-08-02T06:41:04.141Z -- guangdong -- pythagorean%20oa%20office%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3035</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Guangdong Pythagorean OA Office System up to 4.50.31 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Schedule Handler. The manipulation of the argument description leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-230467.
In Guangdong Pythagorean OA Office System bis 4.50.31 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Komponente Schedule Handler. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments description mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3035|2024-08-02T06:41:04.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 13:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3029|2024-08-02T06:41:04.129Z -- guangdong -- pythagorean%20oa%20office%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3029</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Guangdong Pythagorean OA Office System up to 4.50.31 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /note/index/delete. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-230458 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Guangdong Pythagorean OA Office System bis 4.50.31 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /note/index/delete. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross-site request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3029|2024-08-02T06:41:04.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 06:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
