<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for nasirahmed -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nasirahmed/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for nasirahmed -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-32134|2024-04-15T07:32:47.635Z -- Nasirahmed -- Forms to Zapier, Integromat, IFTTT, Workato, Automate.io, elastic.io, Built.io, APIANT, Webhook
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32134</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Nasirahmed Forms to Zapier, Integromat, IFTTT, Workato, Automate.Io, elastic.Io, Built.Io, APIANT, Webhook.This issue affects Forms to Zapier, Integromat, IFTTT, Workato, Automate.Io, elastic.Io, Built.Io, APIANT, Webhook: from n/a through 1.1.12.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32134|2024-04-15T07:32:47.635Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 07:32:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2387|2024-03-20T01:57:55.902Z -- nasirahmed -- Advanced Form Integration – Connect WooCommerce and Contact Form 7 to Google Sheets and other platforms
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2387</link><description>The Advanced Form Integration – Connect WooCommerce and Contact Form 7 to Google Sheets and other platforms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘integration_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.82.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries and subsequently inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2387|2024-03-20T01:57:55.902Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 01:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>