<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Visualware -- MyConnection Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/visualware/myconnection%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Visualware -- MyConnection Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42034|2024-06-04T17:25:37.203Z -- visualware -- myconnection%20server
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42034</link>
      <description>Visualware MyConnection Server doRTAAccessCTConfig Cross-Site Scripting Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Visualware MyConnection Server. Minimal user interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the doRTAAccessCTConfig method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can lead to the injection of an arbitrary script. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-21613.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42034|2024-06-04T17:25:37.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42035|2024-06-05T19:35:26.543Z -- visualware -- myconnection%20server
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42035</link>
      <description>Visualware MyConnection Server doIForward XML External Entity Processing Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Visualware MyConnection Server. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the doIForward method. Due to the improper restriction of XML External Entity (XXE) references, a crafted document specifying a URI causes the XML parser to access the URI and embed the contents back into the XML document for further processing. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21774.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42035|2024-06-05T19:35:26.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42032|2024-06-04T17:25:29.232Z -- visualware -- myconnection%20server
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42032</link>
      <description>Visualware MyConnection Server doRTAAccessUPass Exposed Dangerous Method Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Visualware MyConnection Server. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the doRTAAccessUPass method. The issue results from an exposed dangerous method. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of the application. Was ZDI-CAN-21611.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42032|2024-06-04T17:25:29.232Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42033|2024-06-04T17:25:20.776Z -- visualware -- myconnection%20server
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42033</link>
      <description>Visualware MyConnection Server doPostUploadfiles Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Visualware MyConnection Server. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the doPostUploadfiles method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21612.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42033|2024-06-04T17:25:20.776Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
