<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-20361|2024-05-22T16:54:00.334Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Management Center
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20361</link><description>A vulnerability in the Object Groups for Access Control Lists (ACLs) feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured access controls on managed devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect deployment of the Object Groups for ACLs feature from Cisco FMC Software to managed FTD devices in high-availability setups. After an affected device is rebooted following Object Groups for ACLs deployment, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access controls and successfully send traffic to devices that are expected to be protected by the affected device.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20361|2024-05-22T16:54:00.334Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20336|2024-03-06T17:07:15.946Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Business Wireless Access Point Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20336</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based user interface of Cisco Small Business 100, 300, and 500 Series Wireless APs could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform buffer overflow attacks against an affected device. In order to exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative credentials for the device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the web-based management interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code as the root user on the underlying operating system.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20336|2024-03-06T17:07:15.946Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 16:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20320|2024-03-13T16:41:52.488Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XR Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20320</link><description>A vulnerability in the SSH client feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco 8000 Series Routers and Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) 540 Series and 5700 Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device. &#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are included with the SSH client CLI command. An attacker with low-privileged access to an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by issuing a crafted SSH client command to the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root on the affected device.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20320|2024-03-13T16:41:52.488Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-03-27T17:03:54.505Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20265</link><description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-03-27T17:03:54.505Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20357|2024-05-01T16:36:53.907Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IP Phones with Multiplatform Firmware
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20357</link><description>A vulnerability in the XML service of Cisco IP Phone firmware could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to initiate phone calls on an affected device.  &#13;
&#13; This vulnerability exists because bounds-checking does not occur while parsing XML requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted XML request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to initiate calls or play sounds on the device.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20357|2024-05-01T16:36:53.907Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20253|2024-02-02T15:42:33.881Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Unified Contact Center Enterprise
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20253</link><description>A vulnerability in multiple Cisco Unified Communications and Contact Center Solutions products could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to the improper processing of user-provided data that is being read into memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted message to a listening port of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of the web services user. With access to the underlying operating system, the attacker could also establish root access on the affected device.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20253|2024-02-02T15:42:33.881Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 17:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-03-27T16:49:03.113Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20316</link><description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-03-27T16:49:03.113Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20290|2024-02-07T16:16:00.975Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Secure Endpoint
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20290</link><description>A vulnerability in the OLE2 file format parser of ClamAV could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an incorrect check for end-of-string values during scanning, which may result in a heap buffer over-read. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted file containing OLE2 content to be scanned by ClamAV on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ClamAV scanning process to terminate, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected software and consuming available system resources.&#13;
&#13; For a description of this vulnerability, see the ClamAV blog .</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20290|2024-02-07T16:16:00.975Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20394|2024-05-15T17:21:46.986Z -- Cisco -- Cisco AppDynamics
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20394</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco AppDynamics Network Visibility Agent could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the inability to handle unexpected input. An attacker who has local device access could exploit this vulnerability by sending an HTTP request to the targeted service. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition by stopping the Network Agent Service on the local device.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20394|2024-05-15T17:21:46.986Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20287|2024-02-02T15:42:45.536Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Business Wireless Access Point Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20287</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of the Cisco WAP371 Wireless-AC/N Dual Radio Access Point (AP) with Single Point Setup could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform command injection attacks against an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to the web-based management interface of an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges on the device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative credentials for the device.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20287|2024-02-02T15:42:45.536Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 16:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20291|2024-02-28T16:16:33.950Z -- Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20291</link><description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) programming for port channel subinterfaces of Cisco Nexus 3000 and 9000 Series Switches in standalone NX-OS mode could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to send traffic that should be blocked through an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect hardware programming that occurs when configuration changes are made to port channel member ports. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access network resources that should be protected by an ACL that was applied on port channel subinterfaces.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20291|2024-02-28T16:16:33.950Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20383|2024-05-15T18:13:46.829Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Secure Email and Web Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20383</link><description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Crosswork NSO CLI and the ConfD CLI could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to elevate privileges to root on the underlying operating system.&#13;
&#13; The vulnerability is due to an incorrect privilege assignment when specific CLI commands are used. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by executing an affected CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root on the underlying operating system.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20383|2024-05-15T18:13:46.829Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20252|2024-02-07T16:15:06.066Z -- Cisco -- Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) Expressway
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20252</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks that perform arbitrary actions on an affected device. &#13;
&#13; Note: "Cisco Expressway Series" refers to Cisco Expressway Control (Expressway-C) devices and Cisco Expressway Edge (Expressway-E) devices.&#13;
&#13; For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details ["#details"] section of this advisory.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20252|2024-02-07T16:15:06.066Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20356|2024-04-24T19:40:33.312Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System (Standalone)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20356</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with Administrator-level privileges to perform command injection attacks on an affected system and elevate their privileges to root. This vulnerability is due to insufficient user input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted commands to the web-based management interface of the affected software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate their privileges to root.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20356|2024-04-24T19:40:33.312Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20301|2024-03-06T16:28:22.087Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Duo
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20301</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Duo Authentication for Windows Logon and RDP could allow an authenticated, physical attacker to bypass secondary authentication and access an affected Windows device. &#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a failure to invalidate locally created trusted sessions after a reboot of the affected device. An attacker with primary user credentials could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to authenticate to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access the affected device without valid permissions.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20301|2024-03-06T16:28:22.087Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20376|2024-05-01T16:43:15.553Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IP Phones with Multiplatform Firmware
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20376</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco IP Phone firmware could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.  &#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the web-based management interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20376|2024-05-01T16:43:15.553Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20321|2024-02-28T16:14:28.992Z -- Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20321</link><description>A vulnerability in the External Border Gateway Protocol (eBGP) implementation of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability exists because eBGP traffic is mapped to a shared hardware rate-limiter queue. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending large amounts of network traffic with certain characteristics through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause eBGP neighbor sessions to be dropped, leading to a DoS condition in the network.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20321|2024-02-28T16:14:28.992Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20337|2024-03-06T16:30:02.285Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Secure Client
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20337</link><description>A vulnerability in the SAML authentication process of Cisco Secure Client could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a carriage return line feed (CRLF) injection attack against a user. &#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link while establishing a VPN session. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the browser or access sensitive, browser-based information, including a valid SAML token. The attacker could then use the token to establish a remote access VPN session with the privileges of the affected user. Individual hosts and services behind the VPN headend would still need additional credentials for successful access.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20337|2024-03-06T16:30:02.285Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 16:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20272|2024-02-02T15:42:44.885Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Unity Connection
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20272</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unity Connection could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected system and execute commands on the underlying operating system. This vulnerability is due to a lack of authentication in a specific API and improper validation of user-supplied data. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20272|2024-02-02T15:42:44.885Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 16:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20360|2024-05-22T17:46:25.091Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Management Center
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20360</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not adequately validate user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain any data from the database, execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system, and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least Read Only user credentials.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20360|2024-05-22T17:46:25.091Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20306|2024-03-27T16:58:22.583Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20306</link><description>A vulnerability in the Unified Threat Defense (UTD) configuration CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying host operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have level 15 privileges on the affected device. &#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20306|2024-03-27T16:58:22.583Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20347|2024-04-03T16:40:55.449Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Emergency Responder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20347</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Emergency Responder could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a CSRF attack, which could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient protections for the web UI of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privilege level of the affected user, such as deleting users from the device.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20347|2024-04-03T16:40:55.449Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:27:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20255|2024-02-07T16:15:36.068Z -- Cisco -- Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) Expressway
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20255</link><description>A vulnerability in the SOAP API of Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the REST API to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected system to reload.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20255|2024-02-07T16:15:36.068Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-04-03T16:36:06.520Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20310</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-04-03T16:36:06.520Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20392|2024-05-15T17:22:39.980Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Secure Email
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20392</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management API of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Secure Email Gateway could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct an HTTP response splitting attack. &#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of some parameters that are passed to the web-based management API of the affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of an affected interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks, resulting in the execution of arbitrary script code in the browser of the targeted user, or could allow the attacker to access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20392|2024-05-15T17:22:39.980Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:22:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20259|2024-03-27T16:53:53.073Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20259</link><description>A vulnerability in the DHCP snooping feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a crafted IPv4 DHCP request packet being mishandled when endpoint analytics are enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCP request through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.&#13;
&#13; Note: The attack vector is listed as network because a DHCP relay anywhere on the network could allow exploits from networks other than the adjacent one.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20259|2024-03-27T16:53:53.073Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:53:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20367|2024-04-03T16:22:22.902Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Enterprise Chat and Email
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20367</link><description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco Enterprise Chat and Email (ECE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web UI does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid agent credentials.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20367|2024-04-03T16:22:22.902Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20326|2024-05-16T14:08:18.634Z -- Cisco -- Cisco ConfD
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20326</link><description>A vulnerability in the ConfD CLI and the Cisco  Crosswork Network Services Orchestrator CLI could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to read and write arbitrary files as root on the underlying operating system.


This vulnerability is due to improper authorization enforcement when specific CLI commands are used. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by executing an affected CLI command with crafted arguments. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read or write arbitrary files on the underlying operating system with the privileges of the root user.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20326|2024-05-16T14:08:18.634Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20263|2024-02-02T15:42:34.210Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Small Business Smart and Managed Switches
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20263</link><description>A vulnerability with the access control list (ACL) management within a stacked switch configuration of Cisco Business 250 Series Smart Switches and Business 350 Series Managed Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass protection offered by a configured ACL on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of ACLs on a stacked configuration when either the primary or backup switches experience a full stack reload or power cycle. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACLs, causing traffic to be dropped or forwarded in an unexpected manner. The attacker does not have control over the conditions that result in the device being in the vulnerable state. Note: In the vulnerable state, the ACL would be correctly applied on the primary devices but could be incorrectly applied to the backup devices.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20263|2024-02-02T15:42:34.210Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 17:27:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20327|2024-03-13T16:40:38.336Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XR Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20327</link><description>A vulnerability in the PPP over Ethernet (PPPoE) termination feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco ASR 9000 Series Aggregation Services Routers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the improper handling of malformed PPPoE packets that are received on a router that is running Broadband Network Gateway (BNG) functionality with PPPoE termination on a Lightspeed-based or Lightspeed-Plus-based line card. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted PPPoE packet to an affected line card interface that does not terminate PPPoE. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a DoS condition for PPPoE traffic across the router.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20327|2024-03-13T16:40:38.336Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20262|2024-03-13T16:46:45.467Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XR Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20262</link><description>A vulnerability in the Secure Copy Protocol (SCP) and SFTP feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to create or overwrite files in a system directory, which could lead to a denial of service (DoS) condition. The attacker would require valid user credentials to perform this attack.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper validation of SCP and SFTP CLI input parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and issuing SCP or SFTP CLI commands with specific parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to impact the functionality of the device, which could lead to a DoS condition. The device may need to be manually rebooted to recover.&#13;
&#13; Note: This vulnerability is exploitable only when a local user invokes SCP or SFTP commands at the Cisco IOS XR CLI. A local user with administrative privileges could exploit this vulnerability remotely.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20262|2024-03-13T16:46:45.467Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20366|2024-05-15T17:25:09.258Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Network Services Orchestrator
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20366</link><description>A vulnerability in the Tail-f High Availability Cluster Communications (HCC) function pack of Cisco Crosswork Network Services Orchestrator (NSO) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability exists because a user-controlled search path is used to locate executable files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by configuring the application in a way that causes a malicious file to be executed. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device as the root user. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid credentials on an affected device.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20366|2024-05-15T17:25:09.258Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20389|2024-05-16T14:08:21.745Z -- Cisco -- Cisco ConfD
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20389</link><description>A vulnerability in the ConfD CLI and the Cisco  Crosswork Network Services Orchestrator CLI could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to read and write arbitrary files as root on the underlying operating system.


This vulnerability is due to improper authorization enforcement when specific CLI commands are used. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by executing an affected CLI command with crafted arguments. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read or write arbitrary files on the underlying operating system with the privileges of the root user.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20389|2024-05-16T14:08:21.745Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20258|2024-05-15T17:32:16.125Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Secure Email
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20258</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Secure Email and Web Manager and Secure Email Gateway could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of an affected interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20258|2024-05-15T17:32:16.125Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20281|2024-04-03T16:20:04.470Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Data Center Network Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20281</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Nexus Dashboard and Cisco Nexus Dashboard hosted services could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privilege level of the affected user. If the affected user has administrative privileges, these actions could include modifying the system configuration and creating new privileged accounts.&#13;
&#13; Note: There are internal security mechanisms in place that limit the scope of this exploit, reducing the Security Impact Rating of this vulnerability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20281|2024-04-03T16:20:04.470Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:20:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20278|2024-03-27T16:59:12.963Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20278</link><description>A vulnerability in the NETCONF feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input over NETCONF to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges from Administrator to root.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20278|2024-03-27T16:59:12.963Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20254|2024-02-07T16:15:25.666Z -- Cisco -- Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) Expressway
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20254</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks that perform arbitrary actions on an affected device. &#13;
&#13; Note: "Cisco Expressway Series" refers to Cisco Expressway Control (Expressway-C) devices and Cisco Expressway Edge (Expressway-E) devices.&#13;
&#13; For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details ["#details"] section of this advisory.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20254|2024-02-07T16:15:25.666Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20311|2024-03-27T16:50:15.099Z -- Cisco -- IOS
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20311</link><description>A vulnerability in the Locator ID Separation Protocol (LISP) feature of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of LISP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted LISP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.&#13;
&#13; Note: This vulnerability could be exploited over either IPv4 or IPv6 transport.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20311|2024-03-27T16:50:15.099Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20346|2024-03-06T16:33:26.815Z -- Cisco -- Cisco AppDynamics
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20346</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco AppDynamics Controller could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20346|2024-03-06T16:33:26.815Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 16:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20307|2024-03-27T17:23:40.022Z -- Cisco -- IOS
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20307</link><description>A vulnerability in the IKEv1 fragmentation code of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a heap overflow, resulting in an affected device reloading.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability exists because crafted, fragmented IKEv1 packets are not properly reassembled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted UDP packets to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.&#13;
&#13; Note: Only traffic that is directed to the affected system can be used to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability can be triggered by IPv4 and IPv6 traffic.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20307|2024-03-27T17:23:40.022Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20328|2024-03-01T20:48:15.328Z -- Cisco -- ClamAV
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20328</link><description>A vulnerability in the VirusEvent feature of ClamAV could allow a local attacker to inject arbitrary commands with the privileges of the application service account.The vulnerability is due to unsafe handling of file names. A local attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a file name containing command-line sequences. When processed on a system using configuration options for the VirusEvent feature, the attacker could cause the application to execute arbitrary commands.
ClamAV has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.


</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20328|2024-03-01T20:48:15.328Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 20:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20282|2024-04-03T16:20:33.850Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Nexus Dashboard
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20282</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Nexus Dashboard could allow an authenticated, local attacker with valid rescue-user credentials to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient protections for a sensitive access token. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using this token to access resources within the device infrastructure. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to gain root access to the filesystem or hosted containers on an affected device.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20282|2024-04-03T16:20:33.850Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20294|2024-02-28T16:16:56.717Z -- Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20294</link><description>A vulnerability in the Link Layer Discovery Protocol (LLDP) feature of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of specific fields in an LLDP frame. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted LLDP packet to an interface of an affected device and having an authenticated user retrieve LLDP statistics from the affected device through CLI show commands or Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) requests. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the LLDP service to crash and stop running on the affected device. In certain situations, the LLDP crash may result in a reload of the affected device.&#13;
&#13; Note: LLDP is a Layer 2 link protocol. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to be directly connected to an interface of an affected device, either physically or logically (for example, through a Layer 2 Tunnel configured to transport the LLDP protocol).</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20294|2024-02-28T16:16:56.717Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20369|2024-05-15T17:23:34.938Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Network Services Orchestrator
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20369</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Crosswork Network Services Orchestrator (NSO) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to redirect a user to a malicious web page.&#13;
&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation of a parameter in an HTTP request. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to redirect a user to a malicious website.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20369|2024-05-15T17:23:34.938Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20312|2024-03-27T16:56:42.490Z -- Cisco -- IOS
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20312</link><description>A vulnerability in the Intermediate System-to-Intermediate System (IS-IS) protocol of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation when parsing an ingress IS-IS packet. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IS-IS packet to an affected device after forming an adjacency. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.&#13;
&#13; Note: The IS-IS protocol is a routing protocol. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must be Layer 2-adjacent to the affected device and have formed an adjacency.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20312|2024-03-27T16:56:42.490Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:56:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20257|2024-05-15T17:58:59.579Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Secure Email
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20257</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Secure Email Gateway could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.r
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of an affected interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20257|2024-05-15T17:58:59.579Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:58:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20345|2024-03-06T16:33:48.826Z -- Cisco -- Cisco AppDynamics
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20345</link><description>A vulnerability in the file upload functionality of Cisco AppDynamics Controller could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct directory traversal attacks on an affected device. &#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access sensitive data on an affected device.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20345|2024-03-06T16:33:48.826Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 16:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20353|2024-04-24T18:15:57.646Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20353</link><description>A vulnerability in the management and VPN web servers for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incomplete error checking when parsing an HTTP header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to a targeted web server on a device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition when the device reloads.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20353|2024-04-24T18:15:57.646Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20261|2024-05-22T16:53:27.346Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20261</link><description>A vulnerability in the file policy feature that is used to inspect encrypted archive files of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured file policy to block an encrypted archive file. This vulnerability exists because of a logic error when a specific class of encrypted archive files is inspected. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted, encrypted archive file through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send an encrypted archive file, which could contain malware and should have been blocked and dropped at the Cisco FTD device.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20261|2024-05-22T16:53:27.346Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:53:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20324|2024-03-27T16:55:53.837Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20324</link><description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to access WLAN configuration details including passwords.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper privilege checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the show and show tech wireless CLI commands to access configuration details, including passwords. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access configuration details that they are not authorized to access.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20324|2024-03-27T16:55:53.837Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20277|2024-02-02T15:42:45.235Z -- Cisco -- Cisco ThousandEyes Recorder Application
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20277</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ThousandEyes Enterprise Agent, Virtual Appliance installation type, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a command injection and elevate privileges to root. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input for the web interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP packet to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands and elevate privileges to root.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20277|2024-02-02T15:42:45.235Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 16:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20332|2024-04-03T16:22:02.111Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Identity Services Engine Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20332</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack through an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation for specific HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send arbitrary network requests that are sourced from the affected device. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid Super Admin credentials.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20332|2024-04-03T16:22:02.111Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20308|2024-03-27T17:22:11.592Z -- Cisco -- IOS
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20308</link><description>A vulnerability in the IKEv1 fragmentation code of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a heap underflow, resulting in an affected device reloading.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability exists because crafted, fragmented IKEv1 packets are not properly reassembled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted UDP packets to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.&#13;
&#13; Note: Only traffic that is directed to the affected system can be used to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability can be triggered by IPv4 and IPv6 traffic..</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20308|2024-03-27T17:22:11.592Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:22:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20309|2024-03-27T17:02:19.749Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20309</link><description>A vulnerability in auxiliary asynchronous port (AUX) functions of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause an affected device to reload or stop responding.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific ingress traffic when flow control hardware is enabled on the AUX port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by reverse telnetting to the AUX port and sending specific data after connecting. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reset or stop responding, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20309|2024-03-27T17:02:19.749Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20348|2024-04-03T16:25:38.367Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Data Center Network Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20348</link><description>A vulnerability in the Out-of-Band (OOB) Plug and Play (PnP) feature of Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to read arbitrary files.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an unauthenticated provisioning web server. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability through direct web requests to the provisioning server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read sensitive files in the PnP container that could facilitate further attacks on the PnP infrastructure.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20348|2024-04-03T16:25:38.367Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20276|2024-03-27T16:51:46.937Z -- Cisco -- IOS
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20276</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco IOS Software for Cisco Catalyst 6000 Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of process-switched traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20276|2024-03-27T16:51:46.937Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20333|2024-03-27T16:43:33.371Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Digital Network Architecture Center (DNA Center)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20333</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Catalyst Center, formerly Cisco DNA Center, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to change specific data within the interface on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization enforcement. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to change a specific field within the web-based management interface, even though they should not have access to change that field.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20333|2024-03-27T16:43:33.371Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20325|2024-02-21T16:09:03.422Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Unified Intelligence Center
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20325</link><description>A vulnerability in the Live Data server of Cisco Unified Intelligence Center could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker to read and modify data in a repository that belongs to an internal service on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient access control implementations on cluster configuration CLI requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a cluster configuration CLI request to specific directories on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read and modify data that is handled by an internal service on the affected device.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20325|2024-02-21T16:09:03.422Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:09:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20305|2024-02-02T15:42:45.832Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Unity Connection
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20305</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unity Connection could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20305|2024-02-02T15:42:45.832Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 17:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20352|2024-04-03T16:42:03.852Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Emergency Responder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20352</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Emergency Responder could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a directory traversal attack, which could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient protections for the web UI of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted requests to the web UI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privilege level of the affected user, such as accessing password or log files or uploading and deleting existing files from the system.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20352|2024-04-03T16:42:03.852Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:27:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20344|2024-02-28T16:16:03.042Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System (Managed)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20344</link><description>A vulnerability in system resource management in Cisco UCS 6400 and 6500 Series Fabric Interconnects that are in Intersight Managed Mode (IMM) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the Device Console UI of an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient rate-limiting of TCP connections to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high number of TCP packets to the Device Console UI. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to cause the Device Console UI process to crash, resulting in a DoS condition. A manual reload of the fabric interconnect is needed to restore complete functionality.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20344|2024-02-28T16:16:03.042Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20313|2024-04-24T20:42:10.379Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20313</link><description>A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of OSPF updates that are processed by a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF update to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20313|2024-04-24T20:42:10.379Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20256|2024-05-15T17:56:38.074Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Secure Web Appliance
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20256</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Secure Email and Web Manager and Secure Web Appliance could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.&#13;
&#13;This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of an affected interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20256|2024-05-15T17:56:38.074Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20368|2024-04-03T16:23:02.055Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Identity Services Engine Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20368</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on the affected device with the privileges of the targeted user.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20368|2024-04-03T16:23:02.055Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20295|2024-04-24T19:41:02.339Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System (Standalone)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20295</link><description>A vulnerability in the CLI of the Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have read-only or higher privileges on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20295|2024-04-24T19:41:02.339Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:41:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20283|2024-04-03T16:25:09.906Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Nexus Dashboard
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20283</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Nexus Dashboard could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to learn cluster deployment information on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper access controls on a specific API endpoint. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending queries to the API endpoint. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to access metrics and information about devices in the Nexus Dashboard cluster.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20283|2024-04-03T16:25:09.906Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20391|2024-05-15T17:24:34.138Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Secure Client
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20391</link><description>A vulnerability in the Network Access Manager (NAM) module of Cisco Secure Client could allow an unauthenticated attacker with physical access to an affected device to elevate privileges to SYSTEM.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a lack of authentication on a specific function. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privileges on an affected device.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20391|2024-05-15T17:24:34.138Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20267|2024-02-28T16:15:18.044Z -- Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20267</link><description>A vulnerability with the handling of MPLS traffic for Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the netstack process to unexpectedly restart, which could cause the device to stop processing network traffic or to reload. &#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to lack of proper error checking when processing an ingress MPLS frame. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPv6 packet that is encapsulated within an MPLS frame to an MPLS-enabled interface of the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.&#13;
&#13; Note: The IPv6 packet can be generated multiple hops away from the targeted device and then encapsulated within MPLS. The DoS condition may occur when the NX-OS device processes the packet.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20267|2024-02-28T16:15:18.044Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20322|2024-03-13T16:43:53.196Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XR Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20322</link><description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on Pseudowire interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20322|2024-03-13T16:43:53.196Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:43:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20271|2024-03-27T17:05:27.473Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Aironet Access Point Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20271</link><description>A vulnerability in the IP packet processing of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPv4 packet either to or through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker does not need to be associated with the affected AP. This vulnerability cannot be exploited by sending IPv6 packets.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20271|2024-03-27T17:05:27.473Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:05:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20334|2024-04-03T16:24:49.812Z -- Cisco -- Cisco TelePresence Management Suite (TMS)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20334</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco TelePresence Management Suite (TMS) could allow a low-privileged, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting malicious data in a specific data field in the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20334|2024-04-03T16:24:49.812Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20363|2024-05-22T16:52:53.274Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20363</link><description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort Intrusion Prevention System (IPS) rule engine that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured rules on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to incorrect HTTP packet handling. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured IPS rules and allow uninspected traffic onto the network.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20363|2024-05-22T16:52:53.274Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20318|2024-03-13T16:46:24.113Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XR Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20318</link><description>A vulnerability in the Layer 2 Ethernet services of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the line card network processor to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific Ethernet frames that are received on line cards that have the Layer 2 services feature enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific Ethernet frames through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ingress interface network processor to reset, resulting in a loss of traffic over the interfaces that are supported by the network processor. Multiple resets of the network processor would cause the line card to reset, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20318|2024-03-13T16:46:24.113Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20359|2024-04-24T18:16:49.769Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20359</link><description>A vulnerability in a legacy capability that allowed for the preloading of VPN clients and plug-ins and that has been available in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of a file when it is read from system flash memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by copying a crafted file to the disk0: file system of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected device after the next reload of the device, which could alter system behavior. Because the injected code could persist across device reboots, Cisco has raised the Security Impact Rating (SIR) of this advisory from Medium to High.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20359|2024-04-24T18:16:49.769Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:16:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20292|2024-03-06T16:32:55.529Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Duo
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20292</link><description>A vulnerability in the logging component of Cisco Duo Authentication for Windows Logon and RDP could allow an authenticated, local attacker to view sensitive information in clear text on an affected system. &#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper storage of an unencrypted registry key in certain logs. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the logs on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view sensitive information in clear text.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20292|2024-03-06T16:32:55.529Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 16:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20338|2024-03-06T16:29:33.440Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Secure Client
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20338</link><description>A vulnerability in the ISE Posture (System Scan) module of Cisco Secure Client for Linux could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the use of an uncontrolled search path element. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by copying a malicious library file to a specific directory in the filesystem and persuading an administrator to restart a specific process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device with root privileges.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20338|2024-03-06T16:29:33.440Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 16:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20380|2024-04-18T19:19:21.423Z -- Cisco -- ClamAV
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20380</link><description>A vulnerability in the HTML parser of ClamAV could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&#13;
The vulnerability is due to an issue in the C to Rust foreign function interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted file containing HTML content to be scanned by ClamAV on an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ClamAV scanning process to terminate, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected software.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20380|2024-04-18T19:19:21.423Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 19:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-03-27T16:57:27.974Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20314</link><description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-03-27T16:57:27.974Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20251|2024-02-02T15:42:33.426Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Identity Services Engine Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20251</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface on an affected device. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20251|2024-02-02T15:42:33.426Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 16:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20355|2024-05-22T16:54:35.619Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20355</link><description>A vulnerability in the implementation of SAML 2.0 single sign-on (SSO) for remote access VPN services in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to successfully establish a VPN session on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper separation of authorization domains when using SAML authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using valid credentials to successfully authenticate using their designated connection profile (tunnel group), intercepting the SAML SSO token that is sent back from the Cisco ASA device, and then submitting the same SAML SSO token to a different tunnel group for authentication. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to establish a remote access VPN session using a connection profile that they are not authorized to use and connect to secured networks behind the affected device that they are not authorized to access. For successful exploitation, the attacker must have valid remote access VPN user credentials.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20355|2024-05-22T16:54:35.619Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20302|2024-04-03T16:21:29.900Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Nexus Dashboard Orchestrator
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20302</link><description>A vulnerability in the tenant security implementation of Cisco Nexus Dashboard Orchestrator (NDO) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to modify or delete tenant templates on an affected system. &#13;
 &#13;
This vulnerability is due to improper access controls within tenant security. An attacker who is using a valid user account with write privileges and either a Site Manager or Tenant Manager role could exploit this vulnerability. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify or delete tenant templates under non-associated tenants, which could disrupt network traffic.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20302|2024-04-03T16:21:29.900Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:21:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20303|2024-03-27T17:00:37.075Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20303</link><description>A vulnerability in the multicast DNS (mDNS) gateway feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Wireless LAN Controllers (WLCs) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper management of mDNS client entries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the wireless network and sending a continuous stream of specific mDNS packets. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the wireless controller to have high CPU utilization, which could lead to access points (APs) losing their connection to the controller and result in a DoS condition.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20303|2024-03-27T17:00:37.075Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20354|2024-03-27T16:47:04.924Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Aironet Access Point Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20354</link><description>A vulnerability in the handling of encrypted wireless frames of Cisco Aironet Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incomplete cleanup of resources when dropping certain malformed frames. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting as a wireless client to an affected AP and sending specific malformed frames over the wireless connection. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause degradation of service to other clients, which could potentially lead to a complete DoS condition.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20354|2024-03-27T16:47:04.924Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20315|2024-03-13T16:45:58.046Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XR Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20315</link><description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on MPLS interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20315|2024-03-13T16:45:58.046Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20293|2024-05-22T16:55:32.309Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20293</link><description>A vulnerability in the activation of an access control list (ACL) on Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the protection that is offered by a configured ACL on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an ACL changes from inactive to active in the running configuration of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device that should be denied by the configured ACL. The reverse condition is also truetraffic that should be permitted could be denied by the configured ACL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL protections on the affected device, allowing the attacker to access trusted networks that the device might be protecting. Note: This vulnerability applies to both IPv4 and IPv6 traffic as well as dual-stack ACL configurations in which both IPv4 and IPv6 ACLs are configured on an interface.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20293|2024-05-22T16:55:32.309Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20378|2024-05-01T16:41:52.385Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IP Phones with Multiplatform Firmware
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20378</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco IP Phone firmware could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to retrieve sensitive information from an affected device.  &#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a lack of authentication for specific endpoints of the web-based management interface on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain unauthorized access to the device, enabling the recording of user credentials and traffic to and from the affected device, including VoIP calls that could be replayed.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20378|2024-05-01T16:41:52.385Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20358|2024-04-24T19:38:23.689Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20358</link><description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) restore functionality that is available in Cisco ASA Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because the contents of a backup file are improperly sanitized at restore time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system as root.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20358|2024-04-24T19:38:23.689Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:38:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20319|2024-03-13T16:47:09.543Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XR Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20319</link><description>A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured management plane protection policies and access the Simple Network Management Plane (SNMP) server of an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect UDP forwarding programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to perform an SNMP operation using broadcast as the destination address that could be processed by an affected device that is configured with an SNMP server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to communicate to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Although an unauthenticated attacker could send UDP datagrams to the configured SNMP port, only an authenticated user can retrieve or modify data using SNMP requests.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20319|2024-03-13T16:47:09.543Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20362|2024-04-03T16:25:56.368Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Small Business RV Series Router Firmware
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20362</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business RV016, RV042, RV042G, RV082, RV320, and RV325 Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to visit specific web pages that include malicious payloads. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20362|2024-04-03T16:25:56.368Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20270|2024-02-02T15:42:39.819Z -- Cisco -- Cisco BroadWorks
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20270</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco BroadWorks Application Delivery Platform and Cisco BroadWorks Xtended Services Platform could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20270|2024-02-02T15:42:39.819Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 16:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20335|2024-03-06T17:06:13.554Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Business Wireless Access Point Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20335</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business 100, 300, and 500 Series Wireless APs could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform command injection attacks against an affected device. In order to exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative credentials for the device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the web-based management interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code as the root user on the underlying operating system.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20335|2024-03-06T17:06:13.554Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 16:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20266|2024-03-13T16:42:27.815Z -- Cisco -- Cisco IOS XR Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20266</link><description>A vulnerability in the DHCP version 4 (DHCPv4) server feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a crash of the dhcpd process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability exists because certain DHCPv4 messages are improperly validated when they are processed by an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed DHCPv4 message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a crash of the dhcpd process. While the dhcpd process is restarting, which may take approximately two minutes, DHCPv4 server services are unavailable on the affected device. This could temporarily prevent network access to clients that join the network during that time period and rely on the DHCPv4 server of the affected device.&#13;
&#13; Notes: &#13;
&#13; &#13; Only the dhcpd process crashes and eventually restarts automatically. The router does not reload.&#13; This vulnerability only applies to DHCPv4. DHCP version 6 (DHCPv6) is not affected.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20266|2024-03-13T16:42:27.815Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:42:27 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>