<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Content Security Management Appliance (SMA)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20content%20security%20management%20appliance%20%28sma%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Content Security Management Appliance (SMA)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1447|2024-08-03T16:11:17.339Z -- cisco -- cisco%20content%20security%20management%20appliance%20%28sma%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1447</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the user account management system of Cisco AsyncOS for Cisco Content Security Management Appliance (SMA) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate their privileges to root. This vulnerability is due to a procedural flaw in the password generation algorithm. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by enabling specific Administrator-only features and connecting to the appliance through the CLI with elevated privileges. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root and access the underlying operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1447|2024-08-03T16:11:17.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1561|2024-08-03T16:18:10.416Z -- cisco -- cisco%20content%20security%20management%20appliance%20%28sma%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1561</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the spam quarantine feature of Cisco Secure Email and Web Manager, formerly Cisco Security Management Appliance (SMA), could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to gain unauthorized access and modify the spam quarantine settings of another user. This vulnerability exists because access to the spam quarantine feature is not properly restricted. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify another user's spam quarantine settings, possibly disabling security controls or viewing email messages stored on the spam quarantine interfaces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1561|2024-08-03T16:18:10.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
