<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS 12.2(60)EZ16</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%2012.2%2860%29ez16.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS 12.2(60)EZ16</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:19:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3208|2024-08-04T07:24:00.737Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%2012.2%2860%29ez16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3208</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the image verification feature of Cisco IOS Software for Cisco 809 and 829 Industrial Integrated Services Routers (Industrial ISRs) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to boot a malicious software image on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient access restrictions on the area of code that manages the image verification feature. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by first authenticating to the targeted device and then logging in to the Virtual Device Server (VDS) of an affected device. The attacker could then, from the VDS shell, disable Cisco IOS Software integrity (image) verification. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to boot a malicious Cisco IOS Software image on the targeted device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid user credentials at privilege level 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3208|2024-08-04T07:24:00.737Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3234|2024-08-04T07:30:56.479Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%2012.2%2860%29ez16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3234</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the virtual console authentication of Cisco IOS Software for Cisco 809 and 829 Industrial Integrated Services Routers (Industrial ISRs) and Cisco 1000 Series Connected Grid Routers (CGR1000) could allow an authenticated but low-privileged, local attacker to log in to the Virtual Device Server (VDS) of an affected device by using a set of default credentials. The vulnerability is due to the presence of weak, hard-coded credentials. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the targeted device and then connecting to VDS through the device&amp;rsquo;s virtual console by using the static credentials. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access the Linux shell of VDS as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3234|2024-08-04T07:30:56.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3205|2024-08-04T07:24:00.796Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%2012.2%2860%29ez16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3205</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the inter-VM channel of Cisco IOS Software for Cisco 809 and 829 Industrial Integrated Services Routers (Industrial ISRs) and Cisco 1000 Series Connected Grid Routers (CGR1000) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to execute arbitrary shell commands on the Virtual Device Server (VDS) of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of signaling packets that are destined to VDS. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands in the context of the Linux shell of VDS with the privileges of the root user. Because the device is designed on a hypervisor architecture, exploitation of a vulnerability that affects the inter-VM channel may lead to a complete system compromise. For more information about this vulnerability, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3205|2024-08-04T07:24:00.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3198|2024-08-04T07:24:00.909Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%2012.2%2860%29ez16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3198</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco IOS Software for Cisco 809 and 829 Industrial Integrated Services Routers (Industrial ISRs) and Cisco 1000 Series Connected Grid Routers (CGR1000) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker or an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected system or cause an affected system to crash and reload. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3198|2024-08-04T07:24:00.909Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3210|2024-08-04T07:24:00.869Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%2012.2%2860%29ez16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3210</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI parsers of Cisco IOS Software for Cisco 809 and 829 Industrial Integrated Services Routers (Industrial ISRs) and Cisco 1000 Series Connected Grid Routers (CGR1000) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary shell commands on the Virtual Device Server (VDS) of an affected device. The attacker must have valid user credentials at privilege level 15. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific VDS-related CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the targeted device and including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands in the context of the Linux shell of VDS with the privileges of the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3210|2024-08-04T07:24:00.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3199|2024-08-04T07:24:00.919Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%2012.2%2860%29ez16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3199</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Cisco IOx application environment of Cisco 809 and 829 Industrial Integrated Services Routers (Industrial ISRs) and Cisco 1000 Series Connected Grid Routers (CGR1000) that are running Cisco IOS Software could allow an attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition or execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3199|2024-08-04T07:24:00.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3257|2024-08-04T07:30:57.374Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%2012.2%2860%29ez16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3257</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Cisco IOx application environment of Cisco 809 and 829 Industrial Integrated Services Routers (Industrial ISRs) and Cisco 1000 Series Connected Grid Routers (CGR1000) that are running Cisco IOS Software could allow an attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition or execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3257|2024-08-04T07:30:57.374Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3258|2024-08-04T07:30:57.643Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%2012.2%2860%29ez16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3258</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco IOS Software for Cisco 809 and 829 Industrial Integrated Services Routers (Industrial ISRs) and Cisco 1000 Series Connected Grid Routers (CGR1000) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker or an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected system or cause an affected system to crash and reload. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3258|2024-08-04T07:30:57.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
