<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System E-Series Software (UCSE)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20e-series%20software%20%28ucse%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System E-Series Software (UCSE)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:22:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1634|2024-09-17T03:54:15.572Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20e-series%20software%20%28ucse%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1634</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Intelligent Platform Management Interface (IPMI) of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary commands that are executed with root privileges on the underlying operating system (OS). The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of user-supplied commands. An attacker who has administrator privileges and access to the network where the IPMI resides could exploit this vulnerability by submitting crafted input to the affected commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain root privileges on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1634|2024-09-17T03:54:15.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 18:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1863|2024-09-17T02:31:57.790Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20e-series%20software%20%28ucse%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1863</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to make unauthorized changes to the system configuration. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization enforcement. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the affected software. A successful exploit could allow a user with read-only privileges to change critical system configurations using administrator privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1863|2024-09-17T02:31:57.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 18:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
