<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Webex Meetings</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20webex%20meetings.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Webex Meetings</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:21:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1420|2024-08-03T16:11:17.058Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1420</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in certain web pages of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to modify a web page in the context of a user's browser. The vulnerability is due to improper checks on parameter values in affected pages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to follow a crafted link that is designed to pass HTML code into an affected parameter. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to alter the contents of a web page to redirect the user to potentially malicious websites, or the attacker could use this vulnerability to conduct further client-side attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1420|2024-08-03T16:11:17.058Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1351|2024-08-03T16:11:16.943Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1351</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based interface of the affected service. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based interface of the affected service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a maliciously crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1351|2024-08-03T16:11:16.943Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20778|2024-08-03T02:24:49.609Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20778</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the authentication component of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based interface. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based interface of the authentication component of Cisco Webex Meetings. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a maliciously crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20778|2024-08-03T02:24:49.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1467|2024-08-03T16:11:17.404Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1467</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings for Android could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to modify the avatar of another user. This vulnerability is due to improper authorization checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the Cisco Webex Meetings client of a targeted user of a meeting in which they are both participants. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify the avatar of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1467|2024-08-03T16:11:17.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20852|2024-08-03T02:24:50.049Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20852</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web interface of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow a remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack or a frame hijacking attack against a user of the web interface. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20852|2024-08-03T02:24:50.049Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20763|2024-08-03T02:24:49.459Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20763</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the login authorization components of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary Java code. This vulnerability is due to improper deserialization of Java code within login requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious login requests to the Cisco Webex Meetings service. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to inject arbitrary Java code and take arbitrary actions within the Cisco Webex Meetings application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20763|2024-08-03T02:24:49.459Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1503|2024-08-03T16:11:17.686Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1503</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Network Recording Player for Windows and MacOS and Cisco Webex Player for Windows and MacOS could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of values in Webex recording files that are in either Advanced Recording Format (ARF) or Webex Recording Format (WRF). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a user a malicious ARF or WRF file through a link or email attachment and persuading the user to open the file with the affected software on the local system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected system with the privileges of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1503|2024-08-03T16:11:17.686Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1502|2024-08-03T16:11:17.339Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1502</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Network Recording Player for Windows and MacOS and Cisco Webex Player for Windows and MacOS could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of values within Webex recording files formatted as either Advanced Recording Format (ARF) or Webex Recording Format (WRF). An attacker could exploit the vulnerability by sending a user a malicious ARF or WRF file through a link or email attachment and persuading the user to open the file. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected system with the privileges of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1502|2024-08-03T16:11:17.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1310|2024-08-03T16:02:56.425Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to redirect a user to an untrusted web page, bypassing the warning mechanism that should prompt the user before the redirection. This vulnerability is due to improper input validation of the URL parameters in an HTTP request. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to redirect a user to a malicious website, bypassing the Webex URL check that should result in a warning before the redirection to the web page. Attackers may use this type of vulnerability, known as an open redirect attack, as part of a phishing attack to convince users to unknowingly visit malicious sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1310|2024-08-03T16:02:56.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20820|2024-08-03T02:24:49.929Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20820</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web interface of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow a remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack or a frame hijacking attack against a user of the web interface. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20820|2024-08-03T02:24:49.929Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1544|2024-08-03T16:11:17.685Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1544</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in logging mechanisms of Cisco Webex Meetings client software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain access to sensitive information. This vulnerability is due to unsafe logging of application actions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging onto the local system and accessing files containing the logged details. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to sensitive information, including meeting data and recorded meeting transcriptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1544|2024-08-03T16:11:17.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1527|2024-08-03T16:11:17.688Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1527</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Player for Windows and MacOS could allow an attacker to cause the affected software to terminate or to gain access to memory state information that is related to the vulnerable application. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of values in Webex recording files that are stored in Webex Recording Format (WRF). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious WRF file to a user as a link or email attachment and then persuading the user to open the file with the affected software on the local system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the affected software and view memory state information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1527|2024-08-03T16:11:17.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1526|2024-08-03T16:11:17.564Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1526</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Player for Windows and MacOS could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of values in Webex recording files that are in Webex Recording Format (WRF). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a user a malicious WRF file through a link or email attachment and persuading the user to open the file with the affected software on the local system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected system with the privileges of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1526|2024-08-03T16:11:17.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
