<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Management Center</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20firepower%20management%20center.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Management Center</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:23:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15268|2024-09-17T02:06:09.273Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15268</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15268|2024-09-17T02:06:09.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 18:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12683|2024-09-17T02:21:23.150Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12683</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL injections on an affected device. These vulnerabilities exist due to improper input validation. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted SQL queries to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view information that they are not authorized to view, make changes to the system that they are not authorized to make, and execute commands within the underlying operating system that may affect the availability of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12683|2024-09-17T02:21:23.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15458|2024-09-17T01:41:24.590Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15458</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Shell Access Filter feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC), when used in conjunction with remote authentication, could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high disk utilization, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability occurs because the configuration of the Shell Access Filter, when used with a specific type of remote authentication, can cause a system file to have unbounded writes. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a steady stream of remote authentication requests to the appliance when the specific configuration is applied. Successful exploitation could allow the attacker to increase the size of a system log file so that it consumes most of the disk space. The lack of available disk space could lead to a DoS condition in which the device functions could operate abnormally, making the device unstable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15458|2024-09-17T01:41:24.590Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3320|2024-09-17T01:25:42.830Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3320</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by first entering input within the web-based management interface and then persuading a user of the interface to view the crafted input within the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3320|2024-09-17T01:25:42.830Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 04:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34764|2024-09-17T03:48:08.076Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34764</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an attacker to execute a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack or an open redirect attack. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34764|2024-09-17T03:48:08.076Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3302|2024-09-17T01:51:45.726Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3302</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to overwrite files on the file system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a crafted file to the web UI on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite files on the file system of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3302|2024-09-17T01:51:45.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20629|2024-09-17T02:52:51.777Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20629</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20629|2024-09-17T02:52:51.777Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 03:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12686|2024-09-17T02:11:02.456Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12686</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL injections on an affected device. These vulnerabilities exist due to improper input validation. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted SQL queries to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view information that they are not authorized to view, make changes to the system that they are not authorized to make, and execute commands within the underlying operating system that may affect the availability of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12686|2024-09-17T02:11:02.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1238|2024-09-17T00:56:36.278Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1238</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected system. The vulnerabilities exist because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1238|2024-09-17T00:56:36.278Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 21:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1802|2024-09-17T01:01:35.041Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1802</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input in the web-based management interface of the affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to access a report containing malicious content. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. Versions 6.2.3, 6.3.0, and 6.4.0 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1802|2024-09-17T01:01:35.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 01:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12681|2024-09-17T03:59:09.260Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12681</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL injections on an affected device. These vulnerabilities exist due to improper input validation. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted SQL queries to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view information that they are not authorized to view, make changes to the system that they are not authorized to make, and execute commands within the underlying operating system that may affect the availability of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12681|2024-09-17T03:59:09.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34763|2024-09-17T03:22:30.342Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34763</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an attacker to execute a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack or an open redirect attack. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34763|2024-09-17T03:22:30.342Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1671|2024-09-17T01:31:41.195Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1671</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of the affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a maliciously crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1671|2024-09-17T01:31:41.195Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12684|2024-09-17T00:06:11.815Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12684</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL injections on an affected device. These vulnerabilities exist due to improper input validation. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted SQL queries to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view information that they are not authorized to view, make changes to the system that they are not authorized to make, and execute commands within the underlying operating system that may affect the availability of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12684|2024-09-17T00:06:11.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3557|2024-09-17T01:31:37.945Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3557</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the host input API daemon of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper certificate validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted data stream to the host input daemon of the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the host input daemon to restart. The attacker could use repeated attacks to cause the daemon to continuously reload, creating a DoS condition for the API.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3557|2024-09-17T01:31:37.945Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20627|2024-09-17T03:27:32.510Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20627</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20627|2024-09-17T03:27:32.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 03:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3550|2024-09-17T03:13:44.645Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3550</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the sfmgr daemon of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform directory traversal and access directories outside the restricted path. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using a relative path in specific sfmgr commands. An exploit could allow the attacker to read or write arbitrary files on an sftunnel-connected peer device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3550|2024-09-17T03:13:44.645Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34762|2024-09-17T00:57:06.081Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34762</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a directory traversal attack on an affected device. The attacker would require valid device credentials. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of the HTTPS URL by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTPS request that contains directory traversal character sequences to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read or write arbitrary files on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34762|2024-09-17T00:57:06.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12679|2024-09-17T04:20:13.891Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12679</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL injections on an affected device. These vulnerabilities exist due to improper input validation. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted SQL queries to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view information that they are not authorized to view, make changes to the system that they are not authorized to make, and execute commands within the underlying operating system that may affect the availability of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12679|2024-09-17T04:20:13.891Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1642|2024-09-17T03:18:57.841Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1642</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of the affected software. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1642|2024-09-17T03:18:57.841Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3311|2024-09-17T04:03:36.685Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3311</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to redirect a user to a malicious web page. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation of HTTP request parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting and modifying an HTTP request from a user. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to redirect the user to a specific malicious web page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3311|2024-09-17T04:03:36.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20361|2024-08-01T21:59:41.652Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Object Groups for Access Control Lists (ACLs) feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured access controls on managed devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect deployment of the Object Groups for ACLs feature from Cisco FMC Software to managed FTD devices in high-availability setups. After an affected device is rebooted following Object Groups for ACLs deployment, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access controls and successfully send traffic to devices that are expected to be protected by the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20361|2024-08-01T21:59:41.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20360|2024-08-01T21:59:42.328Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20360</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not adequately validate user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain any data from the database, execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system, and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least Read Only user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20360|2024-08-01T21:59:42.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-04T17:40:51.215Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Object Groups for Access Control Lists (ACLs) feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured access controls on managed devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect deployment of the Object Groups for ACLs feature from Cisco FMC Software to managed FTD devices in high-availability setups. After an affected device is rebooted following Object Groups for ACLs deployment, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access controls and successfully send traffic to devices that are expected to be protected by the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-04T17:40:51.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20360|2024-06-04T17:40:39.489Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20360</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not adequately validate user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain any data from the database, execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system, and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least Read Only user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20360|2024-06-04T17:40:39.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-13T14:05:52.072Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Object Groups for Access Control Lists (ACLs) feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured access controls on managed devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect deployment of the Object Groups for ACLs feature from Cisco FMC Software to managed FTD devices in high-availability setups. After an affected device is rebooted following Object Groups for ACLs deployment, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access controls and successfully send traffic to devices that are expected to be protected by the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-13T14:05:52.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
