<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20and%20ios%20xe%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:23:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1746|2024-08-04T18:28:42.410Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20and%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1746</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cluster Management Protocol (CMP) processing code in Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation when processing CMP management packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious CMP management packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could cause the switch to crash, resulting in a DoS condition. The switch will reload automatically.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1746|2024-08-04T18:28:42.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1748|2024-08-04T18:28:42.335Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20and%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1748</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Network Plug-and-Play (PnP) agent of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain unauthorized access to sensitive data. The vulnerability exists because the affected software insufficiently validates certificates. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a crafted certificate to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct man-in-the-middle attacks to decrypt and modify confidential information on user connections to the affected software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1748|2024-08-04T18:28:42.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1762|2024-08-04T18:28:42.663Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20and%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1762</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Storage feature of Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access sensitive system information on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper memory operations performed at encryption time, when affected software handles configuration updates. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by retrieving the contents of specific memory locations of an affected device. A successful exploit could result in the disclosure of keying materials that are part of the device configuration, which can be used to recover critical system information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1762|2024-08-04T18:28:42.663Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1761|2024-08-04T18:28:42.469Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20and%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1761</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Hot Standby Router Protocol (HSRP) subsystem of Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to receive potentially sensitive information from an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient memory initialization. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by receiving HSRPv2 traffic from an adjacent HSRP member. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to receive potentially sensitive information from the adjacent device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1761|2024-08-04T18:28:42.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1747|2024-08-04T18:28:42.027Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20and%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1747</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the Short Message Service (SMS) handling functionality of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper processing of SMS protocol data units (PDUs) that are encoded with a special character set. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious SMS message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the wireless WAN (WWAN) cellular interface module on an affected device to crash, resulting in a DoS condition that would require manual intervention to restore normal operating conditions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1747|2024-08-04T18:28:42.027Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1757|2024-08-04T18:28:42.249Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20and%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1757</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Smart Call Home feature of Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain unauthorized read access to sensitive data using an invalid certificate. The vulnerability is due to insufficient certificate validation by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a crafted certificate to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct man-in-the-middle attacks to decrypt confidential information on user connections to the affected software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1757|2024-08-04T18:28:42.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1752|2024-08-04T18:28:42.897Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20and%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1752</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the ISDN functions of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload. The vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of specific values in the Q.931 information elements. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by calling the affected device with specific Q.931 information elements being present. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1752|2024-08-04T18:28:42.897Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
