<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software for Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches ACI Mode</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20nx-os%20software%20for%20nexus%209000%20series%20fabric%20switches%20aci%20mode.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software for Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches ACI Mode</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:21:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1588|2024-09-16T20:26:44.101Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software%20for%20nexus%209000%20series%20fabric%20switches%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1588</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches running in Application-Centric Infrastructure (ACI) mode could allow an authenticated, local attacker to read arbitrary files on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a lack of proper input and validation checking mechanisms of user-supplied input sent to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker unauthorized access to read arbitrary files on an affected device. This vulnerability has been fixed in version 14.0(1h).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1588|2024-09-16T20:26:44.101Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1590|2024-09-16T22:50:32.318Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software%20for%20nexus%209000%20series%20fabric%20switches%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1590</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Transport Layer Security (TLS) certificate validation functionality of Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Application Centric Infrastructure (ACI) Mode Switch Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to perform insecure TLS client authentication on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient TLS client certificate validations for certificates sent between the various components of an ACI fabric. An attacker who has possession of a certificate that is trusted by the Cisco Manufacturing CA and the corresponding private key could exploit this vulnerability by presenting a valid certificate while attempting to connect to the targeted device. An exploit could allow the attacker to gain full control of all other components within the ACI fabric of an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1590|2024-09-16T22:50:32.318Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 14:50:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
