<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:26:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20080|2024-08-02T08:57:35.867Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20080</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv6 DHCP version 6 (DHCPv6) relay and server features of Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of data boundaries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted DHCPv6 messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20080|2024-08-02T08:57:35.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20081|2024-08-02T08:57:35.826Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20081</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv6 DHCP (DHCPv6) client module of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software, Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software, Cisco IOS Software, and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of DHCPv6 messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted DHCPv6 messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition. Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to either control the DHCPv6 server or be in a man-in-the-middle position.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20081|2024-08-02T08:57:35.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20076|2024-08-02T08:57:35.567Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20076</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco IOx application hosting environment could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying host operating system. This vulnerability is due to incomplete sanitization of parameters that are passed in for activation of an application. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by deploying and activating an application in the Cisco IOx application hosting environment with a crafted activation payload file. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying host operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20076|2024-08-02T08:57:35.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
