<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Aironet Access Point Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Aironet Access Point Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:23:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3552|2024-08-04T07:37:54.983Z -- cisco -- cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3552</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Ethernet packet handling of Cisco Aironet Access Points (APs) Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting as a wired client to the Ethernet interface of an affected device and sending a series of specific packets within a short time frame. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a NULL pointer access that results in a reload of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3552|2024-08-04T07:37:54.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1835|2024-08-04T18:28:42.888Z -- cisco -- cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1835</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco Aironet Access Points (APs) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access sensitive information stored in an AP. The vulnerability is due to improper sanitization of user-supplied input in specific CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the CLI of an affected AP with administrator privileges and issuing crafted commands that result in directory traversal. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view system files on the affected device, which could contain sensitive information. Software versions 8.8 and 8.9 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1835|2024-08-04T18:28:42.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34740|2024-08-04T00:19:48.125Z -- cisco -- cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34740</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the WLAN Control Protocol (WCP) implementation for Cisco Aironet Access Point (AP) software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to incorrect error handling when an affected device receives an unexpected 802.11 frame. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain 802.11 frames over the wireless network to an interface on an affected AP. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a packet buffer leak. This could eventually result in buffer allocation failures, which would trigger a reload of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34740|2024-08-04T00:19:48.125Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1834|2024-08-04T18:28:42.946Z -- cisco -- cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1834</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the internal packet processing of Cisco Aironet Series Access Points (APs) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected AP if the switch interface where the AP is connected has port security configured. The vulnerability exists because the AP forwards some malformed wireless client packets outside of the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) tunnel. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted wireless packets to an affected AP. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to trigger a security violation on the adjacent switch port, which could result in a DoS condition. Note: Though the Common Vulnerability Scoring System (CVSS) score corresponds to a High Security Impact Rating (SIR), this vulnerability is considered Medium because a workaround is available and exploitation requires a specific switch configuration. There are workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1834|2024-08-04T18:28:42.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1826|2024-08-04T18:28:42.817Z -- cisco -- cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1826</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the quality of service (QoS) feature of Cisco Aironet Series Access Points (APs) could allow an authenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation on QoS fields within Wi-Fi frames by the affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malformed Wi-Fi frames to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1826|2024-08-04T18:28:42.817Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3260|2024-08-04T07:30:57.423Z -- cisco -- cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3260</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Aironet Series Access Points Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to the improper processing of client packets that are sent to an affected access point (AP). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of sustained client packets to the affected AP. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected AP to crash, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3260|2024-08-04T07:30:57.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1920|2024-08-04T18:35:51.296Z -- cisco -- cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1920</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the 802.11r Fast Transition (FT) implementation for Cisco IOS Access Points (APs) Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected interface. The vulnerability is due to a lack of complete error handling condition for client authentication requests sent to a targeted interface configured for FT. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted authentication request traffic to the targeted interface, causing the device to restart unexpectedly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1920|2024-08-04T18:35:51.296Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1654|2024-08-04T18:20:28.459Z -- cisco -- cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1654</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the development shell (devshell) authentication for Cisco Aironet Series Access Points (APs) running the Cisco AP-COS operating system could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access the development shell without proper authentication, which allows for root access to the underlying Linux OS. The attacker would need valid device credentials. The vulnerability exists because the software improperly validates user-supplied input at the CLI authentication prompt for development shell access. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and entering crafted input at the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access the AP development shell without proper authentication, which allows for root access to the underlying Linux OS. Software versions prior to 8.3.150.0, 8.5.135.0, and 8.8.100.0 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1654|2024-08-04T18:20:28.459Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1829|2024-08-04T18:28:42.897Z -- cisco -- cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1829</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco Aironet Series Access Points (APs) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain access to the underlying Linux operating system (OS) without the proper authentication. The attacker would need valid administrator device credentials. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input for certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to an affected device and submitting crafted input for a CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain access to the underlying Linux OS without proper authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1829|2024-08-04T18:28:42.897Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3262|2024-08-04T07:30:57.586Z -- cisco -- cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3262</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol handler of Cisco Wireless LAN Controller (WLC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to restart, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3262|2024-08-04T07:30:57.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3559|2024-08-04T07:37:54.981Z -- cisco -- cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3559</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Aironet Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of clients that are trying to connect to the AP. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending authentication requests from multiple clients to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3559|2024-08-04T07:37:54.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3560|2024-08-04T07:37:54.978Z -- cisco -- cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3560</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Aironet Access Points (APs) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper resource management while processing specific packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of crafted UDP packets to a specific port on an affected device. A successful exploit could either allow the attacker to tear down the connection between the AP and the wireless LAN controller, resulting in the affected device not being able to process client traffic, or cause the vulnerable device to reload, triggering a DoS condition. After the attack, the affected device should automatically recover its normal functions without manual intervention.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3560|2024-08-04T07:37:54.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20354|2024-08-01T21:59:41.707Z -- cisco -- cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20354</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the handling of encrypted wireless frames of Cisco Aironet Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incomplete cleanup of resources when dropping certain malformed frames. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting as a wireless client to an affected AP and sending specific malformed frames over the wireless connection. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause degradation of service to other clients, which could potentially lead to a complete DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20354|2024-08-01T21:59:41.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20271|2024-08-01T21:52:38.878Z -- cisco -- cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20271</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IP packet processing of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPv4 packet either to or through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker does not need to be associated with the affected AP. This vulnerability cannot be exploited by sending IPv6 packets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20271|2024-08-01T21:52:38.878Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20271|2024-06-28T13:07:00.717Z -- cisco -- cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20271</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IP packet processing of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPv4 packet either to or through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker does not need to be associated with the affected AP. This vulnerability cannot be exploited by sending IPv6 packets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20271|2024-06-28T13:07:00.717Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20354|2024-03-27T16:47:04.924Z -- cisco -- cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20354</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the handling of encrypted wireless frames of Cisco Aironet Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incomplete cleanup of resources when dropping certain malformed frames. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting as a wireless client to an affected AP and sending specific malformed frames over the wireless connection. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause degradation of service to other clients, which could potentially lead to a complete DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20354|2024-03-27T16:47:04.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20271|2024-03-27T17:05:27.473Z -- cisco -- cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20271</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IP packet processing of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPv4 packet either to or through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker does not need to be associated with the affected AP. This vulnerability cannot be exploited by sending IPv6 packets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20271|2024-03-27T17:05:27.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20354|2024-07-23T18:28:01.520Z -- cisco -- cisco%20aironet%20access%20point%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20354</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the handling of encrypted wireless frames of Cisco Aironet Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incomplete cleanup of resources when dropping certain malformed frames. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting as a wireless client to an affected AP and sending specific malformed frames over the wireless connection. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause degradation of service to other clients, which could potentially lead to a complete DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20354|2024-07-23T18:28:01.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
