<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco DNA Spaces </title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20dna%20spaces.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco DNA Spaces </description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:45:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15996|2024-08-05T01:03:32.791Z -- cisco -- cisco%20dna%20spaces
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15996</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco DNA Spaces: Connector could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges and execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system as root. The vulnerability is due to insufficient restrictions during the execution of an affected CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by leveraging the insufficient restrictions to modify sensitive files. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges and execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15996|2024-08-05T01:03:32.791Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15995|2024-08-05T01:03:32.670Z -- cisco -- cisco%20dna%20spaces
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15995</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco DNA Spaces: Connector could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries. The vulnerability exists because the web UI does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by entering malicious SQL statements in an affected field in the web UI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to remove the SQL database, which would require the reinstallation of the Connector VM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15995|2024-08-05T01:03:32.670Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15997|2024-08-05T01:03:32.622Z -- cisco -- cisco%20dna%20spaces
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15997</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco DNA Spaces: Connector could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform a command injection attack and execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system as root. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a specific CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input during the execution of the affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15997|2024-08-05T01:03:32.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
