<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Communications Manager</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20unified%20communications%20manager.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Communications Manager</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 18:24:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0474|2024-08-05T03:28:10.828Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20communications%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0474</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to view digest credentials in clear text. The vulnerability is due to the incorrect inclusion of saved passwords in configuration pages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to the Cisco Unified Communications Manager web-based management interface and viewing the source code for the configuration page. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to recover passwords and expose those accounts to further attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0474|2024-08-05T03:28:10.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15272|2024-08-05T00:42:03.947Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20communications%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15272</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager and Cisco Unified Communications Manager Session Management Edition (SME) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass security restrictions. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of malformed HTTP methods. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain unauthorized access to the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15272|2024-08-05T00:42:03.947Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15972|2024-08-05T01:03:32.567Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20communications%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15972</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface improperly validates SQL values. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application and sending malicious requests to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify values on or return values from the underlying database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15972|2024-08-05T01:03:32.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
