<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System E-Series Software (UCSE) </title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20e-series%20software%20%28ucse%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System E-Series Software (UCSE) </description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:19:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1883|2024-08-04T18:35:50.734Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20e-series%20software%20%28ucse%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1883</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the command-line interface of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, local attacker with read-only credentials to inject arbitrary commands that could allow them to obtain root privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input on the command-line interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating with read-only privileges via the CLI of an affected device and submitting crafted input to the affected commands. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the device with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1883|2024-08-04T18:35:50.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1850|2024-08-04T18:28:42.888Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20e-series%20software%20%28ucse%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1850</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary commands that are executed with root privileges on an affected device. An attacker would need to have valid administrator credentials on the device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the affected software. An attacker with elevated privileges could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted commands to the administrative web management interface of the affected software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to inject and execute arbitrary, system-level commands with root privileges on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1850|2024-08-04T18:28:42.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1865|2024-08-04T18:28:42.892Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20e-series%20software%20%28ucse%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1865</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary commands that are executed with root privileges on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by invoking an interface monitoring mechanism with a crafted argument on the affected software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to inject and execute arbitrary, system-level commands with root privileges on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1865|2024-08-04T18:28:42.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1896|2024-08-04T18:35:51.570Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20e-series%20software%20%28ucse%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1896</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary commands and obtain root privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input in the Certificate Signing Request (CSR) function of the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CSR in the web-based management interface. A successful exploit could allow an attacker with administrator privileges to execute arbitrary commands on the device with full root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1896|2024-08-04T18:35:51.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1634|2024-08-04T18:20:28.540Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20e-series%20software%20%28ucse%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1634</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Intelligent Platform Management Interface (IPMI) of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary commands that are executed with root privileges on the underlying operating system (OS). The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of user-supplied commands. An attacker who has administrator privileges and access to the network where the IPMI resides could exploit this vulnerability by submitting crafted input to the affected commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain root privileges on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1634|2024-08-04T18:20:28.540Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1864|2024-08-04T18:28:42.956Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20e-series%20software%20%28ucse%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1864</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary commands that are executed with root privileges on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of command input by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious commands to the web-based management interface of the affected software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker, with read-only privileges, to inject and execute arbitrary, system-level commands with root privileges on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1864|2024-08-04T18:28:42.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1863|2024-08-04T18:28:43.087Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20e-series%20software%20%28ucse%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1863</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to make unauthorized changes to the system configuration. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization enforcement. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the affected software. A successful exploit could allow a user with read-only privileges to change critical system configurations using administrator privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1863|2024-08-04T18:28:43.087Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
