<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Content Security Management Appliance (SMA)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20content%20security%20management%20appliance%20%28sma%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Content Security Management Appliance (SMA)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:24:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15393|2024-09-17T02:05:54.667Z -- cisco -- cisco%20content%20security%20management%20appliance%20%28sma%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15393</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Content Security Management Appliance (SMA) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a maliciously crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15393|2024-09-17T02:05:54.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1561|2024-09-17T01:46:41.189Z -- cisco -- cisco%20content%20security%20management%20appliance%20%28sma%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1561</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the spam quarantine feature of Cisco Secure Email and Web Manager, formerly Cisco Security Management Appliance (SMA), could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to gain unauthorized access and modify the spam quarantine settings of another user. This vulnerability exists because access to the spam quarantine feature is not properly restricted. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify another user's spam quarantine settings, possibly disabling security controls or viewing email messages stored on the spam quarantine interfaces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1561|2024-09-17T01:46:41.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 19:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
