<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Umbrella</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20umbrella.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Umbrella</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 22:22:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1792|2024-09-16T18:39:14.219Z -- cisco -- cisco%20umbrella
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1792</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the URL block page of Cisco Umbrella could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user in a network protected by Umbrella. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of input parameters passed to that page. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a maliciously crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive browser-based information. This vulnerability has been fixed in the current version of Cisco Umbrella. Cisco Umbrella is a cloud service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1792|2024-09-16T18:39:14.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 00:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3337|2024-09-16T20:48:15.262Z -- cisco -- cisco%20umbrella
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3337</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web server of Cisco Umbrella could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to redirect a user to an undesired web page. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation of the URL parameters in an HTTP request that is sent to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request that could cause the web application to redirect the request to a specified malicious URL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to redirect a user to a malicious website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3337|2024-09-16T20:48:15.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 02:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0438|2024-09-16T21:09:02.543Z -- cisco -- cisco%20umbrella
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0438</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Umbrella Enterprise Roaming Client (ERC) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to Administrator. To exploit the vulnerability, the attacker must authenticate with valid local user credentials. This vulnerability is due to improper implementation of file system permissions, which could allow non-administrative users to place files within restricted directories. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by placing an executable file within the restricted directory, which when executed by the ERC client, would run with Administrator privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0438|2024-09-16T21:09:02.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0435|2024-09-16T18:02:59.697Z -- cisco -- cisco%20umbrella
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0435</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Umbrella API could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to view and modify data across their organization and other organizations. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authentication configurations for the API interface of Cisco Umbrella. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to view and potentially modify data for their organization or other organizations. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read or modify data across multiple organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0435|2024-09-16T18:02:59.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
