<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20xe%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 01:37:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3509|2024-09-17T00:50:48.557Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3509</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP message handler of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco cBR-8 Converged Broadband Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the supervisor to crash, which could result in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to insufficient error handling when DHCP version 4 (DHCPv4) messages are parsed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious DHCPv4 message to or through a WAN interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a reload of the affected device. Note: On Cisco cBR-8 Converged Broadband Routers, all of the following are considered WAN interfaces: 10 Gbps Ethernet interfaces 100 Gbps Ethernet interfaces Port channel interfaces that include multiple 10 and/or 100 Gbps Ethernet interfaces</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3509|2024-09-17T00:50:48.557Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3497|2024-09-17T01:10:40.991Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3497</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3497|2024-09-17T01:10:40.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12664|2024-09-17T00:26:36.860Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12664</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Dialer interface feature for ISDN connections in Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco 4000 Series Integrated Services Routers (ISRs) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to pass IPv4 traffic through an ISDN channel prior to successful PPP authentication. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of the state of the PPP IP Control Protocol (IPCP). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by making an ISDN call to an affected device and sending traffic through the ISDN channel prior to successful PPP authentication. Alternatively, an unauthenticated, remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through an affected device that is configured to exit via an ISDN connection for which both the Dialer interface and the Basic Rate Interface (BRI) have been configured, but the Challenge Handshake Authentication Protocol (CHAP) password for PPP does not match the remote end. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to pass IPv4 traffic through an unauthenticated ISDN connection for a few seconds, from initial ISDN call setup until PPP authentication fails.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12664|2024-09-17T00:26:36.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 20:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20847|2024-09-17T01:00:29.150Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20847</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP processing functionality of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Catalyst 9000 Family could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to the improper processing of DHCP messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious DHCP messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20847|2024-09-17T01:00:29.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 18:45:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12653|2024-09-17T01:00:40.043Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12653</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Raw Socket Transport feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to improper parsing of Raw Socket Transport payloads. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing a TCP session and then sending a malicious TCP segment via IPv4 to an affected device. This cannot be exploited via IPv6, as the Raw Socket Transport feature does not support IPv6 as a network layer protocol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12653|2024-09-17T01:00:40.043Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 20:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1436|2024-09-17T00:11:02.193Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1436</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to conduct path traversal attacks and obtain read access to sensitive files on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view arbitrary files on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1436|2024-09-17T00:11:02.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20693|2024-09-17T00:30:31.717Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20693</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform an injection attack against an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input to the web UI API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to inject commands to the underlying operating system with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20693|2024-09-17T00:30:31.717Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0476|2024-09-17T01:21:34.212Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0476</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Network Address Translation (NAT) Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) Application Layer Gateway (ALG) of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload. The vulnerability is due to improper processing of SIP packets in transit while NAT is performed on an affected device. An unauthenticated, remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted SIP packets via UDP port 5060 through an affected device that is performing NAT for SIP packets. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0476|2024-09-17T01:21:34.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3417|2024-09-17T00:06:50.166Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3417</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute persistent code at boot time and break the chain of trust. This vulnerability is due to incorrect validations by boot scripts when specific ROM monitor (ROMMON) variables are set. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by installing code to a specific directory in the underlying operating system (OS) and setting a specific ROMMON variable. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute persistent code on the underlying OS. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need access to the root shell on the device or have physical access to the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3417|2024-09-17T00:06:50.166Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 18:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20684|2024-09-17T00:37:22.200Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20684</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) trap generation for wireless clients of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Catalyst 9000 Family could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to unexpectedly reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on the device. This vulnerability is due to a lack of input validation of the information used to generate an SNMP trap related to a wireless client connection event. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending an 802.1x packet with crafted parameters during the wireless authentication setup phase of a connection. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20684|2024-09-17T00:37:22.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3418|2024-09-17T00:47:01.648Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3418</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Routers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to send ICMPv6 traffic prior to the client being placed into RUN state. The vulnerability is due to an incomplete access control list (ACL) being applied prior to RUN state. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the associated service set identifier (SSID) and sending ICMPv6 traffic. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send ICMPv6 traffic prior to RUN state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3418|2024-09-17T00:47:01.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 18:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20864|2024-09-17T00:37:06.142Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20864</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the password-recovery disable feature of Cisco IOS XE ROM Monitor (ROMMON) Software for Cisco Catalyst Switches could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker to recover the configuration or reset the enable password. This vulnerability is due to a problem with the file and boot variable permissions in ROMMON. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by rebooting the switch into ROMMON and entering specific commands through the console. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read any file or reset the enable password.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20864|2024-09-17T00:37:06.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 20:43:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1742|2024-09-17T00:26:25.889Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1742</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive configuration information. The vulnerability is due to improper access control to files within the web UI. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to sensitive configuration information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1742|2024-09-17T00:26:25.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 23:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20324|2024-08-27T20:50:51.192Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20324</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to access WLAN configuration details including passwords.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper privilege checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the show and show tech wireless CLI commands to access configuration details, including passwords. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access configuration details that they are not authorized to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20324|2024-08-27T20:50:51.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20278|2024-08-15T16:45:09.481Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20278</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NETCONF feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input over NETCONF to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges from Administrator to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20278|2024-08-15T16:45:09.481Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T15:33:37.498Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T15:33:37.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-06-20T20:52:30.286Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-06-20T20:52:30.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-06-20T20:50:12.348Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-06-20T20:50:12.348Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-03-27T17:03:54.505Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-03-27T17:03:54.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-03-27T16:49:03.113Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-03-27T16:49:03.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20306|2024-03-27T16:58:22.583Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Unified Threat Defense (UTD) configuration CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying host operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have level 15 privileges on the affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20306|2024-03-27T16:58:22.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-04-03T16:36:06.520Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-04-03T16:36:06.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20259|2024-03-27T16:53:53.073Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP snooping feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a crafted IPv4 DHCP request packet being mishandled when endpoint analytics are enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCP request through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; Note: The attack vector is listed as network because a DHCP relay anywhere on the network could allow exploits from networks other than the adjacent one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20259|2024-03-27T16:53:53.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20278|2024-03-27T16:59:12.963Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20278</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NETCONF feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input over NETCONF to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges from Administrator to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20278|2024-03-27T16:59:12.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20324|2024-03-27T16:55:53.837Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20324</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to access WLAN configuration details including passwords.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper privilege checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the show and show tech wireless CLI commands to access configuration details, including passwords. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access configuration details that they are not authorized to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20324|2024-03-27T16:55:53.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20309|2024-03-27T17:02:19.749Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in auxiliary asynchronous port (AUX) functions of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause an affected device to reload or stop responding.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific ingress traffic when flow control hardware is enabled on the AUX port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by reverse telnetting to the AUX port and sending specific data after connecting. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reset or stop responding, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20309|2024-03-27T17:02:19.749Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20313|2024-04-24T20:42:10.379Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20313</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of OSPF updates that are processed by a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF update to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20313|2024-04-24T20:42:10.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-03-27T16:57:27.974Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-03-27T16:57:27.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20303|2024-06-04T17:39:55.892Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20303</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multicast DNS (mDNS) gateway feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Wireless LAN Controllers (WLCs) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper management of mDNS client entries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the wireless network and sending a continuous stream of specific mDNS packets. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the wireless controller to have high CPU utilization, which could lead to access points (APs) losing their connection to the controller and result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20303|2024-06-04T17:39:55.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-06-20T17:42:35.196Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-06-20T17:42:35.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-07-02T16:25:58.752Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-07-02T16:25:58.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-07-02T16:25:13.272Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-07-02T16:25:13.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-07-02T16:23:39.427Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-07-02T16:23:39.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20309|2024-08-01T21:59:41.337Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in auxiliary asynchronous port (AUX) functions of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause an affected device to reload or stop responding.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific ingress traffic when flow control hardware is enabled on the AUX port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by reverse telnetting to the AUX port and sending specific data after connecting. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reset or stop responding, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20309|2024-08-01T21:59:41.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20259|2024-08-01T21:52:31.719Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP snooping feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a crafted IPv4 DHCP request packet being mishandled when endpoint analytics are enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCP request through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; Note: The attack vector is listed as network because a DHCP relay anywhere on the network could allow exploits from networks other than the adjacent one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20259|2024-08-01T21:52:31.719Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20324|2024-08-01T21:59:41.715Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20324</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to access WLAN configuration details including passwords.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper privilege checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the show and show tech wireless CLI commands to access configuration details, including passwords. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access configuration details that they are not authorized to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20324|2024-08-01T21:59:41.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20303|2024-08-01T21:59:41.376Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20303</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multicast DNS (mDNS) gateway feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Wireless LAN Controllers (WLCs) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper management of mDNS client entries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the wireless network and sending a continuous stream of specific mDNS packets. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the wireless controller to have high CPU utilization, which could lead to access points (APs) losing their connection to the controller and result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20303|2024-08-01T21:59:41.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-08-01T21:59:42.311Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-08-01T21:59:42.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-08-01T21:59:42.197Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-08-01T21:59:42.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T21:52:31.616Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T21:52:31.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20278|2024-08-01T21:59:41.100Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20278</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NETCONF feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input over NETCONF to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges from Administrator to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20278|2024-08-01T21:59:41.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20306|2024-08-01T21:59:41.650Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Unified Threat Defense (UTD) configuration CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying host operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have level 15 privileges on the affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20306|2024-08-01T21:59:41.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-08-01T21:59:41.851Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-08-01T21:59:41.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20313|2024-08-01T21:59:42.856Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20313</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of OSPF updates that are processed by a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF update to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20313|2024-08-01T21:59:42.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20309|2024-08-09T18:34:29.824Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in auxiliary asynchronous port (AUX) functions of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause an affected device to reload or stop responding.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific ingress traffic when flow control hardware is enabled on the AUX port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by reverse telnetting to the AUX port and sending specific data after connecting. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reset or stop responding, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20309|2024-08-09T18:34:29.824Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20313|2024-08-09T18:34:02.110Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20313</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of OSPF updates that are processed by a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF update to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20313|2024-08-09T18:34:02.110Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20306|2024-08-16T18:48:47.441Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Unified Threat Defense (UTD) configuration CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying host operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have level 15 privileges on the affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20306|2024-08-16T18:48:47.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20259|2024-08-27T21:04:37.666Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP snooping feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a crafted IPv4 DHCP request packet being mishandled when endpoint analytics are enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCP request through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; Note: The attack vector is listed as network because a DHCP relay anywhere on the network could allow exploits from networks other than the adjacent one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20259|2024-08-27T21:04:37.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
