<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 17:22:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1972|2024-09-16T16:22:42.362Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1972</link>
      <description>A vulnerability the Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) restricted CLI could allow an authenticated, local attacker with valid administrator-level credentials to elevate privileges and execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system as root. The vulnerability is due to insufficient restrictions during the execution of an affected CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by leveraging the insufficient restrictions during the execution of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges and execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1972|2024-09-16T16:22:42.362Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 07:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34746|2024-09-16T16:38:27.137Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34746</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TACACS+ authentication, authorization and accounting (AAA) feature of Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass authentication and log in to an affected device as an administrator. This vulnerability is due to incomplete validation of user-supplied input that is passed to an authentication script. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting parameters into an authentication request. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass authentication and log in as an administrator to the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34746|2024-09-16T16:38:27.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 03:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12623|2024-09-16T16:48:15.124Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12623</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web server functionality of Cisco Enterprise Network Functions Virtualization Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform file enumeration on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to the web server responding with different error codes for existing and non-existing files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending GET requests for different file names. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to enumerate files residing on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12623|2024-09-16T16:48:15.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 18:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3236|2024-09-16T16:43:56.877Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3236</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain root shell access to the underlying operating system and overwrite or read arbitrary files. The attacker would need valid administrative credentials. This vulnerability is due to improper input validation of CLI command arguments. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using path traversal techniques when executing a vulnerable command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain root shell access to the underlying operating system and overwrite or read arbitrary files on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3236|2024-09-16T16:43:56.877Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 02:21:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1953|2024-09-16T16:53:11.829Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1953</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web portal of Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to view a password in clear text. The vulnerability is due to incorrectly logging the admin password when a user is forced to modify the default password when logging in to the web portal for the first time. Subsequent password changes are not logged and other accounts are not affected. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by viewing the admin clear text password and using it to access the affected system. The attacker would need a valid user account to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1953|2024-09-16T16:53:11.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 07:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
