<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS and IOS-XE Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20and%20ios-xe%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS and IOS-XE Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:23:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1738|2024-08-04T18:28:42.874Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20and%20ios-xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1738</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Network-Based Application Recognition (NBAR) feature of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload. This vulnerability is due to a parsing issue on DNS packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted DNS packets through routers that are running an affected version and have NBAR enabled. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1738|2024-08-04T18:28:42.874Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1737|2024-08-04T18:28:42.695Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20and%20ios-xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1737</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the processing of IP Service Level Agreement (SLA) packets by Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an interface wedge and an eventual denial of service (DoS) condition on the affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper socket resources handling in the IP SLA responder application code. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted IP SLA packets to an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause an interface to become wedged, resulting in an eventual denial of service (DoS) condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1737|2024-08-04T18:28:42.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
