<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Umbrella</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20umbrella.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Umbrella</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 16:24:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1807|2024-09-17T00:26:17.620Z -- cisco -- cisco%20umbrella
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1807</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the session management functionality of the web UI for the Cisco Umbrella Dashboard could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to access the Dashboard via an active, user session. The vulnerability exists due to the affected application not invalidating an existing session when a user authenticates to the application and changes the users credentials via another authenticated session. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using a separate, authenticated, active session to connect to the application through the web UI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to maintain access to the dashboard via an authenticated user's browser session. Cisco has addressed this vulnerability in the Cisco Umbrella Dashboard. No user action is required.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1807|2024-09-17T00:26:17.620Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 16:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3246|2024-09-17T00:55:36.193Z -- cisco -- cisco%20umbrella
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3246</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web server of Cisco Umbrella could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to perform a carriage return line feed (CRLF) injection attack against a user of an affected service. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to access a crafted URL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to inject arbitrary HTTP headers into valid HTTP responses sent to the browser of the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3246|2024-09-17T00:55:36.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
