<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Management Center</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20firepower%20management%20center.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Management Center</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 19:20:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12700|2024-09-16T18:13:12.864Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12700</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the configuration of the Pluggable Authentication Module (PAM) used in Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software, Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software, and Cisco FXOS Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to improper resource management in the context of user session management. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to an affected system and performing many simultaneous successful Secure Shell (SSH) logins. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust system resources and cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker needs valid user credentials on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12700|2024-09-16T18:13:12.864Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1930|2024-09-16T17:34:19.670Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1930</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the RSS dashboard in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device. The vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of the affected device. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1930|2024-09-16T17:34:19.670Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 01:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15443|2024-09-16T16:57:50.652Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15443</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the detection engine of Cisco Firepower System Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured Intrusion Prevention System (IPS) rule that inspects certain types of TCP traffic. The vulnerability is due to incorrect TCP retransmission handling. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted TCP connection request through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured IPS rules and allow uninspected traffic onto the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15443|2024-09-16T16:57:50.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12682|2024-09-16T18:45:11.398Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12682</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL injections on an affected device. These vulnerabilities exist due to improper input validation. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted SQL queries to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view information that they are not authorized to view, make changes to the system that they are not authorized to make, and execute commands within the underlying operating system that may affect the availability of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12682|2024-09-16T18:45:11.398Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3515|2024-09-16T17:42:41.912Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3515</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3515|2024-09-16T17:42:41.912Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1126|2024-09-16T18:33:45.667Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1126</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the storage of proxy server credentials of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to view credentials for a configured proxy server. The vulnerability is due to clear-text storage and weak permissions of related configuration files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the CLI of the affected software and viewing the contents of the affected files. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view the credentials that are used to access the proxy server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1126|2024-09-16T18:33:45.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 21:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1239|2024-09-16T16:17:48.137Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1239</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected system. The vulnerabilities exist because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1239|2024-09-16T16:17:48.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 21:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1458|2024-09-16T17:43:40.006Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1458</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1458|2024-09-16T17:43:40.006Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12691|2024-09-16T17:17:45.805Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12691</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a directory traversal attack on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the web-based management interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass Cisco FMC Software security restrictions and gain access to the underlying filesystem of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12691|2024-09-16T17:17:45.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20743|2024-09-16T17:49:15.146Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20743</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to bypass security protections and upload malicious files to the affected system. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files uploaded to the web management interface of Cisco FMC Software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a maliciously crafted file to a device running affected software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the device, which they could access later to conduct additional attacks, including executing arbitrary code on the affected device with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20743|2024-09-16T17:49:15.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 03:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1477|2024-09-16T16:18:51.166Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1477</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in an access control mechanism of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to access services beyond the scope of their authorization. This vulnerability is due to insufficient enforcement of access control in the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by directly accessing the internal services of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite policies and impact the configuration and operation of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1477|2024-09-16T16:18:51.166Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15280|2024-09-16T16:32:26.078Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15280</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting malicious code in certain sections of the interface that are visible to other users. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15280|2024-09-16T16:32:26.078Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 18:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20744|2024-09-16T18:49:07.534Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20744</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the input protection mechanisms of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to view data without proper authorization. This vulnerability exists because of a protection mechanism that relies on the existence or values of a specific input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by modifying this input to bypass the protection mechanism and sending a crafted request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view data beyond the scope of their authorization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20744|2024-09-16T18:49:07.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 03:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15269|2024-09-16T18:59:10.194Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15269</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15269|2024-09-16T18:59:10.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 18:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1456|2024-09-16T17:17:55.788Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1456</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1456|2024-09-16T17:17:55.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12689|2024-09-16T18:49:02.440Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12689</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious commands to the web-based management interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12689|2024-09-16T18:49:02.440Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1267|2024-09-16T18:08:47.755Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1267</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the dashboard widget of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper restrictions on XML entities. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting an XML-based widget on an affected server. A successful exploit could cause increased memory and CPU utilization, which could result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1267|2024-09-16T18:08:47.755Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 21:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-13T14:05:52.072Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Object Groups for Access Control Lists (ACLs) feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured access controls on managed devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect deployment of the Object Groups for ACLs feature from Cisco FMC Software to managed FTD devices in high-availability setups. After an affected device is rebooted following Object Groups for ACLs deployment, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access controls and successfully send traffic to devices that are expected to be protected by the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-13T14:05:52.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20360|2024-06-04T17:40:39.489Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20360</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not adequately validate user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain any data from the database, execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system, and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least Read Only user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20360|2024-06-04T17:40:39.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-04T17:40:51.215Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Object Groups for Access Control Lists (ACLs) feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured access controls on managed devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect deployment of the Object Groups for ACLs feature from Cisco FMC Software to managed FTD devices in high-availability setups. After an affected device is rebooted following Object Groups for ACLs deployment, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access controls and successfully send traffic to devices that are expected to be protected by the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-04T17:40:51.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20360|2024-08-01T21:59:42.328Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20360</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not adequately validate user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain any data from the database, execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system, and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least Read Only user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20360|2024-08-01T21:59:42.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20361|2024-08-01T21:59:41.652Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Object Groups for Access Control Lists (ACLs) feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured access controls on managed devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect deployment of the Object Groups for ACLs feature from Cisco FMC Software to managed FTD devices in high-availability setups. After an affected device is rebooted following Object Groups for ACLs deployment, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access controls and successfully send traffic to devices that are expected to be protected by the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20361|2024-08-01T21:59:41.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
