<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Data Center Network Manager</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Data Center Network Manager</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:22:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20449|2024-10-02T16:54:50.760Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20449</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with low privileges to execute arbitrary code on an affected device.&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability is due to improper path validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the Secure Copy Protocol (SCP) to upload malicious code to an affected device using path traversal techniques. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary&amp;nbsp;code in a specific container with the privileges of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20449|2024-10-02T16:54:50.760Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20441|2024-10-02T16:53:32.918Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20441</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a specific REST API endpoint of Cisco NDFC could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, remote attacker to learn sensitive information on an affected device.&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization controls on the affected REST API endpoint. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted API requests to the&amp;nbsp;affected endpoint. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to download config only or full backup files and learn sensitive configuration information. This vulnerability only affects a specific REST API endpoint and does not affect the web-based management interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20441|2024-10-02T16:53:32.918Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20448|2024-10-02T16:54:17.748Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20448</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC) software, formerly Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM), could allow an attacker with access to a backup file to view sensitive information.&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability is due to the improper storage of sensitive information within config only and full backup files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by parsing the contents of a backup file that is generated from an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access sensitive information, including NDFC-connected device credentials, the NDFC site manager private key, and the scheduled backup file encryption key.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20448|2024-10-02T16:54:17.748Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20490|2024-10-02T16:55:15.650Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20490</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a logging function of Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC) and Cisco Nexus Dashboard Orchestrator (NDO) could allow an attacker with access to a tech support file to view sensitive information.&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability exists because HTTP proxy credentials could be recorded in an internal log that is stored in the tech support file. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing a tech support file that is generated from an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view HTTP proxy server admin credentials in clear text that are configured on Nexus Dashboard to reach an external network.&#13;
Note: Best practice is to store debug logs and tech support files safely and to share them only with trusted parties because they may contain sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20490|2024-10-02T16:55:15.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20438|2024-10-02T16:53:23.486Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20438</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the REST API endpoints of Cisco NDFC could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, remote attacker to read or write files on an affected device.&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability exists because of missing authorization controls on some REST API endpoints. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted API requests to an affected endpoint. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform limited network-admin functions such as reading device configuration information, uploading files, and modifying uploaded files.&#13;
Note: This vulnerability only affects a subset of REST API endpoints and does not affect the web-based management interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20438|2024-10-02T16:53:23.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:53:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20477|2024-10-02T16:55:07.208Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20477</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a specific REST API endpoint of Cisco NDFC could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, remote attacker to upload or delete files on an affected device.&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability exists because of missing authorization controls on the affected REST API endpoint. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted API requests to the affected endpoint. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to upload files into a specific container or delete files from a specific folder within that container. This vulnerability only affects a specific REST API endpoint and does not affect the web-based management interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20477|2024-10-02T16:55:07.208Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20432|2024-10-02T16:53:15.038Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20432</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the REST API and web UI of Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC) could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, remote attacker to perform a command injection attack against an affected device.&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&#13;
This vulnerability is due to improper user authorization and insufficient validation of command arguments. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting crafted commands to an affected REST API endpoint or through the web UI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the CLI of a Cisco NDFC-managed device with network-admin privileges.&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&#13;
Note: This vulnerability does not affect Cisco NDFC when it is configured for storage area network (SAN) controller deployment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20432|2024-10-02T16:53:15.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20444|2024-10-02T16:54:09.855Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20444</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC), formerly Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM), could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with network-admin privileges to perform a command injection attack against an affected device.&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&#13;
This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of command arguments. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting crafted command arguments to a specific REST API endpoint. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite sensitive files or crash a specific container, which would restart on its own, causing a low-impact denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20444|2024-10-02T16:54:09.855Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:54:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
