<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco TelePresence TC Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20telepresence%20tc%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco TelePresence TC Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 21:21:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3143|2024-08-04T07:24:00.620Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20tc%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3143</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the video endpoint API (xAPI) of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) Software, Cisco TelePresence Codec (TC) Software, and Cisco RoomOS Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct directory traversal attacks on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input to the xAPI of the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the xAPI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read and write arbitrary files in the system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need either an In-Room Control or administrator account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3143|2024-08-04T07:24:00.620Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1878|2024-08-04T18:28:42.911Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20tc%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1878</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Discovery Protocol (CDP) implementation for the Cisco TelePresence Codec (TC) and Collaboration Endpoint (CE) Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to inject arbitrary shell commands that are executed by the device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of received CDP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted CDP packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary shell commands or scripts on the targeted device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1878|2024-08-04T18:28:42.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
