<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System (Management Software)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28management%20software%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System (Management Software)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 14:23:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3242|2024-08-04T07:30:58.119Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28management%20software%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3242</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the REST API of Cisco UCS Director could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative privileges to obtain confidential information from an affected device. The vulnerability exists because confidential information is returned as part of an API response. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain the API key of another user, which would allow the attacker to impersonate the account of that user on the affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have administrative privileges on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3242|2024-08-04T07:30:58.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3241|2024-08-04T07:30:56.529Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28management%20software%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3241</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the orchestration tasks of Cisco UCS Director could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a path traversal attack on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input on the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by creating a task with specific configuration parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite arbitrary files in the file system of an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3241|2024-08-04T07:30:56.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
