<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN Solution</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20sd-wan%20solution.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN Solution</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 18:24:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1614|2024-09-16T16:18:27.417Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1614</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Multiprotocol Label Switching (MPLS) packet handling function of Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain access to information stored in MPLS buffer memory. This vulnerability is due to insufficient handling of malformed MPLS packets that are processed by a device that is running Cisco SD-WAN Software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted MPLS packet to an affected device that is running Cisco SD-WAN Software or Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain unauthorized access to sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1614|2024-09-16T16:18:27.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 15:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1137|2024-09-16T16:48:46.591Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1137</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code or allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain escalated privileges on an affected system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1137|2024-09-16T16:48:46.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 04:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1279|2024-09-16T16:47:58.028Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1279</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN products could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute denial of service (DoS) attacks against an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1279|2024-09-16T16:47:58.028Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1626|2024-09-16T17:22:57.753Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1626</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the vManage web-based UI (Web UI) of the Cisco SD-WAN Solution could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to gain elevated privileges on an affected vManage device. The vulnerability is due to a failure to properly authorize certain user actions in the device configuration. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to the vManage Web UI and sending crafted HTTP requests to vManage. A successful exploit could allow attackers to gain elevated privileges and make changes to the configuration that they would not normally be authorized to make.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1626|2024-09-16T17:22:57.753Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 02:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15387|2024-09-16T16:48:53.585Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15387</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco SD-WAN Solution could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass certificate validation on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper certificate validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a system image signed with a crafted certificate to an affected device, bypassing the certificate validation. An exploit could allow an attacker to deploy a crafted system image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15387|2024-09-16T16:48:53.585Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1262|2024-09-16T16:52:48.583Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1262</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN products could allow an authenticated attacker to perform command injection attacks against an affected device, which could allow the attacker to take certain actions with root privileges on the device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1262|2024-09-16T16:52:48.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
