<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Intelligence Center</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20unified%20intelligence%20center.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Intelligence Center</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:19:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1860|2024-08-04T18:28:42.901Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20intelligence%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1860</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the dashboard gadget rendering of Cisco Unified Intelligence Center could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to obtain or manipulate sensitive information between a user&amp;rsquo;s browser and Cisco Unified Intelligence Center. The vulnerability is due to the lack of gadget validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by forcing a user to load a malicious gadget. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain sensitive information, such as current user credentials, or manipulate data between the user&amp;rsquo;s browser and Cisco Unified Intelligence Center in the context of the malicious gadget.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1860|2024-08-04T18:28:42.901Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1658|2024-08-04T18:20:28.447Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20intelligence%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1658</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unified Intelligence Center could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections in the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a malicious, customized link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on the affected device via a web browser and with the privileges of the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1658|2024-08-04T18:20:28.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20325|2024-08-01T21:59:41.553Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20intelligence%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20325</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Live Data server of Cisco Unified Intelligence Center could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker to read and modify data in a repository that belongs to an internal service on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient access control implementations on cluster configuration CLI requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a cluster configuration CLI request to specific directories on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read and modify data that is handled by an internal service on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20325|2024-08-01T21:59:41.553Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20325|2024-02-21T16:09:03.422Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20intelligence%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20325</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Live Data server of Cisco Unified Intelligence Center could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker to read and modify data in a repository that belongs to an internal service on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient access control implementations on cluster configuration CLI requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a cluster configuration CLI request to specific directories on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read and modify data that is handled by an internal service on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20325|2024-02-21T16:09:03.422Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
