<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20xe%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:42:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1281|2024-09-16T20:59:04.782Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1281</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in CLI management in Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access the underlying operating system as the root user. This vulnerability is due to the way the software handles concurrent CLI sessions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device as an administrative user and executing a sequence of commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain access to the underlying operating system as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1281|2024-09-16T20:59:04.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1376|2024-09-16T16:59:03.734Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1376</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the fast reload feature of Cisco IOS XE Software running on Cisco Catalyst 3850, Cisco Catalyst 9300, and Cisco Catalyst 9300L Series Switches could allow an authenticated, local attacker to either execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system, install and boot a malicious software image, or execute unsigned binaries on an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to improper checks performed by system boot routines. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker would need privileged access to the CLI of the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to either execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system or execute unsigned code and bypass the image verification check part of the secure boot process. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1376|2024-09-16T16:59:03.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1374|2024-09-16T18:19:46.721Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1374</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller software for the Catalyst 9000 Family of switches could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against another user of the web-based management interface of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device as a high-privileged user, adding certain configurations with malicious code in one of its fields, and persuading another user to click on it. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or to access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1374|2024-09-16T18:19:46.721Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3476|2024-09-16T18:38:56.552Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3476</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI implementation of a specific command of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to overwrite arbitrary files in the underlying host file system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of the parameters of a specific CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by issuing that command with specific parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite the content of any arbitrary file that resides on the underlying host file system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3476|2024-09-16T18:38:56.552Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3404|2024-09-16T19:41:43.871Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3404</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the persistent Telnet/Secure Shell (SSH) CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain shell access on an affected device and execute commands on the underlying operating system (OS) with root privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient enforcement of the consent token in authorizing shell access. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the persistent Telnet/SSH CLI on an affected device and requesting shell access. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain shell access on the affected device and execute commands on the underlying OS with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3404|2024-09-16T19:41:43.871Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 18:02:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12643|2024-09-16T17:02:54.236Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12643</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco REST API virtual service container for Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass authentication on the managed Cisco IOS XE device. The vulnerability is due to an improper check performed by the area of code that manages the REST API authentication service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting malicious HTTP requests to the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain the token-id of an authenticated user. This token-id could be used to bypass authentication and execute privileged actions through the interface of the REST API virtual service container on the affected Cisco IOS XE device. The REST API interface is not enabled by default and must be installed and activated separately on IOS XE devices. See the Details section for more information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12643|2024-09-16T17:02:54.236Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 18:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20915|2024-09-16T18:56:22.725Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20915</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of IPv6 VPN over MPLS (6VPE) with Zone-Based Firewall (ZBFW) of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper error handling of an IPv6 packet that is forwarded from an MPLS and ZBFW-enabled interface in a 6VPE deployment. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPv6 packet sourced from a device on the IPv6-enabled virtual routing and forwarding (VRF) interface through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to reload the device, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20915|2024-09-16T18:56:22.725Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 20:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1622|2024-09-16T20:38:05.820Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1622</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Common Open Policy Service (COPS) of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco cBR-8 Converged Broadband Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause resource exhaustion, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to a deadlock condition in the code when processing COPS packets under certain conditions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending COPS packets with high burst rates to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the CPU to consume excessive resources, which prevents other control plane processes from obtaining resources and results in a DoS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1622|2024-09-16T20:38:05.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0477|2024-09-16T19:56:37.772Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0477</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI parser of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute commands on the underlying Linux shell of an affected device with root privileges. The vulnerability exist because the affected software improperly sanitizes command arguments, failing to prevent access to certain internal data structures on an affected device. An attacker who has privileged EXEC mode (privilege level 15) access to an affected device could exploit these vulnerabilities on the device by executing CLI commands that contain custom arguments. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0477|2024-09-16T19:56:37.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15371|2024-09-16T17:13:49.704Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15371</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the shell access request mechanism of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to bypass authentication and gain unrestricted access to the root shell of an affected device. The vulnerability exists because the affected software has insufficient authentication mechanisms for certain commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by requesting access to the root shell of an affected device, after the shell access feature has been enabled. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass authentication and gain unrestricted access to the root shell of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15371|2024-09-16T17:13:49.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3487|2024-09-16T20:13:26.185Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3487</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3487|2024-09-16T20:13:26.185Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3493|2024-09-16T16:43:27.365Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3493</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3493|2024-09-16T16:43:27.365Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1356|2024-09-16T17:03:28.041Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1356</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web UI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with read-only privileges to cause the web UI software to become unresponsive and consume vty line instances, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient error handling in the web UI. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted HTTP packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the web UI software to become unresponsive and consume all available vty lines, preventing new session establishment and resulting in a DoS condition. Manual intervention would be required to regain web UI and vty session functionality. Note: These vulnerabilities do not affect the console connection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1356|2024-09-16T17:03:28.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12624|2024-09-16T19:04:26.697Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12624</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco IOS XE New Generation Wireless Controller (NGWC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on an affected device by using a web browser and with the privileges of the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12624|2024-09-16T19:04:26.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 18:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1862|2024-09-16T20:47:37.361Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1862</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based user interface (Web UI) of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute commands on the underlying Linux shell of an affected device with root privileges. The vulnerability occurs because the affected software improperly sanitizes user-supplied input. An attacker who has valid administrator access to an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a crafted input parameter on a form in the Web UI and then submitting that form. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to run arbitrary commands on the device with root privileges, which may lead to complete system compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1862|2024-09-16T20:47:37.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 19:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1611|2024-09-16T19:52:12.357Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1611</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Ethernet over GRE (EoGRE) packet processing of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Cisco Catalyst 9800 Family Wireless Controller, Embedded Wireless Controller, and Embedded Wireless on Catalyst 9000 Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper processing of malformed EoGRE packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious packets to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1611|2024-09-16T19:52:12.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1745|2024-09-16T19:09:49.692Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1745</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject arbitrary commands that are executed with elevated privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of commands supplied by the user. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to a device and submitting crafted input to the affected commands. An exploit could allow the attacker to gain root privileges on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1745|2024-09-16T19:09:49.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 23:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1390|2024-09-16T20:02:36.627Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1390</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in one of the diagnostic test CLI commands of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have valid user credentials at privilege level 15. This vulnerability exists because the affected software permits modification of the run-time memory of an affected device under specific circumstances. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the affected device and issuing a specific diagnostic test command at the CLI. A successful exploit could trigger a logic error in the code that was designed to restrict run-time memory modifications. The attacker could take advantage of this logic error to overwrite system memory locations and execute arbitrary code on the underlying Linux operating system (OS) of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1390|2024-09-16T20:02:36.627Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1749|2024-09-16T16:48:12.607Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1749</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the ingress traffic validation of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Aggregation Services Router (ASR) 900 Route Switch Processor 3 (RSP3) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to trigger a reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability exists because the software insufficiently validates ingress traffic on the ASIC used on the RSP3 platform. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a reload of the iosd process, triggering a reload of the affected device and resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1749|2024-09-16T16:48:12.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 23:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1756|2024-09-16T20:27:57.710Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1756</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute commands on the underlying Linux shell of an affected device with root privileges. The vulnerability occurs because the affected software improperly sanitizes user-supplied input. An attacker who has valid administrator access to an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a username with a malicious payload in the web UI and subsequently making a request to a specific endpoint in the web UI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to run arbitrary commands as the root user, allowing complete compromise of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1756|2024-09-16T20:27:57.710Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15368|2024-09-16T19:01:46.167Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15368</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI parser of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain access to the underlying Linux shell of an affected device and execute arbitrary commands with root privileges on the device. The vulnerability is due to the affected software improperly sanitizing command arguments to prevent modifications to the underlying Linux filesystem on a device. An attacker who has privileged EXEC mode (privilege level 15) access to an affected device could exploit this vulnerability on the device by executing CLI commands that contain crafted arguments. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to the underlying Linux shell of the affected device and execute arbitrary commands with root privileges on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15368|2024-09-16T19:01:46.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3400|2024-09-16T17:08:05.135Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3400</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to utilize parts of the web UI for which they are not authorized.The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization of web UI access requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the web UI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to utilize parts of the web UI for which they are not authorized. This could allow a Read-Only user to perform actions of an Admin user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3400|2024-09-16T17:08:05.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 18:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20694|2024-09-16T20:37:46.902Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20694</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the Resource Public Key Infrastructure (RPKI) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) process to crash, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of a specific RPKI to Router (RTR) Protocol packet header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by compromising the RPKI validator server and sending a specifically crafted RTR packet to an affected device. Alternatively, the attacker could use man-in-the-middle techniques to impersonate the RPKI validator server and send a crafted RTR response packet over the established RTR TCP connection to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition because the BGP process could constantly restart and BGP routing could become unstable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20694|2024-09-16T20:37:46.902Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3429|2024-09-16T20:33:00.558Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3429</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the WPA2 and WPA3 security implementation of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to incorrect packet processing during the WPA2 and WPA3 authentication handshake when configured for dot1x or pre-shared key (PSK) authentication key management (AKM) with 802.11r BSS Fast Transition (FT) enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted authentication packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could cause an affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3429|2024-09-16T20:33:00.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20678|2024-09-16T18:34:18.037Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20678</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the AppNav-XE feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of certain TCP segments. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a stream of crafted TCP traffic at a high rate through an interface of an affected device. That interface would need to have AppNav interception enabled. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20678|2024-09-16T18:34:18.037Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3480|2024-09-16T17:38:07.702Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3480</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Zone-Based Firewall feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload or stop forwarding traffic through the firewall. The vulnerabilities are due to incomplete handling of Layer 4 packets through the device. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a certain sequence of traffic patterns through the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload or stop forwarding traffic through the firewall, resulting in a denial of service. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3480|2024-09-16T17:38:07.702Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:52:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1433|2024-09-16T20:32:59.987Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1433</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the vDaemon process in Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a buffer overflow on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient bounds checking when the device processes traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted traffic to the device. The attacker must have a man-in-the-middle position between Cisco vManage and an associated device that is running an affected version of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software. An exploit could allow the attacker to conduct a controllable buffer overflow attack (and possibly execute arbitrary commands as the root user) or cause a device reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1433|2024-09-16T20:32:59.987Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1755|2024-09-16T19:30:18.460Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1755</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Web Services Management Agent (WSMA) function of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary Cisco IOS commands as a privilege level 15 user. The vulnerability occurs because the affected software improperly sanitizes user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting crafted HTTP requests to the targeted application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1755|2024-09-16T19:30:18.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3503|2024-09-16T16:18:22.540Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3503</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the file system permissions of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to obtain read and write access to critical configuration or system files. The vulnerability is due to insufficient file system permissions on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to an affected device's guest shell, and accessing or modifying restricted files. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view or modify restricted information or configurations that are normally not accessible to system administrators.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3503|2024-09-16T16:18:22.540Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20870|2024-09-16T18:08:44.095Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20870</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the egress MPLS packet processing function of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 3650, Catalyst 3850, and Catalyst 9000 Family Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of IPv4 traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed packet out of an affected MPLS-enabled interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20870|2024-09-16T18:08:44.095Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 20:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20810|2024-09-16T16:38:35.712Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20810</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Catalyst 9000 Family could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive information. This vulnerability is due to insufficient restrictions that allow a sensitive configuration detail to be disclosed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by retrieving data through SNMP read-only community access. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view Service Set Identifier (SSID) preshared keys (PSKs) that are configured on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20810|2024-09-16T16:38:35.712Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 18:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20856|2024-09-16T17:43:55.408Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20856</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the processing of Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) Mobility messages in Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Catalyst 9000 Family could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error and improper management of resources related to the handling of CAPWAP Mobility messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted CAPWAP Mobility packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust resources on the affected device. This would cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20856|2024-09-16T17:43:55.408Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 18:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20681|2024-09-16T19:14:46.619Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20681</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family Switches and Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family Wireless Controllers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to level 15 on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user privileges after the user executes certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to an affected device as a low-privileged user and then executing certain CLI commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands with level 15 privileges on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20681|2024-09-16T19:14:46.619Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1616|2024-09-16T19:55:45.376Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1616</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the H.323 application level gateway (ALG) used by the Network Address Translation (NAT) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the ALG. This vulnerability is due to insufficient data validation of traffic that is traversing the ALG. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted traffic to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the ALG and open connections that should not be allowed to a remote device located behind the ALG. Note: This vulnerability has been publicly discussed as NAT Slipstreaming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1616|2024-09-16T19:55:45.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1453|2024-09-16T19:01:41.133Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1453</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the software image verification functionality of Cisco IOS XE Software for the Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family of switches could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to execute unsigned code at system boot time. The vulnerability is due to an improper check in the code function that manages the verification of the digital signatures of system image files during the initial boot process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by loading unsigned software on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to boot a malicious software image or execute unsigned code and bypass the image verification check part of the secure boot process of an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have unauthenticated physical access to the device or obtain privileged access to the root shell on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1453|2024-09-16T19:01:41.133Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20851|2024-09-16T17:28:09.001Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20851</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform an injection attack against an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input to the web UI API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root privileges. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have valid Administrator privileges on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20851|2024-09-16T17:28:09.001Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 18:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3513|2024-09-16T16:43:31.921Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3513</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the initialization routines that are executed during bootup of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco ASR 900 Series Aggregation Services Routers with a Route Switch Processor 3 (RSP3) installed could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to execute persistent code at bootup and break the chain of trust. These vulnerabilities are due to incorrect validations by boot scripts when specific ROM monitor (ROMMON) variables are set. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by copying a specific file to the local file system of an affected device and defining specific ROMMON variables. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to run arbitrary code on the underlying operating system (OS) with root privileges. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker would need to have access to the root shell on the device or have physical access to the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3513|2024-09-16T16:43:31.921Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3421|2024-09-16T18:55:40.734Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3421</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Zone-Based Firewall feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload or stop forwarding traffic through the firewall. The vulnerabilities are due to incomplete handling of Layer 4 packets through the device. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a certain sequence of traffic patterns through the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload or stop forwarding traffic through the firewall, resulting in a denial of service. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3421|2024-09-16T18:55:40.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 18:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1435|2024-09-16T18:45:15.044Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1435</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary commands that can be executed as the root user. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the web UI of an affected device with arbitrary commands injected into a portion of the request. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1435|2024-09-16T18:45:15.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0480|2024-09-16T18:07:58.296Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0480</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the errdisable per VLAN feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the device to crash, leading to a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to a race condition that occurs when the VLAN and port enter an errdisabled state, resulting in an incorrect state in the software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending frames that trigger the errdisable condition. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash, leading to a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0480|2024-09-16T18:07:58.296Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20676|2024-09-16T18:54:55.467Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20676</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Tool Command Language (Tcl) interpreter of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to escalate from privilege level 15 to root-level privileges. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of data that is passed into the Tcl interpreter. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by loading malicious Tcl code on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root. By default, Tcl shell access requires privilege level 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20676|2024-09-16T18:54:55.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1454|2024-09-16T20:48:21.990Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1454</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access the underlying operating system with root privileges. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient input validation of certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by authenticating to the device and submitting crafted input to the CLI. The attacker must be authenticated as an administrative user to execute the affected commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access the underlying operating system with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1454|2024-09-16T20:48:21.990Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0471|2024-09-16T20:17:27.242Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0471</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Discovery Protocol (CDP) module of Cisco IOS XE Software Releases 16.6.1 and 16.6.2 could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a memory leak that may lead to a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of certain CDP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain CDP packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could cause an affected device to continuously consume memory and eventually result in a memory allocation failure that leads to a crash, triggering a reload of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0471|2024-09-16T20:17:27.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3416|2024-09-16T20:47:58.826Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3416</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the initialization routines that are executed during bootup of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco ASR 900 Series Aggregation Services Routers with a Route Switch Processor 3 (RSP3) installed could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to execute persistent code at bootup and break the chain of trust. These vulnerabilities are due to incorrect validations by boot scripts when specific ROM monitor (ROMMON) variables are set. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by copying a specific file to the local file system of an affected device and defining specific ROMMON variables. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to run arbitrary code on the underlying operating system (OS) with root privileges. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker would need to have access to the root shell on the device or have physical access to the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3416|2024-09-16T20:47:58.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 18:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3393|2024-09-16T17:47:39.174Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3393</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the application-hosting subsystem of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device. The attacker could execute IOS XE commands outside the application-hosting subsystem Docker container as well as on the underlying Linux operating system. These commands could be run as the root user. The vulnerability is due to a combination of two factors: (a) incomplete input validation of the user payload of CLI commands, and (b) improper role-based access control (RBAC) when commands are issued at the command line within the application-hosting subsystem. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using a CLI command with crafted user input. A successful exploit could allow the lower-privileged attacker to execute arbitrary CLI commands with root privileges. The attacker would need valid user credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3393|2024-09-16T17:47:39.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 18:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1403|2024-09-16T17:39:05.269Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1403</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site WebSocket hijacking (CSWSH) attack and cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient HTTP protections in the web UI on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the web UI to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to corrupt memory on the affected device, forcing it to reload and causing a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1403|2024-09-16T17:39:05.269Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20855|2024-09-16T19:51:07.946Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20855</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the self-healing functionality of Cisco IOS XE Software for Embedded Wireless Controllers on Catalyst Access Points could allow an authenticated, local attacker to escape the restricted controller shell and execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of the access point. This vulnerability is due to improper checks throughout the restart of certain system processes. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging on to an affected device and executing certain CLI commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying OS as root. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid credentials for a privilege level 15 user of the wireless controller.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20855|2024-09-16T19:51:07.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 18:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12646|2024-09-16T19:14:40.922Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12646</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Network Address Translation (NAT) Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) Application Layer Gateway (ALG) of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload. The vulnerability is due to improper processing of transient SIP packets on which NAT is performed on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using UDP port 5060 to send crafted SIP packets through an affected device that is performing NAT for SIP packets. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12646|2024-09-16T19:14:40.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 20:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1565|2024-09-16T16:43:08.618Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1565</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit the vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1565|2024-09-16T16:43:08.618Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20837|2024-09-16T19:39:57.433Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20837</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DNS application layer gateway (ALG) functionality that is used by Network Address Translation (NAT) in Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an affected device inspects certain TCP DNS packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted DNS packets through the affected device that is performing NAT for DNS packets. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on the affected device. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited only by sending IPv4 TCP packets through an affected device. This vulnerability cannot be exploited by sending IPv6 traffic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20837|2024-09-16T19:39:57.433Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 20:43:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1432|2024-09-16T19:24:44.097Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1432</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system as the root user. The attacker must be authenticated on the affected device as a low-privileged user to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting arbitrary commands to a file as a lower-privileged user. The commands are then executed on the device by the root user. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1432|2024-09-16T19:24:44.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20848|2024-09-16T17:03:33.757Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20848</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the UDP processing functionality of Cisco IOS XE Software for Embedded Wireless Controllers on Catalyst 9100 Series Access Points could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to the improper processing of UDP datagrams. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious UDP datagrams to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20848|2024-09-16T17:03:33.757Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 18:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3489|2024-09-16T20:32:46.245Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3489</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3489|2024-09-16T20:32:46.245Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:52:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1384|2024-09-16T17:18:36.802Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1384</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco IOx application hosting environment of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject commands into the underlying operating system as the root user. This vulnerability is due to incomplete validation of fields in the application packages loaded onto IOx. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by creating a crafted application .tar file and loading it onto the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform command injection into the underlying operating system as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1384|2024-09-16T17:18:36.802Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34767|2024-09-16T18:13:05.150Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34767</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in IPv6 traffic processing of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a Layer 2 (L2) loop in a configured VLAN, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition for that VLAN. The vulnerability is due to a logic error when processing specific link-local IPv6 traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPv6 packet that would flow inbound through the wired interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause traffic drops in the affected VLAN, thus triggering the DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34767|2024-09-16T18:13:05.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20324|2024-08-27T20:50:51.192Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20324</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to access WLAN configuration details including passwords.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper privilege checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the show and show tech wireless CLI commands to access configuration details, including passwords. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access configuration details that they are not authorized to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20324|2024-08-27T20:50:51.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20278|2024-08-15T16:45:09.481Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20278</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NETCONF feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input over NETCONF to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges from Administrator to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20278|2024-08-15T16:45:09.481Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T15:33:37.498Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T15:33:37.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-06-20T20:52:30.286Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-06-20T20:52:30.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-06-20T20:50:12.348Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-06-20T20:50:12.348Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-03-27T17:03:54.505Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-03-27T17:03:54.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-03-27T16:49:03.113Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-03-27T16:49:03.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20306|2024-03-27T16:58:22.583Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Unified Threat Defense (UTD) configuration CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying host operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have level 15 privileges on the affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20306|2024-03-27T16:58:22.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-04-03T16:36:06.520Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-04-03T16:36:06.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20259|2024-03-27T16:53:53.073Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP snooping feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a crafted IPv4 DHCP request packet being mishandled when endpoint analytics are enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCP request through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; Note: The attack vector is listed as network because a DHCP relay anywhere on the network could allow exploits from networks other than the adjacent one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20259|2024-03-27T16:53:53.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20278|2024-03-27T16:59:12.963Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20278</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NETCONF feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input over NETCONF to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges from Administrator to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20278|2024-03-27T16:59:12.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20324|2024-03-27T16:55:53.837Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20324</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to access WLAN configuration details including passwords.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper privilege checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the show and show tech wireless CLI commands to access configuration details, including passwords. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access configuration details that they are not authorized to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20324|2024-03-27T16:55:53.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20309|2024-03-27T17:02:19.749Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in auxiliary asynchronous port (AUX) functions of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause an affected device to reload or stop responding.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific ingress traffic when flow control hardware is enabled on the AUX port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by reverse telnetting to the AUX port and sending specific data after connecting. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reset or stop responding, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20309|2024-03-27T17:02:19.749Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20313|2024-04-24T20:42:10.379Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20313</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of OSPF updates that are processed by a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF update to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20313|2024-04-24T20:42:10.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-03-27T16:57:27.974Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-03-27T16:57:27.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20303|2024-06-04T17:39:55.892Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20303</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multicast DNS (mDNS) gateway feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Wireless LAN Controllers (WLCs) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper management of mDNS client entries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the wireless network and sending a continuous stream of specific mDNS packets. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the wireless controller to have high CPU utilization, which could lead to access points (APs) losing their connection to the controller and result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20303|2024-06-04T17:39:55.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-06-20T17:42:35.196Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-06-20T17:42:35.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-07-02T16:25:58.752Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-07-02T16:25:58.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-07-02T16:25:13.272Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-07-02T16:25:13.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-07-02T16:23:39.427Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-07-02T16:23:39.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20309|2024-08-01T21:59:41.337Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in auxiliary asynchronous port (AUX) functions of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause an affected device to reload or stop responding.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific ingress traffic when flow control hardware is enabled on the AUX port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by reverse telnetting to the AUX port and sending specific data after connecting. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reset or stop responding, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20309|2024-08-01T21:59:41.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20259|2024-08-01T21:52:31.719Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP snooping feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a crafted IPv4 DHCP request packet being mishandled when endpoint analytics are enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCP request through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; Note: The attack vector is listed as network because a DHCP relay anywhere on the network could allow exploits from networks other than the adjacent one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20259|2024-08-01T21:52:31.719Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20324|2024-08-01T21:59:41.715Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20324</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to access WLAN configuration details including passwords.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper privilege checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the show and show tech wireless CLI commands to access configuration details, including passwords. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access configuration details that they are not authorized to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20324|2024-08-01T21:59:41.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20303|2024-08-01T21:59:41.376Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20303</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multicast DNS (mDNS) gateway feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Wireless LAN Controllers (WLCs) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper management of mDNS client entries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the wireless network and sending a continuous stream of specific mDNS packets. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the wireless controller to have high CPU utilization, which could lead to access points (APs) losing their connection to the controller and result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20303|2024-08-01T21:59:41.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-08-01T21:59:42.311Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-08-01T21:59:42.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-08-01T21:59:42.197Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-08-01T21:59:42.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T21:52:31.616Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T21:52:31.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20278|2024-08-01T21:59:41.100Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20278</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NETCONF feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input over NETCONF to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges from Administrator to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20278|2024-08-01T21:59:41.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20306|2024-08-01T21:59:41.650Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Unified Threat Defense (UTD) configuration CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying host operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have level 15 privileges on the affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20306|2024-08-01T21:59:41.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-08-01T21:59:41.851Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-08-01T21:59:41.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20313|2024-08-01T21:59:42.856Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20313</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of OSPF updates that are processed by a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF update to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20313|2024-08-01T21:59:42.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20309|2024-08-09T18:34:29.824Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in auxiliary asynchronous port (AUX) functions of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause an affected device to reload or stop responding.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific ingress traffic when flow control hardware is enabled on the AUX port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by reverse telnetting to the AUX port and sending specific data after connecting. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reset or stop responding, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20309|2024-08-09T18:34:29.824Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20313|2024-08-09T18:34:02.110Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20313</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of OSPF updates that are processed by a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF update to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20313|2024-08-09T18:34:02.110Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20306|2024-08-16T18:48:47.441Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Unified Threat Defense (UTD) configuration CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying host operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have level 15 privileges on the affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20306|2024-08-16T18:48:47.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20259|2024-08-27T21:04:37.666Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP snooping feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a crafted IPv4 DHCP request packet being mishandled when endpoint analytics are enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCP request through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; Note: The attack vector is listed as network because a DHCP relay anywhere on the network could allow exploits from networks other than the adjacent one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20259|2024-08-27T21:04:37.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
