<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Data Center Network Manager</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Data Center Network Manager</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 18:24:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3523|2024-08-04T07:37:54.653Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3523</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3523|2024-08-04T07:37:54.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3349|2024-08-04T07:30:58.148Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3349</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface on an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a customized link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3349|2024-08-04T07:30:58.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3386|2024-08-04T07:30:58.392Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3386</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the REST API endpoint of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with a low-privileged account to bypass authorization on the API of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization of certain API functions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the API using low-privileged credentials. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions through the REST API with administrative privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3386|2024-08-04T07:30:58.392Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3376|2024-08-04T07:30:58.164Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3376</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Device Manager application of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass authentication and execute arbitrary actions on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a failure in the software to perform proper authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by browsing to one of the hosted URLs in Cisco DCNM. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to interact with and use certain functions within the Cisco DCNM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3376|2024-08-04T07:30:58.164Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3348|2024-08-04T07:30:58.150Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3348</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface on an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a customized link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3348|2024-08-04T07:30:58.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3384|2024-08-04T07:30:58.169Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3384</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in specific REST API endpoints of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of the logged-in user. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input to the API. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to inject arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3384|2024-08-04T07:30:58.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3383|2024-08-04T07:30:58.214Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3383</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the archive utility of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct directory traversal attacks on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a lack of proper input validation of paths that are embedded within archive files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to write arbitrary files in the system with the privileges of the logged-in user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3383|2024-08-04T07:30:58.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3461|2024-08-04T07:37:54.875Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3461</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to obtain confidential information from an affected device. The vulnerability is due to missing authentication on a specific part of the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read confidential information from an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3461|2024-08-04T07:37:54.875Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3114|2024-08-04T07:24:00.502Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3114</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a malicious link while having an active session on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privilege level of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3114|2024-08-04T07:24:00.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3522|2024-08-04T07:37:54.662Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3522</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to bypass authorization on an affected device and access sensitive information that is related to the device. The vulnerability exists because the affected software allows users to access resources that are intended for administrators only. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted URL to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to add, delete, and edit certain network configurations in the same manner as a user with administrative privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3522|2024-08-04T07:37:54.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3356|2024-08-04T07:30:58.711Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3356</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interacting with the interface in a way that injects malicious content in a log file. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3356|2024-08-04T07:30:58.711Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3355|2024-08-04T07:30:58.197Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3355</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative credentials to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting malicious data into a specific data field in the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need administrative credentials on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3355|2024-08-04T07:30:58.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3382|2024-08-04T07:30:58.193Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3382</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the REST API of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass authentication and execute arbitrary actions with administrative privileges on an affected device. The vulnerability exists because different installations share a static encryption key. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the static key to craft a valid session token. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions through the REST API with administrative privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3382|2024-08-04T07:30:58.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3354|2024-08-04T07:30:58.206Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3354</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative credentials to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting malicious data into a specific data field in the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need administrative credentials on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3354|2024-08-04T07:30:58.206Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3112|2024-08-04T07:23:59.955Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3112</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the REST API endpoint of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges on the application. The vulnerability is due to insufficient access control validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating with a low-privilege account and sending a crafted request to the API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to interact with the API with administrative privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3112|2024-08-04T07:23:59.955Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3521|2024-08-04T07:37:54.644Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3521</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a specific REST API of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct directory traversal attacks on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input to the API. An attacker with a low-privileged account could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read arbitrary files on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3521|2024-08-04T07:37:54.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3519|2024-08-04T07:37:54.652Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3519</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a specific REST API method of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a path traversal attack on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input to the API. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite arbitrary files on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3519|2024-08-04T07:37:54.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3460|2024-08-04T07:37:54.964Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3460</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting a request from a user and injecting malicious data into an HTTP header. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3460|2024-08-04T07:37:54.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3439|2024-08-04T07:37:54.313Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3439</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting malicious data into a specific data field in the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3439|2024-08-04T07:37:54.313Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3520|2024-08-04T07:37:54.661Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3520</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to obtain confidential information from an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient protection of confidential information on an affected device. An attacker at any privilege level could exploit this vulnerability by accessing local filesystems and extracting sensitive information from them. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view sensitive data, which they could use to elevate their privilege.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3520|2024-08-04T07:37:54.661Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3113|2024-08-04T07:23:59.947Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3113</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3113|2024-08-04T07:23:59.947Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3518|2024-08-04T07:37:54.680Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3518</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of the affected software. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3518|2024-08-04T07:37:54.680Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3377|2024-08-04T07:30:58.203Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3377</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Device Manager application of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary commands on the affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted arguments to a specific field within the application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to run commands as the administrator on the DCNM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3377|2024-08-04T07:30:58.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3462|2024-08-04T07:37:54.475Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3462</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-submitted parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application and sending malicious requests to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain and modify sensitive information that is stored in the underlying database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3462|2024-08-04T07:37:54.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3380|2024-08-04T07:30:58.325Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3380</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to root and execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient restrictions during the execution of an affected CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating as the fmserver user and submitting malicious input to a specific command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root and execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3380|2024-08-04T07:30:58.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20348|2024-08-01T21:59:41.558Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20348</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Out-of-Band (OOB) Plug and Play (PnP) feature of Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to read arbitrary files.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an unauthenticated provisioning web server. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability through direct web requests to the provisioning server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read sensitive files in the PnP container that could facilitate further attacks on the PnP infrastructure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20348|2024-08-01T21:59:41.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20281|2024-08-01T21:59:41.178Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20281</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Nexus Dashboard and Cisco Nexus Dashboard hosted services could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privilege level of the affected user. If the affected user has administrative privileges, these actions could include modifying the system configuration and creating new privileged accounts.
&#13; Note: There are internal security mechanisms in place that limit the scope of this exploit, reducing the Security Impact Rating of this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20281|2024-08-01T21:59:41.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20348|2024-06-04T17:40:12.463Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20348</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Out-of-Band (OOB) Plug and Play (PnP) feature of Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to read arbitrary files.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an unauthenticated provisioning web server. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability through direct web requests to the provisioning server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read sensitive files in the PnP container that could facilitate further attacks on the PnP infrastructure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20348|2024-06-04T17:40:12.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20281|2024-06-04T17:40:22.646Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20281</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Nexus Dashboard and Cisco Nexus Dashboard hosted services could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privilege level of the affected user. If the affected user has administrative privileges, these actions could include modifying the system configuration and creating new privileged accounts.
&#13; Note: There are internal security mechanisms in place that limit the scope of this exploit, reducing the Security Impact Rating of this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20281|2024-06-04T17:40:22.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
