<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN vManage</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN vManage</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 10:22:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20930|2024-08-03T02:31:57.960Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20930</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to overwrite and possibly corrupt files on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting arbitrary commands that are executed as the root user account. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite arbitrary system files, which could result in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20930|2024-08-03T02:31:57.960Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20747|2024-08-03T02:24:49.306Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20747</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the History API of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to gain access to sensitive information on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient API authorization checking on the underlying operating system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted API request to Cisco vManage as a lower-privileged user and gaining access to sensitive information that they would not normally be authorized to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20747|2024-08-03T02:24:49.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20735|2024-08-03T02:24:49.341Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20735</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privilege level of the affected user. These actions could include modifying the system configuration and deleting accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20735|2024-08-03T02:24:49.341Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20830|2024-08-03T02:24:49.961Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20830</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in authentication mechanism of Cisco Software-Defined Application Visibility and Control (SD-AVC) on Cisco vManage could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access the GUI of Cisco SD-AVC without authentication. This vulnerability exists because the GUI is accessible on self-managed cloud installations or local server installations of Cisco vManage. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the exposed GUI of Cisco SD-AVC. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view managed device names, SD-AVC logs, and SD-AVC DNS server IP addresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20830|2024-08-03T02:24:49.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20734|2024-08-03T02:24:49.315Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20734</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to view sensitive information on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient file system restrictions. An authenticated attacker with netadmin privileges could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the vshell of an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read sensitive information on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20734|2024-08-03T02:24:49.315Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20844|2024-08-03T02:24:50.064Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20844</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in authentication mechanism of Cisco Software-Defined Application Visibility and Control (SD-AVC) on Cisco vManage could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access the GUI of Cisco SD-AVC using a default static username and password combination. This vulnerability exists because the GUI is accessible on self-managed cloud installations or local server installations of Cisco vManage. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the exposed GUI of Cisco SD-AVC. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view managed device names, SD-AVC logs, and SD-AVC DNS server IP addresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20844|2024-08-03T02:24:50.064Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20696|2024-08-03T02:24:48.467Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20696</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the binding configuration of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software containers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker who has access to the VPN0 logical network to also access the messaging service ports on an affected system. This vulnerability exists because the messaging server container ports on an affected system lack sufficient protection mechanisms. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the messaging service ports of the affected system. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must be able to send network traffic to interfaces within the VPN0 logical network. This network may be restricted to protect logical or physical adjacent networks, depending on device deployment configuration. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view and inject messages into the messaging service, which can cause configuration changes or cause the system to reload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20696|2024-08-03T02:24:48.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20739|2024-08-03T02:24:49.338Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20739</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system as the root user. The attacker must be authenticated on the affected system as a low-privileged user to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because a file leveraged by a root user is executed when a low-privileged user runs specific commands on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting arbitrary commands to a specific file as a lower-privileged user and then waiting until an admin user executes specific commands. The commands would then be executed on the device by the root user. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to escalate their privileges on the affected system from a low-privileged user to the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20739|2024-08-03T02:24:49.338Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
