<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software 16.1.1</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%2016.1.1.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software 16.1.1</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 22:22:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3474|2024-09-16T21:03:36.223Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%2016.1.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3474</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web management framework of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with read-only privileges to gain unauthorized read access to sensitive data or cause the web management software to hang or crash, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3474|2024-09-16T21:03:36.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3475|2024-09-16T16:33:14.079Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%2016.1.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3475</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web management framework of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with read-only privileges to gain unauthorized read access to sensitive data or cause the web management software to hang or crash, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3475|2024-09-16T16:33:14.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12658|2024-09-16T20:27:39.462Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%2016.1.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12658</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the filesystem resource management code of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to exhaust filesystem resources on an affected device and cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to ineffective management of the underlying filesystem resources. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by performing specific actions that result in messages being sent to specific operating system log files. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust available filesystem space on an affected device. This could cause the device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition for clients whose network traffic is transiting the device. Upon reload of the device, the impacted filesystem space is cleared, and the device will return to normal operation. However, continued exploitation of this vulnerability could cause subsequent forced crashes and reloads, which could lead to an extended DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12658|2024-09-16T20:27:39.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 20:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3425|2024-09-16T20:01:19.545Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%2016.1.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3425</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web management framework of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with read-only privileges to elevate privileges to the level of an Administrator user on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3425|2024-09-16T20:01:19.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 18:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
