<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco RoomOS Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20roomos%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco RoomOS Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 04:24:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20811|2024-09-17T02:27:07.493Z -- cisco -- cisco%20roomos%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20811</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) Software and Cisco RoomOS Software could allow an attacker to conduct path traversal attacks, view sensitive data, or write arbitrary files on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20811|2024-09-17T02:27:07.493Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 14:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34758|2024-09-17T01:36:52.919Z -- cisco -- cisco%20roomos%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34758</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the memory management of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) Software and Cisco RoomOS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to corrupt a shared memory segment, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to insufficient access controls to a shared memory resource. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by corrupting a shared memory segment on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload. The device will recover from the corruption upon reboot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34758|2024-09-17T01:36:52.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 19:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20783|2024-09-17T03:17:45.870Z -- cisco -- cisco%20roomos%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20783</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the packet processing functionality of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) Software and Cisco RoomOS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted H.323 traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to either reboot normally or reboot into maintenance mode, which could result in a DoS condition on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20783|2024-09-17T03:17:45.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 18:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20794|2024-09-17T03:32:57.624Z -- cisco -- cisco%20roomos%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20794</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web engine of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) Software and Cisco RoomOS Software could allow a remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition, view sensitive data on an affected device, or redirect users to an attacker-controlled destination. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20794|2024-09-17T03:32:57.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 17:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20955|2024-09-17T03:02:51.839Z -- cisco -- cisco%20roomos%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20955</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) Software and Cisco RoomOS Software could allow an attacker to conduct path traversal attacks, view sensitive data, or write arbitrary files on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20955|2024-09-17T03:02:51.839Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 14:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
