<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Contact Center Express</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20unified%20contact%20center%20express.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Contact Center Express</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 04:24:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1395|2024-09-17T00:45:40.081Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20contact%20center%20express
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1395</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unified Intelligence Center could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1395|2024-09-17T00:45:40.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 17:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1670|2024-09-17T02:27:56.507Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20contact%20center%20express
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1670</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unified Intelligence Center Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web interface of an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of a user-supplied value. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by convincing a user to click a specific link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to submit arbitrary requests to the affected system via a web browser with the privileges of the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1670|2024-09-17T02:27:56.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15259|2024-09-17T00:42:10.610Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20contact%20center%20express
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Unified Contact Center Express (UCCX) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct an HTTP response splitting attack. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of some parameters that are passed to the web server of the affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by convincing a user to follow a malicious link or by intercepting a user request on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform cross-site scripting attacks, web cache poisoning, access sensitive browser-based information, and similar exploits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15259|2024-09-17T00:42:10.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1463|2024-09-17T00:06:05.859Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20contact%20center%20express
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1463</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unified Intelligence Center Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of an affected interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1463|2024-09-17T00:06:05.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 04:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1254|2024-09-17T03:32:44.080Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20contact%20center%20express
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1254</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Finesse could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of the affected software. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by injecting malicious code into the web-based management interface and persuading a user to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. An attacker needs valid administrator credentials to inject the malicious script code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1254|2024-09-17T03:32:44.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 06:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
