<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Webex Meetings</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20webex%20meetings.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Webex Meetings</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40128|2024-08-04T02:27:31.615Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40128</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the account activation feature of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to send an account activation email with an activation link that points to an arbitrary domain. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the account activation page of Cisco Webex Meetings. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send to any recipient an account activation email that contains a tampered activation link, which could direct the user to an attacker-controlled website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40128|2024-08-04T02:27:31.615Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3472|2024-08-04T07:37:54.293Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3472</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the contacts feature of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with a legitimate user account to access sensitive information. The vulnerability is due to improper access restrictions on users who are added within user contacts. An attacker on one Webex Meetings site could exploit this vulnerability by sending specially crafted requests to the Webex Meetings site. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view the details of users on another Webex site, including user names and email addresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3472|2024-08-04T07:37:54.293Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3194|2024-08-04T07:24:00.790Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3194</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Network Recording Player for Microsoft Windows and Cisco Webex Player for Microsoft Windows could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected system. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient validation of certain elements with a Webex recording stored in either the Advanced Recording Format (ARF) or the Webex Recording Format (WRF). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a user a malicious ARF or WRF file through a link or email attachment and persuading the user to open the file with the affected software on the local system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected system with the privileges of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3194|2024-08-04T07:24:00.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3542|2024-08-04T07:37:54.939Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3542</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Training could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to join a password-protected meeting without providing the meeting password. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of input to API requests that are a part of meeting join flow. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending an API request to the application, which would return a URL that includes a meeting join page that is prepopulated with the meeting username and password. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to join the password-protected meeting. The attacker would be visible in the attendee list of the meeting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3542|2024-08-04T07:37:54.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34743|2024-08-04T00:19:48.163Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34743</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the application integration feature of Cisco Webex Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to authorize an external application to integrate with and access a user's account without that user's express consent. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of cross-site request forgery (CSRF) tokens. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by convincing a targeted user who is currently authenticated to Cisco Webex Software to follow a link designed to pass malicious input to the Cisco Webex Software application authorization interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause Cisco Webex Software to authorize an application on the user's behalf without the express consent of the user, possibly allowing external applications to read data from that user's profile.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34743|2024-08-04T00:19:48.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3413|2024-08-04T07:30:58.173Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3413</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the scheduled meeting template feature of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to delete a scheduled meeting template that belongs to another user in their organization. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization enforcement for requests to delete scheduled meeting templates. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the Webex Meetings interface to delete a scheduled meeting template. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to delete a scheduled meeting template that belongs to a user other than themselves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3413|2024-08-04T07:30:58.173Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3501|2024-08-04T07:37:54.338Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3501</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the user interface of Cisco Webex Meetings Desktop App could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain restricted information from other Webex users. These vulnerabilities are due to improper input validation of parameters returned to the application from a web site. An attacker with a valid Webex account could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user to follow a URL that is designed to return malicious path parameters to the affected software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain restricted information from other Webex users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3501|2024-08-04T07:37:54.338Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3502|2024-08-04T07:37:54.322Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3502</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the user interface of Cisco Webex Meetings Desktop App could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain restricted information from other Webex users. These vulnerabilities are due to improper input validation of parameters returned to the application from a web site. An attacker with a valid Webex account could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user to follow a URL that is designed to return malicious path parameters to the affected software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain restricted information from other Webex users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3502|2024-08-04T07:37:54.322Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3463|2024-08-04T07:37:54.294Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3463</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of the affected service. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of the affected service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3463|2024-08-04T07:37:54.294Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3541|2024-08-04T07:37:55.032Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3541</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the media engine component of Cisco Webex Meetings Client for Windows, Cisco Webex Meetings Desktop App for Windows, and Cisco Webex Teams for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain access to sensitive information. The vulnerability is due to unsafe logging of authentication requests by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by reading log files that are stored in the application directory. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to sensitive information, which could be used in further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3541|2024-08-04T07:37:55.032Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3412|2024-08-04T07:30:58.384Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3412</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the scheduled meeting template feature of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to create a scheduled meeting template that would belong to another user in their organization. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization enforcement for the creation of scheduled meeting templates. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the Webex Meetings interface to create a scheduled meeting template. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to create a scheduled meeting template that would belong to a user other than themselves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3412|2024-08-04T07:30:58.384Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3440|2024-08-04T07:37:54.386Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3440</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings Desktop App for Windows could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to overwrite arbitrary files on an end-user system. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of URL parameters that are sent from a website to the affected application. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to follow a URL to a website that is designed to submit crafted input to the affected application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite arbitrary files on the affected system, possibly corrupting or deleting critical system files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3440|2024-08-04T07:37:54.386Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27126|2024-08-04T16:11:35.638Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27126</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in an API of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site scripting attacks. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input to an application programmatic interface (API) within Cisco Webex Meetings. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by convincing a targeted user to follow a link designed to submit malicious input to the API used by Cisco Webex Meetings. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct cross-site scripting attacks and potentially gain access to sensitive browser-based information from the system of a targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27126|2024-08-04T16:11:35.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3182|2024-08-04T07:24:00.769Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3182</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multicast DNS (mDNS) protocol configuration of Cisco Webex Meetings Client for MacOS could allow an unauthenticated adjacent attacker to obtain sensitive information about the device on which the Webex client is running. The vulnerability exists because sensitive information is included in the mDNS reply. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by doing an mDNS query for a particular service against an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3182|2024-08-04T07:24:00.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3142|2024-08-04T07:24:00.718Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3142</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings Suite sites and Cisco Webex Meetings Online sites could allow an unauthenticated, remote attendee to join a password-protected meeting without providing the meeting password. The connection attempt must initiate from a Webex mobile application for either iOS or Android. The vulnerability is due to unintended meeting information exposure in a specific meeting join flow for mobile applications. An unauthorized attendee could exploit this vulnerability by accessing a known meeting ID or meeting URL from the mobile device&amp;rsquo;s web browser. The browser will then request to launch the device&amp;rsquo;s Webex mobile application. A successful exploit could allow the unauthorized attendee to join the password-protected meeting. The unauthorized attendee will be visible in the attendee list of the meeting as a mobile attendee. Cisco has applied updates that address this vulnerability and no user action is required. This vulnerability affects Cisco Webex Meetings Suite sites and Cisco Webex Meetings Online sites releases earlier than 39.11.5 and 40.1.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3142|2024-08-04T07:24:00.718Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
