<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco WebEx Event Center</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20webex%20event%20center.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco WebEx Event Center</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:21:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15442|2024-09-16T18:23:35.518Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20event%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15442</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the update service of Cisco Webex Meetings Desktop App for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as a privileged user. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by invoking the update service command with a crafted argument. An exploit could allow the attacker to run arbitrary commands with SYSTEM user privileges. While the CVSS Attack Vector metric denotes the requirement for an attacker to have local access, administrators should be aware that in Active Directory deployments, the vulnerability could be exploited remotely by leveraging the operating system remote management tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15442|2024-09-16T18:23:35.518Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3116|2024-09-16T22:50:48.971Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20event%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3116</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the way Cisco Webex applications process Universal Communications Format (UCF) files could allow an attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of UCF media files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a user a malicious UCF file through a link or email attachment and persuading the user to open the file with the affected software on the local system. A successful exploit would cause the application to quit unexpectedly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3116|2024-09-16T22:50:48.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:25:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
