<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco BroadWorks</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20broadworks.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco BroadWorks</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:23:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20020|2024-08-02T08:57:35.651Z -- cisco -- cisco%20broadworks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20020</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Device Management Servlet application of Cisco BroadWorks Application Delivery Platform and Cisco BroadWorks Xtended Services Platform could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation when parsing HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a sustained stream of crafted requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause all subsequent requests to be dropped, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20020|2024-08-02T08:57:35.651Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 01:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20019|2024-08-02T08:57:35.601Z -- cisco -- cisco%20broadworks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20019</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco BroadWorks Application Delivery Platform, Cisco BroadWorks Application Server, and Cisco BroadWorks Xtended Services Platform could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20019|2024-08-02T08:57:35.601Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 01:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
