<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco RV180W Wireless-N Multifunction VPN Router</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20rv180w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco RV180W Wireless-N Multifunction VPN Router</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:24:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0404|2024-08-05T03:21:15.517Z -- cisco -- cisco%20rv180w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0404</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web framework code for Cisco RV180W Wireless-N Multifunction VPN Router and Small Business RV Series RV220W Wireless Network Security Firewall could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries. The attacker could retrieve sensitive information which should be restricted. A vulnerability in the web framework code for Cisco RV180W Wireless-N Multifunction VPN Router and Small Business RV Series RV220W Wireless Network Security Firewall could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries. The attacker could retrieve sensitive information which should be restricted. The product has entered the end-of-life phase and there will be no more firmware fixes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0404|2024-08-05T03:21:15.517Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0405|2024-08-05T03:21:15.612Z -- cisco -- cisco%20rv180w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0405</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web framework code for Cisco RV180W Wireless-N Multifunction VPN Router and Small Business RV Series RV220W Wireless Network Security Firewall could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a directory path traversal attack on a targeted device. The issue is due to improper sanitization of user-supplied input in HTTP request parameters that describe filenames. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using directory traversal techniques to submit a path to a desired file location.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0405|2024-08-05T03:21:15.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
