<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:21:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0485|2024-08-05T03:28:10.955Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0485</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SM-1T3/E3 firmware on Cisco Second Generation Integrated Services Routers (ISR G2) and the Cisco 4451-X Integrated Services Router (ISR4451-X) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the ISR G2 Router or the SM-1T3/E3 module on the ISR4451-X to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by first connecting to the SM-1T3/E3 module console and entering a string sequence. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ISR G2 Router or the SM-1T3/E3 module on the ISR4451-X to reload, resulting in a DoS condition on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0485|2024-08-05T03:28:10.955Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15369|2024-08-05T09:54:01.935Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15369</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TACACS+ client subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of crafted TACACS+ response packets by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting a crafted TACACS+ packet into an existing TACACS+ session between an affected device and a TACACS+ server or by impersonating a known, valid TACACS+ server and sending a crafted TACACS+ packet to an affected device when establishing a connection to the device. To exploit this vulnerability by using either method, the attacker must know the shared TACACS+ secret and the crafted packet must be sent in response to a TACACS+ request from a TACACS+ client. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15369|2024-08-05T09:54:01.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0473|2024-08-05T03:28:11.115Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0473</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Precision Time Protocol (PTP) subsystem of Cisco IOS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of the Precision Time Protocol. The vulnerability is due to insufficient processing of PTP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a custom PTP packet to, or through, an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition for the PTP subsystem, resulting in time synchronization issues across the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0473|2024-08-05T03:28:11.115Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15377|2024-08-05T09:54:02.656Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15377</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Network Plug and Play agent, also referred to as the Cisco Open Plug-n-Play agent, of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a memory leak on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending invalid data to the Cisco Network Plug and Play agent on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a memory leak on the affected device, which could cause the device to reload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15377|2024-08-05T09:54:02.656Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15376|2024-08-05T09:54:02.595Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15376</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the embedded test subsystem of Cisco IOS Software for Cisco 800 Series Industrial Integrated Services Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to write arbitrary values to arbitrary locations in the memory space of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to the presence of certain test commands that were intended to be available only in internal development builds of the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using these commands on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to write arbitrary values to arbitrary locations in the memory space of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15376|2024-08-05T09:54:02.595Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0467|2024-08-05T03:28:10.991Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0467</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv6 processing code of Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload. The vulnerability is due to incorrect handling of specific IPv6 hop-by-hop options. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious IPv6 packet to or through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0467|2024-08-05T03:28:10.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0475|2024-08-05T03:28:10.360Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0475</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the cluster feature of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation when handling Cluster Management Protocol (CMP) messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious CMP message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the switch to crash and reload or to hang, resulting in a DoS condition. If the switch hangs it will not reboot automatically, and it will need to be power cycled manually to recover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0475|2024-08-05T03:28:10.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15375|2024-08-05T09:54:02.455Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15375</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the embedded test subsystem of Cisco IOS Software for Cisco 800 Series Industrial Integrated Services Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to write arbitrary values to arbitrary locations in the memory space of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to the presence of certain test commands that were intended to be available only in internal development builds of the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using these commands on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to write arbitrary values to arbitrary locations in the memory space of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15375|2024-08-05T09:54:02.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15373|2024-08-05T09:54:02.398Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15373</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of Cisco Discovery Protocol functionality in Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to exhaust memory on an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to improper memory handling by the affected software when the software processes high rates of Cisco Discovery Protocol packets that are sent to a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high rate of Cisco Discovery Protocol packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust memory on the affected device, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15373|2024-08-05T09:54:02.398Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0466|2024-08-05T03:28:11.009Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0466</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Open Shortest Path First version 3 (OSPFv3) implementation in Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload. The vulnerability is due to incorrect handling of specific OSPFv3 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted OSPFv3 Link-State Advertisements (LSA) to an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause an affected device to reload, leading to a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0466|2024-08-05T03:28:11.009Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
