<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco WebEx Meetings Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco WebEx Meetings Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:43:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3471|2024-09-16T19:10:56.342Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3471</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings and Cisco Webex Meetings Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to maintain bidirectional audio despite being expelled from an active Webex session. The vulnerability is due to a synchronization issue between meeting and media services on a vulnerable Webex site. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted requests to a vulnerable Cisco Webex Meetings or Cisco Webex Meetings Server site. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to maintain the audio connection of a Webex session despite being expelled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3471|2024-09-16T19:10:56.342Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 17:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3361|2024-09-16T16:18:13.335Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings and Cisco Webex Meetings Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain unauthorized access to a vulnerable Webex site. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of authentication tokens by a vulnerable Webex site. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted requests to a vulnerable Cisco Webex Meetings or Cisco Webex Meetings Server site. If successful, the attacker could gain the privileges of another user within the affected Webex site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3361|2024-09-16T16:18:13.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 02:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3347|2024-09-16T17:08:13.612Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3347</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings Desktop App for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain access to sensitive information on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to unsafe usage of shared memory that is used by the affected software. An attacker with permissions to view system memory could exploit this vulnerability by running an application on the local system that is designed to read shared memory. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve sensitive information from the shared memory, including usernames, meeting information, or authentication tokens that could aid the attacker in future attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3347|2024-09-16T17:08:13.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 02:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3419|2024-09-16T19:24:40.441Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3419</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings and Cisco Webex Meetings Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to join a Webex session without appearing on the participant list. This vulnerability is due to improper handling of authentication tokens by a vulnerable Webex site. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted requests to a vulnerable Cisco Webex Meetings or Cisco Webex Meetings Server site. A successful exploit requires the attacker to have access to join a Webex meeting, including applicable meeting join links and passwords. The attacker could then exploit this vulnerability to join meetings, without appearing in the participant list, while having full access to audio, video, chat, and screen sharing capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3419|2024-09-16T19:24:40.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 17:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3441|2024-09-16T18:34:04.973Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3441</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings and Cisco Webex Meetings Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to view sensitive information from the meeting room lobby. This vulnerability is due to insufficient protection of sensitive participant information. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by browsing the Webex roster. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gather information about other Webex participants, such as email address and IP address, while waiting in the lobby.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3441|2024-09-16T18:34:04.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 17:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1525|2024-09-16T18:49:09.788Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1525</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings and Cisco Webex Meetings Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to redirect users to a malicious file. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of URL paths in the application interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to follow a specially crafted URL that is designed to cause Cisco Webex Meetings to include a remote file in the web UI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the application to offer a remote file to a user, which could allow the attacker to conduct further phishing or spoofing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1525|2024-09-16T18:49:09.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 16:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1868|2024-09-16T17:53:45.793Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1868</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Webex Meetings Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive system information. The vulnerability is due to improper access control to files within the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access sensitive system information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1868|2024-09-16T17:53:45.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 16:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
