<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco WebEx Meetings Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco WebEx Meetings Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 02:24:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1221|2024-09-17T01:16:26.826Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1221</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the user interface of Cisco Webex Meetings and Cisco Webex Meetings Server Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject a hyperlink into a meeting invitation email. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by entering a URL into a field in the user interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to generate a Webex Meetings invitation email that contains a link to a destination of their choosing. Because this email is sent from a trusted source, the recipient may be more likely to click the link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1221|2024-09-17T01:16:26.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 16:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1517|2024-09-17T00:06:01.688Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1517</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multimedia viewer feature of Cisco Webex Meetings and Cisco Webex Meetings Server could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to bypass security protections. This vulnerability is due to unsafe handling of shared content within the multimedia viewer feature. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sharing a file through the multimedia viewer feature. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass security protections and prevent warning dialogs from appearing before files are offered to other users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1517|2024-09-17T00:06:01.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 16:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1311|2024-09-17T01:46:49.705Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1311</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the reclaim host role feature of Cisco Webex Meetings and Cisco Webex Meetings Server could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to take over the host role during a meeting. This vulnerability is due to a lack of protection against brute forcing of the host key. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted requests to a vulnerable Cisco Webex Meetings or Webex Meetings Server site. A successful exploit would require the attacker to have access to join a Webex meeting, including applicable meeting join links and passwords. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to acquire or take over the host role for a meeting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1311|2024-09-17T01:46:49.705Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 21:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3342|2024-09-17T02:01:13.880Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3342</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the software update feature of Cisco Webex Meetings Desktop App for Mac could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of cryptographic protections on files that are downloaded by the application as part of a software update. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to go to a website that returns files to the client that are similar to files that are returned from a valid Webex website. The client may fail to properly validate the cryptographic protections of the provided files before executing them as part of an update. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected system with the privileges of the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3342|2024-09-17T02:01:13.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 02:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
