<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software 16.4.1</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%2016.4.1.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software 16.4.1</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:43:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12666|2024-09-16T19:19:21.284Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%2016.4.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12666</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Guest Shell of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform directory traversal on the base Linux operating system of Cisco IOS XE Software. The vulnerability is due to incomplete validation of certain commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by first accessing the Guest Shell and then entering specific commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the base Linux operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12666|2024-09-16T19:19:21.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 20:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3220|2024-09-16T16:14:18.978Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%2016.4.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3220</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the hardware crypto driver of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco 4300 Series Integrated Services Routers and Cisco Catalyst 9800-L Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to disconnect legitimate IPsec VPN sessions to an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient verification of authenticity of received Encapsulating Security Payload (ESP) packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by tampering with ESP cleartext values as a man-in-the-middle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3220|2024-09-16T16:14:18.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 17:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
