<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco HyperFlex HX-Series</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco HyperFlex HX-Series</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:24:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15407|2024-08-05T09:54:02.560Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15407</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the installation process of Cisco HyperFlex Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to read sensitive information. The vulnerability is due to insufficient cleanup of installation files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the residual installation files on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to collect sensitive information regarding the configuration of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15407|2024-08-05T09:54:02.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15423|2024-08-05T09:54:03.399Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15423</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco HyperFlex Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to affect the integrity of a device via a clickjacking attack. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of iFrame data in HTTP requests that are sent to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets with malicious iFrame data. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform a clickjacking attack where the user is tricked into clicking a malicious link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15423|2024-08-05T09:54:03.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15382|2024-08-05T09:54:02.948Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15382</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco HyperFlex Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to generate valid, signed session tokens. The vulnerability is due to a static signing key that is present in all Cisco HyperFlex systems. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the static signing key from one HyperFlex system and using it to generate valid, signed session tokens for another HyperFlex system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access the HyperFlex Web UI of a system for which they are not authorized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15382|2024-08-05T09:54:02.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15380|2024-08-05T09:54:02.911Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15380</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the cluster service manager of Cisco HyperFlex Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to execute commands as the root user. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the cluster service manager and injecting commands into the bound process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to run commands on the affected host as the root user. This vulnerability affects Cisco HyperFlex Software releases prior to 3.5(2a).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15380|2024-08-05T09:54:02.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
