<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco HyperFlex HX Data Platform</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20hyperflex%20hx%20data%20platform.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco HyperFlex HX Data Platform</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 11:21:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3389|2024-09-17T04:18:56.832Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx%20data%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3389</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the installation component of Cisco Hyperflex HX-Series Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to retrieve the password that was configured at installation on an affected device. The vulnerability exists because sensitive information is stored as clear text. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to an affected device and navigating to the directory that contains sensitive information. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain sensitive information in clear text from the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3389|2024-09-17T04:18:56.832Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 16:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1499|2024-09-17T03:48:08.598Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx%20data%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1499</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco HyperFlex HX Data Platform could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to upload files to an affected device. This vulnerability is due to missing authentication for the upload function. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specific HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to upload files to the affected device with the permissions of the tomcat8 user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1499|2024-09-17T03:48:08.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 12:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1497|2024-09-17T02:21:40.011Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx%20data%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1497</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco HyperFlex HX could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to perform command injection attacks against an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1497|2024-09-17T02:21:40.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 12:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
