<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Webex Meetings</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20webex%20meetings.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Webex Meetings</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:24:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1420|2024-09-17T03:07:32.498Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1420</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in certain web pages of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to modify a web page in the context of a user's browser. The vulnerability is due to improper checks on parameter values in affected pages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to follow a crafted link that is designed to pass HTML code into an affected parameter. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to alter the contents of a web page to redirect the user to potentially malicious websites, or the attacker could use this vulnerability to conduct further client-side attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1420|2024-09-17T03:07:32.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 04:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1544|2024-09-17T02:31:32.958Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1544</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in logging mechanisms of Cisco Webex Meetings client software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain access to sensitive information. This vulnerability is due to unsafe logging of application actions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging onto the local system and accessing files containing the logged details. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to sensitive information, including meeting data and recorded meeting transcriptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1544|2024-09-17T02:31:32.958Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 16:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3412|2024-09-17T01:26:05.215Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3412</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the scheduled meeting template feature of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to create a scheduled meeting template that would belong to another user in their organization. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization enforcement for the creation of scheduled meeting templates. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the Webex Meetings interface to create a scheduled meeting template. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to create a scheduled meeting template that would belong to a user other than themselves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3412|2024-09-17T01:26:05.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 18:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15960|2024-09-17T00:45:30.202Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15960</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Webex Network Recording Admin page of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges in the context of the affected page. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must be logged in as a low-level administrator. The vulnerability is due to insufficient access control validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted URL request to gain privileged access in the context of the affected page. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges in the Webex Recording Admin page, which could allow them to view or delete recordings that they would not normally be able to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15960|2024-09-17T00:45:30.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 03:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20820|2024-09-17T02:27:01.587Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20820</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web interface of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow a remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack or a frame hijacking attack against a user of the web interface. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20820|2024-09-17T02:27:01.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 08:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20852|2024-09-17T03:03:25.950Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20852</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web interface of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow a remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack or a frame hijacking attack against a user of the web interface. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20852|2024-09-17T03:03:25.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 08:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1503|2024-09-17T00:56:19.153Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1503</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Network Recording Player for Windows and MacOS and Cisco Webex Player for Windows and MacOS could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of values in Webex recording files that are in either Advanced Recording Format (ARF) or Webex Recording Format (WRF). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a user a malicious ARF or WRF file through a link or email attachment and persuading the user to open the file with the affected software on the local system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected system with the privileges of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1503|2024-09-17T00:56:19.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 16:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1310|2024-09-17T04:15:17.229Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to redirect a user to an untrusted web page, bypassing the warning mechanism that should prompt the user before the redirection. This vulnerability is due to improper input validation of the URL parameters in an HTTP request. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to redirect a user to a malicious website, bypassing the Webex URL check that should result in a warning before the redirection to the web page. Attackers may use this type of vulnerability, known as an open redirect attack, as part of a phishing attack to convince users to unknowingly visit malicious sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1310|2024-09-17T04:15:17.229Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 21:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3501|2024-09-17T00:30:37.757Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3501</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the user interface of Cisco Webex Meetings Desktop App could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain restricted information from other Webex users. These vulnerabilities are due to improper input validation of parameters returned to the application from a web site. An attacker with a valid Webex account could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user to follow a URL that is designed to return malicious path parameters to the affected software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain restricted information from other Webex users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3501|2024-09-17T00:30:37.757Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 18:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3502|2024-09-17T02:41:56.684Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3502</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the user interface of Cisco Webex Meetings Desktop App could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain restricted information from other Webex users. These vulnerabilities are due to improper input validation of parameters returned to the application from a web site. An attacker with a valid Webex account could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user to follow a URL that is designed to return malicious path parameters to the affected software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain restricted information from other Webex users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3502|2024-09-17T02:41:56.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 18:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
