<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System (Managed)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System (Managed)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:23:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20016|2024-08-02T08:57:35.614Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20016</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the backup configuration feature of Cisco UCS Manager Software and in the configuration export feature of Cisco FXOS Software could allow an unauthenticated attacker with access to a backup file to decrypt sensitive information stored in the full state and configuration backup files. This vulnerability is due to a weakness in the encryption method used for the backup function. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by leveraging a static key used for the backup configuration feature. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to decrypt sensitive information that is stored in full state and configuration backup files, such as local user credentials, authentication server passwords, Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) community names, and other credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20016|2024-08-02T08:57:35.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20012|2024-08-02T08:57:35.036Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20012</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI console login authentication of Cisco Nexus 9300-FX3 Series Fabric Extender (FEX) when used in UCS Fabric Interconnect deployments could allow an unauthenticated attacker with physical access to bypass authentication. This vulnerability is due to the improper implementation of the password validation function. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to the console port on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass authentication and execute a limited set of commands local to the FEX, which could cause a device reboot and denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20012|2024-08-02T08:57:35.036Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20200|2024-08-02T09:05:35.047Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20200</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) service of Cisco FXOS Software for Firepower 4100 Series and Firepower 9300 Security Appliances and of Cisco UCS 6300 Series Fabric Interconnects could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the improper handling of specific SNMP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SNMP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.&#13;
&#13; Note: This vulnerability affects all supported SNMP versions. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMPv2c or earlier, an attacker must know the SNMP community string that is configured on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability through SNMPv3, the attacker must have valid credentials for an SNMP user who is configured on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20200|2024-08-02T09:05:35.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 18:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20015|2024-08-02T08:57:35.589Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20015</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco Firepower 4100 Series, Cisco Firepower 9300 Security Appliances, and Cisco UCS 6200, 6300, 6400, and 6500 Series Fabric Interconnects could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject unauthorized commands. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of commands supplied by the user. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to a device and submitting crafted input to the affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute unauthorized commands within the CLI. An attacker with Administrator privileges could also execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of Cisco UCS 6400 and 6500 Series Fabric Interconnects with root-level privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20015|2024-08-02T08:57:35.589Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20344|2024-07-26T14:35:04.588Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20344</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in system resource management in Cisco UCS 6400 and 6500 Series Fabric Interconnects that are in Intersight Managed Mode (IMM) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the Device Console UI of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient rate-limiting of TCP connections to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high number of TCP packets to the Device Console UI. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to cause the Device Console UI process to crash, resulting in a DoS condition. A manual reload of the fabric interconnect is needed to restore complete functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20344|2024-07-26T14:35:04.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20344|2024-02-28T16:16:03.042Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20344</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in system resource management in Cisco UCS 6400 and 6500 Series Fabric Interconnects that are in Intersight Managed Mode (IMM) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the Device Console UI of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient rate-limiting of TCP connections to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high number of TCP packets to the Device Console UI. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to cause the Device Console UI process to crash, resulting in a DoS condition. A manual reload of the fabric interconnect is needed to restore complete functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20344|2024-02-28T16:16:03.042Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20344|2024-08-01T21:59:42.290Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20344</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in system resource management in Cisco UCS 6400 and 6500 Series Fabric Interconnects that are in Intersight Managed Mode (IMM) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the Device Console UI of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient rate-limiting of TCP connections to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high number of TCP packets to the Device Console UI. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to cause the Device Console UI process to crash, resulting in a DoS condition. A manual reload of the fabric interconnect is needed to restore complete functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20344|2024-08-01T21:59:42.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
