<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS System Software in ACI Mode</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20nx-os%20system%20software%20in%20aci%20mode.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS System Software in ACI Mode</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:26:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1230|2024-09-17T03:43:52.105Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20system%20software%20in%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1230</link>
      <description>A vulnerability with the Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) for Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches in Application Centric Infrastructure (ACI) mode could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a routing process to crash, which could lead to a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to an issue with the installation of routes upon receipt of a BGP update. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted BGP update to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the routing process to crash, which could cause the device to reload. This vulnerability applies to both Internal BGP (IBGP) and External BGP (EBGP). Note: The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP traffic from explicitly configured peers only. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to send a specific BGP update message over an established TCP connection that appears to come from a trusted BGP peer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1230|2024-09-17T03:43:52.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 19:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1231|2024-09-17T00:37:03.695Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20system%20software%20in%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1231</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Link Layer Discovery Protocol (LLDP) for Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches in Application Centric Infrastructure (ACI) mode could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to disable switching on a small form-factor pluggable (SFP) interface. This vulnerability is due to incomplete validation of the source of a received LLDP packet. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted LLDP packet on an SFP interface to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to disable switching on the SFP interface, which could disrupt network traffic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1231|2024-09-17T00:37:03.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 19:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
