<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Nexus Dashboard</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20nexus%20dashboard.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Nexus Dashboard</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-20282|2024-04-03T16:20:33.850Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Nexus Dashboard
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20282</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Nexus Dashboard could allow an authenticated, local attacker with valid rescue-user credentials to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient protections for a sensitive access token. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using this token to access resources within the device infrastructure. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to gain root access to the filesystem or hosted containers on an affected device.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20282|2024-04-03T16:20:33.850Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20283|2024-04-03T16:25:09.906Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Nexus Dashboard
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20283</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Nexus Dashboard could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to learn cluster deployment information on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper access controls on a specific API endpoint. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending queries to the API endpoint. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to access metrics and information about devices in the Nexus Dashboard cluster.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20283|2024-04-03T16:25:09.906Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>