<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20xe%20sd-wan%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 16:24:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34729|2024-08-04T00:19:48.140Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20sd-wan%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34729</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileges on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input in the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileges on the underlying operating system. An attacker would need valid user credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34729|2024-08-04T00:19:48.140Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34727|2024-08-04T00:19:48.130Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20sd-wan%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34727</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the vDaemon process in Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a buffer overflow on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient bounds checking when an affected device processes traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted traffic to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a buffer overflow and possibly execute arbitrary commands with root-level privileges, or cause the device to reload, which could result in a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34727|2024-08-04T00:19:48.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34724|2024-08-04T00:19:48.119Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20sd-wan%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34724</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software CLI could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges and execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system as the root user. An attacker must be authenticated on an affected device as a PRIV15 user. This vulnerability is due to insufficient file system protection and the presence of a sensitive file in the bootflash directory on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by overwriting an installer file stored in the bootflash directory with arbitrary commands that can be executed with root-level privileges. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read and write changes to the configuration database on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34724|2024-08-04T00:19:48.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3216|2024-08-04T07:30:56.420Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20sd-wan%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3216</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass authentication and gain unrestricted access to the root shell of an affected device. The vulnerability exists because the affected software has insufficient authentication mechanisms for certain commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by stopping the boot initialization of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass authentication and gain unrestricted access to the root shell of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3216|2024-08-04T07:30:56.420Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34725|2024-08-04T00:19:48.128Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20sd-wan%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34725</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject arbitrary commands to be executed with root-level privileges on the underlying operating system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation on certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to an affected device and submitting crafted input to the CLI. The attacker must be authenticated as an administrative user to execute the affected commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands with root-level privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34725|2024-08-04T00:19:48.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
