<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN Solution</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20sd-wan%20solution.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN Solution</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 07:21:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0432|2024-08-05T03:28:09.775Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0432</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the error reporting feature of the Cisco SD-WAN Solution could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to gain elevated privileges on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a failure to properly validate certain parameters included within the error reporting application configuration. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted command to the error reporting feature. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain root-level privileges and take full control of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0432|2024-08-05T03:28:09.775Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0434|2024-08-05T03:28:10.336Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0434</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Zero Touch Provisioning feature of the Cisco SD-WAN Solution could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain unauthorized access to sensitive data by using an invalid certificate. The vulnerability is due to insufficient certificate validation by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a crafted certificate to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct man-in-the-middle attacks to decrypt confidential information on user connections to the affected software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0434|2024-08-05T03:28:10.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0433|2024-08-05T03:28:09.813Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0433</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the command-line interface (CLI) in the Cisco SD-WAN Solution could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject arbitrary commands that are executed with root privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and submitting crafted input to the CLI utility. The attacker must be authenticated to access the CLI utility. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0433|2024-08-05T03:28:09.813Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
