<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Content Security Management Appliance (SMA)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20content%20security%20management%20appliance%20%28sma%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Content Security Management Appliance (SMA)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 17:22:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1447|2024-09-16T16:42:46.209Z -- cisco -- cisco%20content%20security%20management%20appliance%20%28sma%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1447</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the user account management system of Cisco AsyncOS for Cisco Content Security Management Appliance (SMA) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate their privileges to root. This vulnerability is due to a procedural flaw in the password generation algorithm. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by enabling specific Administrator-only features and connecting to the appliance through the CLI with elevated privileges. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root and access the underlying operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1447|2024-09-16T16:42:46.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 12:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3178|2024-09-16T16:23:30.505Z -- cisco -- cisco%20content%20security%20management%20appliance%20%28sma%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3178</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based GUI of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Content Security Management Appliance (SMA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to redirect a user to a malicious web page. The vulnerabilities are due to improper input validation of the parameters of an HTTP request. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by intercepting an HTTP request and modifying it to redirect a user to a specific malicious URL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to redirect a user to a malicious web page or to obtain sensitive browser-based information. This type of attack is commonly referred to as an open redirect attack and is used in phishing attacks to get users to unknowingly visit malicious sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3178|2024-09-16T16:23:30.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
