<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Small Business Smart and Managed Switches</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20small%20business%20smart%20and%20managed%20switches.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Small Business Smart and Managed Switches</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 11:20:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34739|2024-08-04T00:19:48.160Z -- cisco -- cisco%20small%20business%20smart%20and%20managed%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34739</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of multiple Cisco Small Business Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to replay valid user session credentials and gain unauthorized access to the web-based management interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient expiration of session credentials. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by conducting a man-in-the-middle attack against an affected device to intercept valid session credentials and then replaying the intercepted credentials toward the same device at a later time. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access the web-based management interface with administrator privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34739|2024-08-04T00:19:48.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40127|2024-08-04T02:27:31.591Z -- cisco -- cisco%20small%20business%20smart%20and%20managed%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40127</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business 200 Series Smart Switches, Cisco Small Business 300 Series Managed Switches, and Cisco Small Business 500 Series Stackable Managed Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to render the web-based management interface unusable, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a permanent invalid redirect for requests sent to the web-based management interface of the device, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40127|2024-08-04T02:27:31.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
