<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20nx-os%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1808|2024-08-04T18:28:42.844Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1808</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Image Signature Verification feature of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator-level credentials to install a malicious software patch on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper verification of digital signatures for patch images. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by loading an unsigned software patch on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to boot a malicious software patch image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1808|2024-08-04T18:28:42.844Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1775|2024-08-04T18:28:42.804Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1775</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1775|2024-08-04T18:28:42.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1813|2024-08-04T18:28:42.901Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1813</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Image Signature Verification feature of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator-level credentials to install a malicious software image on an affected device. The vulnerability exists because software digital signatures are not properly verified during CLI command execution. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to install an unsigned software image on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1813|2024-08-04T18:28:42.901Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1810|2024-08-04T18:28:42.870Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1810</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Image Signature Verification feature used in an NX-OS CLI command in Cisco Nexus 3000 Series and 9000 Series Switches could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator-level credentials to install a malicious software image on an affected device. The vulnerability exists because software digital signatures are not properly verified during CLI command execution. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to install an unsigned software image on an affected device. Note: If the device has not been patched for the vulnerability previously disclosed in the Cisco Security Advisory cisco-sa-20190306-nxos-sig-verif, a successful exploit could allow the attacker to boot a malicious software image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1810|2024-08-04T18:28:42.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1780|2024-08-04T18:28:42.632Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1780</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator credentials to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device with elevated privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability. NX-OS versions prior to 8.3(1) are affected. NX-OS versions prior to 8.3(1) are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1780|2024-08-04T18:28:42.632Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3398|2024-08-04T07:30:58.383Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3398</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) Multicast VPN (MVPN) implementation of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a BGP session to repeatedly reset, causing a partial denial of service (DoS) condition due to the BGP session being down. The vulnerability is due to incorrect parsing of a specific type of BGP MVPN update message. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending this BGP MVPN update message to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the BGP peer connections to reset, which could lead to BGP route instability and impact traffic. The incoming BGP MVPN update message is valid but is parsed incorrectly by the NX-OS device, which could send a corrupted BGP update to the configured BGP peer. Note: The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP traffic from only explicitly configured peers. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must send a specific BGP MVPN update message over an established TCP connection that appears to come from a trusted BGP peer. To do so, the attacker must obtain information about the BGP peers in the trusted network of the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3398|2024-08-04T07:30:58.383Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1729|2024-08-04T18:28:41.640Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1729</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI implementation of a specific command used for image maintenance for Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to overwrite any file on the file system including system files. These file overwrites by the attacker are accomplished at the root privilege level. The vulnerability occurs because there is no verification of user-input parameters and or digital-signature verification for image files when using a specific CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and issuing a command at the CLI. Because an exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite any file on the disk, including system files, a denial of service (DoS) condition could occur. The attacker must have valid administrator credentials for the affected device to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1729|2024-08-04T18:28:41.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3415|2024-08-04T07:30:58.399Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3415</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Data Management Engine (DME) of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to execute arbitrary code with administrative privileges or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted Cisco Discovery Protocol packet to a Layer 2-adjacent affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code with administrative privileges or cause the Cisco Discovery Protocol process to crash and restart multiple times, causing the affected device to reload and resulting in a DoS condition. Note: Cisco Discovery Protocol is a Layer 2 protocol. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must be in the same broadcast domain as the affected device (Layer 2 adjacent). Exploitation of this vulnerability also requires jumbo frames to be enabled on the interface that receives the crafted Cisco Discovery Protocol packets on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3415|2024-08-04T07:30:58.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1769|2024-08-04T18:28:42.806Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1769</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator credentials to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system of an attached line card with the privilege level of root. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a specific CLI command on the affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system of an attached line card with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1769|2024-08-04T18:28:42.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1967|2024-08-04T18:35:51.286Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1967</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Network Time Protocol (NTP) feature of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to excessive use of system resources when the affected device is logging a drop action for received MODE_PRIVATE (Mode 7) NTP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by flooding the device with a steady stream of Mode 7 NTP packets. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause high CPU and memory usage on the affected device, which could cause internal system processes to restart or cause the affected device to unexpectedly reload. Note: The NTP feature is enabled by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1967|2024-08-04T18:35:51.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1726|2024-08-04T18:28:42.237Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1726</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access internal services that should be restricted on an affected device, such as the NX-API. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a certain CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument to the affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass intended restrictions and access internal services of the device. An attacker would need valid device credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1726|2024-08-04T18:28:42.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1727|2024-08-04T18:28:41.635Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1727</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Python scripting subsystem of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to escape the Python parser and issue arbitrary commands to elevate the attacker's privilege level. The vulnerability is due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied parameters that are passed to certain Python functions in the scripting sandbox of the affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to escape the scripting sandbox and execute arbitrary commands to elevate the attacker's privilege level. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have local access and be authenticated to the targeted device with administrative or Python execution privileges. These requirements could limit the possibility of a successful exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1727|2024-08-04T18:28:41.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3517|2024-08-04T07:37:54.679Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3517</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Fabric Services component of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated attacker to cause process crashes, which could result in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The attack vector is configuration dependent and could be remote or adjacent. For more information about the attack vector, see the Details section of this advisory. The vulnerability is due to insufficient error handling when the affected software parses Cisco Fabric Services messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious Cisco Fabric Services messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a reload of an affected device, which could result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3517|2024-08-04T07:37:54.679Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1728|2024-08-04T18:28:42.538Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1728</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Configuration Validation functionality of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to run arbitrary commands at system boot time with the privileges of root. The vulnerability is due to a lack of proper validation of system files when the persistent configuration information is read from the file system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and overwriting the persistent configuration storage with malicious executable files. An exploit could allow the attacker to run arbitrary commands at system startup and those commands will run as the root user. The attacker must have valid administrative credentials for the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1728|2024-08-04T18:28:42.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3165|2024-08-04T07:24:00.707Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3165</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) Message Digest 5 (MD5) authentication in Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass MD5 authentication and establish a BGP connection with the device. The vulnerability occurs because the BGP MD5 authentication is bypassed if the peer does not have MD5 authentication configured, the NX-OS device does have BGP MD5 authentication configured, and the NX-OS BGP virtual routing and forwarding (VRF) name is configured to be greater than 19 characters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to establish a BGP session with the NX-OS peer. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to establish a BGP session with the NX-OS device without MD5 authentication. The Cisco implementation of the BGP protocol accepts incoming BGP traffic only from explicitly configured peers. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must send the malicious packets over a TCP connection that appears to come from a trusted BGP peer. To do so, the attacker must obtain information about the BGP peers in the affected system&amp;rsquo;s trusted network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3165|2024-08-04T07:24:00.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1733|2024-08-04T18:28:41.043Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1733</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NX API (NX-API) Sandbox interface for Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the NX-API Sandbox interface of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the NX-API Sandbox interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the NX-API Sandbox interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected NX-API Sandbox interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1733|2024-08-04T18:28:41.043Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1791|2024-08-04T18:28:42.852Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1791</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator credentials to execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileges on the underlying operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1791|2024-08-04T18:28:42.852Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1783|2024-08-04T18:28:42.745Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1783</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator credentials to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with the privilege level of root. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a specific CLI command on the affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1783|2024-08-04T18:28:42.745Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1770|2024-08-04T18:28:42.721Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1770</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator credentials to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with the privilege level of root. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a specific CLI command on the affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1770|2024-08-04T18:28:42.721Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1965|2024-08-04T18:35:51.782Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1965</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Virtual Shell (VSH) session management for Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a VSH process to fail to delete upon termination. This can lead to a build-up of VSH processes that overtime can deplete system memory. When there is no system memory available, this can cause unexpected system behaviors and crashes. The vulnerability is due to the VSH process not being properly deleted when a remote management connection to the device is disconnected. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by repeatedly performing a remote management connection to the device and terminating the connection in an unexpected manner. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the VSH processes to fail to delete, which can lead to a system-wide denial of service (DoS) condition. The attacker must have valid user credentials to log in to the device using the remote management connection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1965|2024-08-04T18:35:51.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1735|2024-08-04T18:28:41.976Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1735</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileges on the underlying operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid user credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1735|2024-08-04T18:28:41.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1781|2024-08-04T18:28:42.734Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1781</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1781|2024-08-04T18:28:42.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3397|2024-08-04T07:30:58.213Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3397</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) Multicast VPN (MVPN) implementation of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to unexpectedly reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to incomplete input validation of a specific type of BGP MVPN update message. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending this specific, valid BGP MVPN update message to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause one of the BGP-related routing applications to restart multiple times, leading to a system-level restart. Note: The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP traffic from only explicitly configured peers. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must send a specific BGP MVPN update message over an established TCP connection that appears to come from a trusted BGP peer. To do so, the attacker must obtain information about the BGP peers in the trusted network of the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3397|2024-08-04T07:30:58.213Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3394|2024-08-04T07:30:58.161Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3394</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Enable Secret feature of Cisco Nexus 3000 Series Switches and Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Switches in standalone NX-OS mode could allow an authenticated, local attacker to issue the enable command and get full administrative privileges. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have valid credentials for the affected device. The vulnerability is due to a logic error in the implementation of the enable command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to the device and issuing the enable command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain full administrative privileges without using the enable password. Note: The Enable Secret feature is disabled by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3394|2024-08-04T07:30:58.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1776|2024-08-04T18:28:42.791Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1776</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with a privilege level of root. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a specific CLI command on the affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1776|2024-08-04T18:28:42.791Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3168|2024-08-04T07:24:00.707Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3168</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Login Enhancements capability of Cisco Nexus 1000V Switch for VMware vSphere could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected Nexus 1000V Virtual Supervisor Module (VSM) to become inaccessible to users through the CLI. The vulnerability is due to improper resource allocation during failed CLI login attempts when login parameters that are part of the Secure Login Enhancements capability are configured on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by performing a high amount of login attempts against the affected device. A successful exploit could cause the affected device to become inaccessible to other users, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition requiring a manual power cycle of the VSM to recover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3168|2024-08-04T07:24:00.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1779|2024-08-04T18:28:42.641Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1779</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device with elevated privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid device credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1779|2024-08-04T18:28:42.641Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1768|2024-08-04T18:28:42.669Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1768</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of a specific CLI command for Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator credentials to cause a buffer overflow condition or perform command injection. This could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileges on the underlying operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a certain CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of the affected CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit these vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1768|2024-08-04T18:28:42.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1778|2024-08-04T18:28:42.803Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1778</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with the privilege level of root. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a specific CLI command on the affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1778|2024-08-04T18:28:42.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1795|2024-08-04T18:28:42.777Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1795</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with the privilege level of root. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a specific CLI command on the affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1795|2024-08-04T18:28:42.777Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1969|2024-08-04T18:35:52.047Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1969</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) Access Control List (ACL) feature of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to perform SNMP polling of an affected device, even if it is configured to deny SNMP traffic. The vulnerability is due to an incorrect length check when the configured ACL name is the maximum length, which is 32 ASCII characters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by performing SNMP polling of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform SNMP polling that should have been denied. The attacker has no control of the configuration of the SNMP ACL name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1969|2024-08-04T18:35:52.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1732|2024-08-04T18:28:42.300Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1732</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Remote Package Manager (RPM) subsystem of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator credentials to leverage a time-of-check, time-of-use (TOCTOU) race condition to corrupt local variables, which could lead to arbitrary command injection. The vulnerability is due to the lack of a proper locking mechanism on critical variables that need to stay static until used. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to an affected device and issuing a set of RPM-related CLI commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary command injection. The attacker would need administrator credentials for the targeted device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1732|2024-08-04T18:28:42.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1811|2024-08-04T18:28:42.875Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1811</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Image Signature Verification feature of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator-level credentials to install a malicious software image on an affected device. The vulnerability exists because software digital signatures are not properly verified during CLI command execution. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to install an unsigned software image on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1811|2024-08-04T18:28:42.875Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1734|2024-08-04T18:28:42.554Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1734</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of a CLI diagnostic command in Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to view sensitive system files that should be restricted. The attacker could use this information to conduct additional reconnaissance attacks. The vulnerability is due to incomplete role-based access control (RBAC) verification. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and issuing a specific CLI diagnostic command with crafted user-input parameters. An exploit could allow the attacker to perform an arbitrary read of a file on the device, and the file may contain sensitive information. The attacker needs valid device credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1734|2024-08-04T18:28:42.554Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1595|2024-08-04T18:20:28.326Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1595</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Fibre Channel over Ethernet (FCoE) protocol implementation in Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to an incorrect allocation of an internal interface index. An adjacent attacker with the ability to submit a crafted FCoE packet that crosses affected interfaces could trigger this vulnerability. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a packet loop and high throughput on the affected interfaces, resulting in a DoS condition. This vulnerability has been fixed in version 7.3(5)N1(1).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1595|2024-08-04T18:20:28.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1812|2024-08-04T18:28:42.875Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1812</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Image Signature Verification feature of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator-level credentials to install a malicious software image on an affected device. The vulnerability exists because software digital signatures are not properly verified during CLI command execution. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to install an unsigned software image on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1812|2024-08-04T18:28:42.875Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1784|2024-08-04T18:28:42.848Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1784</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with the privilege level of root. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a specific CLI command on the affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1784|2024-08-04T18:28:42.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1767|2024-08-04T18:28:42.722Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1767</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of a specific CLI command for Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator credentials to cause a buffer overflow condition or perform command injection. This could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileges on the underlying operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a certain CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of the affected CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit these vulnerabilities. NX-OS versions prior to 8.3(1) are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1767|2024-08-04T18:28:42.722Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1790|2024-08-04T18:28:42.802Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1790</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with valid administrator credentials to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1790|2024-08-04T18:28:42.802Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1730|2024-08-04T18:28:42.051Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1730</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Bash shell implementation for Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to bypass the limited command set of the restricted Guest Shell and execute commands at the privilege level of a network-admin user outside of the Guest Shell. The attacker must authenticate with valid administrator device credentials. The vulnerability is due to the incorrect implementation of a CLI command that allows a Bash command to be incorrectly invoked on the Guest Shell CLI. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and entering a crafted command at the Guest Shell prompt. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to issue commands that should be restricted by a Guest Shell account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1730|2024-08-04T18:28:42.051Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1782|2024-08-04T18:28:42.805Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1782</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1782|2024-08-04T18:28:42.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1809|2024-08-04T18:28:42.815Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1809</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Image Signature Verification feature of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator-level credentials to install a malicious software patch on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper verification of digital signatures for patch images. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting an unsigned software patch to bypass signature checks and loading it on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to boot a malicious software patch image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1809|2024-08-04T18:28:42.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1774|2024-08-04T18:28:42.695Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1774</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1774|2024-08-04T18:28:42.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1731|2024-08-04T18:28:41.644Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1731</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSH CLI key management functionality of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to expose a user's private SSH key to all authenticated users on the targeted device. The attacker must authenticate with valid administrator device credentials. The vulnerability is due to incomplete error handling if a specific error type occurs during the SSH key export. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and entering a crafted command at the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to expose a user's private SSH key. In addition, a similar type of error in the SSH key import could cause the passphrase-protected private SSH key to be imported unintentionally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1731|2024-08-04T18:28:41.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T20:40:44.265Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T20:40:44.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T15:08:18.404Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T15:08:18.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-01T18:57:52.266Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-01T18:57:52.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20291|2024-02-28T16:16:33.950Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20291</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) programming for port channel subinterfaces of Cisco Nexus 3000 and 9000 Series Switches in standalone NX-OS mode could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to send traffic that should be blocked through an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect hardware programming that occurs when configuration changes are made to port channel member ports. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access network resources that should be protected by an ACL that was applied on port channel subinterfaces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20291|2024-02-28T16:16:33.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20321|2024-02-28T16:14:28.992Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20321</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the External Border Gateway Protocol (eBGP) implementation of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because eBGP traffic is mapped to a shared hardware rate-limiter queue. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending large amounts of network traffic with certain characteristics through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause eBGP neighbor sessions to be dropped, leading to a DoS condition in the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20321|2024-02-28T16:14:28.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20294|2024-06-04T17:40:18.434Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20294</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Link Layer Discovery Protocol (LLDP) feature of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of specific fields in an LLDP frame. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted LLDP packet to an interface of an affected device and having an authenticated user retrieve LLDP statistics from the affected device through CLI show commands or Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) requests. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the LLDP service to crash and stop running on the affected device. In certain situations, the LLDP crash may result in a reload of the affected device.
&#13; Note: LLDP is a Layer 2 link protocol. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to be directly connected to an interface of an affected device, either physically or logically (for example, through a Layer 2 Tunnel configured to transport the LLDP protocol).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20294|2024-06-04T17:40:18.434Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20267|2024-02-28T16:15:18.044Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20267</link>
      <description>A vulnerability with the handling of MPLS traffic for Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the netstack process to unexpectedly restart, which could cause the device to stop processing network traffic or to reload. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to lack of proper error checking when processing an ingress MPLS frame. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPv6 packet that is encapsulated within an MPLS frame to an MPLS-enabled interface of the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; Note: The IPv6 packet can be generated multiple hops away from the targeted device and then encapsulated within MPLS. The DoS condition may occur when the NX-OS device processes the packet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20267|2024-02-28T16:15:18.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-01T16:11:44.028Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-01T16:11:44.028Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T03:55:37.582Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T03:55:37.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T16:20:21.935Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T16:20:21.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-08-01T21:59:42.407Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-08-01T21:59:42.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20294|2024-08-01T21:59:41.160Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20294</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Link Layer Discovery Protocol (LLDP) feature of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of specific fields in an LLDP frame. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted LLDP packet to an interface of an affected device and having an authenticated user retrieve LLDP statistics from the affected device through CLI show commands or Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) requests. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the LLDP service to crash and stop running on the affected device. In certain situations, the LLDP crash may result in a reload of the affected device.
&#13; Note: LLDP is a Layer 2 link protocol. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to be directly connected to an interface of an affected device, either physically or logically (for example, through a Layer 2 Tunnel configured to transport the LLDP protocol).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20294|2024-08-01T21:59:41.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20291|2024-08-01T21:59:41.713Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20291</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) programming for port channel subinterfaces of Cisco Nexus 3000 and 9000 Series Switches in standalone NX-OS mode could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to send traffic that should be blocked through an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect hardware programming that occurs when configuration changes are made to port channel member ports. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access network resources that should be protected by an ACL that was applied on port channel subinterfaces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20291|2024-08-01T21:59:41.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20321|2024-08-01T21:59:41.467Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20321</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the External Border Gateway Protocol (eBGP) implementation of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because eBGP traffic is mapped to a shared hardware rate-limiter queue. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending large amounts of network traffic with certain characteristics through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause eBGP neighbor sessions to be dropped, leading to a DoS condition in the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20321|2024-08-01T21:59:41.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20267|2024-08-01T21:52:31.664Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20267</link>
      <description>A vulnerability with the handling of MPLS traffic for Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the netstack process to unexpectedly restart, which could cause the device to stop processing network traffic or to reload. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to lack of proper error checking when processing an ingress MPLS frame. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPv6 packet that is encapsulated within an MPLS frame to an MPLS-enabled interface of the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; Note: The IPv6 packet can be generated multiple hops away from the targeted device and then encapsulated within MPLS. The DoS condition may occur when the NX-OS device processes the packet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20267|2024-08-01T21:52:31.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
