<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Data Center Network Manager</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Data Center Network Manager</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 17:23:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1270|2024-09-16T16:32:42.557Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1270</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to view, modify, and delete data without proper authorization. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1270|2024-09-16T16:32:42.557Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3521|2024-09-16T16:53:03.200Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3521</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a specific REST API of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct directory traversal attacks on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input to the API. An attacker with a low-privileged account could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read arbitrary files on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3521|2024-09-16T16:53:03.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 16:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3355|2024-09-16T16:38:45.293Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3355</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Data Center Network Manager (DCNM) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative credentials to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting malicious data into a specific data field in the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need administrative credentials on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3355|2024-09-16T16:38:45.293Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 02:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20281|2024-06-04T17:40:22.646Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20281</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Nexus Dashboard and Cisco Nexus Dashboard hosted services could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privilege level of the affected user. If the affected user has administrative privileges, these actions could include modifying the system configuration and creating new privileged accounts.
&#13; Note: There are internal security mechanisms in place that limit the scope of this exploit, reducing the Security Impact Rating of this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20281|2024-06-04T17:40:22.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20348|2024-06-04T17:40:12.463Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20348</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Out-of-Band (OOB) Plug and Play (PnP) feature of Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to read arbitrary files.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an unauthenticated provisioning web server. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability through direct web requests to the provisioning server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read sensitive files in the PnP container that could facilitate further attacks on the PnP infrastructure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20348|2024-06-04T17:40:12.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20281|2024-08-01T21:59:41.178Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20281</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Nexus Dashboard and Cisco Nexus Dashboard hosted services could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privilege level of the affected user. If the affected user has administrative privileges, these actions could include modifying the system configuration and creating new privileged accounts.
&#13; Note: There are internal security mechanisms in place that limit the scope of this exploit, reducing the Security Impact Rating of this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20281|2024-08-01T21:59:41.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20348|2024-08-01T21:59:41.558Z -- cisco -- cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20348</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Out-of-Band (OOB) Plug and Play (PnP) feature of Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to read arbitrary files.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an unauthenticated provisioning web server. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability through direct web requests to the provisioning server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read sensitive files in the PnP container that could facilitate further attacks on the PnP infrastructure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20348|2024-08-01T21:59:41.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
