<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco HyperFlex HX-Series</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco HyperFlex HX-Series</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:24:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1667|2024-09-17T01:26:36.560Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1667</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Graphite interface of Cisco HyperFlex software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to write arbitrary data to the Graphite interface. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization controls. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the Graphite service and sending arbitrary data. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to write arbitrary data to Graphite, which could result in invalid statistics being presented in the interface. Versions prior to 3.5(2a) are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1667|2024-09-17T01:26:36.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15380|2024-09-17T01:26:44.170Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15380</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the cluster service manager of Cisco HyperFlex Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to execute commands as the root user. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the cluster service manager and injecting commands into the bound process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to run commands on the affected host as the root user. This vulnerability affects Cisco HyperFlex Software releases prior to 3.5(2a).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15380|2024-09-17T01:26:44.170Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15382|2024-09-17T01:35:43.157Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15382</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco HyperFlex Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to generate valid, signed session tokens. The vulnerability is due to a static signing key that is present in all Cisco HyperFlex systems. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the static signing key from one HyperFlex system and using it to generate valid, signed session tokens for another HyperFlex system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access the HyperFlex Web UI of a system for which they are not authorized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15382|2024-09-17T01:35:43.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1664|2024-09-17T02:16:44.512Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1664</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the hxterm service of Cisco HyperFlex Software could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker to gain root access to all nodes in the cluster. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authentication controls. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the hxterm service as a non-privileged, local user. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain root access to all member nodes of the HyperFlex cluster. This vulnerability affects Cisco HyperFlex Software Releases prior to 3.5(2a).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1664|2024-09-17T02:16:44.512Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12620|2024-09-17T01:26:32.775Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12620</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the statistics collection service of Cisco HyperFlex Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary values on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authentication for the statistics collection service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending properly formatted data values to the statistics collection service of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the web interface statistics view to present invalid data to users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12620|2024-09-17T01:26:32.775Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 16:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1857|2024-09-17T02:27:18.712Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1857</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco HyperFlex HX-Series could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on an affected system by using a web browser and with the privileges of the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1857|2024-09-17T02:27:18.712Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 16:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12621|2024-09-17T01:06:54.468Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12621</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco HyperFlex Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to perform a man-in-the-middle attack. The vulnerability is due to insufficient key management. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by obtaining a specific encryption key for the cluster. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform a man-in-the-middle attack against other nodes in the cluster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12621|2024-09-17T01:06:54.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 18:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1975|2024-09-17T02:02:41.304Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1975</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco HyperFlex Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute a cross-frame scripting (XFS) attack on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient HTML iframe protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by directing a user to an attacker-controlled web page that contains a malicious HTML iframe. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct clickjacking or other clientside browser attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1975|2024-09-17T02:02:41.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 16:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
