<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software 3.2.11aSG</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%203.2.11asg.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software 3.2.11aSG</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:42:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12651|2024-09-16T20:07:21.485Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%203.2.11asg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12651</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based user interface (Web UI) of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute commands with elevated privileges on the affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12651|2024-09-16T20:07:21.485Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 20:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12649|2024-09-16T19:30:27.068Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%203.2.11asg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12649</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Image Verification feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to install and boot a malicious software image or execute unsigned binaries on an affected device. The vulnerability exists because, under certain circumstances, an affected device can be configured to not verify the digital signatures of system image files during the boot process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by abusing a specific feature that is part of the device boot process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to install and boot a malicious software image or execute unsigned binaries on the targeted device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12649|2024-09-16T19:30:27.068Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 20:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12670|2024-09-16T19:00:37.626Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%203.2.11asg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12670</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the filesystem of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker within the IOx Guest Shell to modify the namespace container protections on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient file permissions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by modifying files that they should not have access to. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to remove container protections and perform file actions outside the namespace of the container.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12670|2024-09-16T19:00:37.626Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 20:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
