<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE ROMMON Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20xe%20rommon%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE ROMMON Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:23:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3524|2024-09-16T19:05:40.731Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20rommon%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3524</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco IOS XE ROM Monitor (ROMMON) Software for Cisco 4000 Series Integrated Services Routers, Cisco ASR 920 Series Aggregation Services Routers, Cisco ASR 1000 Series Aggregation Services Routers, and Cisco cBR-8 Converged Broadband Routers could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to break the chain of trust and load a compromised software image on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to the presence of a debugging configuration option in the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to an affected device through the console, forcing the device into ROMMON mode, and writing a malicious pattern using that specific option on the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to break the chain of trust and load a compromised software image on the affected device. A compromised software image is any software image that has not been digitally signed by Cisco.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3524|2024-09-16T19:05:40.731Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1452|2024-09-16T16:58:06.111Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20rommon%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1452</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the ROM Monitor (ROMMON) of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst IE3200, IE3300, and IE3400 Rugged Series Switches, Cisco Catalyst IE3400 Heavy Duty Series Switches, and Cisco Embedded Services 3300 Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to execute unsigned code at system boot time. This vulnerability is due to incorrect validations of specific function arguments passed to a boot script when specific ROMMON variables are set. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by setting malicious values for a specific ROMMON variable. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute unsigned code and bypass the image verification check during the secure boot process of an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have unauthenticated, physical access to the device or obtain privileged access to the root shell on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1452|2024-09-16T16:58:06.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
