<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Digital Network Architecture Center (DNA Center)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Digital Network Architecture Center (DNA Center)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34782|2024-08-04T00:19:48.191Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34782</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the API endpoints for Cisco DNA Center could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to gain access to sensitive information that should be restricted. The attacker must have valid device credentials. This vulnerability is due to improper access controls on API endpoints. An attacker could exploit the vulnerability by sending a specific API request to an affected application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain sensitive information about other users who are configured with higher privileges on the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34782|2024-08-04T00:19:48.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1841|2024-08-04T18:28:42.884Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1841</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Software Image Management feature of Cisco DNA Center could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to access to internal services without additional authentication. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending arbitrary HTTP requests to internal services. An exploit could allow the attacker to bypass any firewall or other protections to access unauthorized internal services. DNAC versions prior to 1.2.5 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1841|2024-08-04T18:28:42.884Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1848|2024-08-04T18:28:42.877Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1848</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Digital Network Architecture (DNA) Center could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass authentication and access critical internal services. The vulnerability is due to insufficient access restriction to ports necessary for system operation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting an unauthorized network device to the subnet designated for cluster services. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to reach internal services that are not hardened for external access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1848|2024-08-04T18:28:42.877Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3466|2024-08-04T07:37:54.235Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3466</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco DNA Center software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. The vulnerabilities exist because the web-based management interface on an affected device does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3466|2024-08-04T07:37:54.235Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3391|2024-08-04T07:30:58.220Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3391</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Digital Network Architecture (DNA) Center could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to view sensitive information in clear text. The vulnerability is due to insecure storage of certain unencrypted credentials on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by viewing the network device configuration and obtaining credentials that they may not normally have access to. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to use those credentials to discover and manage network devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3391|2024-08-04T07:30:58.220Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3411|2024-08-04T07:30:58.172Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3411</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco DNA Center software could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker access to sensitive information on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of authentication tokens by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker access to sensitive device information, which includes configuration files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3411|2024-08-04T07:30:58.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3281|2024-08-04T07:30:57.416Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3281</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the audit logging component of Cisco Digital Network Architecture (DNA) Center could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to view sensitive information in clear text. The vulnerability is due to the storage of certain unencrypted credentials. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the audit logs and obtaining credentials that they may not normally have access to. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to use those credentials to discover and manage network devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3281|2024-08-04T07:30:57.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1707|2024-08-04T18:28:41.648Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1707</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco DNA Center could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or allow the attacker to access sensitive browser-based information. Cisco DNA Center versions prior to 1.2.5 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1707|2024-08-04T18:28:41.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20333|2024-08-01T21:59:42.856Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20333</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Catalyst Center, formerly Cisco DNA Center, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to change specific data within the interface on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization enforcement. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to change a specific field within the web-based management interface, even though they should not have access to change that field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20333|2024-08-01T21:59:42.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20333|2024-06-04T17:40:11.205Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20333</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Catalyst Center, formerly Cisco DNA Center, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to change specific data within the interface on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization enforcement. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to change a specific field within the web-based management interface, even though they should not have access to change that field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20333|2024-06-04T17:40:11.205Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
