<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 03:24:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15988|2024-09-17T00:57:25.004Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15988</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the antispam protection mechanisms of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the URL reputation filters on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of URLs. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting the URL in a particular way. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the URL reputation filters that are configured for the affected device, which could allow malicious URLs to pass through the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15988|2024-09-17T00:57:25.004Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 03:42:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3546|2024-09-17T01:21:41.929Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3546</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco AsyncOS software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive information on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of requests that are sent to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain the IP addresses that are configured on the internal interfaces of the affected device. There is a workaround that addresses this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3546|2024-09-17T01:21:41.929Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 02:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1955|2024-09-17T00:05:45.093Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1955</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Sender Policy Framework (SPF) functionality of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliances (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured user filters on the device. The vulnerability is due to incomplete input and validation checking mechanisms for certain SPF messages that are sent to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a customized SPF packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the header filters that are configured for the affected device, which could allow malicious content to pass through the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1955|2024-09-17T00:05:45.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 07:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1831|2024-09-17T00:11:12.022Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1831</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the email message scanning of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured content filters on the device. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation of the email body. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting specific character strings in the message. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured content filters that would normally drop the email.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1831|2024-09-17T00:11:12.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 01:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12706|2024-09-17T01:17:07.301Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12706</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Sender Policy Framework (SPF) functionality of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured user filters on an affected device. The vulnerability exists because the affected software insufficiently validates certain incoming SPF messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a custom SPF packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the configured header filters, which could allow malicious content to pass through the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12706|2024-09-17T01:17:07.301Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3370|2024-09-17T01:46:58.278Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3370</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in URL filtering of Cisco Content Security Management Appliance (SMA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass URL filtering on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted, malicious HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to redirect users to malicious sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3370|2024-09-17T01:46:58.278Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15460|2024-09-17T02:00:39.797Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15460</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the email message filtering feature of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliances (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the CPU utilization to increase to 100 percent, causing a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper filtering of email messages that contain references to whitelisted URLs. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious email message that contains a large number of whitelisted URLs. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a sustained DoS condition that could force the affected device to stop scanning and forwarding email messages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15460|2024-09-17T02:00:39.797Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
