<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco ASR 5000 Series Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20asr%205000%20series%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco ASR 5000 Series Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 10:22:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3602|2024-08-04T07:37:55.605Z -- cisco -- cisco%20asr%205000%20series%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3602</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco StarOS operating system for Cisco ASR 5000 Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted commands to the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code with the privileges of the root user on the affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have valid credentials on an affected device and know the password for the cli test-commands command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3602|2024-08-04T07:37:55.605Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3500|2024-08-04T07:37:54.212Z -- cisco -- cisco%20asr%205000%20series%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3500</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv6 implementation of Cisco StarOS could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of incoming IPv6 traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPv6 packet to an affected device with the goal of reaching the vulnerable section of the input buffer. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition. This vulnerability is specific to IPv6 traffic. IPv4 traffic is not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3500|2024-08-04T07:37:54.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3244|2024-08-04T07:30:58.066Z -- cisco -- cisco%20asr%205000%20series%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3244</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Enhanced Charging Service (ECS) functionality of Cisco ASR 5000 Series Aggregation Services Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the traffic classification rules on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of user traffic going through an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the traffic classification rules and potentially avoid being charged for traffic consumption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3244|2024-08-04T07:30:58.066Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3601|2024-08-04T07:37:55.677Z -- cisco -- cisco%20asr%205000%20series%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3601</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco StarOS operating system for Cisco ASR 5000 Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted commands to the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code with the privileges of the root user. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have valid administrative credentials on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3601|2024-08-04T07:37:55.677Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
