<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco ASR 5000 Series Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20asr%205000%20series%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco ASR 5000 Series Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:23:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20051|2024-08-02T08:57:35.844Z -- cisco -- cisco%20asr%205000%20series%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20051</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Vector Packet Processor (VPP) of Cisco Packet Data Network Gateway (PGW) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to stop ICMP traffic from being processed over an IPsec connection. This vulnerability is due to the VPP improperly handling a malformed packet. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed Encapsulating Security Payload (ESP) packet over an IPsec connection. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to stop ICMP traffic over an IPsec connection and cause a denial of service (DoS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20051|2024-08-02T08:57:35.844Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20046|2024-08-02T08:57:35.853Z -- cisco -- cisco%20asr%205000%20series%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20046</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the key-based SSH authentication feature of Cisco StarOS Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied credentials. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a valid low-privileged SSH key to an affected device from a host that has an IP address that is configured as the source for a high-privileged user account. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to log in to the affected device through SSH as a high-privileged user.&#13;
&#13;   There are workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20046|2024-08-02T08:57:35.853Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
