<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XR Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20xr%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XR Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16023|2024-08-05T01:03:32.611Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16023</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the implementation of Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) Ethernet VPN (EVPN) functionality in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerabilities are due to incorrect processing of BGP update messages that contain crafted EVPN attributes. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending BGP EVPN update messages with malformed attributes to be processed by an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the BGP process to restart unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition. The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP traffic only from explicitly defined peers. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the malicious BGP update message would need to come from a configured, valid BGP peer, or would need to be injected by the attacker into the victim's BGP network on an existing, valid TCP connection to a BGP peer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16023|2024-08-05T01:03:32.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15428|2024-08-05T09:54:03.419Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15428</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) functionality in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of certain BGP update messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending BGP update messages that include a specific, malformed attribute to be processed by an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the BGP process to restart unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition. The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP traffic only from explicitly defined peers. To exploit this vulnerability, the malicious BGP update message would need to come from a configured, valid BGP peer, or would need to be injected by the attacker into the victim's BGP network on an existing, valid TCP connection to a BGP peer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15428|2024-08-05T09:54:03.419Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16022|2024-08-05T01:03:32.825Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16022</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the implementation of Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) Ethernet VPN (EVPN) functionality in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerabilities are due to incorrect processing of BGP update messages that contain crafted EVPN attributes. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending BGP EVPN update messages with malformed attributes to be processed by an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the BGP process to restart unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition. The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP traffic only from explicitly defined peers. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the malicious BGP update message would need to come from a configured, valid BGP peer, or would need to be injected by the attacker into the victim's BGP network on an existing, valid TCP connection to a BGP peer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16022|2024-08-05T01:03:32.825Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16018|2024-08-05T01:03:32.796Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16018</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) Ethernet VPN (EVPN) functionality in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of a BGP update message that contains crafted EVPN attributes. An attacker could indirectly exploit the vulnerability by sending BGP EVPN update messages with a specific, malformed attribute to an affected system and waiting for a user on the device to display the EVPN operational routes&amp;rsquo; status. If successful, the attacker could cause the BGP process to restart unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition. The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP traffic only from explicitly defined peers. To exploit this vulnerability, the malicious BGP update message would need to come from a configured, valid BGP peer, or would need to be injected by the attacker into the victim's BGP network on an existing, valid TCP connection to a BGP peer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16018|2024-08-05T01:03:32.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16019|2024-08-05T01:03:32.650Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16019</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the implementation of Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) Ethernet VPN (EVPN) functionality in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerabilities are due to incorrect processing of BGP update messages that contain crafted EVPN attributes. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending BGP EVPN update messages with malformed attributes to be processed by an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the BGP process to restart unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition. The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP traffic only from explicitly defined peers. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the malicious BGP update message would need to come from a configured, valid BGP peer, or would need to be injected by the attacker into the victim's BGP network on an existing, valid TCP connection to a BGP peer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16019|2024-08-05T01:03:32.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15989|2024-08-05T01:03:32.644Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15989</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) functionality in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of a BGP update message that contains a specific BGP attribute. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending BGP update messages that include a specific, malformed attribute to be processed by an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the BGP process to restart unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition. The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP traffic only from explicitly defined peers. To exploit this vulnerability, the malicious BGP update message would need to come from a configured, valid BGP peer or would need to be injected by the attacker into the victim&amp;rsquo;s BGP network on an existing, valid TCP connection to a BGP peer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15989|2024-08-05T01:03:32.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16020|2024-08-05T01:03:32.663Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16020</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the implementation of Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) Ethernet VPN (EVPN) functionality in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerabilities are due to incorrect processing of BGP update messages that contain crafted EVPN attributes. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending BGP EVPN update messages with malformed attributes to be processed by an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the BGP process to restart unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition. The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP traffic only from explicitly defined peers. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the malicious BGP update message would need to come from a configured, valid BGP peer, or would need to be injected by the attacker into the victim's BGP network on an existing, valid TCP connection to a BGP peer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16020|2024-08-05T01:03:32.663Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16021|2024-08-05T01:03:32.890Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16021</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the implementation of Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) Ethernet VPN (EVPN) functionality in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerabilities are due to incorrect processing of BGP update messages that contain crafted EVPN attributes. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending BGP EVPN update messages with malformed attributes to be processed by an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the BGP process to restart unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition. The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP traffic only from explicitly defined peers. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the malicious BGP update message would need to come from a configured, valid BGP peer, or would need to be injected by the attacker into the victim's BGP network on an existing, valid TCP connection to a BGP peer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16021|2024-08-05T01:03:32.890Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16027|2024-08-05T01:03:32.808Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16027</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the Intermediate System&amp;ndash;to&amp;ndash;Intermediate System (IS&amp;ndash;IS) routing protocol functionality in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition in the IS&amp;ndash;IS process. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of a Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) request for specific Object Identifiers (OIDs) by the IS&amp;ndash;IS process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SNMP request to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition in the IS&amp;ndash;IS process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16027|2024-08-05T01:03:32.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15998|2024-08-05T01:03:32.726Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15998</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access-control logic of the NETCONF over Secure Shell (SSH) of Cisco IOS XR Software may allow connections despite an access control list (ACL) that is configured to deny access to the NETCONF over SSH of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a missing check in the NETCONF over SSH access control list (ACL). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to an affected device using NETCONF over SSH. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to connect to the device on the NETCONF port. Valid credentials are required to access the device. This vulnerability does not affect connections to the default SSH process on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15998|2024-08-05T01:03:32.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20322|2024-08-02T19:49:57.842Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20322</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on Pseudowire interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20322|2024-08-02T19:49:57.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20319|2024-08-01T21:59:41.556Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20319</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured management plane protection policies and access the Simple Network Management Plane (SNMP) server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect UDP forwarding programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to perform an SNMP operation using broadcast as the destination address that could be processed by an affected device that is configured with an SNMP server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to communicate to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Although an unauthenticated attacker could send UDP datagrams to the configured SNMP port, only an authenticated user can retrieve or modify data using SNMP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20319|2024-08-01T21:59:41.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20320|2024-08-01T21:59:42.846Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20320</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSH client feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco 8000 Series Routers and Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) 540 Series and 5700 Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are included with the SSH client CLI command. An attacker with low-privileged access to an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by issuing a crafted SSH client command to the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20320|2024-08-01T21:59:42.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20322|2024-08-01T21:59:41.959Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20322</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on Pseudowire interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20322|2024-08-01T21:59:41.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20327|2024-08-01T21:59:42.888Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20327</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the PPP over Ethernet (PPPoE) termination feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco ASR 9000 Series Aggregation Services Routers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the improper handling of malformed PPPoE packets that are received on a router that is running Broadband Network Gateway (BNG) functionality with PPPoE termination on a Lightspeed-based or Lightspeed-Plus-based line card. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted PPPoE packet to an affected line card interface that does not terminate PPPoE. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a DoS condition for PPPoE traffic across the router.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20327|2024-08-01T21:59:42.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20266|2024-08-01T21:52:31.683Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20266</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP version 4 (DHCPv4) server feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a crash of the dhcpd process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because certain DHCPv4 messages are improperly validated when they are processed by an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed DHCPv4 message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a crash of the dhcpd process. While the dhcpd process is restarting, which may take approximately two minutes, DHCPv4 server services are unavailable on the affected device. This could temporarily prevent network access to clients that join the network during that time period and rely on the DHCPv4 server of the affected device.
&#13; Notes: 
&#13; &#13; Only the dhcpd process crashes and eventually restarts automatically. The router does not reload.&#13; This vulnerability only applies to DHCPv4. DHCP version 6 (DHCPv6) is not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20266|2024-08-01T21:52:31.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20262|2024-08-01T21:52:31.788Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20262</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Copy Protocol (SCP) and SFTP feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to create or overwrite files in a system directory, which could lead to a denial of service (DoS) condition. The attacker would require valid user credentials to perform this attack.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper validation of SCP and SFTP CLI input parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and issuing SCP or SFTP CLI commands with specific parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to impact the functionality of the device, which could lead to a DoS condition. The device may need to be manually rebooted to recover.
&#13; Note: This vulnerability is exploitable only when a local user invokes SCP or SFTP commands at the Cisco IOS XR CLI. A local user with administrative privileges could exploit this vulnerability remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20262|2024-08-01T21:52:31.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-08-01T21:59:42.190Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-08-01T21:59:42.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20318|2024-08-01T21:59:41.382Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20318</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Layer 2 Ethernet services of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the line card network processor to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific Ethernet frames that are received on line cards that have the Layer 2 services feature enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific Ethernet frames through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ingress interface network processor to reset, resulting in a loss of traffic over the interfaces that are supported by the network processor. Multiple resets of the network processor would cause the line card to reset, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20318|2024-08-01T21:59:41.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20315|2024-08-01T21:59:41.535Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20315</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on MPLS interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20315|2024-08-01T21:59:41.535Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-12T03:55:19.039Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-12T03:55:19.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T14:40:37.931Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T14:40:37.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20318|2024-07-05T17:22:18.112Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20318</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Layer 2 Ethernet services of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the line card network processor to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific Ethernet frames that are received on line cards that have the Layer 2 services feature enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific Ethernet frames through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ingress interface network processor to reset, resulting in a loss of traffic over the interfaces that are supported by the network processor. Multiple resets of the network processor would cause the line card to reset, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20318|2024-07-05T17:22:18.112Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20319|2024-06-21T18:49:10.353Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20319</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured management plane protection policies and access the Simple Network Management Plane (SNMP) server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect UDP forwarding programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to perform an SNMP operation using broadcast as the destination address that could be processed by an affected device that is configured with an SNMP server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to communicate to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Although an unauthenticated attacker could send UDP datagrams to the configured SNMP port, only an authenticated user can retrieve or modify data using SNMP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20319|2024-06-21T18:49:10.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20266|2024-03-13T16:42:27.815Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20266</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP version 4 (DHCPv4) server feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a crash of the dhcpd process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because certain DHCPv4 messages are improperly validated when they are processed by an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed DHCPv4 message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a crash of the dhcpd process. While the dhcpd process is restarting, which may take approximately two minutes, DHCPv4 server services are unavailable on the affected device. This could temporarily prevent network access to clients that join the network during that time period and rely on the DHCPv4 server of the affected device.
&#13; Notes: 
&#13; &#13; Only the dhcpd process crashes and eventually restarts automatically. The router does not reload.&#13; This vulnerability only applies to DHCPv4. DHCP version 6 (DHCPv6) is not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20266|2024-03-13T16:42:27.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20319|2024-03-13T16:47:09.543Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20319</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured management plane protection policies and access the Simple Network Management Plane (SNMP) server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect UDP forwarding programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to perform an SNMP operation using broadcast as the destination address that could be processed by an affected device that is configured with an SNMP server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to communicate to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Although an unauthenticated attacker could send UDP datagrams to the configured SNMP port, only an authenticated user can retrieve or modify data using SNMP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20319|2024-03-13T16:47:09.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20315|2024-03-13T16:45:58.046Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20315</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on MPLS interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20315|2024-03-13T16:45:58.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20318|2024-03-13T16:46:24.113Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20318</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Layer 2 Ethernet services of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the line card network processor to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific Ethernet frames that are received on line cards that have the Layer 2 services feature enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific Ethernet frames through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ingress interface network processor to reset, resulting in a loss of traffic over the interfaces that are supported by the network processor. Multiple resets of the network processor would cause the line card to reset, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20318|2024-03-13T16:46:24.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20322|2024-03-13T16:43:53.196Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20322</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on Pseudowire interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20322|2024-03-13T16:43:53.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20262|2024-06-04T17:40:27.162Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20262</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Copy Protocol (SCP) and SFTP feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to create or overwrite files in a system directory, which could lead to a denial of service (DoS) condition. The attacker would require valid user credentials to perform this attack.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper validation of SCP and SFTP CLI input parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and issuing SCP or SFTP CLI commands with specific parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to impact the functionality of the device, which could lead to a DoS condition. The device may need to be manually rebooted to recover.
&#13; Note: This vulnerability is exploitable only when a local user invokes SCP or SFTP commands at the Cisco IOS XR CLI. A local user with administrative privileges could exploit this vulnerability remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20262|2024-06-04T17:40:27.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20327|2024-06-04T17:40:27.563Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20327</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the PPP over Ethernet (PPPoE) termination feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco ASR 9000 Series Aggregation Services Routers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the improper handling of malformed PPPoE packets that are received on a router that is running Broadband Network Gateway (BNG) functionality with PPPoE termination on a Lightspeed-based or Lightspeed-Plus-based line card. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted PPPoE packet to an affected line card interface that does not terminate PPPoE. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a DoS condition for PPPoE traffic across the router.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20327|2024-06-04T17:40:27.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20320|2024-03-13T16:41:52.488Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20320</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSH client feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco 8000 Series Routers and Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) 540 Series and 5700 Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are included with the SSH client CLI command. An attacker with low-privileged access to an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by issuing a crafted SSH client command to the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20320|2024-03-13T16:41:52.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20319|2024-07-02T16:26:46.466Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20319</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured management plane protection policies and access the Simple Network Management Plane (SNMP) server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect UDP forwarding programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to perform an SNMP operation using broadcast as the destination address that could be processed by an affected device that is configured with an SNMP server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to communicate to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Although an unauthenticated attacker could send UDP datagrams to the configured SNMP port, only an authenticated user can retrieve or modify data using SNMP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20319|2024-07-02T16:26:46.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-10T16:06:22.104Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-10T16:06:22.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T21:23:07.031Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T21:23:07.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20315|2024-07-19T17:25:44.385Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20315</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on MPLS interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20315|2024-07-19T17:25:44.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
