<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Management Center</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20firepower%20management%20center.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Management Center</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3515|2024-08-04T07:37:54.667Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3515</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3515|2024-08-04T07:37:54.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3307|2024-08-04T07:30:58.218Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3307</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to write arbitrary entries to the log file on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send incorrect information to the system log on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3307|2024-08-04T07:30:58.218Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1949|2024-08-04T18:35:51.259Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1949</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of the affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1949|2024-08-04T18:35:51.259Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1931|2024-08-04T18:35:50.820Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1931</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the RSS dashboard in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device. The vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of the affected device. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1931|2024-08-04T18:35:50.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3557|2024-08-04T07:37:54.937Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3557</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the host input API daemon of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper certificate validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted data stream to the host input daemon of the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the host input daemon to restart. The attacker could use repeated attacks to cause the daemon to continuously reload, creating a DoS condition for the API.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3557|2024-08-04T07:37:54.937Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3550|2024-08-04T07:37:55.239Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3550</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the sfmgr daemon of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform directory traversal and access directories outside the restricted path. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using a relative path in specific sfmgr commands. An exploit could allow the attacker to read or write arbitrary files on an sftunnel-connected peer device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3550|2024-08-04T07:37:55.239Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3549|2024-08-04T07:37:54.873Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3549</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the sftunnel functionality of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to obtain the device registration hash. The vulnerability is due to insufficient sftunnel negotiation protection during initial device registration. An attacker in a man-in-the-middle position could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting a specific flow of the sftunnel communication between an FMC device and an FTD device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to decrypt and modify the sftunnel communication between FMC and FTD devices, allowing the attacker to modify configuration data sent from an FMC device to an FTD device or alert data sent from an FTD device to an FMC device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3549|2024-08-04T07:37:54.873Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3553|2024-08-04T07:37:54.963Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3553</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3553|2024-08-04T07:37:54.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3313|2024-08-04T07:30:57.821Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3313</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of the FMC Software. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or to access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3313|2024-08-04T07:30:57.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3318|2024-08-04T07:30:58.026Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3318</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software and Cisco Firepower User Agent Software could allow an attacker to access a sensitive part of an affected system with a high-privileged account. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3318|2024-08-04T07:30:58.026Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3311|2024-08-04T07:30:57.960Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3311</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to redirect a user to a malicious web page. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation of HTTP request parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting and modifying an HTTP request from a user. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to redirect the user to a specific malicious web page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3311|2024-08-04T07:30:57.960Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3499|2024-08-04T07:37:54.319Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3499</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the licensing service of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.The vulnerability is due to improper handling of system resource values by the affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests to the targeted system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected system to become unresponsive, resulting in a DoS condition and preventing the management of dependent devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3499|2024-08-04T07:37:54.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1642|2024-08-04T18:20:28.443Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1642</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of the affected software. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1642|2024-08-04T18:20:28.443Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3558|2024-08-04T07:37:55.314Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3558</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to redirect a user to a malicious web page. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation of the parameters of an HTTP request. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting an HTTP request from a user. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify the HTTP request to cause the interface to redirect the user to a specific, malicious URL. This type of vulnerability is known as an open redirect attack and is used in phishing attacks that get users to unknowingly visit malicious sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3558|2024-08-04T07:37:55.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3301|2024-08-04T07:30:57.688Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3301</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software and Cisco Firepower User Agent Software could allow an attacker to access a sensitive part of an affected system with a high-privileged account. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3301|2024-08-04T07:30:57.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3410|2024-08-04T07:30:58.398Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3410</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Common Access Card (CAC) authentication feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass authentication and access the FMC system. The attacker must have a valid CAC to initiate the access attempt. The vulnerability is due to incorrect session invalidation during CAC authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by performing a CAC-based authentication attempt to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access an affected system with the privileges of a CAC-authenticated user who is currently logged in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3410|2024-08-04T07:30:58.398Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1982|2024-08-04T18:35:52.175Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1982</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the HTTP traffic filtering component of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software, Cisco FirePOWER Services Software for ASA, and Cisco Firepower Management Center Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass filtering protections. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of HTTP requests, including those communicated over a secure HTTPS connection, that contain maliciously crafted headers. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests to an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to bypass filtering and deliver malicious requests to protected systems, allowing attackers to deliver malicious content that would otherwise be blocked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1982|2024-08-04T18:35:52.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1930|2024-08-04T18:35:51.246Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1930</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the RSS dashboard in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device. The vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of the affected device. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1930|2024-08-04T18:35:51.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34762|2024-08-04T00:19:48.207Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34762</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a directory traversal attack on an affected device. The attacker would require valid device credentials. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of the HTTPS URL by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTPS request that contains directory traversal character sequences to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read or write arbitrary files on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34762|2024-08-04T00:19:48.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34764|2024-08-04T00:19:48.194Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34764</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an attacker to execute a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack or an open redirect attack. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34764|2024-08-04T00:19:48.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1671|2024-08-04T18:20:28.490Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1671</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of the affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a maliciously crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1671|2024-08-04T18:20:28.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3320|2024-08-04T07:30:57.835Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3320</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by first entering input within the web-based management interface and then persuading a user of the interface to view the crafted input within the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3320|2024-08-04T07:30:57.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3302|2024-08-04T07:30:57.928Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3302</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to overwrite files on the file system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a crafted file to the web UI on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite files on the file system of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3302|2024-08-04T07:30:57.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34763|2024-08-04T00:19:48.143Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34763</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an attacker to execute a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack or an open redirect attack. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34763|2024-08-04T00:19:48.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1802|2024-08-04T18:28:42.849Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1802</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input in the web-based management interface of the affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to access a report containing malicious content. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. Versions 6.2.3, 6.3.0, and 6.4.0 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1802|2024-08-04T18:28:42.849Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20361|2024-08-01T21:59:41.652Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Object Groups for Access Control Lists (ACLs) feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured access controls on managed devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect deployment of the Object Groups for ACLs feature from Cisco FMC Software to managed FTD devices in high-availability setups. After an affected device is rebooted following Object Groups for ACLs deployment, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access controls and successfully send traffic to devices that are expected to be protected by the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20361|2024-08-01T21:59:41.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20360|2024-08-01T21:59:42.328Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20360</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not adequately validate user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain any data from the database, execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system, and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least Read Only user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20360|2024-08-01T21:59:42.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-04T17:40:51.215Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Object Groups for Access Control Lists (ACLs) feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured access controls on managed devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect deployment of the Object Groups for ACLs feature from Cisco FMC Software to managed FTD devices in high-availability setups. After an affected device is rebooted following Object Groups for ACLs deployment, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access controls and successfully send traffic to devices that are expected to be protected by the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-04T17:40:51.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20360|2024-06-04T17:40:39.489Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20360</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not adequately validate user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain any data from the database, execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system, and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least Read Only user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20360|2024-06-04T17:40:39.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-13T14:05:52.072Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Object Groups for Access Control Lists (ACLs) feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured access controls on managed devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect deployment of the Object Groups for ACLs feature from Cisco FMC Software to managed FTD devices in high-availability setups. After an affected device is rebooted following Object Groups for ACLs deployment, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access controls and successfully send traffic to devices that are expected to be protected by the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-13T14:05:52.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
