<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System (Managed)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System (Managed)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 18:24:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3504|2024-08-04T07:37:54.362Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3504</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the local management (local-mgmt) CLI of Cisco UCS Manager Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of CLI command parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by executing specific commands on the local-mgmt CLI on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause internal system processes to fail to terminate properly, which could result in a buildup of stuck processes and lead to slowness in accessing the UCS Manager CLI and web UI. A sustained attack may result in a restart of internal UCS Manager processes and a temporary loss of access to the UCS Manager CLI and web UI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3504|2024-08-04T07:37:54.362Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34736|2024-08-04T00:19:48.111Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34736</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the web-based management interface to unexpectedly restart. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation on the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the interface to restart, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34736|2024-08-04T00:19:48.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3119|2024-08-04T07:24:00.514Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3119</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Discovery Protocol implementation for Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to execute arbitrary code or cause a reload on an affected device. The vulnerability exists because the Cisco Discovery Protocol parser does not properly validate input for certain fields in a Cisco Discovery Protocol message. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious Cisco Discovery Protocol packet to an affected device. An successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a stack overflow, which could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code with administrative privileges on an affected device. Cisco Discovery Protocol is a Layer 2 protocol. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must be in the same broadcast domain as the affected device (Layer 2 adjacent).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3119|2024-08-04T07:24:00.514Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3172|2024-08-04T07:24:00.791Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3172</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Discovery Protocol feature of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to execute arbitrary code as root or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability exists because of insufficiently validated Cisco Discovery Protocol packet headers. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted Cisco Discovery Protocol packet to a Layer 2-adjacent affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a buffer overflow that could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code as root or cause a DoS condition on the affected device. Note: Cisco Discovery Protocol is a Layer 2 protocol. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must be in the same broadcast domain as the affected device (Layer 2 adjacent). Note: This vulnerability is different from the following Cisco FXOS and NX-OS Software Cisco Discovery Protocol vulnerabilities that Cisco announced on Feb. 5, 2020: Cisco FXOS, IOS XR, and NX-OS Software Cisco Discovery Protocol Denial of Service Vulnerability and Cisco NX-OS Software Cisco Discovery Protocol Remote Code Execution Vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3172|2024-08-04T07:24:00.791Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3173|2024-08-04T07:24:00.704Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3173</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the local management (local-mgmt) CLI of Cisco UCS Manager Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system (OS) on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of command arguments. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted arguments to specific commands on the local management CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying OS with the privileges of the currently logged-in user for all affected platforms excluding Cisco UCS 6400 Series Fabric Interconnects. On Cisco UCS 6400 Series Fabric Interconnects, the injected commands are executed with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3173|2024-08-04T07:24:00.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20344|2024-08-01T21:59:42.290Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20344</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in system resource management in Cisco UCS 6400 and 6500 Series Fabric Interconnects that are in Intersight Managed Mode (IMM) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the Device Console UI of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient rate-limiting of TCP connections to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high number of TCP packets to the Device Console UI. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to cause the Device Console UI process to crash, resulting in a DoS condition. A manual reload of the fabric interconnect is needed to restore complete functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20344|2024-08-01T21:59:42.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20344|2024-02-28T16:16:03.042Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20344</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in system resource management in Cisco UCS 6400 and 6500 Series Fabric Interconnects that are in Intersight Managed Mode (IMM) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the Device Console UI of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient rate-limiting of TCP connections to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high number of TCP packets to the Device Console UI. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to cause the Device Console UI process to crash, resulting in a DoS condition. A manual reload of the fabric interconnect is needed to restore complete functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20344|2024-02-28T16:16:03.042Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20344|2024-07-26T14:35:04.588Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20344</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in system resource management in Cisco UCS 6400 and 6500 Series Fabric Interconnects that are in Intersight Managed Mode (IMM) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the Device Console UI of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient rate-limiting of TCP connections to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high number of TCP packets to the Device Console UI. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to cause the Device Console UI process to crash, resulting in a DoS condition. A manual reload of the fabric interconnect is needed to restore complete functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20344|2024-07-26T14:35:04.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
