<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco TelePresence TC Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20telepresence%20tc%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco TelePresence TC Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 03:24:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15288|2024-09-17T00:31:03.110Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20tc%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15288</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE), Cisco TelePresence Codec (TC), and Cisco RoomOS Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to escalate privileges to an unrestricted user of the restricted shell. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including specific arguments when opening an SSH connection to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain unrestricted user access to the restricted shell of an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15288|2024-09-17T00:31:03.110Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 03:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3143|2024-09-17T00:26:30.480Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20tc%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3143</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the video endpoint API (xAPI) of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) Software, Cisco TelePresence Codec (TC) Software, and Cisco RoomOS Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct directory traversal attacks on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input to the xAPI of the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the xAPI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read and write arbitrary files in the system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need either an In-Room Control or administrator account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3143|2024-09-17T00:26:30.480Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15967|2024-09-17T01:31:13.159Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20tc%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15967</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) and Cisco RoomOS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to enable audio recording without notifying users. The vulnerability is due to the presence of unnecessary debug commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by gaining unrestricted access to the restricted shell and using the specific debug commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to enable the microphone of an affected device to record audio without notifying users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15967|2024-09-17T01:31:13.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 03:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1878|2024-09-17T01:45:54.634Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20tc%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1878</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Discovery Protocol (CDP) implementation for the Cisco TelePresence Codec (TC) and Collaboration Endpoint (CE) Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to inject arbitrary shell commands that are executed by the device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of received CDP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted CDP packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary shell commands or scripts on the targeted device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1878|2024-09-17T01:45:54.634Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 03:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15274|2024-09-17T01:01:40.499Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20tc%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15274</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injections. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating as an administrative level user within the restricted shell and submitting malicious input to a specific command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute previously staged code from the underlying filesystem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15274|2024-09-17T01:01:40.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 18:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
