<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco RV130W Wireless-N Multifunction VPN Router Firmware</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20rv130w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router%20firmware.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco RV130W Wireless-N Multifunction VPN Router Firmware</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:24:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0423|2024-08-05T03:28:09.626Z -- cisco -- cisco%20rv130w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0423</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of the Cisco RV110W Wireless-N VPN Firewall, Cisco RV130W Wireless-N Multifunction VPN Router, and Cisco RV215W Wireless-N VPN Router could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition or to execute arbitrary code. The vulnerability is due to improper boundary restrictions on user-supplied input in the Guest user feature of the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests to a targeted device, triggering a buffer overflow condition. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to stop responding, resulting in a denial of service condition, or could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0423|2024-08-05T03:28:09.626Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0425|2024-08-05T03:28:09.842Z -- cisco -- cisco%20rv130w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0425</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of the Cisco RV110W Wireless-N VPN Firewall, Cisco RV130W Wireless-N Multifunction VPN Router, and Cisco RV215W Wireless-N VPN Router could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain access to sensitive information. The vulnerability is due to improper access control to files within the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to sensitive configuration information, including user authentication credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0425|2024-08-05T03:28:09.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0426|2024-08-05T03:28:09.683Z -- cisco -- cisco%20rv130w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0426</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of the Cisco RV110W Wireless-N VPN Firewall, Cisco RV130W Wireless-N Multifunction VPN Router, and Cisco RV215W Wireless-N VPN Router could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain access to sensitive information. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of directory traversal character sequences within the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests to the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to arbitrary files on the affected device, resulting in the disclosure of sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0426|2024-08-05T03:28:09.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0424|2024-08-05T03:28:09.828Z -- cisco -- cisco%20rv130w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0424</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of the Cisco RV110W Wireless-N VPN Firewall, Cisco RV130W Wireless-N Multifunction VPN Router, and Cisco RV215W Wireless-N VPN Router could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input to scripts by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands with the privileges of the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0424|2024-08-05T03:28:09.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
