<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 03:22:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20798|2024-08-03T02:24:49.567Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20798</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the external authentication functionality of Cisco Secure Email and Web Manager, formerly known as Cisco Security Management Appliance (SMA), and Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass authentication and log in to the web management interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper authentication checks when an affected device uses Lightweight Directory Access Protocol (LDAP) for external authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by entering a specific input on the login page of the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain unauthorized access to the web-based management interface of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20798|2024-08-03T02:24:49.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20664|2024-08-03T02:17:53.012Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20664</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web management interface of Cisco Secure Email and Web Manager, formerly Cisco Security Management Appliance (SMA), and Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to retrieve sensitive information from a Lightweight Directory Access Protocol (LDAP) external authentication server connected to an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper input sanitization while querying the external authentication server. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted query through an external authentication web page. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to sensitive information, including user credentials from the external authentication server. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid operator-level (or higher) credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20664|2024-08-03T02:17:53.012Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20653|2024-08-03T02:17:52.984Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20653</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DNS-based Authentication of Named Entities (DANE) email verification component of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient error handling in DNS name resolution by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specially formatted email messages that are processed by an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to become unreachable from management interfaces or to process additional email messages for a period of time until the device recovers, resulting in a DoS condition. Continued attacks could cause the device to become completely unavailable, resulting in a persistent DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20653|2024-08-03T02:17:52.984Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
