<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Identity Services Engine Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Identity Services Engine Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:21:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3353|2024-09-16T17:23:12.681Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3353</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the syslog processing engine of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a race condition that may occur when syslog messages are processed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high rate of syslog messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Application Server process to crash, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3353|2024-09-16T17:23:12.681Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 17:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34702|2024-09-16T20:12:24.282Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34702</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain sensitive information. This vulnerability is due to improper enforcement of administrator privilege levels for low-value sensitive data. An attacker with read-only administrator access to the web-based management interface could exploit this vulnerability by browsing to the page that contains the sensitive data. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to collect sensitive information regarding the configuration of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34702|2024-09-16T20:12:24.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 19:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27122|2024-09-16T17:42:42.402Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27122</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Microsoft Active Directory integration of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have a valid administrator account on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to incorrect privilege assignment. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to the system with a crafted Active Directory account. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain root privileges on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27122|2024-09-16T17:42:42.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 18:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15255|2024-09-16T19:04:04.298Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15255</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to bypass authorization and access sensitive information related to the device. The vulnerability exists because the software fails to sanitize URLs before it handles requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted URL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain unauthorized access to sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15255|2024-09-16T19:04:04.298Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 04:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1851|2024-09-16T17:28:54.542Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1851</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the External RESTful Services (ERS) API of the Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to generate arbitrary certificates signed by the Internal Certificate Authority (CA) Services on ISE. This vulnerability is due to an incorrect implementation of role-based access control (RBAC). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting a specific HTTP request with administrative credentials. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to generate a certificate that is signed and trusted by the ISE CA with arbitrary attributes. The attacker could use this certificate to access other networks or assets that are protected by certificate authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1851|2024-09-16T17:28:54.542Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 01:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1607|2024-09-16T17:54:02.353Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1607</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user. These vulnerabilities exist because the web-based management interface does not sufficiently validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker would need valid administrative credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1607|2024-09-16T17:54:02.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 18:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15425|2024-09-16T17:14:20.028Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15425</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device with the privileges of the web server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15425|2024-09-16T17:14:20.028Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1736|2024-09-16T17:18:37.782Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1736</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the firmware of the Cisco UCS C-Series Rack Servers could allow an authenticated, physical attacker to bypass Unified Extensible Firmware Interface (UEFI) Secure Boot validation checks and load a compromised software image on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of the server firmware upgrade images. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by installing a server firmware version that would allow the attacker to disable UEFI Secure Boot. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the signature validation checks that are done by UEFI Secure Boot technology and load a compromised software image on the affected device. A compromised software image is any software image that has not been digitally signed by Cisco.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1736|2024-09-16T17:18:37.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3149|2024-09-16T17:44:02.164Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3149</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by providing malicious data to a specific field within the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. Cisco ISE Software releases 2.7.0 and later contains the fix for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3149|2024-09-16T17:44:02.164Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 17:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1594|2024-09-16T16:53:16.146Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1594</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the REST API of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to perform a command injection attack and elevate privileges to root. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation for specific API endpoints. An attacker in a man-in-the-middle position could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting and modifying specific internode communications from one ISE persona to another ISE persona. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to run arbitrary commands with root privileges on the underlying operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to decrypt HTTPS traffic between two ISE personas that are located on separate nodes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1594|2024-09-16T16:53:16.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 19:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12637|2024-09-16T20:58:26.500Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12637</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks against a user of the web-based management interface. The vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input that is processed by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12637|2024-09-16T20:58:26.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 18:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40123|2024-09-16T22:14:10.988Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40123</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative read-only privileges to download files that should be restricted. This vulnerability is due to incorrect permissions settings on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to download files that should be restricted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40123|2024-09-16T22:14:10.988Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 02:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1718|2024-09-16T20:53:14.959Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1718</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger high CPU usage, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) renegotiation requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending renegotiation requests at a high rate. An successful exploit could increase the resource usage on the system, eventually leading to a DoS condition. This vulnerability affects version 2.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1718|2024-09-16T20:53:14.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 22:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12631|2024-09-16T18:13:19.511Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12631</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based guest portal of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input that is processed by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12631|2024-09-16T18:13:19.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 18:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15456|2024-09-16T16:58:58.111Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Admin Portal of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to view saved passwords in plain text. The vulnerability is due to the incorrect inclusion of saved passwords when loading configuration pages in the Admin Portal. An attacker with read or write access to the Admin Portal could exploit this vulnerability by browsing to a page that contains sensitive data. An exploit could allow the attacker to recover passwords for unauthorized use and expose those accounts to further attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15456|2024-09-16T16:58:58.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15459|2024-09-16T17:53:50.101Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15459</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the administrative web interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to gain additional privileges on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper controls on certain pages in the web interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device with an administrator account and sending a crafted HTTP request. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to create additional Admin accounts with different user roles. An attacker could then use these accounts to perform actions within their scope. The attacker would need valid Admin credentials for the device. This vulnerability cannot be exploited to add a Super Admin account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15459|2024-09-16T17:53:50.101Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20782|2024-09-16T18:03:40.367Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20782</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain sensitive information from an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper enforcement of administrative privilege levels for high-value sensitive data. An attacker with read-only Administrator privileges to the web-based management interface on an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by browsing to a page that contains sensitive data. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to collect sensitive information regarding the configuration of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20782|2024-09-16T18:03:40.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 18:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15455|2024-09-16T22:50:56.187Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15455</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the logging component of Cisco Identity Services Engine could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site scripting attacks. The vulnerability is due to the improper validation of requests stored in the system's logging database. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests to the targeted system. An exploit could allow the attacker to conduct cross-site scripting attacks when an administrator views the logs in the Admin Portal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15455|2024-09-16T22:50:56.187Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3156|2024-09-16T17:15:22.168Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3156</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the logging component of Cisco Identity Services Engine could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to conduct cross-site scripting attacks. The vulnerability is due to the improper validation of endpoint data stored in logs used by the web-based interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious endpoint data to the targeted system. An exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or to access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3156|2024-09-16T17:15:22.168Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 19:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15281|2024-09-16T19:41:58.348Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15281</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device. The attacker must have valid administrator credentials. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into a troubleshooting file. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15281|2024-09-16T19:41:58.348Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 18:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15440|2024-09-16T19:46:35.953Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15440</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web interface of an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied data that is written to log files and displayed in certain web pages of the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by convincing a user of the interface to click a specific link or view an affected log file. The injected script code may be executed in the context of the web-based management interface or allow the attacker to access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15440|2024-09-16T19:46:35.953Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3157|2024-09-16T21:56:38.040Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3157</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based interface. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting a malicious configuration and saving it to the targeted system. An exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information when an administrator views the configuration. An attacker would need write permissions to exploit this vulnerability successfully.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3157|2024-09-16T21:56:38.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 18:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1416|2024-09-16T22:14:41.741Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1416</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Admin portal of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain sensitive information. These vulnerabilities are due to improper enforcement of administrator privilege levels for sensitive data. An attacker with read-only administrator access to the Admin portal could exploit these vulnerabilities by browsing to one of the pages that contains sensitive data. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to collect sensitive information regarding the configuration of the system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1416|2024-09-16T22:14:41.741Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 16:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26083|2024-09-16T20:52:27.294Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26083</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative credentials to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have valid administrative credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26083|2024-09-16T20:52:27.294Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 18:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20914|2024-09-16T19:14:10.339Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20914</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the External RESTful Services (ERS) API of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain sensitive information. This vulnerability is due to excessive verbosity in a specific REST API output. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain sensitive information, including administrative credentials for an external authentication server. Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid ERS administrative credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20914|2024-09-16T19:14:10.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 08:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20819|2024-09-16T18:24:15.124Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20819</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain sensitive information from an affected device. This vulnerability exists because administrative privilege levels for sensitive data are not properly enforced. An attacker with read-only privileges for the web-based management interface on an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by browsing to a page that contains sensitive data. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to collect sensitive information about the system configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20819|2024-09-16T18:24:15.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 17:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1941|2024-09-16T22:50:34.239Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1941</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. At the time of publication, this vulnerability affected Cisco ISE running software releases prior to 2.4.0 Patch 9 and 2.6.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1941|2024-09-16T22:50:34.239Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 20:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34759|2024-09-16T18:14:18.486Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34759</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative credentials to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid administrative credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34759|2024-09-16T18:14:18.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 03:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20959|2024-09-16T16:23:49.482Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20959</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the External RESTful Services (ERS) API of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated administrator of the web-based management interface to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20959|2024-09-16T16:23:49.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 14:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40121|2024-09-16T18:38:39.767Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40121</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) Software could allow an attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40121|2024-09-16T18:38:39.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 02:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20469|2024-09-06T03:55:19.640Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20469</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in specific CLI commands in Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid Administrator privileges on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20469|2024-09-06T03:55:19.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20469|2024-09-04T16:28:56.583Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20469</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in specific CLI commands in Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid Administrator privileges on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20469|2024-09-04T16:28:56.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20466|2024-08-22T13:44:19.503Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20466</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain sensitive information from an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper enforcement of administrative privilege levels for high-value sensitive data. An attacker with read-only Administrator privileges for the web-based management interface on an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by browsing to a page that contains sensitive data. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to collect sensitive information regarding the configuration of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20466|2024-08-22T13:44:19.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 19:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20479|2024-08-08T03:55:31.843Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20479</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have Admin privileges on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20479|2024-08-08T03:55:31.843Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20479|2024-08-07T16:43:57.683Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20479</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have Admin privileges on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20479|2024-08-07T16:43:57.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20368|2024-08-01T21:59:41.799Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20368</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on the affected device with the privileges of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20368|2024-08-01T21:59:41.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20332|2024-08-01T21:59:41.923Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20332</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack through an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation for specific HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send arbitrary network requests that are sourced from the affected device. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid Super Admin credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20332|2024-08-01T21:59:41.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-08-01T21:59:41.103Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-08-01T21:59:41.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T21:20:23.314Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T21:20:23.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20332|2024-06-04T17:40:15.273Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20332</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack through an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation for specific HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send arbitrary network requests that are sourced from the affected device. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid Super Admin credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20332|2024-06-04T17:40:15.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20368|2024-06-04T17:40:10.016Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20368</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on the affected device with the privileges of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20368|2024-06-04T17:40:10.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T16:28:22.193Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T16:28:22.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-18T03:55:22.366Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-18T03:55:22.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20479|2024-08-07T17:37:24.445Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20479</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have Admin privileges on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20479|2024-08-07T17:37:24.445Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20466|2024-08-21T19:16:36.810Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20466</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain sensitive information from an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper enforcement of administrative privilege levels for high-value sensitive data. An attacker with read-only Administrator privileges for the web-based management interface on an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by browsing to a page that contains sensitive data. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to collect sensitive information regarding the configuration of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20466|2024-08-21T19:16:36.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 19:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20486|2024-08-21T19:53:51.297Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20486</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on the affected device with the privileges of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20486|2024-08-21T19:53:51.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 19:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20417|2024-08-21T19:16:43.196Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20417</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the REST API of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct blind SQL injection attacks.

These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input in REST API calls. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted input to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view or modify data on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20417|2024-08-21T19:16:43.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 19:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20417|2024-08-27T13:43:25.274Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20417</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the REST API of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct blind SQL injection attacks.

These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input in REST API calls. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted input to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view or modify data on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20417|2024-08-27T13:43:25.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 19:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20469|2024-09-04T18:07:36.979Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20469</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in specific CLI commands in Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid Administrator privileges on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20469|2024-09-04T18:07:36.979Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20466|2024-09-11T15:09:40.573Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20466</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain sensitive information from an affected device. 

This vulnerability is due to improper enforcement of administrative privilege levels for high-value sensitive data. An attacker with read-only Administrator privileges for the web-based management interface on an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by browsing to a page that contains sensitive data. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to collect sensitive information regarding the configuration of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20466|2024-09-11T15:09:40.573Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 19:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
