<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 22:23:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3259|2024-10-24T17:40:59.135Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web services interface of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to retrieve memory contents on an affected device, which could lead to the disclosure of confidential information. The vulnerability is due to a buffer tracking issue when the software parses invalid URLs that are requested from the web services interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted GET request to the web services interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve memory contents, which could lead to the disclosure of confidential information. Note: This vulnerability affects only specific AnyConnect and WebVPN configurations. For more information, see the Vulnerable Products section.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3259|2024-10-24T17:40:59.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20384|2024-10-24T17:04:49.872Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20384</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Network Service Group (NSG) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured access control list (ACL) and allow traffic that should be denied to flow through an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when NSG ACLs are populated on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing a connection to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20384|2024-10-24T17:04:49.872Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20370|2024-10-24T17:34:23.269Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20370</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco FXOS CLI feature on specific hardware platforms for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate their administrative privileges to root. The attacker would need valid administrative credentials on the device to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because certain system configurations and executable files have insecure storage and permissions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating on the device and then performing a series of steps that includes downloading malicious system files and accessing the Cisco FXOS CLI to configure the attack. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain root access on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20370|2024-10-24T17:34:23.269Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20331|2024-10-24T17:48:23.908Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20331</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the session authentication functionality of the Remote Access SSL VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to prevent users from authenticating.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient entropy in the authentication process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by determining the handle of an authenticating user and using it to terminate their authentication session. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to force a user to restart the authentication process, preventing a legitimate user from establishing remote access VPN sessions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20331|2024-10-24T17:48:23.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20382|2024-10-24T17:47:33.387Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20382</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the VPN web client services feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a browser that is accessing an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input to application endpoints. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to follow a link designed to submit malicious input to the affected application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or script code in the browser in the context of the web services page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20382|2024-10-24T17:47:33.387Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20268|2024-10-24T17:51:17.009Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20268</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause an unexpected reload of the device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of SNMP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SNMP request to an affected device using IPv4 or IPv6. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability affects all versions of SNMP (versions 1, 2c, and 3) and requires a valid SNMP community string or valid SNMPv3 user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20268|2024-10-24T17:51:17.009Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:06:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20408|2024-10-24T17:47:04.680Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20408</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Dynamic Access Policies (DAP) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid remote access VPN user credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of data in HTTPS POST requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTPS POST request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20408|2024-10-24T17:47:04.680Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20297|2024-10-24T17:14:45.950Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20297</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the AnyConnect firewall for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured access control list (ACL) and allow traffic that should have been denied to flow through an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error in populating group ACLs when an AnyConnect client establishes a new session toward an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing an AnyConnect connection to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20297|2024-10-24T17:14:45.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:07:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20341|2024-10-24T17:48:03.330Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20341</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the VPN web client services feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a browser that is accessing an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input to application endpoints. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to follow a link designed to submit malicious input to the affected application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or script code in the browser in the context of the web services page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20341|2024-10-24T17:48:03.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20260|2024-10-24T17:30:13.136Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20260</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the VPN and management web servers of the Cisco Adaptive Security Virtual Appliance (ASAv) and Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defense Virtual (FTDv), formerly Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Virtual, platforms could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the virtual devices to run out of system memory, which could cause SSL VPN connection processing to slow down and eventually cease all together.

This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper memory management for new incoming SSL/TLS connections on the virtual platforms. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of new incoming SSL/TLS connections to the targeted virtual platform. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to deplete system memory,&amp;nbsp;resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The memory could be reclaimed slowly if the attack traffic is stopped, but a manual reload may be required to restore operations quickly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20260|2024-10-24T17:30:13.136Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20426|2024-10-24T15:27:42.137Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20426</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Internet Key Exchange version 2 (IKEv2) protocol for VPN termination of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted IKEv2 traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20426|2024-10-24T15:27:42.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20481|2024-10-24T15:15:07.946Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20481</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Remote Access VPN (RAVPN) service of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) of the RAVPN service.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to resource exhaustion. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of VPN authentication requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust resources, resulting in a DoS of the RAVPN service on the affected device. Depending on the impact of the attack, a reload of the device may be required to restore the RAVPN service. Services that are not related to VPN are not affected.
&#13; Cisco Talos discussed these attacks in the blog post Large-scale brute-force activity targeting VPNs, SSH services with commonly used login credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20481|2024-10-24T15:15:07.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20495|2024-10-23T19:12:27.560Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20495</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Remote Access VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of client key data after the TLS session is established. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted key value to an affected system over the secure TLS session. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20495|2024-10-23T19:12:27.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20493|2024-10-23T19:52:38.386Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20493</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the login authentication functionality of the Remote Access SSL VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to deny further VPN user authentications for several minutes, resulting in a temporary denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to ineffective handling of memory resources during the authentication process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted packets, which could cause resource exhaustion of the authentication process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to deny authentication for Remote Access SSL VPN users for several minutes, resulting in a temporary DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20493|2024-10-23T19:52:38.386Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20494|2024-10-23T19:39:04.608Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20494</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TLS cryptography functionality of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper data validation during the TLS 1.3 handshake. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted TLS 1.3 packet to an affected system through a TLS 1.3-enabled listening socket. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; Note: This vulnerability can also impact the integrity of a device by causing VPN HostScan communication failures or file transfer failures when Cisco ASA Software is upgraded using Cisco Adaptive Security Device Manager (ASDM).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20494|2024-10-23T19:39:04.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20297|2024-10-23T19:55:59.555Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20297</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the AnyConnect firewall for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured access control list (ACL) and allow traffic that should have been denied to flow through an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error in populating group ACLs when an AnyConnect client establishes a new session toward an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing an AnyConnect connection to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20297|2024-10-23T19:55:59.555Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:07:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20260|2024-10-23T19:40:17.959Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20260</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the VPN and management web servers of the Cisco Adaptive Security Virtual Appliance (ASAv) and Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defense Virtual (FTDv), formerly Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Virtual, platforms could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the virtual devices to run out of system memory, which could cause SSL VPN connection processing to slow down and eventually cease all together.

This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper memory management for new incoming SSL/TLS connections on the virtual platforms. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of new incoming SSL/TLS connections to the targeted virtual platform. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to deplete system memory,&amp;nbsp;resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The memory could be reclaimed slowly if the attack traffic is stopped, but a manual reload may be required to restore operations quickly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20260|2024-10-23T19:40:17.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20495|2024-10-23T17:53:14.516Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20495</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Remote Access VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of client key data after the TLS session is established. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted key value to an affected system over the secure TLS session. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20495|2024-10-23T17:53:14.516Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20384|2024-10-23T17:32:29.353Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20384</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Network Service Group (NSG) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured access control list (ACL) and allow traffic that should be denied to flow through an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when NSG ACLs are populated on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing a connection to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20384|2024-10-23T17:32:29.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20370|2024-10-23T17:29:05.240Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20370</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco FXOS CLI feature on specific hardware platforms for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate their administrative privileges to root. The attacker would need valid administrative credentials on the device to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because certain system configurations and executable files have insecure storage and permissions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating on the device and then performing a series of steps that includes downloading malicious system files and accessing the Cisco FXOS CLI to configure the attack. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain root access on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20370|2024-10-23T17:29:05.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20329|2024-10-23T17:08:34.266Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20329</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSH subsystem of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute operating system commands as root.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting crafted input when executing remote CLI commands over SSH. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands on the underlying operating system with root-level privileges. An attacker with limited user privileges could use this vulnerability to gain complete control over the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20329|2024-10-23T17:08:34.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20331|2024-10-23T17:08:53.583Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20331</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the session authentication functionality of the Remote Access SSL VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to prevent users from authenticating.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient entropy in the authentication process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by determining the handle of an authenticating user and using it to terminate their authentication session. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to force a user to restart the authentication process, preventing a legitimate user from establishing remote access VPN sessions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20331|2024-10-23T17:08:53.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20526|2024-10-23T17:53:35.602Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20526</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSH server of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition for the SSH server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a logic error when an SSH session is established. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted SSH messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust available SSH resources on the affected device so that new SSH connections to the device are denied, resulting in a DoS condition. Existing SSH connections to the device would continue to function normally. The device must be rebooted manually to recover. However, user traffic would not be impacted and could be managed using a remote application such as Cisco Adaptive Security Device Manager (ASDM).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20526|2024-10-23T17:53:35.602Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:53:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20485|2024-10-23T17:52:26.811Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20485</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the VPN web server of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of a specific file when it is read from system flash memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected device after the next reload of the device, which could alter system behavior. Because the injected code could persist across device reboots, Cisco has raised the Security Impact Rating (SIR) of this advisory from Medium to High.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20485|2024-10-23T17:52:26.811Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20382|2024-10-23T17:31:49.114Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20382</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the VPN web client services feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a browser that is accessing an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input to application endpoints. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to follow a link designed to submit malicious input to the affected application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or script code in the browser in the context of the web services page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20382|2024-10-23T17:31:49.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20268|2024-10-23T17:06:57.460Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20268</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause an unexpected reload of the device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of SNMP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SNMP request to an affected device using IPv4 or IPv6. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability affects all versions of SNMP (versions 1, 2c, and 3) and requires a valid SNMP community string or valid SNMPv3 user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20268|2024-10-23T17:06:57.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:06:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20493|2024-10-23T17:52:42.024Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20493</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the login authentication functionality of the Remote Access SSL VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to deny further VPN user authentications for several minutes, resulting in a temporary denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to ineffective handling of memory resources during the authentication process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted packets, which could cause resource exhaustion of the authentication process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to deny authentication for Remote Access SSL VPN users for several minutes, resulting in a temporary DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20493|2024-10-23T17:52:42.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20426|2024-10-23T17:46:42.692Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20426</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Internet Key Exchange version 2 (IKEv2) protocol for VPN termination of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted IKEv2 traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20426|2024-10-23T17:46:42.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20494|2024-10-23T17:53:00.574Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20494</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TLS cryptography functionality of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper data validation during the TLS 1.3 handshake. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted TLS 1.3 packet to an affected system through a TLS 1.3-enabled listening socket. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; Note: This vulnerability can also impact the integrity of a device by causing VPN HostScan communication failures or file transfer failures when Cisco ASA Software is upgraded using Cisco Adaptive Security Device Manager (ASDM).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20494|2024-10-23T17:53:00.574Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20408|2024-10-23T17:37:12.496Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20408</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Dynamic Access Policies (DAP) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid remote access VPN user credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of data in HTTPS POST requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTPS POST request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20408|2024-10-23T17:37:12.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20297|2024-10-23T17:07:52.657Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20297</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the AnyConnect firewall for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured access control list (ACL) and allow traffic that should have been denied to flow through an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error in populating group ACLs when an AnyConnect client establishes a new session toward an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing an AnyConnect connection to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20297|2024-10-23T17:07:52.657Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:07:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20341|2024-10-23T17:09:19.351Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20341</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the VPN web client services feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a browser that is accessing an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input to application endpoints. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to follow a link designed to submit malicious input to the affected application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or script code in the browser in the context of the web services page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20341|2024-10-23T17:09:19.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20402|2024-10-23T17:35:43.314Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20402</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSL VPN feature for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a logic error in memory management when the device is handling SSL VPN connections. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted SSL/TLS packets to the SSL VPN server of the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20402|2024-10-23T17:35:43.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:35:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20299|2024-10-23T17:08:13.630Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20299</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the AnyConnect firewall for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured access control list (ACL) and allow traffic that should have been denied to flow through an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error in populating group ACLs when an AnyConnect client establishes a new session toward an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing an AnyConnect connection to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20299|2024-10-23T17:08:13.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20481|2024-10-23T17:51:38.649Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20481</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Remote Access VPN (RAVPN) service of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) of the RAVPN service.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to resource exhaustion. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of VPN authentication requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust resources, resulting in a DoS of the RAVPN service on the affected device. Depending on the impact of the attack, a reload of the device may be required to restore the RAVPN service. Services that are not related to VPN are not affected.
&#13; Cisco Talos discussed these attacks in the blog post Large-scale brute-force activity targeting VPNs, SSH services with commonly used login credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20481|2024-10-23T17:51:38.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20260|2024-10-23T17:07:17.073Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20260</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the VPN and management web servers of the Cisco Adaptive Security Virtual Appliance (ASAv) and Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defense Virtual (FTDv), formerly Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Virtual, platforms could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the virtual devices to run out of system memory, which could cause SSL VPN connection processing to slow down and eventually cease all together.

This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper memory management for new incoming SSL/TLS connections on the virtual platforms. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of new incoming SSL/TLS connections to the targeted virtual platform. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to deplete system memory,&amp;nbsp;resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The memory could be reclaimed slowly if the attack traffic is stopped, but a manual reload may be required to restore operations quickly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20260|2024-10-23T17:07:17.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20443|2024-08-07T18:13:18.759Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20443</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have at least a low-privileged account on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20443|2024-08-07T18:13:18.759Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20293|2024-08-01T21:59:41.290Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the activation of an access control list (ACL) on Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the protection that is offered by a configured ACL on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an ACL changes from inactive to active in the running configuration of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device that should be denied by the configured ACL. The reverse condition is also true—traffic that should be permitted could be denied by the configured ACL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL protections on the affected device, allowing the attacker to access trusted networks that the device might be protecting. Note: This vulnerability applies to both IPv4 and IPv6 traffic as well as dual-stack ACL configurations in which both IPv4 and IPv6 ACLs are configured on an interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20293|2024-08-01T21:59:41.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20355|2024-08-01T21:59:42.284Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20355</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of SAML 2.0 single sign-on (SSO) for remote access VPN services in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to successfully establish a VPN session on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper separation of authorization domains when using SAML authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using valid credentials to successfully authenticate using their designated connection profile (tunnel group), intercepting the SAML SSO token that is sent back from the Cisco ASA device, and then submitting the same SAML SSO token to a different tunnel group for authentication. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to establish a remote access VPN session using a connection profile that they are not authorized to use and connect to secured networks behind the affected device that they are not authorized to access. For successful exploitation, the attacker must have valid remote access VPN user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20355|2024-08-01T21:59:42.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20355|2024-06-04T17:39:58.380Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20355</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of SAML 2.0 single sign-on (SSO) for remote access VPN services in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to successfully establish a VPN session on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper separation of authorization domains when using SAML authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using valid credentials to successfully authenticate using their designated connection profile (tunnel group), intercepting the SAML SSO token that is sent back from the Cisco ASA device, and then submitting the same SAML SSO token to a different tunnel group for authentication. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to establish a remote access VPN session using a connection profile that they are not authorized to use and connect to secured networks behind the affected device that they are not authorized to access. For successful exploitation, the attacker must have valid remote access VPN user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20355|2024-06-04T17:39:58.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20293|2024-06-04T17:39:54.684Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the activation of an access control list (ACL) on Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the protection that is offered by a configured ACL on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an ACL changes from inactive to active in the running configuration of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device that should be denied by the configured ACL. The reverse condition is also true—traffic that should be permitted could be denied by the configured ACL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL protections on the affected device, allowing the attacker to access trusted networks that the device might be protecting. Note: This vulnerability applies to both IPv4 and IPv6 traffic as well as dual-stack ACL configurations in which both IPv4 and IPv6 ACLs are configured on an interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20293|2024-06-04T17:39:54.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20293|2024-07-02T15:36:56.903Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the activation of an access control list (ACL) on Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the protection that is offered by a configured ACL on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an ACL changes from inactive to active in the running configuration of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device that should be denied by the configured ACL. The reverse condition is also true—traffic that should be permitted could be denied by the configured ACL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL protections on the affected device, allowing the attacker to access trusted networks that the device might be protecting. Note: This vulnerability applies to both IPv4 and IPv6 traffic as well as dual-stack ACL configurations in which both IPv4 and IPv6 ACLs are configured on an interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20293|2024-07-02T15:36:56.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20443|2024-08-07T16:42:05.023Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20443</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have at least a low-privileged account on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20443|2024-08-07T16:42:05.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20443|2024-08-08T03:55:30.688Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20443</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have at least a low-privileged account on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20443|2024-08-08T03:55:30.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20526|2024-10-23T18:41:16.962Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20526</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSH server of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition for the SSH server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a logic error when an SSH session is established. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted SSH messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust available SSH resources on the affected device so that new SSH connections to the device are denied, resulting in a DoS condition. Existing SSH connections to the device would continue to function normally. The device must be rebooted manually to recover. However, user traffic would not be impacted and could be managed using a remote application such as Cisco Adaptive Security Device Manager (ASDM).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20526|2024-10-23T18:41:16.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:53:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20485|2024-10-23T20:52:46.637Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20485</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the VPN web server of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of a specific file when it is read from system flash memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected device after the next reload of the device, which could alter system behavior. Because the injected code could persist across device reboots, Cisco has raised the Security Impact Rating (SIR) of this advisory from Medium to High.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20485|2024-10-23T20:52:46.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20481|2024-10-24T16:20:23.198Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20481</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Remote Access VPN (RAVPN) service of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) of the RAVPN service.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to resource exhaustion. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of VPN authentication requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust resources, resulting in a DoS of the RAVPN service on the affected device. Depending on the impact of the attack, a reload of the device may be required to restore the RAVPN service. Services that are not related to VPN are not affected.
&#13; Cisco Talos discussed these attacks in the blog post Large-scale brute-force activity targeting VPNs, SSH services with commonly used login credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20481|2024-10-24T16:20:23.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20299|2024-10-24T16:39:38.139Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20299</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the AnyConnect firewall for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured access control list (ACL) and allow traffic that should have been denied to flow through an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error in populating group ACLs when an AnyConnect client establishes a new session toward an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing an AnyConnect connection to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20299|2024-10-24T16:39:38.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20402|2024-10-24T16:16:53.323Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20402</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSL VPN feature for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a logic error in memory management when the device is handling SSL VPN connections. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted SSL/TLS packets to the SSL VPN server of the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20402|2024-10-24T16:16:53.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:35:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20329|2024-10-24T16:27:18.335Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20329</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSH subsystem of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute operating system commands as root.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting crafted input when executing remote CLI commands over SSH. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands on the underlying operating system with root-level privileges. An attacker with limited user privileges could use this vulnerability to gain complete control over the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20329|2024-10-24T16:27:18.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
