<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Contact Center Express</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20unified%20contact%20center%20express.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Contact Center Express</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20096|2023-04-05T00:00:00 -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20contact%20center%20express
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-20096</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unified Contact Center Express (Unified CCX) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of user-supplied data. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by entering crafted text into various input fields within the web-based management interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform a stored XSS attack, which could allow the execution of scripts within the context of other users of the interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20096|2023-04-05T00:00:00</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20232|2024-01-25T16:58:26.865Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20contact%20center%20express
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-20232</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Tomcat implementation for Cisco Unified Contact Center Express (Unified CCX) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a web cache poisoning attack on an affected device. &#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation of HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to a specific API endpoint on the Unified CCX Finesse Portal. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the internal WebProxy to redirect users to an attacker-controlled host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20232|2024-01-25T16:58:26.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:39:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
