<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Small Business 220 Series Smart Plus Switches</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20small%20business%20220%20series%20smart%20plus%20switches.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Small Business 220 Series Smart Plus Switches</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 06:24:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1543|2024-09-17T03:43:51.049Z -- cisco -- cisco%20small%20business%20220%20series%20smart%20plus%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1543</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business 220 Series Smart Switches could allow an attacker to do the following: Hijack a user session Execute arbitrary commands as a root user on the underlying operating system Conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack Conduct an HTML injection attack For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1543|2024-09-17T03:43:51.049Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 17:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1912|2024-09-17T02:37:00.103Z -- cisco -- cisco%20small%20business%20220%20series%20smart%20plus%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1912</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web management interface of Cisco Small Business 220 Series Smart Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files. The vulnerability is due to incomplete authorization checks in the web management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious request to certain parts of the web management interface. Depending on the configuration of the affected switch, the malicious request must be sent via HTTP or HTTPS. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify the configuration of an affected device or to inject a reverse shell. This vulnerability affects Cisco Small Business 220 Series Smart Switches running firmware versions prior to 1.1.4.4 with the web management interface enabled. The web management interface is enabled via both HTTP and HTTPS by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1912|2024-09-17T02:37:00.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 05:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1571|2024-09-17T03:37:48.502Z -- cisco -- cisco%20small%20business%20220%20series%20smart%20plus%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1571</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business 220 Series Smart Switches could allow an attacker to do the following: Hijack a user session Execute arbitrary commands as a root user on the underlying operating system Conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack Conduct an HTML injection attack For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1571|2024-09-17T03:37:48.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 17:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
