<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 23:23:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0484|2024-09-17T02:32:39.374Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0484</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control logic of the Secure Shell (SSH) server of Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software may allow connections sourced from a virtual routing and forwarding (VRF) instance despite the absence of the vrf-also keyword in the access-class configuration. The vulnerability is due to a missing check in the SSH server. An attacker could use this vulnerability to open an SSH connection to an affected Cisco IOS or IOS XE device with a source address belonging to a VRF instance. Once connected, the attacker would still need to provide valid credentials to access the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0484|2024-09-17T02:32:39.374Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1460|2024-09-17T00:10:56.637Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1460</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco IOx Application Framework of Cisco 809 Industrial Integrated Services Routers (Industrial ISRs), Cisco 829 Industrial ISRs, Cisco CGR 1000 Compute Module, and Cisco IC3000 Industrial Compute Gateway could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient error handling during packet processing. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high and sustained rate of crafted TCP traffic to the IOx web server on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the IOx web server to stop processing requests, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1460|2024-09-17T00:10:56.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3477|2024-09-17T04:19:17.561Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3477</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI parser of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access files from the flash: filesystem. The vulnerability is due to insufficient application of restrictions during the execution of a specific command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using a specific command at the command line. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain read-only access to files that are located on the flash: filesystem that otherwise might not have been accessible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3477|2024-09-17T04:19:17.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34703|2024-09-17T03:38:24.005Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34703</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Link Layer Discovery Protocol (LLDP) message parser of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an attacker to trigger a reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper initialization of a buffer. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability via any of the following methods: An authenticated, remote attacker could access the LLDP neighbor table via either the CLI or SNMP while the device is in a specific state. An unauthenticated, adjacent attacker could corrupt the LLDP neighbor table by injecting specific LLDP frames into the network and then waiting for an administrator of the device or a network management system (NMS) managing the device to retrieve the LLDP neighbor table of the device via either the CLI or SNMP. An authenticated, adjacent attacker with SNMP read-only credentials or low privileges on the device CLI could corrupt the LLDP neighbor table by injecting specific LLDP frames into the network and then accessing the LLDP neighbor table via either the CLI or SNMP. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash, resulting in a reload of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34703|2024-09-17T03:38:24.005Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20721|2024-09-17T03:33:09.640Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20721</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Cisco IOx application hosting environment on multiple Cisco platforms could allow an attacker to inject arbitrary commands into the underlying host operating system, execute arbitrary code on the underlying host operating system, install applications without being authenticated, or conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the affected software. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20721|2024-09-17T03:33:09.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1620|2024-09-17T00:41:20.139Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1620</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Internet Key Exchange Version 2 (IKEv2) support for the AutoReconnect feature of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to exhaust the free IP addresses from the assigned local pool. This vulnerability occurs because the code does not release the allocated IP address under certain failure conditions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by trying to connect to the device with a non-AnyConnect client. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust the IP addresses from the assigned local pool, which prevents users from logging in and leads to a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1620|2024-09-17T00:41:20.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3511|2024-09-17T03:59:55.252Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3511</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the ISDN subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation when the ISDN Q.931 messages are processed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious ISDN Q.931 message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the process to crash, resulting in a reload of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3511|2024-09-17T03:59:55.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20697|2024-09-17T02:27:17.717Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20697</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web services interface of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper resource management in the HTTP server code. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of HTTP requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20697|2024-09-17T02:27:17.717Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20720|2024-09-17T02:47:07.707Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20720</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Cisco IOx application hosting environment on multiple Cisco platforms could allow an attacker to inject arbitrary commands into the underlying host operating system, execute arbitrary code on the underlying host operating system, install applications without being authenticated, or conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the affected software. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20720|2024-09-17T02:47:07.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20718|2024-09-17T03:53:42.768Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20718</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Cisco IOx application hosting environment on multiple Cisco platforms could allow an attacker to inject arbitrary commands into the underlying host operating system, execute arbitrary code on the underlying host operating system, install applications without being authenticated, or conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the affected software. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20718|2024-09-17T03:53:42.768Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0282|2024-09-17T02:11:14.781Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0282</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TCP socket code of Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload. The vulnerability is due to a state condition between the socket state and the transmission control block (TCB) state. While this vulnerability potentially affects all TCP applications, the only affected application observed so far is the HTTP server. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific HTTP requests at a sustained rate to a reachable IP address of the affected software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0282|2024-09-17T02:11:14.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20719|2024-09-17T03:38:29.211Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20719</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Cisco IOx application hosting environment on multiple Cisco platforms could allow an attacker to inject arbitrary commands into the underlying host operating system, execute arbitrary code on the underlying host operating system, install applications without being authenticated, or conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the affected software. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20719|2024-09-17T03:38:29.211Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20725|2024-09-17T02:46:35.280Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20725</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Cisco IOx application hosting environment on multiple Cisco platforms could allow an attacker to inject arbitrary commands into the underlying host operating system, execute arbitrary code on the underlying host operating system, install applications without being authenticated, or conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the affected software. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20725|2024-09-17T02:46:35.280Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:21:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3512|2024-09-17T04:29:15.538Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3512</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the PROFINET handler for Link Layer Discovery Protocol (LLDP) messages of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a crash on an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of LLDP messages in the PROFINET LLDP message handler. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious LLDP message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3512|2024-09-17T04:29:15.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20724|2024-09-17T01:50:49.444Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20724</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Cisco IOx application hosting environment on multiple Cisco platforms could allow an attacker to inject arbitrary commands into the underlying host operating system, execute arbitrary code on the underlying host operating system, install applications without being authenticated, or conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the affected software. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20724|2024-09-17T01:50:49.444Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:21:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
