<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:23:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1534|2024-09-16T19:56:52.599Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1534</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the antispam protection mechanisms of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the URL reputation filters on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper processing of URLs. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting a URL in a particular way. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the URL reputation filters that are configured for an affected device, which could allow malicious URLs to pass through the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1534|2024-09-16T19:56:52.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 19:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3133|2024-09-16T16:17:40.867Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3133</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the email message scanning of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured filters on the device. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of incoming emails. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted email message to a recipient protected by the ESA. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the configured content filters, which could allow malicious content to pass through the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3133|2024-09-16T16:17:40.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20798|2024-09-16T19:09:22.295Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20798</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the external authentication functionality of Cisco Secure Email and Web Manager, formerly known as Cisco Security Management Appliance (SMA), and Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass authentication and log in to the web management interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper authentication checks when an affected device uses Lightweight Directory Access Protocol (LDAP) for external authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by entering a specific input on the login page of the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain unauthorized access to the web-based management interface of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20798|2024-09-16T19:09:22.295Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 17:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3181|2024-09-16T16:53:26.678Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3181</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the malware detection functionality in Cisco Advanced Malware Protection (AMP) in Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliances (ESAs) could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to exhaust resources on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient control over system memory allocation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted email through the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an email attachment that contains malware to be delivered to a user and cause email processing delays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3181|2024-09-16T16:53:26.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 18:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15453|2024-09-16T19:19:26.638Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15453</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure/Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions (S/MIME) Decryption and Verification or S/MIME Public Key Harvesting features of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to corrupt system memory. A successful exploit could cause the filtering process to unexpectedly reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on the device. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation of S/MIME-signed emails. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious S/MIME-signed email through a targeted device. If Decryption and Verification or Public Key Harvesting is configured, the filtering process could crash due to memory corruption and restart, resulting in a DoS condition. The software could then resume processing the same S/MIME-signed email, causing the filtering process to crash and restart again. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a permanent DoS condition. This vulnerability may require manual intervention to recover the ESA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15453|2024-09-16T19:19:26.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34741|2024-09-16T19:29:57.114Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34741</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the email scanning algorithm of Cisco AsyncOS software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to perform a denial of service (DoS) attack against an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of incoming emails. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted email through Cisco ESA. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust all the available CPU resources on an affected device for an extended period of time, preventing other emails from being processed and resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34741|2024-09-16T19:29:57.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1844|2024-09-16T19:24:58.177Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1844</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in certain attachment detection mechanisms of the Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the filtering functionality of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper detection of certain content sent to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain file types without Content-Disposition information to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to send messages that contain malicious content to users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1844|2024-09-16T19:24:58.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 16:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20653|2024-09-16T16:53:23.675Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20653</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DNS-based Authentication of Named Entities (DANE) email verification component of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient error handling in DNS name resolution by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specially formatted email messages that are processed by an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to become unreachable from management interfaces or to process additional email messages for a period of time until the device recovers, resulting in a DoS condition. Continued attacks could cause the device to become completely unavailable, resulting in a persistent DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20653|2024-09-16T16:53:23.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 15:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3568|2024-09-16T16:37:58.977Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3568</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the antispam protection mechanisms of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the URL reputation filters on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of URLs. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting a URL in a particular way. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the URL reputation filters that are configured for the affected device, which could allow malicious URLs to pass through the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3568|2024-09-16T16:37:58.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 04:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
