<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:23:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20919|2024-09-16T18:34:46.102Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20919</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the processing of malformed Common Industrial Protocol (CIP) packets that are sent to Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to unexpectedly reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation during processing of CIP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed CIP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to unexpectedly reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20919|2024-09-16T18:34:46.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 18:46:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1385|2024-09-16T19:15:57.992Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1385</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco IOx application hosting environment of multiple Cisco platforms could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct directory traversal attacks and read and write files on the underlying operating system or host system. This vulnerability occurs because the device does not properly validate URIs in IOx API requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted API request that contains directory traversal character sequences to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read or write arbitrary files on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1385|2024-09-16T19:15:57.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20722|2024-09-16T18:08:18.562Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20722</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Cisco IOx application hosting environment on multiple Cisco platforms could allow an attacker to inject arbitrary commands into the underlying host operating system, execute arbitrary code on the underlying host operating system, install applications without being authenticated, or conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the affected software. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20722|2024-09-16T18:08:18.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20726|2024-09-16T18:43:22.070Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20726</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Cisco IOx application hosting environment on multiple Cisco platforms could allow an attacker to inject arbitrary commands into the underlying host operating system, execute arbitrary code on the underlying host operating system, install applications without being authenticated, or conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the affected software. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20726|2024-09-16T18:43:22.070Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20727|2024-09-16T19:30:51.918Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20727</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Cisco IOx application hosting environment on multiple Cisco platforms could allow an attacker to inject arbitrary commands into the underlying host operating system, execute arbitrary code on the underlying host operating system, install applications without being authenticated, or conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the affected software. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20727|2024-09-16T19:30:51.918Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34705|2024-09-16T18:33:27.582Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34705</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Voice Telephony Service Provider (VTSP) service of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured destination patterns and dial arbitrary numbers. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of dial strings at Foreign Exchange Office (FXO) interfaces. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed dial string to an affected device via either the ISDN protocol or SIP. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct toll fraud, resulting in unexpected financial impact to affected customers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34705|2024-09-16T18:33:27.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1392|2024-09-16T19:10:17.111Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1392</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI command permissions of Cisco IOS and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to retrieve the password for Common Industrial Protocol (CIP) and then remotely configure the device as an administrative user. This vulnerability exists because incorrect permissions are associated with the show cip security CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by issuing the command to retrieve the password for CIP on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to reconfigure the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1392|2024-09-16T19:10:17.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
