<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Wireless LAN Controller (WLC)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20wireless%20lan%20controller%20%28wlc%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Wireless LAN Controller (WLC)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 13:23:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3492|2024-08-04T07:37:54.461Z -- cisco -- cisco%20wireless%20lan%20controller%20%28wlc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3492</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Flexible NetFlow Version 9 packet processor of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers and Cisco AireOS Software for Cisco Wireless LAN Controllers (WLC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of certain parameters in a Flexible NetFlow Version 9 record. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by spoofing the address of an existing Access Point on the network and sending a Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) packet that includes a crafted Flexible NetFlow Version 9 record to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a process crash that would lead to a reload of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3492|2024-08-04T07:37:54.461Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3273|2024-08-04T07:30:57.547Z -- cisco -- cisco%20wireless%20lan%20controller%20%28wlc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3273</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the 802.11 Generic Advertisement Service (GAS) frame processing function of Cisco Wireless LAN Controller (WLC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS). The vulnerability is due to incomplete input validation of the 802.11 GAS frames that are processed by an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted 802.11 GAS frame over the air to an access point (AP), and that frame would then be relayed to the affected WLC. Also, an attacker with Layer 3 connectivity to the WLC could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious 802.11 GAS payload in a Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) packet to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3273|2024-08-04T07:30:57.547Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
