<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Umbrella Insights Virtual Appliance</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20umbrella%20insights%20virtual%20appliance.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Umbrella Insights Virtual Appliance</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:19:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20805|2024-08-03T02:24:49.669Z -- cisco -- cisco%20umbrella%20insights%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20805</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the automatic decryption process in Cisco Umbrella Secure Web Gateway (SWG) could allow an authenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass the SSL decryption and content filtering policies on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to how the decryption function uses the TLS Sever Name Indication (SNI) extension of an HTTP request to discover the destination domain and determine if the request needs to be decrypted. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request over TLS from a client to an unknown or controlled URL. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to bypass the decryption process of Cisco Umbrella SWG and allow malicious content to be downloaded to a host on a protected network. There are workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20805|2024-08-03T02:24:49.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1350|2024-08-03T16:11:16.712Z -- cisco -- cisco%20umbrella%20insights%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1350</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco Umbrella could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to negatively affect the performance of this service. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient rate limiting controls in the web UI. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTPS packets at a high and sustained rate. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to negatively affect the performance of the web UI. Cisco has addressed this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1350|2024-08-03T16:11:16.712Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20738|2024-08-03T02:24:49.429Z -- cisco -- cisco%20umbrella%20insights%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20738</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Umbrella Secure Web Gateway service could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the file inspection feature. This vulnerability is due to insufficient restrictions in the file inspection feature. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by downloading a crafted payload through specific methods. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass file inspection protections and download a malicious payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20738|2024-08-03T02:24:49.429Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1475|2024-08-03T16:11:17.380Z -- cisco -- cisco%20umbrella%20insights%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1475</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Admin audit log export feature and Scheduled Reports feature of Cisco Umbrella could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform formula and link injection attacks on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1475|2024-08-03T16:11:17.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1474|2024-08-03T16:11:17.469Z -- cisco -- cisco%20umbrella%20insights%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1474</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Admin audit log export feature and Scheduled Reports feature of Cisco Umbrella could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform formula and link injection attacks on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1474|2024-08-03T16:11:17.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20773|2024-08-03T02:24:49.537Z -- cisco -- cisco%20umbrella%20insights%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20773</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the key-based SSH authentication mechanism of Cisco Umbrella Virtual Appliance (VA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to impersonate a VA. This vulnerability is due to the presence of a static SSH host key. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by performing a man-in-the-middle attack on an SSH connection to the Umbrella VA. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to learn the administrator credentials, change configurations, or reload the VA. Note: SSH is not enabled by default on the Umbrella VA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20773|2024-08-03T02:24:49.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
