<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20telepresence%20video%20communication%20server%20%28vcs%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 05:23:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1872|2024-09-17T00:26:06.668Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20video%20communication%20server%20%28vcs%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1872</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) and Cisco Expressway Series software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected system to send arbitrary network requests. The vulnerability is due to improper restrictions on network services in the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests to the affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send arbitrary network requests sourced from the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1872|2024-09-17T00:26:06.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 16:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1720|2024-09-17T00:21:21.297Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20video%20communication%20server%20%28vcs%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1720</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the XML API of Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause the CPU to increase to 100% utilization, causing a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of the XML input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specifically crafted XML payload. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust CPU resources, resulting in a DoS condition until the system is manually rebooted. Software versions prior to X12.5.1 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1720|2024-09-17T00:21:21.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 00:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
