<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Wireless LAN Controller (WLC)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20wireless%20lan%20controller%20%28wlc%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Wireless LAN Controller (WLC)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 20:23:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15395|2024-09-17T04:19:31.335Z -- cisco -- cisco%20wireless%20lan%20controller%20%28wlc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15395</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the authentication and authorization checking mechanisms of Cisco Wireless LAN Controller (WLC) Software could allow an authenticated, adjacent attacker to gain network access to a Cisco TrustSec domain. Under normal circumstances, this access should be prohibited. The vulnerability is due to the dynamic assignment of Security Group Tags (SGTs) during a wireless roam from one Service Set Identifier (SSID) to another within the Cisco TrustSec domain. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to acquire an SGT from other SSIDs within the domain. Successful exploitation could allow the attacker to gain privileged network access that should be prohibited under normal circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15395|2024-09-17T04:19:31.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0416|2024-09-17T00:42:41.075Z -- cisco -- cisco%20wireless%20lan%20controller%20%28wlc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0416</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Wireless LAN Controller (WLC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to view system information that under normal circumstances should be prohibited. The vulnerability is due to incomplete input and validation checking mechanisms in the web-based interface URL request. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by requesting specific URLs via the web-based interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view sensitive system information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0416|2024-09-17T00:42:41.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1796|2024-09-17T00:21:34.281Z -- cisco -- cisco%20wireless%20lan%20controller%20%28wlc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1796</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the handling of Inter-Access Point Protocol (IAPP) messages by Cisco Wireless LAN Controller (WLC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability exist because the software improperly validates input on fields within IAPP messages. An attacker could exploit the vulnerability by sending malicious IAPP messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Cisco WLC Software to reload, resulting in a DoS condition. Software versions prior to 8.2.170.0, 8.5.150.0, and 8.8.100.0 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1796|2024-09-17T00:21:34.281Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 00:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0248|2024-09-17T01:21:35.660Z -- cisco -- cisco%20wireless%20lan%20controller%20%28wlc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0248</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the administrative GUI configuration feature of Cisco Wireless LAN Controller (WLC) Software could allow an aUTHENTICated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly during device configuration when the administrator is using this GUI, causing a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The attacker would need to have valid administrator credentials on the device. This vulnerability is due to incomplete input validation for unexpected configuration options that the attacker could submit while accessing the GUI configuration menus. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by authenticating to the device and submitting crafted user input when using the administrative GUI configuration feature. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition. Software versions prior to 8.3.150.0, 8.5.140.0, 8.8.111.0 are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0248|2024-09-17T01:21:35.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 21:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15262|2024-09-17T02:06:36.118Z -- cisco -- cisco%20wireless%20lan%20controller%20%28wlc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15262</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Shell (SSH) session management for Cisco Wireless LAN Controller (WLC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability exists because the SSH process is not properly deleted when an SSH connection to the device is disconnected. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by repeatedly opening SSH connections to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust system resources by initiating multiple SSH connections to the device that are not effectively terminated, which could result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15262|2024-09-17T02:06:36.118Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 18:36:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1797|2024-09-17T01:35:42.154Z -- cisco -- cisco%20wireless%20lan%20controller%20%28wlc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1797</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Wireless LAN Controller (WLC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on the device with the privileges of the user, including modifying the device configuration. The vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an interface user to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on the device with the privileges of the user. Software versions prior to 8.3.150.0, 8.5.135.0, and 8.8.100.0 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1797|2024-09-17T01:35:42.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 01:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
