<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 07:21:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1894|2024-09-17T01:06:46.541Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1894</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrator privileges to overwrite or read arbitrary files on the underlying operating system (OS) of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation in NFVIS filesystem commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using crafted variables during the execution of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite or read arbitrary files on the underlying OS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1894|2024-09-17T01:06:46.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 01:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20779|2024-09-17T04:24:40.073Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20779</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an attacker to escape from the guest virtual machine (VM) to the host machine, inject commands that execute at the root level, or leak system data from the host to the VM. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20779|2024-09-17T04:24:40.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 17:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15402|2024-09-17T03:33:11.771Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15402</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of Origin headers on HTTP requests within the management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by convincing a targeted user to follow a URL to a malicious website. An exploit could allow the attacker to take actions within the software with the privileges of the targeted user or gain access to sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15402|2024-09-17T03:33:11.771Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1960|2024-09-17T04:14:01.267Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1960</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to read arbitrary files on the underlying operating system (OS) of an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1960|2024-09-17T04:14:01.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 07:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1973|2024-09-17T03:43:25.389Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1973</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web portal framework of Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based interface. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation of log file content stored on the affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by modifying a log file with malicious code and getting a user to view the modified log file. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or to access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1973|2024-09-17T03:43:25.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 07:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1421|2024-09-17T02:41:17.565Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1421</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform a command injection attack on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input to a configuration command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input during the execution of this command. A successful exploit could allow a non-privileged attacker authenticated in the restricted CLI to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system (OS) with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1421|2024-09-17T02:41:17.565Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 12:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1656|2024-09-17T03:43:16.912Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1656</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access the shell of the underlying Linux operating system on the affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation in the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted commands to the affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to gain shell access with a nonroot user account to the underlying Linux operating system on the affected device and potentially access system configuration files with sensitive information. This vulnerability only affects console connections from CIMC. It does not apply to remote connections, such as telnet or SSH.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1656|2024-09-17T03:43:16.912Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0462|2024-09-17T01:20:57.734Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0462</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the user management functionality of Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a denial of service (DoS) attack against an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-provided input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in with a highly privileged user account and performing a sequence of specific user management operations that interfere with the underlying operating system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to permanently degrade the functionality of the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0462|2024-09-17T01:20:57.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3365|2024-09-17T00:41:21.182Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3365</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the directory permissions of Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a directory traversal attack on a limited set of restricted directories. The vulnerability is due to a flaw in the logic that governs directory permissions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using capabilities that are not controlled by the role-based access control (RBAC) mechanisms of the software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite files on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3365|2024-09-17T00:41:21.182Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 02:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1984|2024-09-17T00:16:10.804Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1984</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Enterprise Network Functions Virtualization Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrator privileges to overwrite files on the underlying operating system (OS) of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation in an NFVIS file-system command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using crafted variables during the execution of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite arbitrary files on the underlying OS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1984|2024-09-17T00:16:10.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 18:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1946|2024-09-17T01:16:07.848Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1946</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass authentication and get limited access to the web-based management interface. The vulnerability is due to an incorrect implementation of authentication in the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted authentication request to the web-based management interface on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view limited configuration details and potentially upload a virtual machine image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1946|2024-09-17T01:16:07.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 07:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0460|2024-09-17T00:17:34.215Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0460</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the REST API of Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to read any file on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization and parameter validation checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious API request with the authentication credentials of a low-privileged user. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read any file on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0460|2024-09-17T00:17:34.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
