<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 03:23:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34703|2024-08-04T00:19:48.150Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34703</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Link Layer Discovery Protocol (LLDP) message parser of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an attacker to trigger a reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper initialization of a buffer. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability via any of the following methods: An authenticated, remote attacker could access the LLDP neighbor table via either the CLI or SNMP while the device is in a specific state. An unauthenticated, adjacent attacker could corrupt the LLDP neighbor table by injecting specific LLDP frames into the network and then waiting for an administrator of the device or a network management system (NMS) managing the device to retrieve the LLDP neighbor table of the device via either the CLI or SNMP. An authenticated, adjacent attacker with SNMP read-only credentials or low privileges on the device CLI could corrupt the LLDP neighbor table by injecting specific LLDP frames into the network and then accessing the LLDP neighbor table via either the CLI or SNMP. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash, resulting in a reload of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34703|2024-08-04T00:19:48.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34699|2024-08-04T00:19:48.092Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34699</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TrustSec CLI parser of Cisco IOS and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload. This vulnerability is due to an improper interaction between the web UI and the CLI parser. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by requesting a particular CLI command to be run through the web UI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34699|2024-08-04T00:19:48.092Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34714|2024-08-04T00:19:48.217Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34714</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Unidirectional Link Detection (UDLD) feature of Cisco FXOS Software, Cisco IOS Software, Cisco IOS XE Software, Cisco IOS XR Software, and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload. This vulnerability is due to improper input validation of the UDLD packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specifically crafted UDLD packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. Note: The UDLD feature is disabled by default, and the conditions to exploit this vulnerability are strict. An attacker must have full control of a directly connected device. On Cisco IOS XR devices, the impact is limited to the reload of the UDLD process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34714|2024-08-04T00:19:48.217Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34705|2024-08-04T00:19:48.113Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34705</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Voice Telephony Service Provider (VTSP) service of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured destination patterns and dial arbitrary numbers. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of dial strings at Foreign Exchange Office (FXO) interfaces. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed dial string to an affected device via either the ISDN protocol or SIP. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct toll fraud, resulting in unexpected financial impact to affected customers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34705|2024-08-04T00:19:48.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
