<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System (Management Software)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28management%20software%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System (Management Software)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 05:23:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3241|2024-09-17T02:36:48.842Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28management%20software%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3241</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the orchestration tasks of Cisco UCS Director could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a path traversal attack on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input on the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by creating a task with specific configuration parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite arbitrary files in the file system of an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3241|2024-09-17T02:36:48.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 02:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1871|2024-09-17T03:07:17.065Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28management%20software%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1871</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Import Cisco IMC configuration utility of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition and implement arbitrary commands with root privileges on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper bounds checking by the import-config process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious packets to an affected device. When the packets are processed, an exploitable buffer overflow condition may occur. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to implement arbitrary code on the affected device with elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1871|2024-09-17T03:07:17.065Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 18:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1900|2024-09-17T00:05:48.946Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28management%20software%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1900</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web server of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the web server process to crash, causing a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input on the web interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted HTTP request to certain endpoints of the affected software. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to cause the web server to crash. Physical access to the device may be required for a restart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1900|2024-09-17T00:05:48.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 18:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1628|2024-09-17T02:27:52.020Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28management%20software%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1628</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web server of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause a buffer overflow, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to incorrect bounds checking. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the affected system. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause a buffer overflow, resulting in a process crash and DoS condition on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1628|2024-09-17T02:27:52.020Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 02:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1630|2024-09-17T01:05:44.786Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28management%20software%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1630</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the firmware signature checking program of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause a buffer overflow, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to insufficient checking of an input buffer. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by passing a crafted file to the affected system. A successful exploit could inhibit an administrator's ability to access the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1630|2024-09-17T01:05:44.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 02:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
