<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 13:22:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20949|2024-08-03T02:31:59.814Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20949</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the management web server of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with high privileges to execute configuration commands on an affected system.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability exists because access to HTTPS endpoints is not properly restricted on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific messages to the affected HTTPS handler. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform configuration changes on the affected system, which should be configured and managed only through Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20949|2024-08-03T02:31:59.814Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20730|2024-08-03T02:24:49.664Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20730</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Security Intelligence feed feature of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the Security Intelligence DNS feed. This vulnerability is due to incorrect feed update processing. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through an affected device that should be blocked by the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass device controls and successfully send traffic to devices that are expected to be protected by the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20730|2024-08-03T02:24:49.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20940|2024-08-03T02:31:58.809Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20940</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TLS handler of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain access to sensitive information.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper implementation of countermeasures against a Bleichenbacher attack on a device that uses SSL decryption policies. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted TLS messages to an affected device, which would act as an oracle and allow the attacker to carry out a chosen-ciphertext attack. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform cryptanalytic operations that may allow decryption of previously captured TLS sessions to the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20940|2024-08-03T02:31:58.809Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20767|2024-08-03T02:24:49.559Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20767</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Snort rule evaluation function of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of the DNS reputation enforcement rule. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted UDP packets through an affected device to force a buildup of UDP connections. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause traffic that is going through the affected device to be dropped, resulting in a DoS condition. Note: This vulnerability only affects Cisco FTD devices that are running Snort 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20767|2024-08-03T02:24:49.559Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20748|2024-08-03T02:24:49.598Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20748</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the local malware analysis process of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient error handling in the local malware analysis process of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted file through the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the local malware analysis process to crash, which could result in a DoS condition. Notes: Manual intervention may be required to recover from this situation. Malware cloud lookup and dynamic analysis will not be impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20748|2024-08-03T02:24:49.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20751|2024-08-03T02:24:49.350Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20751</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Snort detection engine integration for Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause unlimited memory consumption, which could lead to a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient memory management for certain Snort events. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of crafted IP packets that would generate specific Snort events on an affected device. A sustained attack could cause an out of memory condition on the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to interrupt all traffic flowing through the affected device. In some circumstances, the attacker may be able to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20751|2024-08-03T02:24:49.350Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20746|2024-08-03T02:24:49.409Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20746</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TCP proxy functionality of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper handling of TCP flows. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted stream of TCP traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20746|2024-08-03T02:24:49.409Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20757|2024-08-03T02:24:49.534Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20757</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the connection handling function in Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper traffic handling when platform limits are reached. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high rate of UDP traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause all new, incoming connections to be dropped, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20757|2024-08-03T02:24:49.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20950|2024-08-03T02:31:58.477Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20950</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the interaction of SIP and Snort 3 for Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the Snort 3 detection engine to restart.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a lack of error-checking when SIP bidirectional flows are being inspected by Snort 3. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a stream of crafted SIP traffic through an interface on the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to trigger a restart of the Snort 3 process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20950|2024-08-03T02:31:58.477Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20934|2024-08-03T02:31:57.971Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20934</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software and Cisco FXOS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system as root.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation for specific CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting operating system commands into a legitimate command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to escape the restricted command prompt and execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20934|2024-08-03T02:31:57.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20729|2024-08-03T02:24:49.226Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20729</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in CLI of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject XML into the command parser. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input in commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to inject XML into the command parser, which could result in unexpected processing of the command and unexpected command output.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20729|2024-08-03T02:24:49.226Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20946|2024-08-03T02:31:58.684Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20946</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the generic routing encapsulation (GRE) tunnel decapsulation feature of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a memory handling error that occurs when GRE traffic is processed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted GRE payload through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to restart, resulting in a DoS condition.&#13;
&#13;    &#13;
&#13;  https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ftd-gre-dos-hmedHQPM ["https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ftd-gre-dos-hmedHQPM"]&#13;
&#13; &#13; This advisory is part of the November 2022 release of the Cisco ASA, FTD, and FMC Security Advisory Bundled publication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20946|2024-08-03T02:31:58.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20943|2024-08-03T02:31:57.976Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20943</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Server Message Block Version 2 (SMB2) processor of the Snort detection engine on multiple Cisco products could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured policies or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; These vulnerabilities are due to improper management of system resources when the Snort detection engine is processing SMB2 traffic. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a high rate of certain types of SMB2 packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to trigger a reload of the Snort process, resulting in a DoS condition.&#13;
&#13; Note: When the snort preserve-connection option is enabled for the Snort detection engine, a successful exploit could also allow the attacker to bypass the configured policies and deliver a malicious payload to the protected network. The snort preserve-connection setting is enabled by default. See the Details ["#details"] section of this advisory for more information.&#13;
&#13; Note: Only products that have Snort 3 configured are affected. Products that are configured with Snort 2 are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20943|2024-08-03T02:31:57.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20922|2024-08-03T02:31:57.388Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20922</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Server Message Block Version 2 (SMB2) processor of the Snort detection engine on multiple Cisco products could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured policies or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; These vulnerabilities are due to improper management of system resources when the Snort detection engine is processing SMB2 traffic. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a high rate of certain types of SMB2 packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to trigger a reload of the Snort process, resulting in a DoS condition.&#13;
&#13; Note: When the snort preserve-connection option is enabled for the Snort detection engine, a successful exploit could also allow the attacker to bypass the configured policies and deliver a malicious payload to the protected network. The snort preserve-connection setting is enabled by default. See the Details ["#details"] section of this advisory for more information.&#13;
&#13; Note: Only products that have Snort 3 configured are affected. Products that are configured with Snort 2 are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20922|2024-08-03T02:31:57.388Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20363|2024-08-01T21:59:42.321Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20363</link>
      <description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort Intrusion Prevention System (IPS) rule engine that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured rules on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to incorrect HTTP packet handling. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured IPS rules and allow uninspected traffic onto the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20363|2024-08-01T21:59:42.321Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20261|2024-08-01T21:52:31.751Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20261</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the file policy feature that is used to inspect encrypted archive files of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured file policy to block an encrypted archive file. This vulnerability exists because of a logic error when a specific class of encrypted archive files is inspected. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted, encrypted archive file through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send an encrypted archive file, which could contain malware and should have been blocked and dropped at the Cisco FTD device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20261|2024-08-01T21:52:31.751Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20261|2024-05-22T16:53:27.346Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20261</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the file policy feature that is used to inspect encrypted archive files of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured file policy to block an encrypted archive file. This vulnerability exists because of a logic error when a specific class of encrypted archive files is inspected. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted, encrypted archive file through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send an encrypted archive file, which could contain malware and should have been blocked and dropped at the Cisco FTD device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20261|2024-05-22T16:53:27.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20363|2024-06-04T17:40:03.436Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20363</link>
      <description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort Intrusion Prevention System (IPS) rule engine that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured rules on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to incorrect HTTP packet handling. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured IPS rules and allow uninspected traffic onto the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20363|2024-06-04T17:40:03.436Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20261|2024-07-02T16:00:57.104Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20261</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the file policy feature that is used to inspect encrypted archive files of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured file policy to block an encrypted archive file. This vulnerability exists because of a logic error when a specific class of encrypted archive files is inspected. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted, encrypted archive file through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send an encrypted archive file, which could contain malware and should have been blocked and dropped at the Cisco FTD device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20261|2024-07-02T16:00:57.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
