<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Secure Endpoint</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20secure%20endpoint.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Secure Endpoint</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:26:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20212|2024-08-02T09:05:35.369Z -- cisco -- cisco%20secure%20endpoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20212</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the AutoIt module of ClamAV could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. &#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a logic error in the memory management of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted AutoIt file to be scanned by ClamAV on the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ClamAV scanning process to restart unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20212|2024-08-02T09:05:35.369Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 19:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20052|2024-08-02T08:57:35.615Z -- cisco -- cisco%20secure%20endpoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20052</link>
      <description>On Feb 15, 2023, the following vulnerability in the ClamAV scanning library was disclosed:&#13;
&#13; &#13; A vulnerability in the DMG file parser of ClamAV versions 1.0.0 and earlier, 0.105.1 and earlier, and 0.103.7 and earlier could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive information on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; &#13; This vulnerability is due to enabling XML entity substitution that may result in XML external entity injection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted DMG file to be scanned by ClamAV on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to leak bytes from any file that may be read by the ClamAV scanning process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20052|2024-08-02T08:57:35.615Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 15:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20084|2024-08-02T08:57:35.892Z -- cisco -- cisco%20secure%20endpoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20084</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the endpoint software of Cisco Secure Endpoint for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to evade endpoint protection within a limited time window. This vulnerability is due to a timing issue that occurs between various software components. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to put a malicious file into a specific folder and then persuading the user to execute the file within a limited time window. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the endpoint software to fail to quarantine the malicious file or kill its process. Note: This vulnerability only applies to deployments that have the Windows Folder Redirection feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20084|2024-08-02T08:57:35.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20197|2024-08-02T09:05:35.440Z -- cisco -- cisco%20secure%20endpoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20197</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the filesystem image parser for Hierarchical File System Plus (HFS+) of ClamAV could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an incorrect check for completion when a file is decompressed, which may result in a loop condition that could cause the affected software to stop responding. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted HFS+ filesystem image to be scanned by ClamAV on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ClamAV scanning process to stop responding, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected software and consuming available system resources.&#13;
&#13; For a description of this vulnerability, see the ClamAV blog .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20197|2024-08-02T09:05:35.440Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:43:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20290|2024-08-01T21:59:41.158Z -- cisco -- cisco%20secure%20endpoint</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20290</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OLE2 file format parser of ClamAV could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an incorrect check for end-of-string values during scanning, which may result in a heap buffer over-read. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted file containing OLE2 content to be scanned by ClamAV on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ClamAV scanning process to terminate, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected software and consuming available system resources.
&#13; For a description of this vulnerability, see the ClamAV blog .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20290|2024-08-01T21:59:41.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20290|2024-02-07T16:16:00.975Z -- cisco -- cisco%20secure%20endpoint</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20290</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OLE2 file format parser of ClamAV could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an incorrect check for end-of-string values during scanning, which may result in a heap buffer over-read. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted file containing OLE2 content to be scanned by ClamAV on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ClamAV scanning process to terminate, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected software and consuming available system resources.
&#13; For a description of this vulnerability, see the ClamAV blog .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20290|2024-02-07T16:16:00.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
