<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:21:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34787|2024-09-16T22:29:59.820Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34787</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the identity-based firewall (IDFW) rule processing feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass security protections. This vulnerability is due to improper handling of network requests by affected devices configured to use object group search. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted network request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass access control list (ACL) rules on the device, bypass security protections, and send network traffic to unauthorized hosts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34787|2024-09-16T22:29:59.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3458|2024-09-16T22:10:30.176Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3458</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the secure boot process of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software for the Firepower 1000 Series and Firepower 2100 Series Appliances could allow an authenticated, local attacker to bypass the secure boot mechanism. The vulnerabilities are due to insufficient protections of the secure boot process. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by injecting code into specific files that are then referenced during the device boot process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to break the chain of trust and inject code into the boot process of the device, which would be executed at each boot and maintain persistence across reboots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3458|2024-09-16T22:10:30.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:36:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34794|2024-09-16T22:19:59.502Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34794</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Simple Network Management Protocol version 3 (SNMPv3) access control functionality of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to query SNMP data. This vulnerability is due to ineffective access control. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending an SNMPv3 query to an affected device from a host that is not permitted by the SNMPv3 access control list. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send an SNMP query to an affected device and retrieve information from the device. The attacker would need valid credentials to perform the SNMP query.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34794|2024-09-16T22:19:59.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40118|2024-09-16T16:23:52.807Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40118</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web services interface of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper input validation when parsing HTTPS requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious HTTPS request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40118|2024-09-16T16:23:52.807Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20713|2024-09-16T20:53:04.405Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20713</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the VPN web client services component of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct browser-based attacks against users of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of input that is passed to the VPN web client services component before being returned to the browser that is in use. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to visit a website that is designed to pass malicious requests to a device that is running Cisco ASA Software or Cisco FTD Software and has web services endpoints supporting VPN features enabled. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to reflect malicious input from the affected device to the browser that is in use and conduct browser-based attacks, including cross-site scripting attacks. The attacker could not directly impact the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20713|2024-09-16T20:53:04.405Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 16:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1715|2024-09-16T18:29:41.812Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1715</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Deterministic Random Bit Generator (DRBG), also known as Pseudorandom Number Generator (PRNG), used in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a cryptographic collision, enabling the attacker to discover the private key of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient entropy in the DRBG when generating cryptographic keys. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by generating a large number of cryptographic keys on an affected device and looking for collisions with target devices. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to impersonate an affected target device or to decrypt traffic secured by an affected key that is sent to or from an affected target device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1715|2024-09-16T18:29:41.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 16:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20715|2024-09-16T17:19:10.789Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20715</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the remote access SSL VPN features of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of errors that are logged as a result of client connections that are made using remote access VPN. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted requests to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to restart, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20715|2024-09-16T17:19:10.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 03:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3373|2024-09-16T22:56:22.438Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3373</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IP fragment-handling implementation of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a memory leak on an affected device. This memory leak could prevent traffic from being processed through the device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to improper error handling when specific failures occur during IP fragment reassembly. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted, fragmented IP traffic to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to continuously consume memory on the affected device and eventually impact traffic, resulting in a DoS condition. The device could require a manual reboot to recover from the DoS condition. Note: This vulnerability applies to both IP Version 4 (IPv4) and IP Version 6 (IPv6) traffic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3373|2024-09-16T22:56:22.438Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1701|2024-09-16T17:24:04.174Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1701</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the WebVPN service of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the WebVPN portal of an affected device. The vulnerabilities exist because the software insufficiently validates user-supplied input on an affected device. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information. An attacker would need administrator privileges on the device to exploit these vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1701|2024-09-16T17:24:04.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 16:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1445|2024-09-16T22:50:55.250Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1445</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to lack of proper input validation of the HTTPS request. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a crafted HTTPS request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition. Note: This vulnerability affects only specific AnyConnect and WebVPN configurations. For more information, see the Vulnerable Products section.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1445|2024-09-16T22:50:55.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40117|2024-09-16T22:09:13.658Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40117</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in SSL/TLS message handler for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability exists because incoming SSL/TLS packets are not properly processed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SSL/TLS packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40117|2024-09-16T22:09:13.658Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1706|2024-09-16T18:44:06.077Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1706</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the software cryptography module of the Cisco Adaptive Security Virtual Appliance (ASAv) and Firepower 2100 Series running Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an unexpected reload of the device that results in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to a logic error with how the software cryptography module handles IPsec sessions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by creating and sending traffic in a high number of IPsec sessions through the targeted device. A successful exploit could cause the device to reload and result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1706|2024-09-16T18:44:06.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 16:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12678|2024-09-16T16:43:59.998Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12678</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) inspection module of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper parsing of SIP messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious SIP packet through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to trigger an integer underflow, causing the software to try to read unmapped memory and resulting in a crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12678|2024-09-16T16:43:59.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3191|2024-09-16T22:46:51.881Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3191</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in DNS over IPv6 packet processing for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to unexpectedly reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to improper length validation of a field in an IPv6 DNS packet. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DNS query over IPv6, which traverses the affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition. This vulnerability is specific to DNS over IPv6 traffic only.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3191|2024-09-16T22:46:51.881Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3581|2024-09-16T16:33:34.150Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3581</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web services interface of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks against a user of the web services interface of an affected device. The vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web services interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or allow the attacker to access sensitive, browser-based information. Note: These vulnerabilities affect only specific AnyConnect and WebVPN configurations. For more information, see the Vulnerable Products section.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3581|2024-09-16T16:33:34.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12693|2024-09-16T17:58:11.343Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12693</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Copy (SCP) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to the use of an incorrect data type for a length variable. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by initiating the transfer of a large file to an affected device via SCP. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have valid privilege level 15 credentials on the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the length variable to roll over, which could cause the affected device to crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12693|2024-09-16T17:58:11.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15992|2024-09-16T18:23:53.279Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15992</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the Lua interpreter integrated in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the underlying Linux operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient restrictions on the allowed Lua function calls within the context of user-supplied Lua scripts. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to trigger a heap overflow condition and execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the underlying Linux operating system of an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15992|2024-09-16T18:23:53.279Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1697|2024-09-16T20:07:32.096Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1697</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the Lightweight Directory Access Protocol (LDAP) feature in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerabilities are due to the improper parsing of LDAP packets sent to an affected device. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a crafted LDAP packet, using Basic Encoding Rules (BER), to be processed by an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1697|2024-09-16T20:07:32.096Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 15:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1493|2024-09-16T20:16:19.436Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1493</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web services interface of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a buffer overflow on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient boundary checks for specific data that is provided to the web services interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious HTTP request. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a buffer overflow condition on the affected system, which could disclose data fragments or cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1493|2024-09-16T20:16:19.436Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3561|2024-09-16T22:08:42.622Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3561</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Clientless SSL VPN (WebVPN) of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary HTTP headers in the responses of the affected system. The vulnerability is due to improper input sanitization. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct a CRLF injection attack, adding arbitrary HTTP headers in the responses of the system and redirecting the user to arbitrary websites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3561|2024-09-16T22:08:42.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1488|2024-09-16T18:49:23.475Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1488</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the upgrade process of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject commands that could be executed with root privileges on the underlying operating system (OS). This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a crafted upgrade package file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to inject commands that could be executed with root privileges on the underlying OS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1488|2024-09-16T18:49:23.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0472|2024-09-16T22:14:20.366Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0472</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPsec driver code of multiple Cisco IOS XE Software platforms and the Cisco ASA 5500-X Series Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload. The vulnerability is due to improper processing of malformed IPsec Authentication Header (AH) or Encapsulating Security Payload (ESP) packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malformed IPsec packets to be processed by an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause a reload of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0472|2024-09-16T22:14:20.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1705|2024-09-16T18:04:03.862Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1705</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the remote access VPN session manager of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow a unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the remote access VPN services. The vulnerability is due to an issue with the remote access VPN session manager. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by requesting an excessive number of remote access VPN sessions. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1705|2024-09-16T18:04:03.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 16:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3171|2024-09-16T18:50:17.190Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3171</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the local management (local-mgmt) CLI of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco UCS Manager Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system (OS) of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted arguments to specific commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying OS with the privileges of the currently logged-in user for all affected platforms excluding Cisco UCS 6400 Series Fabric Interconnects. On Cisco UCS 6400 Series Fabric Interconnects, the injected commands are executed with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3171|2024-09-16T18:50:17.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 16:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3254|2024-09-16T20:52:13.128Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3254</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP) inspection feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerabilities are due to inefficient memory management. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted MGCP packets through an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause memory exhaustion resulting in a restart of an affected device, causing a DoS condition for traffic traversing the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3254|2024-09-16T20:52:13.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15256|2024-09-16T20:07:24.339Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15256</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Internet Key Exchange version 1 (IKEv1) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to improper management of system memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious IKEv1 traffic to an affected device. The attacker does not need valid credentials to authenticate the VPN session, nor does the attacker's source address need to match a peer statement in the crypto map applied to the ingress interface of the affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust system memory resources, leading to a reload of an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15256|2024-09-16T20:07:24.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34781|2024-09-16T17:59:16.971Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34781</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the processing of SSH connections for multi-instance deployments of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the affected device. This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper error handling when an SSH session fails to be established. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high rate of crafted SSH connections to the instance. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause resource exhaustion, which causes a DoS condition on the affected device. The device must be manually reloaded to recover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34781|2024-09-16T17:59:16.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3554|2024-09-16T17:18:45.001Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3554</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TCP packet processing of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a memory exhaustion condition. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high rate of crafted TCP traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust device resources, resulting in a DoS condition for traffic transiting the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3554|2024-09-16T17:18:45.001Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3125|2024-09-16T19:56:18.820Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3125</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Kerberos authentication feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to impersonate the Kerberos key distribution center (KDC) and bypass authentication on an affected device that is configured to perform Kerberos authentication for VPN or local device access. The vulnerability is due to insufficient identity verification of the KDC when a successful authentication response is received. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by spoofing the KDC server response to the ASA device. This malicious response would not have been authenticated by the KDC. A successful attack could allow an attacker to bypass Kerberos authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3125|2024-09-16T19:56:18.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3298|2024-09-16T17:43:19.611Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3298</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Open Shortest Path First (OSPF) implementation of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to improper memory protection mechanisms while processing certain OSPF packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of malformed OSPF packets in a short period of time to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a reload of the affected device, resulting in a DoS condition for client traffic that is traversing the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3298|2024-09-16T17:43:19.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1695|2024-09-16T16:29:03.320Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1695</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the detection engine of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to send data directly to the kernel of an affected device. The vulnerability exists because the software improperly filters Ethernet frames sent to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted packets to the management interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the Layer 2 (L2) filters and send data directly to the kernel of the affected device. A malicious frame successfully delivered would make the target device generate a specific syslog entry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1695|2024-09-16T16:29:03.320Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 15:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12677|2024-09-16T20:12:03.828Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12677</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition that prevents the creation of new SSL/Transport Layer Security (TLS) connections to an affected device. The vulnerability is due to incorrect handling of Base64-encoded strings. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by opening many SSL VPN sessions to an affected device. The attacker would need to have valid user credentials on the affected device to exploit this vulnerability. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite a special system memory location, which will eventually result in memory allocation errors for new SSL/TLS sessions to the device, preventing successful establishment of these sessions. A reload of the device is required to recover from this condition. Established SSL/TLS connections to the device and SSL/TLS connections through the device are not affected. Note: Although this vulnerability is in the SSL VPN feature, successful exploitation of this vulnerability would affect all new SSL/TLS sessions to the device, including management sessions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12677|2024-09-16T20:12:03.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3583|2024-09-16T18:39:54.024Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3583</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web services interface of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks against a user of the web services interface of an affected device. The vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web services interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or allow the attacker to access sensitive, browser-based information. Note: These vulnerabilities affect only specific AnyConnect and WebVPN configurations. For more information, see the Vulnerable Products section.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3583|2024-09-16T18:39:54.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1422|2024-09-16T20:06:28.952Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1422</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the software cryptography module of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker or an unauthenticated attacker in a man-in-the-middle position to cause an unexpected reload of the device that results in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to a logic error in how the software cryptography module handles specific types of decryption errors. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious packets over an established IPsec connection. A successful exploit could cause the device to crash, forcing it to reload. Important: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability would not cause a compromise of any encrypted data. Note: This vulnerability affects only Cisco ASA Software Release 9.16.1 and Cisco FTD Software Release 7.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1422|2024-09-16T20:06:28.952Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 12:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15388|2024-09-16T17:08:28.641Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15388</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the WebVPN login process of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause increased CPU utilization on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to excessive processing load for existing WebVPN login operations. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending multiple WebVPN login requests to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to increase CPU load on the device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15388|2024-09-16T17:08:28.641Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 14:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12673|2024-09-16T22:36:41.821Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12673</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the FTP inspection engine of Cisco Adaptive Security (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of FTP data. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious FTP traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12673|2024-09-16T22:36:41.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20866|2024-09-16T22:50:25.000Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20866</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the handling of RSA keys on devices running Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to retrieve an RSA private key. This vulnerability is due to a logic error when the RSA key is stored in memory on a hardware platform that performs hardware-based cryptography. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using a Lenstra side-channel attack against the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve the RSA private key. The following conditions may be observed on an affected device: This vulnerability will apply to approximately 5 percent of the RSA keys on a device that is running a vulnerable release of Cisco ASA Software or Cisco FTD Software; not all RSA keys are expected to be affected due to mathematical calculations applied to the RSA key. The RSA key could be valid but have specific characteristics that make it vulnerable to the potential leak of the RSA private key. If an attacker obtains the RSA private key, they could use the key to impersonate a device that is running Cisco ASA Software or Cisco FTD Software or to decrypt the device traffic. See the Indicators of Compromise section for more information on the detection of this type of RSA key. The RSA key could be malformed and invalid. A malformed RSA key is not functional, and a TLS client connection to a device that is running Cisco ASA Software or Cisco FTD Software that uses the malformed RSA key will result in a TLS signature failure, which means a vulnerable software release created an invalid RSA signature that failed verification. If an attacker obtains the RSA private key, they could use the key to impersonate a device that is running Cisco ASA Software or Cisco FTD Software or to decrypt the device traffic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20866|2024-09-16T22:50:25.000Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 16:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1501|2024-09-16T17:08:30.210Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1501</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SIP inspection engine of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a crash and reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.The vulnerability is due to a crash that occurs during a hash lookup for a SIP pinhole connection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted SIP traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a crash and reload of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1501|2024-09-16T17:08:30.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20795|2024-09-16T20:03:00.504Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20795</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the Datagram TLS (DTLS) protocol in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to suboptimal processing that occurs when establishing a DTLS tunnel as part of an AnyConnect SSL VPN connection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a steady stream of crafted DTLS traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust resources on the affected VPN headend device. This could cause existing DTLS tunnels to stop passing traffic and prevent new DTLS tunnels from establishing, resulting in a DoS condition. Note: When the attack traffic stops, the device recovers gracefully.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20795|2024-09-16T20:03:00.504Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 18:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3196|2024-09-16T18:14:40.527Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3196</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL)/Transport Layer Security (TLS) handler of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to exhaust memory resources on the affected device, leading to a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to improper resource management for inbound SSL/TLS connections. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing multiple SSL/TLS connections with specific conditions to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust the memory on the affected device, causing the device to stop accepting new SSL/TLS connections and resulting in a DoS condition for services on the device that process SSL/TLS traffic. Manual intervention is required to recover an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3196|2024-09-16T18:14:40.527Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20358|2024-08-15T16:32:41.453Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20358</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) restore functionality that is available in Cisco ASA Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because the contents of a backup file are improperly sanitized at restore time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20358|2024-08-15T16:32:41.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20443|2024-08-07T18:13:18.759Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20443</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have at least a low-privileged account on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20443|2024-08-07T18:13:18.759Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20353|2024-08-01T21:59:41.487Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20353</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the management and VPN web servers for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incomplete error checking when parsing an HTTP header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to a targeted web server on a device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition when the device reloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20353|2024-08-01T21:59:41.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20358|2024-08-01T21:59:42.299Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20358</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) restore functionality that is available in Cisco ASA Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because the contents of a backup file are improperly sanitized at restore time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20358|2024-08-01T21:59:42.299Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20293|2024-08-01T21:59:41.290Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the activation of an access control list (ACL) on Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the protection that is offered by a configured ACL on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an ACL changes from inactive to active in the running configuration of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device that should be denied by the configured ACL. The reverse condition is also truetraffic that should be permitted could be denied by the configured ACL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL protections on the affected device, allowing the attacker to access trusted networks that the device might be protecting. Note: This vulnerability applies to both IPv4 and IPv6 traffic as well as dual-stack ACL configurations in which both IPv4 and IPv6 ACLs are configured on an interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20293|2024-08-01T21:59:41.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20359|2024-08-01T21:59:42.379Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20359</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a legacy capability that allowed for the preloading of VPN clients and plug-ins and that has been available in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of a file when it is read from system flash memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by copying a crafted file to the disk0: file system of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected device after the next reload of the device, which could alter system behavior. Because the injected code could persist across device reboots, Cisco has raised the Security Impact Rating (SIR) of this advisory from Medium to High.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20359|2024-08-01T21:59:42.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20355|2024-08-01T21:59:42.284Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20355</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of SAML 2.0 single sign-on (SSO) for remote access VPN services in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to successfully establish a VPN session on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper separation of authorization domains when using SAML authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using valid credentials to successfully authenticate using their designated connection profile (tunnel group), intercepting the SAML SSO token that is sent back from the Cisco ASA device, and then submitting the same SAML SSO token to a different tunnel group for authentication. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to establish a remote access VPN session using a connection profile that they are not authorized to use and connect to secured networks behind the affected device that they are not authorized to access. For successful exploitation, the attacker must have valid remote access VPN user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20355|2024-08-01T21:59:42.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20353|2024-06-04T17:40:15.708Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20353</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the management and VPN web servers for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incomplete error checking when parsing an HTTP header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to a targeted web server on a device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition when the device reloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20353|2024-06-04T17:40:15.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20359|2024-06-04T17:40:02.581Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20359</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a legacy capability that allowed for the preloading of VPN clients and plug-ins and that has been available in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of a file when it is read from system flash memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by copying a crafted file to the disk0: file system of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected device after the next reload of the device, which could alter system behavior. Because the injected code could persist across device reboots, Cisco has raised the Security Impact Rating (SIR) of this advisory from Medium to High.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20359|2024-06-04T17:40:02.581Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20355|2024-06-04T17:39:58.380Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20355</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of SAML 2.0 single sign-on (SSO) for remote access VPN services in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to successfully establish a VPN session on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper separation of authorization domains when using SAML authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using valid credentials to successfully authenticate using their designated connection profile (tunnel group), intercepting the SAML SSO token that is sent back from the Cisco ASA device, and then submitting the same SAML SSO token to a different tunnel group for authentication. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to establish a remote access VPN session using a connection profile that they are not authorized to use and connect to secured networks behind the affected device that they are not authorized to access. For successful exploitation, the attacker must have valid remote access VPN user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20355|2024-06-04T17:39:58.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20293|2024-06-04T17:39:54.684Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the activation of an access control list (ACL) on Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the protection that is offered by a configured ACL on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an ACL changes from inactive to active in the running configuration of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device that should be denied by the configured ACL. The reverse condition is also truetraffic that should be permitted could be denied by the configured ACL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL protections on the affected device, allowing the attacker to access trusted networks that the device might be protecting. Note: This vulnerability applies to both IPv4 and IPv6 traffic as well as dual-stack ACL configurations in which both IPv4 and IPv6 ACLs are configured on an interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20293|2024-06-04T17:39:54.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20358|2024-04-24T19:38:23.689Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20358</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) restore functionality that is available in Cisco ASA Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because the contents of a backup file are improperly sanitized at restore time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20358|2024-04-24T19:38:23.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20293|2024-07-02T15:36:56.903Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the activation of an access control list (ACL) on Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the protection that is offered by a configured ACL on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an ACL changes from inactive to active in the running configuration of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device that should be denied by the configured ACL. The reverse condition is also truetraffic that should be permitted could be denied by the configured ACL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL protections on the affected device, allowing the attacker to access trusted networks that the device might be protecting. Note: This vulnerability applies to both IPv4 and IPv6 traffic as well as dual-stack ACL configurations in which both IPv4 and IPv6 ACLs are configured on an interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20293|2024-07-02T15:36:56.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20443|2024-08-07T16:42:05.023Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20443</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have at least a low-privileged account on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20443|2024-08-07T16:42:05.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20443|2024-08-08T03:55:30.688Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20443</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have at least a low-privileged account on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20443|2024-08-08T03:55:30.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20358|2024-08-20T03:55:11.390Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20358</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) restore functionality that is available in Cisco ASA Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because the contents of a backup file are improperly sanitized at restore time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20358|2024-08-20T03:55:11.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
