<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN vManage</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN vManage</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 03:23:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34700|2024-08-04T00:19:48.141Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34700</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to read arbitrary files on the underlying file system of an affected system. This vulnerability exists because access to sensitive information on an affected system is not sufficiently controlled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by gaining unauthorized access to sensitive information on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to create forged authentication requests and gain unauthorized access to the web UI of an affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34700|2024-08-04T00:19:48.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34712|2024-08-04T00:19:48.126Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34712</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct cypher query language injection attacks on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to the interface of an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34712|2024-08-04T00:19:48.126Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
