<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 03:24:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3283|2024-09-17T00:15:31.724Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3283</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL)/Transport Layer Security (TLS) handler of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software when running on the Cisco Firepower 1000 Series platform could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a communication error between internal functions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SSL/TLS message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a buffer underrun, which leads to a crash. The crash causes the affected device to reload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3283|2024-09-17T00:15:31.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:41:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1980|2024-09-17T02:22:04.595Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1980</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the protocol detection component of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software, Cisco FirePOWER Services Software for ASA, and Cisco Firepower Management Center Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass filtering protections. The vulnerability is due to improper detection of the initial use of a protocol on a nonstandard port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic on a nonstandard port for the protocol in use through an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to bypass filtering and deliver malicious requests to protected systems that would otherwise be blocked. Once the initial protocol flow on the nonstandard port is detected, future flows on the nonstandard port will be successfully detected and handled as configured by the applied policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1980|2024-09-17T02:22:04.595Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 19:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34761|2024-09-17T00:51:41.136Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34761</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to overwrite or append arbitrary data to system files using root-level privileges. The attacker must have administrative credentials on the device. This vulnerability is due to incomplete validation of user input for a specific CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device with administrative privileges and issuing a CLI command with crafted user parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite or append arbitrary data to system files using root-level privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34761|2024-09-17T00:51:41.136Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3189|2024-09-17T00:05:57.549Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3189</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the VPN System Logging functionality for Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a memory leak that can deplete system memory over time, which can cause unexpected system behaviors or device crashes. The vulnerability is due to the system memory not being properly freed for a VPN System Logging event generated when a VPN session is created or deleted. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by repeatedly creating or deleting a VPN tunnel connection, which could leak a small amount of system memory for each logging event. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause system memory depletion, which can lead to a systemwide denial of service (DoS) condition. The attacker does not have any control of whether VPN System Logging is configured or not on the device, but it is enabled by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3189|2024-09-17T00:05:57.549Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20730|2024-09-17T02:46:47.612Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20730</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Security Intelligence feed feature of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the Security Intelligence DNS feed. This vulnerability is due to incorrect feed update processing. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through an affected device that should be blocked by the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass device controls and successfully send traffic to devices that are expected to be protected by the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20730|2024-09-17T02:46:47.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15462|2024-09-17T00:25:42.559Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15462</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TCP ingress handler for the data interfaces that are configured with management access to Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an increase in CPU and memory usage, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to insufficient ingress TCP rate limiting for TCP ports 22 (SSH) and 443 (HTTPS). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted, steady stream of TCP traffic to port 22 or 443 on the data interfaces that are configured with management access to the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15462|2024-09-17T00:25:42.559Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 14:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1978|2024-09-17T02:27:45.503Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1978</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the stream reassembly component of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software, Cisco FirePOWER Services Software for ASA, and Cisco Firepower Management Center Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass filtering protections. The vulnerability is due to improper reassembly of traffic streams. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted streams through an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to bypass filtering and deliver malicious requests to protected systems that would otherwise be blocked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1978|2024-09-17T02:27:45.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 19:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1518|2024-09-17T00:51:17.336Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1518</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the REST API of Cisco Firepower Device Manager (FDM) On-Box Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient sanitization of user input on specific REST API commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the API subsystem of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid low-privileged user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1518|2024-09-17T00:51:17.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 15:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34756|2024-09-17T01:45:56.540Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34756</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34756|2024-09-17T01:45:56.540Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1691|2024-09-17T00:42:40.612Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1691</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the detection engine of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the unexpected restart of the SNORT detection engine, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to the incomplete error handling of the SSL or TLS packet header during the connection establishment. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SSL or TLS packet during the connection handshake. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the SNORT detection engine to unexpectedly restart, resulting in a partial DoS condition while the detection engine restarts. Versions prior to 6.2.3.4 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1691|2024-09-17T00:42:40.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20767|2024-09-17T00:31:36.536Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20767</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Snort rule evaluation function of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of the DNS reputation enforcement rule. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted UDP packets through an affected device to force a buildup of UDP connections. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause traffic that is going through the affected device to be dropped, resulting in a DoS condition. Note: This vulnerability only affects Cisco FTD devices that are running Snort 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20767|2024-09-17T00:31:36.536Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3352|2024-09-17T00:30:48.646Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3352</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access hidden commands. The vulnerability is due to the presence of undocumented configuration commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by performing specific steps that make the hidden commands accessible. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to make configuration changes to various sections of an affected device that should not be exposed to CLI access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3352|2024-09-17T00:30:48.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12694|2024-09-17T02:32:31.783Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12694</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the command line interface (CLI) of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrative privileges to execute commands on the underlying operating system with root privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by executing a specific CLI command that includes crafted arguments. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands on the underlying OS with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12694|2024-09-17T02:32:31.783Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3571|2024-09-17T00:15:48.431Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3571</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the ICMP ingress packet processing of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software for Cisco Firepower 4110 appliances could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to incomplete input validation upon receiving ICMP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high number of crafted ICMP or ICMPv6 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a memory exhaustion condition that may result in an unexpected reload. No manual intervention is needed to recover the device after the reload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3571|2024-09-17T00:15:48.431Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3309|2024-09-17T01:11:44.770Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Firepower Device Manager (FDM) On-Box software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to overwrite arbitrary files on the underlying operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a malicious file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite arbitrary files on as well as modify the underlying operating system of an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3309|2024-09-17T01:11:44.770Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1489|2024-09-17T00:52:25.818Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1489</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in filesystem usage management for Cisco Firepower Device Manager (FDM) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to exhaust filesystem resources, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to the insufficient management of available filesystem resources. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading files to the device and exhausting available filesystem resources. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause database errors and cause the device to become unresponsive to web-based management. Manual intervention is required to free filesystem resources and return the device to an operational state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1489|2024-09-17T00:52:25.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20751|2024-09-17T02:42:55.989Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20751</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Snort detection engine integration for Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause unlimited memory consumption, which could lead to a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient memory management for certain Snort events. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of crafted IP packets that would generate specific Snort events on an affected device. A sustained attack could cause an out of memory condition on the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to interrupt all traffic flowing through the affected device. In some circumstances, the attacker may be able to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20751|2024-09-17T02:42:55.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 03:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3317|2024-09-17T00:30:26.563Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3317</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the ssl_inspection component of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to crash Snort instances. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation in the ssl_inspection component. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed TLS packet through a Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA). A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash a Snort instance, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3317|2024-09-17T00:30:26.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3310|2024-09-17T02:53:20.113Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the XML parser code of Cisco Firepower Device Manager On-Box software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected system to become unstable or reload. The vulnerability is due to insufficient hardening of the XML parser configuration. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability in multiple ways using a malicious file: An attacker with administrative privileges could upload a malicious XML file on the system and cause the XML code to parse the malicious file. An attacker with Clientless Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) VPN access could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted XML file. A successful exploit would allow the attacker to crash the XML parser process, which could cause system instability, memory exhaustion, and in some cases lead to a reload of the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3310|2024-09-17T02:53:20.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1704|2024-09-17T00:21:47.422Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1704</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Server Message Block (SMB) Protocol preprocessor detection engine for Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent or remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1704|2024-09-17T00:21:47.422Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 16:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3563|2024-09-17T01:51:53.871Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3563</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the packet processing functionality of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to inefficient memory management. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of TCP packets to a specific port on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust system memory, which could cause the device to reload unexpectedly. No manual intervention is needed to recover the device after it has reloaded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3563|2024-09-17T01:51:53.871Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40116|2024-09-17T02:51:48.922Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40116</link>
      <description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in Snort rules that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.The vulnerability is due to improper handling of the Block with Reset or Interactive Block with Reset actions if a rule is configured without proper constraints. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IP packet to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause through traffic to be dropped. Note: Only products with Snort3 configured and either a rule with Block with Reset or Interactive Block with Reset actions configured are vulnerable. Products configured with Snort2 are not vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40116|2024-09-17T02:51:48.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20261|2024-07-02T16:00:57.104Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20261</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the file policy feature that is used to inspect encrypted archive files of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured file policy to block an encrypted archive file. This vulnerability exists because of a logic error when a specific class of encrypted archive files is inspected. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted, encrypted archive file through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send an encrypted archive file, which could contain malware and should have been blocked and dropped at the Cisco FTD device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20261|2024-07-02T16:00:57.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20363|2024-06-04T17:40:03.436Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20363</link>
      <description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort Intrusion Prevention System (IPS) rule engine that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured rules on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to incorrect HTTP packet handling. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured IPS rules and allow uninspected traffic onto the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20363|2024-06-04T17:40:03.436Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20261|2024-05-22T16:53:27.346Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20261</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the file policy feature that is used to inspect encrypted archive files of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured file policy to block an encrypted archive file. This vulnerability exists because of a logic error when a specific class of encrypted archive files is inspected. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted, encrypted archive file through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send an encrypted archive file, which could contain malware and should have been blocked and dropped at the Cisco FTD device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20261|2024-05-22T16:53:27.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20261|2024-08-01T21:52:31.751Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20261</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the file policy feature that is used to inspect encrypted archive files of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured file policy to block an encrypted archive file. This vulnerability exists because of a logic error when a specific class of encrypted archive files is inspected. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted, encrypted archive file through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send an encrypted archive file, which could contain malware and should have been blocked and dropped at the Cisco FTD device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20261|2024-08-01T21:52:31.751Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20363|2024-08-01T21:59:42.321Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20363</link>
      <description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort Intrusion Prevention System (IPS) rule engine that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured rules on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to incorrect HTTP packet handling. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured IPS rules and allow uninspected traffic onto the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20363|2024-08-01T21:59:42.321Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
