<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco AMP for Endpoints</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco AMP for Endpoints</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3314|2024-08-04T07:30:57.821Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the file scan process of Cisco AMP for Endpoints Mac Connector Software could cause the scan engine to crash during the scan of local files, resulting in a restart of the AMP Connector and a denial of service (DoS) condition of the Cisco AMP for Endpoints service. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of specific file attributes. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by providing a crafted file to a user of an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Cisco AMP for Endpoints service to crash, resulting in missed detection and logging of the potentially malicious file. Continued attempts to scan the file could result in a DoS condition of the Cisco AMP for Endpoints service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3314|2024-08-04T07:30:57.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3344|2024-08-04T07:30:58.163Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3344</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco AMP for Endpoints Linux Connector Software and Cisco AMP for Endpoints Mac Connector Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause a buffer overflow on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Cisco AMP for Endpoints service to crash and restart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3344|2024-08-04T07:30:58.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1932|2024-08-04T18:35:51.257Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1932</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Advanced Malware Protection (AMP) for Endpoints for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator privileges to execute arbitrary code. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of dynamically loaded modules. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by placing a file in a specific location in the Windows filesystem. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute the code with the privileges of the AMP service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1932|2024-08-04T18:35:51.257Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3343|2024-08-04T07:30:58.111Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3343</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco AMP for Endpoints Linux Connector Software and Cisco AMP for Endpoints Mac Connector Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause a buffer overflow on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Cisco AMP for Endpoints service to crash and restart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3343|2024-08-04T07:30:58.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3350|2024-08-04T07:30:58.198Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3350</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the endpoint software of Cisco AMP for Endpoints and Clam AntiVirus could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause the running software to delete arbitrary files on the system. The vulnerability is due to a race condition that could occur when scanning malicious files. An attacker with local shell access could exploit this vulnerability by executing a script that could trigger the race condition. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files on the system that the attacker would not normally have privileges to delete, producing system instability or causing the endpoint software to stop working.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3350|2024-08-04T07:30:58.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
