<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20xe%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:22:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20682|2024-08-03T02:17:53.131Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20682</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Catalyst 9000 Family could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to inadequate input validation of incoming CAPWAP packets encapsulating multicast DNS (mDNS) queries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to a wireless network and sending a crafted mDNS query, which would flow through and be processed by the wireless controller. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20682|2024-08-03T02:17:53.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1624|2024-08-03T16:18:10.396Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1624</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Rate Limiting Network Address Translation (NAT) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization in the Cisco QuantumFlow Processor of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to mishandling of the rate limiting feature within the QuantumFlow Processor. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending large amounts of traffic that would be subject to NAT and rate limiting through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the QuantumFlow Processor utilization to reach 100 percent on the affected device, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1624|2024-08-03T16:18:10.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1432|2024-08-03T16:11:17.238Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1432</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system as the root user. The attacker must be authenticated on the affected device as a low-privileged user to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting arbitrary commands to a file as a lower-privileged user. The commands are then executed on the device by the root user. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1432|2024-08-03T16:11:17.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1451|2024-08-03T16:11:17.327Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1451</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Easy Virtual Switching System (VSS) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 4500 Series Switches and Cisco Catalyst 4500-X Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying Linux operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to incorrect boundary checks of certain values in Easy VSS protocol packets that are destined for an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted Easy VSS protocol packets to UDP port 5500 while the affected device is in a specific state. When the crafted packet is processed, a buffer overflow condition may occur. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition or execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the underlying Linux operating system of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1451|2024-08-03T16:11:17.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1446|2024-08-03T16:11:17.292Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1446</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DNS application layer gateway (ALG) functionality used by Network Address Translation (NAT) in Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload. The vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an affected device inspects certain DNS packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted DNS packets through an affected device that is performing NAT for DNS packets. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability can be exploited only by traffic that is sent through an affected device via IPv4 packets. The vulnerability cannot be exploited via IPv6 traffic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1446|2024-08-03T16:11:17.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20676|2024-08-03T02:17:53.170Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20676</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Tool Command Language (Tcl) interpreter of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to escalate from privilege level 15 to root-level privileges. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of data that is passed into the Tcl interpreter. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by loading malicious Tcl code on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root. By default, Tcl shell access requires privilege level 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20676|2024-08-03T02:17:53.170Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20693|2024-08-03T02:17:53.202Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20693</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform an injection attack against an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input to the web UI API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to inject commands to the underlying operating system with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20693|2024-08-03T02:17:53.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1220|2024-08-03T16:02:56.181Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1220</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web UI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with read-only privileges to cause the web UI software to become unresponsive and consume vty line instances, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient error handling in the web UI. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted HTTP packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the web UI software to become unresponsive and consume all available vty lines, preventing new session establishment and resulting in a DoS condition. Manual intervention would be required to regain web UI and vty session functionality. Note: These vulnerabilities do not affect the console connection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1220|2024-08-03T16:02:56.181Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1435|2024-08-03T16:11:17.264Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1435</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary commands that can be executed as the root user. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the web UI of an affected device with arbitrary commands injected into a portion of the request. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1435|2024-08-03T16:11:17.264Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1619|2024-08-03T16:18:11.250Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1619</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the authentication, authorization, and accounting (AAA) function of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass NETCONF or RESTCONF authentication and do either of the following: Install, manipulate, or delete the configuration of an affected device Cause memory corruption that results in a denial of service (DoS) on an affected device This vulnerability is due to an uninitialized variable. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of NETCONF or RESTCONF requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to use NETCONF or RESTCONF to install, manipulate, or delete the configuration of a network device or to corrupt memory on the device, resulting a DoS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1619|2024-08-03T16:18:11.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1382|2024-08-03T16:11:16.871Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1382</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject arbitrary commands to be executed with root privileges on the underlying operating system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation on certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and submitting crafted input to the CLI. The attacker must be authenticated as an administrative user to execute the affected commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1382|2024-08-03T16:11:16.871Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1621|2024-08-03T16:18:10.424Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1621</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Layer 2 punt code of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a queue wedge on an interface that receives specific Layer 2 frames, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain Layer 2 frames. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific Layer 2 frames on the segment the router is connected to. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a queue wedge on the interface, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1621|2024-08-03T16:18:10.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1434|2024-08-03T16:11:17.259Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1434</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to overwrite arbitrary files in the underlying file system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of the parameters of a specific CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by issuing that command with specific parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite the content of any arbitrary file that resides on the underlying host file system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1434|2024-08-03T16:11:17.259Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1443|2024-08-03T16:11:17.183Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1443</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the underlying operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability exists because the affected software improperly sanitizes values that are parsed from a specific configuration file. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by tampering with a specific configuration file and then sending an API call. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to inject arbitrary code that would be executed on the underlying operating system of the affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have a privileged set of credentials to the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1443|2024-08-03T16:11:17.183Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1625|2024-08-03T16:18:11.123Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1625</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Zone-Based Policy Firewall feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to prevent the Zone-Based Policy Firewall from correctly classifying traffic. This vulnerability exists because ICMP and UDP responder-to-initiator flows are not inspected when the Zone-Based Policy Firewall has either Unified Threat Defense (UTD) or Application Quality of Experience (AppQoE) configured. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send UDP or ICMP flows through the network. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to inject traffic through the Zone-Based Policy Firewall, resulting in traffic being dropped because it is incorrectly classified or in incorrect reporting figures being produced by high-speed logging (HSL).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1625|2024-08-03T16:18:11.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20837|2024-08-03T02:24:49.955Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20837</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DNS application layer gateway (ALG) functionality that is used by Network Address Translation (NAT) in Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an affected device inspects certain TCP DNS packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted DNS packets through the affected device that is performing NAT for DNS packets. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on the affected device. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited only by sending IPv4 TCP packets through an affected device. This vulnerability cannot be exploited by sending IPv6 traffic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20837|2024-08-03T02:24:49.955Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1394|2024-08-03T16:11:16.898Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1394</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the ingress traffic manager of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) 520 Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition in the web management interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of certain IPv4 TCP traffic that is destined to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of crafted TCP packets to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the web management interface to become unavailable, resulting in a DoS condition. Note: This vulnerability does not impact traffic that is going through the device or going to the Management Ethernet interface of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1394|2024-08-03T16:11:16.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1623|2024-08-03T16:18:10.848Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1623</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) punt handling function of Cisco cBR-8 Converged Broadband Routers could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to overload a device punt path, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to the punt path being overwhelmed by large quantities of SNMP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of SNMP requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overload the device punt path, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1623|2024-08-03T16:18:10.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20694|2024-08-03T02:24:48.558Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20694</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the Resource Public Key Infrastructure (RPKI) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) process to crash, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of a specific RPKI to Router (RTR) Protocol packet header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by compromising the RPKI validator server and sending a specifically crafted RTR packet to an affected device. Alternatively, the attacker could use man-in-the-middle techniques to impersonate the RPKI validator server and send a crafted RTR response packet over the established RTR TCP connection to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition because the BGP process could constantly restart and BGP routing could become unstable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20694|2024-08-03T02:24:48.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1622|2024-08-03T16:18:10.416Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1622</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Common Open Policy Service (COPS) of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco cBR-8 Converged Broadband Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause resource exhaustion, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to a deadlock condition in the code when processing COPS packets under certain conditions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending COPS packets with high burst rates to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the CPU to consume excessive resources, which prevents other control plane processes from obtaining resources and results in a DoS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1622|2024-08-03T16:18:10.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20810|2024-08-03T02:24:49.984Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20810</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Catalyst 9000 Family could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive information. This vulnerability is due to insufficient restrictions that allow a sensitive configuration detail to be disclosed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by retrieving data through SNMP read-only community access. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view Service Set Identifier (SSID) preshared keys (PSKs) that are configured on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20810|2024-08-03T02:24:49.984Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20679|2024-08-03T02:17:53.083Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20679</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPSec decryption routine of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to buffer exhaustion that occurs while traffic on a configured IPsec tunnel is being processed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic to an affected device that has a maximum transmission unit (MTU) of 1800 bytes or greater. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker may need access to the trusted network where the affected device is in order to send specific packets to be processed by the device. All network devices between the attacker and the affected device must support an MTU of 1800 bytes or greater. This access requirement could limit the possibility of a successful exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20679|2024-08-03T02:17:53.083Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1390|2024-08-03T16:11:17.328Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1390</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in one of the diagnostic test CLI commands of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have valid user credentials at privilege level 15. This vulnerability exists because the affected software permits modification of the run-time memory of an affected device under specific circumstances. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the affected device and issuing a specific diagnostic test command at the CLI. A successful exploit could trigger a logic error in the code that was designed to restrict run-time memory modifications. The attacker could take advantage of this logic error to overwrite system memory locations and execute arbitrary code on the underlying Linux operating system (OS) of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1390|2024-08-03T16:11:17.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1381|2024-08-03T16:11:16.981Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1381</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges or an unauthenticated attacker with physical access to the device to open a debugging console. The vulnerability is due to insufficient command authorization restrictions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running commands on the hardware platform to open a debugging console. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access a debugging console.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1381|2024-08-03T16:11:16.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20681|2024-08-03T02:17:53.007Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20681</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family Switches and Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family Wireless Controllers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to level 15 on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user privileges after the user executes certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to an affected device as a low-privileged user and then executing certain CLI commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands with level 15 privileges on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20681|2024-08-03T02:17:53.007Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1398|2024-08-03T16:11:17.059Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1398</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot logic of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with level 15 privileges or an unauthenticated attacker with physical access to execute arbitrary code on the underlying Linux operating system of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to incorrect validations of specific function arguments that are passed to the boot script. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by tampering with a specific file, which an affected device would process during the initial boot process. On systems that are protected by the Unified Extensible Firmware Interface (UEFI) secure boot feature, a successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute unsigned code at boot time and bypass the image verification check in the secure boot process of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1398|2024-08-03T16:11:17.059Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20915|2024-08-03T02:31:59.767Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20915</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of IPv6 VPN over MPLS (6VPE) with Zone-Based Firewall (ZBFW) of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper error handling of an IPv6 packet that is forwarded from an MPLS and ZBFW-enabled interface in a 6VPE deployment. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPv6 packet sourced from a device on the IPv6-enabled virtual routing and forwarding (VRF) interface through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to reload the device, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20915|2024-08-03T02:31:59.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20870|2024-08-03T02:24:50.248Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20870</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the egress MPLS packet processing function of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 3650, Catalyst 3850, and Catalyst 9000 Family Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of IPv4 traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed packet out of an affected MPLS-enabled interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20870|2024-08-03T02:24:50.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1615|2024-08-03T16:18:10.808Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1615</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the packet processing functionality of Cisco Embedded Wireless Controller (EWC) Software for Catalyst Access Points (APs) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected AP. This vulnerability is due to insufficient buffer allocation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust available resources and cause a DoS condition on an affected AP, as well as a DoS condition for client traffic traversing the AP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1615|2024-08-03T16:18:10.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20847|2024-08-03T02:24:50.262Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20847</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP processing functionality of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Catalyst 9000 Family could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to the improper processing of DHCP messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious DHCP messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20847|2024-08-03T02:24:50.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1403|2024-08-03T16:11:17.237Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1403</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site WebSocket hijacking (CSWSH) attack and cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient HTTP protections in the web UI on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the web UI to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to corrupt memory on the affected device, forcing it to reload and causing a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1403|2024-08-03T16:11:17.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1374|2024-08-03T16:11:16.888Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1374</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller software for the Catalyst 9000 Family of switches could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against another user of the web-based management interface of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device as a high-privileged user, adding certain configurations with malicious code in one of its fields, and persuading another user to click on it. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or to access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1374|2024-08-03T16:11:16.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20848|2024-08-03T02:24:49.940Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20848</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the UDP processing functionality of Cisco IOS XE Software for Embedded Wireless Controllers on Catalyst 9100 Series Access Points could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to the improper processing of UDP datagrams. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious UDP datagrams to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20848|2024-08-03T02:24:49.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1565|2024-08-03T16:18:10.351Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1565</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit the vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1565|2024-08-03T16:18:10.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1611|2024-08-03T16:18:10.371Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1611</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Ethernet over GRE (EoGRE) packet processing of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Cisco Catalyst 9800 Family Wireless Controller, Embedded Wireless Controller, and Embedded Wireless on Catalyst 9000 Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper processing of malformed EoGRE packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious packets to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1611|2024-08-03T16:18:10.371Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1371|2024-08-03T16:11:17.024Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1371</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the role-based access control of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with read-only privileges to obtain administrative privileges by using the console port when the device is in the default SD-WAN configuration. This vulnerability occurs because the default configuration is applied for console authentication and authorization. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the console port and authenticating as a read-only user. A successful exploit could allow a user with read-only permissions to access administrative privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1371|2024-08-03T16:11:17.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1383|2024-08-03T16:11:16.884Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1383</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access the underlying operating system with root privileges. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient input validation of certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by authenticating to the device and submitting crafted input to the CLI. The attacker must be authenticated as an administrative user to execute the affected commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access the underlying operating system with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1383|2024-08-03T16:11:16.884Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1281|2024-08-03T16:02:56.398Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1281</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in CLI management in Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access the underlying operating system as the root user. This vulnerability is due to the way the software handles concurrent CLI sessions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device as an administrative user and executing a sequence of commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain access to the underlying operating system as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1281|2024-08-03T16:02:56.398Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1454|2024-08-03T16:11:17.235Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1454</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access the underlying operating system with root privileges. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient input validation of certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by authenticating to the device and submitting crafted input to the CLI. The attacker must be authenticated as an administrative user to execute the affected commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access the underlying operating system with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1454|2024-08-03T16:11:17.235Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1433|2024-08-03T16:11:17.363Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1433</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the vDaemon process in Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a buffer overflow on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient bounds checking when the device processes traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted traffic to the device. The attacker must have a man-in-the-middle position between Cisco vManage and an associated device that is running an affected version of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software. An exploit could allow the attacker to conduct a controllable buffer overflow attack (and possibly execute arbitrary commands as the root user) or cause a device reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1433|2024-08-03T16:11:17.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20678|2024-08-03T02:17:53.075Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20678</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the AppNav-XE feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of certain TCP segments. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a stream of crafted TCP traffic at a high rate through an interface of an affected device. That interface would need to have AppNav interception enabled. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20678|2024-08-03T02:17:53.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1442|2024-08-03T16:11:17.201Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1442</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a diagnostic command for the Plug-and-Play (PnP) subsystem of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to the level of an Administrator user (level 15) on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient protection of sensitive information. An attacker with low privileges could exploit this vulnerability by issuing the diagnostic CLI show pnp profile when a specific PnP listener is enabled on the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain a privileged authentication token. This token can be used to send crafted PnP messages and execute privileged commands on the targeted system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1442|2024-08-03T16:11:17.201Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1431|2024-08-03T16:11:16.978Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1431</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the vDaemon process of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a device to reload, resulting a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to insufficient handling of malformed packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1431|2024-08-03T16:11:16.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1375|2024-08-03T16:11:17.044Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1375</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the fast reload feature of Cisco IOS XE Software running on Cisco Catalyst 3850, Cisco Catalyst 9300, and Cisco Catalyst 9300L Series Switches could allow an authenticated, local attacker to either execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system, install and boot a malicious software image, or execute unsigned binaries on an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to improper checks performed by system boot routines. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker would need privileged access to the CLI of the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to either execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system or execute unsigned code and bypass the image verification check part of the secure boot process. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1375|2024-08-03T16:11:17.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20684|2024-08-03T02:17:53.171Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20684</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) trap generation for wireless clients of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Catalyst 9000 Family could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to unexpectedly reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on the device. This vulnerability is due to a lack of input validation of the information used to generate an SNMP trap related to a wireless client connection event. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending an 802.1x packet with crafted parameters during the wireless authentication setup phase of a connection. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20684|2024-08-03T02:17:53.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20944|2024-08-03T02:31:58.131Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20944</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the software image verification functionality of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9200 Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to execute unsigned code at system boot time. This vulnerability is due to an improper check in the code function that manages the verification of the digital signatures of system image files during the initial boot process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by loading unsigned software on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to boot a malicious software image or execute unsigned code and bypass the image verification check part of the boot process of the affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker needs either unauthenticated physical access to the device or privileged access to the root shell on the device. Note: In Cisco IOS XE Software releases 16.11.1 and later, root shell access is protected by the Consent Token mechanism. However, an attacker with level-15 privileges could easily downgrade the Cisco IOS XE Software running on a device to a release where root shell access is more readily available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20944|2024-08-03T02:31:58.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20851|2024-08-03T02:24:50.292Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20851</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform an injection attack against an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input to the web UI API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root privileges. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have valid Administrator privileges on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20851|2024-08-03T02:24:50.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1356|2024-08-03T16:11:16.687Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1356</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web UI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with read-only privileges to cause the web UI software to become unresponsive and consume vty line instances, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient error handling in the web UI. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted HTTP packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the web UI software to become unresponsive and consume all available vty lines, preventing new session establishment and resulting in a DoS condition. Manual intervention would be required to regain web UI and vty session functionality. Note: These vulnerabilities do not affect the console connection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1356|2024-08-03T16:11:16.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1373|2024-08-03T16:11:17.041Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1373</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1373|2024-08-03T16:11:17.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20855|2024-08-03T02:24:50.248Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20855</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the self-healing functionality of Cisco IOS XE Software for Embedded Wireless Controllers on Catalyst Access Points could allow an authenticated, local attacker to escape the restricted controller shell and execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of the access point. This vulnerability is due to improper checks throughout the restart of certain system processes. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging on to an affected device and executing certain CLI commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying OS as root. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid credentials for a privilege level 15 user of the wireless controller.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20855|2024-08-03T02:24:50.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20864|2024-08-03T02:24:50.242Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20864</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the password-recovery disable feature of Cisco IOS XE ROM Monitor (ROMMON) Software for Cisco Catalyst Switches could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker to recover the configuration or reset the enable password. This vulnerability is due to a problem with the file and boot variable permissions in ROMMON. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by rebooting the switch into ROMMON and entering specific commands through the console. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read any file or reset the enable password.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20864|2024-08-03T02:24:50.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1436|2024-08-03T16:11:17.313Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1436</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to conduct path traversal attacks and obtain read access to sensitive files on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view arbitrary files on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1436|2024-08-03T16:11:17.313Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20683|2024-08-03T02:17:53.170Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20683</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Application Visibility and Control (AVC-FNF) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient packet verification for traffic inspected by the AVC feature. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted packets from the wired network to a wireless client, resulting in the crafted packets being processed by the wireless controller. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a crash and reload of the affected device, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20683|2024-08-03T02:17:53.170Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1352|2024-08-03T16:11:16.876Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1352</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DECnet Phase IV and DECnet/OSI protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of DECnet traffic that is received by an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending DECnet traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1352|2024-08-03T16:11:16.876Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1376|2024-08-03T16:11:16.951Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1376</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the fast reload feature of Cisco IOS XE Software running on Cisco Catalyst 3850, Cisco Catalyst 9300, and Cisco Catalyst 9300L Series Switches could allow an authenticated, local attacker to either execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system, install and boot a malicious software image, or execute unsigned binaries on an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to improper checks performed by system boot routines. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker would need privileged access to the CLI of the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to either execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system or execute unsigned code and bypass the image verification check part of the secure boot process. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1376|2024-08-03T16:11:16.951Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1441|2024-08-03T16:11:17.163Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1441</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the hardware initialization routines of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco 1100 Series Industrial Integrated Services Routers and Cisco ESR6300 Embedded Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute unsigned code at system boot time. This vulnerability is due to incorrect validations of parameters passed to a diagnostic script that is executed when the device boots up. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by tampering with an executable file stored on a device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute unsigned code at boot time and bypass the software image verification check part of the secure boot process of an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need administrative level credentials (level 15) on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1441|2024-08-03T16:11:17.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20692|2024-08-03T02:17:53.077Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20692</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NETCONF over SSH feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow a low-privileged, authenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition (DoS) on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient resource management. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by initiating a large number of NETCONF over SSH connections. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust resources, causing the device to reload and resulting in a DoS condition on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20692|2024-08-03T02:17:53.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1453|2024-08-03T16:11:17.274Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1453</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the software image verification functionality of Cisco IOS XE Software for the Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family of switches could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to execute unsigned code at system boot time. The vulnerability is due to an improper check in the code function that manages the verification of the digital signatures of system image files during the initial boot process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by loading unsigned software on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to boot a malicious software image or execute unsigned code and bypass the image verification check part of the secure boot process of an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have unauthenticated physical access to the device or obtain privileged access to the root shell on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1453|2024-08-03T16:11:17.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1384|2024-08-03T16:11:16.871Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1384</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco IOx application hosting environment of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject commands into the underlying operating system as the root user. This vulnerability is due to incomplete validation of fields in the application packages loaded onto IOx. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by creating a crafted application .tar file and loading it onto the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform command injection into the underlying operating system as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1384|2024-08-03T16:11:16.871Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20856|2024-08-03T02:24:50.260Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20856</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the processing of Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) Mobility messages in Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Catalyst 9000 Family could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error and improper management of resources related to the handling of CAPWAP Mobility messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted CAPWAP Mobility packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust resources on the affected device. This would cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20856|2024-08-03T02:24:50.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1616|2024-08-03T16:18:10.302Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1616</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the H.323 application level gateway (ALG) used by the Network Address Translation (NAT) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the ALG. This vulnerability is due to insufficient data validation of traffic that is traversing the ALG. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted traffic to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the ALG and open connections that should not be allowed to a remote device located behind the ALG. Note: This vulnerability has been publicly discussed as NAT Slipstreaming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1616|2024-08-03T16:18:10.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20313|2024-08-01T21:59:42.856Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20313</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of OSPF updates that are processed by a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF update to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20313|2024-08-01T21:59:42.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-08-01T21:59:41.851Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-08-01T21:59:41.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20306|2024-08-01T21:59:41.650Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Unified Threat Defense (UTD) configuration CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying host operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have level 15 privileges on the affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20306|2024-08-01T21:59:41.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20278|2024-08-01T21:59:41.100Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20278</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NETCONF feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input over NETCONF to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges from Administrator to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20278|2024-08-01T21:59:41.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T21:52:31.616Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T21:52:31.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-08-01T21:59:42.197Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-08-01T21:59:42.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-08-01T21:59:42.311Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-08-01T21:59:42.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20303|2024-08-01T21:59:41.376Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20303</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multicast DNS (mDNS) gateway feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Wireless LAN Controllers (WLCs) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper management of mDNS client entries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the wireless network and sending a continuous stream of specific mDNS packets. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the wireless controller to have high CPU utilization, which could lead to access points (APs) losing their connection to the controller and result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20303|2024-08-01T21:59:41.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20324|2024-08-01T21:59:41.715Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20324</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to access WLAN configuration details including passwords.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper privilege checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the show and show tech wireless CLI commands to access configuration details, including passwords. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access configuration details that they are not authorized to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20324|2024-08-01T21:59:41.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20259|2024-08-01T21:52:31.719Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP snooping feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a crafted IPv4 DHCP request packet being mishandled when endpoint analytics are enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCP request through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; Note: The attack vector is listed as network because a DHCP relay anywhere on the network could allow exploits from networks other than the adjacent one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20259|2024-08-01T21:52:31.719Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20309|2024-08-01T21:59:41.337Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in auxiliary asynchronous port (AUX) functions of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause an affected device to reload or stop responding.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific ingress traffic when flow control hardware is enabled on the AUX port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by reverse telnetting to the AUX port and sending specific data after connecting. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reset or stop responding, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20309|2024-08-01T21:59:41.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-07-02T16:23:39.427Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-07-02T16:23:39.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-07-02T16:25:13.272Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-07-02T16:25:13.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-07-02T16:25:58.752Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-07-02T16:25:58.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-06-20T17:42:35.196Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-06-20T17:42:35.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20303|2024-06-04T17:39:55.892Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20303</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multicast DNS (mDNS) gateway feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Wireless LAN Controllers (WLCs) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper management of mDNS client entries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the wireless network and sending a continuous stream of specific mDNS packets. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the wireless controller to have high CPU utilization, which could lead to access points (APs) losing their connection to the controller and result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20303|2024-06-04T17:39:55.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-03-27T16:57:27.974Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-03-27T16:57:27.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20313|2024-04-24T20:42:10.379Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20313</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of OSPF updates that are processed by a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF update to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20313|2024-04-24T20:42:10.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20309|2024-03-27T17:02:19.749Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in auxiliary asynchronous port (AUX) functions of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause an affected device to reload or stop responding.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific ingress traffic when flow control hardware is enabled on the AUX port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by reverse telnetting to the AUX port and sending specific data after connecting. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reset or stop responding, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20309|2024-03-27T17:02:19.749Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20324|2024-03-27T16:55:53.837Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20324</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to access WLAN configuration details including passwords.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper privilege checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the show and show tech wireless CLI commands to access configuration details, including passwords. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access configuration details that they are not authorized to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20324|2024-03-27T16:55:53.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20278|2024-03-27T16:59:12.963Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20278</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NETCONF feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input over NETCONF to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges from Administrator to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20278|2024-03-27T16:59:12.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20259|2024-03-27T16:53:53.073Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP snooping feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a crafted IPv4 DHCP request packet being mishandled when endpoint analytics are enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCP request through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; Note: The attack vector is listed as network because a DHCP relay anywhere on the network could allow exploits from networks other than the adjacent one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20259|2024-03-27T16:53:53.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-04-03T16:36:06.520Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-04-03T16:36:06.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20306|2024-03-27T16:58:22.583Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Unified Threat Defense (UTD) configuration CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying host operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have level 15 privileges on the affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20306|2024-03-27T16:58:22.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-03-27T16:49:03.113Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-03-27T16:49:03.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-03-27T17:03:54.505Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-03-27T17:03:54.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-06-20T20:50:12.348Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-06-20T20:50:12.348Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-06-20T20:52:30.286Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-06-20T20:52:30.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T15:33:37.498Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T15:33:37.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
