<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System (Managed)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System (Managed)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 22:22:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1966|2024-09-16T18:45:26.683Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1966</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a specific CLI command within the local management (local-mgmt) context for Cisco UCS Fabric Interconnect Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain elevated privileges as the root user on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to extraneous subcommand options present for a specific CLI command within the local-mgmt context. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to an affected device, entering the local-mgmt context, and issuing a specific CLI command and submitting user input. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary operating system commands as root on an affected device. The attacker would need to have valid user credentials for the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1966|2024-09-16T18:45:26.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 21:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3504|2024-09-16T17:18:44.467Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3504</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the local management (local-mgmt) CLI of Cisco UCS Manager Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of CLI command parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by executing specific commands on the local-mgmt CLI on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause internal system processes to fail to terminate properly, which could result in a buildup of stuck processes and lead to slowness in accessing the UCS Manager CLI and web UI. A sustained attack may result in a restart of internal UCS Manager processes and a temporary loss of access to the UCS Manager CLI and web UI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3504|2024-09-16T17:18:44.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 15:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1592|2024-09-16T20:43:00.648Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1592</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the way Cisco UCS Manager software handles SSH sessions could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper resource management for established SSH sessions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by opening a significant number of SSH sessions on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a crash and restart of internal Cisco UCS Manager software processes and a temporary loss of access to the Cisco UCS Manager CLI and web UI. Note: The attacker must have valid user credentials to authenticate to the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1592|2024-09-16T20:43:00.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 19:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1963|2024-09-16T19:20:34.728Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1963</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) input packet processor of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause the SNMP application on an affected device to restart unexpectedly. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of Abstract Syntax Notation One (ASN.1)-encoded variables in SNMP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SNMP packet to the SNMP daemon on the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the SNMP application to restart multiple times, leading to a system-level restart and a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1963|2024-09-16T19:20:34.728Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 18:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1880|2024-09-16T20:21:25.067Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1880</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the BIOS upgrade utility of Cisco Unified Computing System (UCS) C-Series Rack Servers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to install compromised BIOS firmware on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of the firmware image file. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by executing the BIOS upgrade utility with a specific set of options. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the firmware signature-verification process and install compromised BIOS firmware on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1880|2024-09-16T20:21:25.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 16:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1962|2024-09-16T18:03:23.143Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20%28managed%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1962</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Fabric Services component of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause process crashes, which can result in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of TCP packets when processed by the Cisco Fabric Services over IP (CFSoIP) feature. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious Cisco Fabric Services TCP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause process crashes, resulting in a device reload and a DoS condition. Note: There are three distribution methods that can be configured for Cisco Fabric Services. This vulnerability affects only distribution method CFSoIP, which is disabled by default. See the Details section for more information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1962|2024-09-16T18:03:23.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 18:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
