<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco vManage Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20vmanage%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco vManage Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 06:24:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16012|2024-08-05T01:03:32.798Z -- cisco -- cisco%20vmanage%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16012</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco SD-WAN Solution vManage software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system. The vulnerability exists because the web UI improperly validates SQL values. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application and sending malicious SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify values on, or return values from, the underlying database as well as the operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16012|2024-08-05T01:03:32.798Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16002|2024-08-05T01:03:32.790Z -- cisco -- cisco%20vmanage%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16002</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the vManage web-based UI (web UI) of the Cisco SD-WAN Solution could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web UI on an affected instance of vManage. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to follow a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privilege level of the affected user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16002|2024-08-05T01:03:32.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16010|2024-08-05T01:03:32.664Z -- cisco -- cisco%20vmanage%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16010</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of the Cisco SD-WAN vManage software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of the vManage software. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16010|2024-08-05T01:03:32.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
