<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Identity Services Engine Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Identity Services Engine Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 16:23:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3467|2024-08-04T07:37:54.227Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3467</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to modify parts of the configuration on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper enforcement of role-based access control (RBAC) within the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify parts of the configuration. The modified configuration could either allow unauthorized devices onto the network or prevent authorized devices from accessing the network. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid Read-Only Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3467|2024-08-04T07:37:54.227Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34738|2024-08-04T00:19:48.193Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34738</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) Software could allow an attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34738|2024-08-04T00:19:48.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3551|2024-08-04T07:37:55.139Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3551</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of an affected interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3551|2024-08-04T07:37:55.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34759|2024-08-04T00:19:48.214Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34759</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative credentials to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid administrative credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34759|2024-08-04T00:19:48.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34702|2024-08-04T00:19:48.133Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34702</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain sensitive information. This vulnerability is due to improper enforcement of administrator privilege levels for low-value sensitive data. An attacker with read-only administrator access to the web-based management interface could exploit this vulnerability by browsing to the page that contains the sensitive data. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to collect sensitive information regarding the configuration of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34702|2024-08-04T00:19:48.133Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3353|2024-08-04T07:30:58.218Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3353</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the syslog processing engine of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a race condition that may occur when syslog messages are processed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high rate of syslog messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Application Server process to crash, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3353|2024-08-04T07:30:58.218Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3149|2024-08-04T07:24:00.626Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3149</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by providing malicious data to a specific field within the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. Cisco ISE Software releases 2.7.0 and later contains the fix for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3149|2024-08-04T07:24:00.626Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3340|2024-08-04T07:30:58.126Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3340</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative credentials to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input that is processed by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker would need valid administrative credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3340|2024-08-04T07:30:58.126Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26083|2024-08-04T15:49:06.679Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26083</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative credentials to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have valid administrative credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26083|2024-08-04T15:49:06.679Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40121|2024-08-04T02:27:31.528Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40121</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) Software could allow an attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40121|2024-08-04T02:27:31.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3156|2024-08-04T07:24:00.665Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3156</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the logging component of Cisco Identity Services Engine could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to conduct cross-site scripting attacks. The vulnerability is due to the improper validation of endpoint data stored in logs used by the web-based interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious endpoint data to the targeted system. An exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or to access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3156|2024-08-04T07:24:00.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34706|2024-08-04T00:19:48.120Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34706</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive information or conduct a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack through an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper handling of XML External Entity (XXE) entries when parsing certain XML files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a crafted XML file that contains references to external entities. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve files from the local system, resulting in the disclosure of sensitive information, or cause the web application to perform arbitrary HTTP requests on behalf of the attacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34706|2024-08-04T00:19:48.120Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40123|2024-08-04T02:27:31.534Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40123</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative read-only privileges to download files that should be restricted. This vulnerability is due to incorrect permissions settings on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to download files that should be restricted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40123|2024-08-04T02:27:31.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3157|2024-08-04T07:24:00.628Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3157</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based interface. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting a malicious configuration and saving it to the targeted system. An exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information when an administrator views the configuration. An attacker would need write permissions to exploit this vulnerability successfully.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3157|2024-08-04T07:24:00.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3589|2024-08-04T07:37:55.631Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3589</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative credentials to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have valid administrative credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3589|2024-08-04T07:37:55.631Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-18T03:55:22.366Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-18T03:55:22.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T16:28:22.193Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T16:28:22.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20368|2024-06-04T17:40:10.016Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20368</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on the affected device with the privileges of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20368|2024-06-04T17:40:10.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20332|2024-06-04T17:40:15.273Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20332</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack through an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation for specific HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send arbitrary network requests that are sourced from the affected device. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid Super Admin credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20332|2024-06-04T17:40:15.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T21:20:23.314Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T21:20:23.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-08-01T21:59:41.103Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-08-01T21:59:41.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20332|2024-08-01T21:59:41.923Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20332</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack through an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation for specific HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send arbitrary network requests that are sourced from the affected device. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid Super Admin credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20332|2024-08-01T21:59:41.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20368|2024-08-01T21:59:41.799Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20368</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on the affected device with the privileges of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20368|2024-08-01T21:59:41.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
