<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software for Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches ACI Mode</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20nx-os%20software%20for%20nexus%209000%20series%20fabric%20switches%20aci%20mode.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software for Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches ACI Mode</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:22:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1836|2024-08-04T18:28:42.811Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software%20for%20nexus%209000%20series%20fabric%20switches%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1836</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the system shell for Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches in Application Centric Infrastructure (ACI) mode could allow an authenticated, local attacker to use symbolic links to overwrite system files. These system files may be sensitive and should not be overwritable by non-root users. The attacker would need valid device credentials. The vulnerability is due to incorrect symbolic link verification of directory paths when they are used in the system shell. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and providing crafted user input to specific symbolic link CLI commands. Successful exploitation could allow the attacker to overwrite system files that should be restricted. This vulnerability has been fixed in software version 14.1(1i).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1836|2024-08-04T18:28:42.811Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1588|2024-08-04T18:20:28.149Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software%20for%20nexus%209000%20series%20fabric%20switches%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1588</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches running in Application-Centric Infrastructure (ACI) mode could allow an authenticated, local attacker to read arbitrary files on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a lack of proper input and validation checking mechanisms of user-supplied input sent to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker unauthorized access to read arbitrary files on an affected device. This vulnerability has been fixed in version 14.0(1h).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1588|2024-08-04T18:20:28.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1589|2024-08-04T18:20:28.311Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software%20for%20nexus%209000%20series%20fabric%20switches%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1589</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Trusted Platform Module (TPM) functionality of software for Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches in Application Centric Infrastructure (ACI) mode could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker with physical access to view sensitive information on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a lack of proper data-protection mechanisms for disk encryption keys that are used within the partitions on an affected device hard drive. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by obtaining physical access to the affected device to view certain cleartext keys. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute a custom boot process or conduct further attacks on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1589|2024-08-04T18:20:28.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1590|2024-08-04T18:20:28.314Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software%20for%20nexus%209000%20series%20fabric%20switches%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1590</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Transport Layer Security (TLS) certificate validation functionality of Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Application Centric Infrastructure (ACI) Mode Switch Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to perform insecure TLS client authentication on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient TLS client certificate validations for certificates sent between the various components of an ACI fabric. An attacker who has possession of a certificate that is trusted by the Cisco Manufacturing CA and the corresponding private key could exploit this vulnerability by presenting a valid certificate while attempting to connect to the targeted device. An exploit could allow the attacker to gain full control of all other components within the ACI fabric of an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1590|2024-08-04T18:20:28.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1585|2024-08-04T18:20:28.365Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software%20for%20nexus%209000%20series%20fabric%20switches%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1585</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the controller authorization functionality of Cisco Nexus 9000 Series ACI Mode Switch Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to escalate standard users with root privilege on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a misconfiguration of certain sudoers files for the bashroot component on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the affected device with a crafted user ID, which may allow temporary administrative access to escalate privileges. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to escalate privileges on an affected device. This Vulnerability has been fixed in version 4.0(1h)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1585|2024-08-04T18:20:28.365Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1591|2024-08-04T18:20:28.309Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software%20for%20nexus%209000%20series%20fabric%20switches%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1591</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a specific CLI command implementation of Cisco Nexus 9000 Series ACI Mode Switch Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to escape a restricted shell on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied input when issuing a specific CLI command with parameters on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device CLI and issuing certain commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to escape the restricted shell and execute arbitrary commands with root-level privileges on the affected device. This vulnerability only affects Cisco Nexus 9000 Series ACI Mode Switches that are running a release prior to 14.0(3d).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1591|2024-08-04T18:20:28.309Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1803|2024-08-04T18:28:42.810Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software%20for%20nexus%209000%20series%20fabric%20switches%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1803</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the filesystem management for the Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Application Centric Infrastructure (ACI) Mode Switch Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator rights to gain elevated privileges as the root user on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to overly permissive file permissions of specific system files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to an affected device, creating a crafted command string, and writing this crafted string to a specific file location. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary operating system commands as root on an affected device. The attacker would need to have valid administrator credentials for the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1803|2024-08-04T18:28:42.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
