<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOx</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20iox.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOx</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3233|2024-08-04T07:30:56.944Z -- cisco -- cisco%20iox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3233</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based Local Manager interface of the Cisco IOx Application Framework could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based Local Manager interface of an affected device. The attacker must have valid Local Manager credentials. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based Local Manager interface of the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into a system settings tab. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected web interface or allow the attacker to access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3233|2024-08-04T07:30:56.944Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3237|2024-08-04T07:30:58.157Z -- cisco -- cisco%20iox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3237</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Application Framework component of the Cisco IOx application environment could allow an authenticated, local attacker to overwrite arbitrary files in the virtual instance that is running on the affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient path restriction enforcement. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including a crafted file in an application package. An exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3237|2024-08-04T07:30:58.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3238|2024-08-04T07:30:57.447Z -- cisco -- cisco%20iox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3238</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Application Framework component of the Cisco IOx application environment could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to write or modify arbitrary files in the virtual instance that is running on the affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of user-supplied application packages. An attacker who can upload a malicious package within Cisco IOx could exploit the vulnerability to modify arbitrary files. The impacts of a successful exploit are limited to the scope of the virtual instance and do not affect the device that is hosting Cisco IOx.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3238|2024-08-04T07:30:57.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
