<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco HyperFlex HX-Series</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco HyperFlex HX-Series</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:21:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1666|2024-09-16T17:04:11.578Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1666</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Graphite service of Cisco HyperFlex software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to retrieve data from the Graphite service. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authentication controls. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted requests to the Graphite service. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve any statistics from the Graphite service. Versions prior to 3.5(2a) are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1666|2024-09-16T17:04:11.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15407|2024-09-16T18:38:57.630Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15407</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the installation process of Cisco HyperFlex Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to read sensitive information. The vulnerability is due to insufficient cleanup of installation files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the residual installation files on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to collect sensitive information regarding the configuration of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15407|2024-09-16T18:38:57.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1958|2024-09-16T20:26:31.605Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1958</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco HyperFlex Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web UI on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privilege level of the affected user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1958|2024-09-16T20:26:31.605Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 07:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1665|2024-09-16T22:41:18.626Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1665</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco HyperFlex software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a maliciously crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. Versions prior to 3.5(1a) are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1665|2024-09-16T22:41:18.626Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15423|2024-09-16T17:08:29.302Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hyperflex%20hx-series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15423</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco HyperFlex Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to affect the integrity of a device via a clickjacking attack. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of iFrame data in HTTP requests that are sent to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets with malicious iFrame data. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform a clickjacking attack where the user is tricked into clicking a malicious link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15423|2024-09-16T17:08:29.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
