<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Customer Voice Portal (CVP)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20unified%20customer%20voice%20portal%20%28cvp%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Customer Voice Portal (CVP)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 05:23:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1246|2024-09-17T03:38:45.561Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20customer%20voice%20portal%20%28cvp%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1246</link>
      <description>Cisco Finesse, Cisco Virtualized Voice Browser, and Cisco Unified CVP OpenSocial Gadget Editor Unauthenticated Access Vulnerability&#13;
&#13;
A vulnerability in the web management interface of Cisco Finesse, Cisco Virtualized Voice Browser, and Cisco Unified CVP could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access the OpenSocial Gadget Editor without providing valid user credentials.&#13;
The vulnerability is due to missing authentication for a specific section of the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing a crafted URL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain access to a section of the interface, which they could use to obtain potentially confidential information and create arbitrary XML files.&#13;
Cisco&amp;nbsp;has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1246|2024-09-17T03:38:45.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 21:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16017|2024-09-17T02:06:48.867Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20customer%20voice%20portal%20%28cvp%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16017</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Operations, Administration, Maintenance and Provisioning (OAMP) OpsConsole Server for Cisco Unified Customer Voice Portal (CVP) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute Insecure Direct Object Reference actions on specific pages within the OAMP application. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation on specific pages of the OAMP application. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to Cisco Unified CVP and sending crafted HTTP requests. A successful exploit could allow an attacker with administrator or read-only privileges to learn information outside of their expected scope. An attacker with administrator privileges could modify certain configuration details of resources outside of their defined scope, which could result in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16017|2024-09-17T02:06:48.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
