<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Contact Center Express</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20unified%20contact%20center%20express.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Contact Center Express</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 16:23:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3280|2024-08-04T07:30:57.525Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20contact%20center%20express
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3280</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Java Remote Management Interface of Cisco Unified Contact Center Express (Unified CCX) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insecure deserialization of user-supplied content by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious serialized Java object to a specific listener on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code as the root user on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3280|2024-08-04T07:30:57.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3267|2024-08-04T07:30:57.603Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20contact%20center%20express
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3267</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the API subsystem of Cisco Unified Contact Center Express (Unified CCX) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to change the availability state of any agent. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization enforcement on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to an affected system with valid agent credentials and performing a specific API call with crafted input. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to change the availability state of an agent, potentially causing a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3267|2024-08-04T07:30:57.603Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
