<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 05:23:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0447|2024-08-05T03:28:09.828Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0447</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the anti-spam protection mechanisms of Cisco AsyncOS Software for the Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass certain content filters on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to incomplete input and validation checking mechanisms for certain Sender Policy Framework (SPF) messages that are sent to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a customized SPF packet to an affected device. If successful, an exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the URL filters that are configured for the affected device, which could allow malicious URLs to pass through the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0447|2024-08-05T03:28:09.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15971|2024-08-05T01:03:32.407Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15971</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the MP3 detection engine of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured content filters on the device. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of certain MP3 file types. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted MP3 file through the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured content filters that would normally drop the email.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15971|2024-08-05T01:03:32.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15988|2024-08-05T01:03:32.812Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15988</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the antispam protection mechanisms of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the URL reputation filters on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of URLs. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting the URL in a particular way. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the URL reputation filters that are configured for the affected device, which could allow malicious URLs to pass through the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15988|2024-08-05T01:03:32.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
