<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System Director</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20director.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Computing System Director</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1935|2024-08-04T18:35:51.256Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20director
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1935</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) Supervisor, Cisco UCS Director, and Cisco UCS Director Express for Big Data could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to log in to the CLI of an affected system by using the SCP User account (scpuser), which has default user credentials. The vulnerability is due to the presence of a documented default account with an undocumented default password and incorrect permission settings for that account. Changing the default password for this account is not enforced during the installation of the product. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the account to log in to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands with the privileges of the scpuser account. This includes full read and write access to the system's database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1935|2024-08-04T18:35:51.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1936|2024-08-04T18:35:51.267Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20director
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1936</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) Supervisor, Cisco UCS Director, and Cisco UCS Director Express for Big Data could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux shell as the root user. Exploitation of this vulnerability requires privileged access to an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to the web-based management interface with administrator privileges and then sending a malicious request to a certain part of the interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1936|2024-08-04T18:35:51.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1938|2024-08-04T18:35:51.269Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20director
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1938</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco UCS Director and Cisco UCS Director Express for Big Data could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass authentication and execute arbitrary actions with administrator privileges on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to improper authentication request handling. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow an unprivileged attacker to access and execute arbitrary actions through certain APIs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1938|2024-08-04T18:35:51.269Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1937|2024-08-04T18:35:51.886Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20director
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1937</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) Supervisor, Cisco UCS Director, and Cisco UCS Director Express for Big Data could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to acquire a valid session token with administrator privileges, bypassing user authentication. The vulnerability is due to insufficient request header validation during the authentication process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of malicious requests to an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to use the acquired session token to gain full administrator access to the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1937|2024-08-04T18:35:51.886Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1974|2024-08-04T18:35:52.473Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20computing%20system%20director
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1974</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) Supervisor, Cisco UCS Director, and Cisco UCS Director Express for Big Data could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass user authentication and gain access as an administrative user. The vulnerability is due to insufficient request header validation during the authentication process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of malicious requests to an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to gain full administrative access to the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1974|2024-08-04T18:35:52.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
