<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Stealthwatch Enterprise</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20stealthwatch%20enterprise.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Stealthwatch Enterprise</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 05:23:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15994|2024-09-17T00:11:54.519Z -- cisco -- cisco%20stealthwatch%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15994</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Stealthwatch Enterprise could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15994|2024-09-17T00:11:54.519Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 03:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15394|2024-09-17T01:51:31.547Z -- cisco -- cisco%20stealthwatch%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15394</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Stealthwatch Management Console (SMC) of Cisco Stealthwatch Enterprise could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass authentication and execute arbitrary actions with administrative privileges on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to an insecure system configuration. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the targeted application. An exploit could allow the attacker to gain unauthenticated access, resulting in elevated privileges in the SMC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15394|2024-09-17T01:51:31.547Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
