<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Web Security Appliance (WSA)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20web%20security%20appliance%20%28wsa%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Web Security Appliance (WSA)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:19:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20781|2024-08-03T02:24:49.565Z -- cisco -- cisco%20web%20security%20appliance%20%28wsa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20781</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Web Security Appliance (WSA) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting malicious data into a specific data field in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20781|2024-08-03T02:24:49.565Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20784|2024-08-03T02:24:49.683Z -- cisco -- cisco%20web%20security%20appliance%20%28wsa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20784</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Web-Based Reputation Score (WBRS) engine of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Web Security Appliance (WSA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass established web request policies and access blocked content on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to incorrect handling of certain character combinations inserted into a URL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted URLs to be processed by an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the web proxy and access web content that has been blocked by policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20784|2024-08-03T02:24:49.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1516|2024-08-03T16:11:17.683Z -- cisco -- cisco%20web%20security%20appliance%20%28wsa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1516</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Content Security Management Appliance (SMA), Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA), and Cisco Web Security Appliance (WSA) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive information on an affected device. The vulnerability exists because confidential information is included in HTTP requests that are exchanged between the user and the device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by looking at the raw HTTP requests that are sent to the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain some of the passwords that are configured throughout the interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1516|2024-08-03T16:11:17.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20675|2024-08-03T02:17:53.082Z -- cisco -- cisco%20web%20security%20appliance%20%28wsa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20675</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TCP/IP stack of Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA), Cisco Web Security Appliance (WSA), and Cisco Secure Email and Web Manager, formerly Security Management Appliance, could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to crash the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) service, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to an open port listener on TCP port 199. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to TCP port 199. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the SNMP service, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20675|2024-08-03T02:17:53.082Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1271|2024-08-03T16:02:56.397Z -- cisco -- cisco%20web%20security%20appliance%20%28wsa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1271</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco AsyncOS for Cisco Web Security Appliance (WSA) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting malicious data into a specific data field in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1271|2024-08-03T16:02:56.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1359|2024-08-03T16:11:16.761Z -- cisco -- cisco%20web%20security%20appliance%20%28wsa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1359</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the configuration management of Cisco AsyncOS for Cisco Web Security Appliance (WSA) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform command injection and elevate privileges to root. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied XML input for the web interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading crafted XML configuration files that contain scripting code to a vulnerable device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. An attacker would need a valid user account with the rights to upload configuration files to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1359|2024-08-03T16:11:16.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1566|2024-08-03T16:18:10.153Z -- cisco -- cisco%20web%20security%20appliance%20%28wsa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1566</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Advanced Malware Protection (AMP) for Endpoints integration of Cisco AsyncOS for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) and Cisco Web Security Appliance (WSA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to intercept traffic between an affected device and the AMP servers. This vulnerability is due to improper certificate validation when an affected device establishes TLS connections. A man-in-the-middle attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted TLS packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to spoof a trusted host and then extract sensitive information or alter certain API requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1566|2024-08-03T16:18:10.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1129|2024-08-03T16:02:55.822Z -- cisco -- cisco%20web%20security%20appliance%20%28wsa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1129</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the authentication for the general purpose APIs implementation of Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA), Cisco Content Security Management Appliance (SMA), and Cisco Web Security Appliance (WSA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access general system information and certain configuration information from an affected device. The vulnerability exists because a secure authentication token is not required when authenticating to the general purpose API. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request for information to the general purpose API on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain system and configuration information from the affected device, resulting in an unauthorized information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1129|2024-08-03T16:02:55.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1490|2024-08-03T16:11:17.337Z -- cisco -- cisco%20web%20security%20appliance%20%28wsa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1490</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco AsyncOS for Cisco Web Security Appliance (WSA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input in the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to retrieve a crafted file that contains malicious payload and upload it to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1490|2024-08-03T16:11:17.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
