<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Extensible Operating System (FXOS)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20firepower%20extensible%20operating%20system%20%28fxos%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Extensible Operating System (FXOS)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 06:24:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3459|2024-09-17T02:46:54.946Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20extensible%20operating%20system%20%28fxos%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3459</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco FXOS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject arbitrary commands that are executed with root privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of commands supplied by the user. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to a device and submitting crafted input to the affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands on the underlying operating system with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3459|2024-09-17T02:46:54.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1700|2024-09-17T03:03:04.792Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20extensible%20operating%20system%20%28fxos%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1700</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in field-programmable gate array (FPGA) ingress buffer management for the Cisco Firepower 9000 Series with the Cisco Firepower 2-port 100G double-width network module (PID: FPR9K-DNM-2X100G) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. Manual intervention may be required before a device will resume normal operations. The vulnerability is due to a logic error in the FPGA related to the processing of different types of input packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by being on the adjacent subnet and sending a crafted sequence of input packets to a specific interface on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a queue wedge condition on the interface. When a wedge occurs, the affected device will stop processing any additional packets that are received on the wedged interface. Version 2.2 is affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1700|2024-09-17T03:03:04.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
