<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco AMP for Endpoints</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco AMP for Endpoints</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:21:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20785|2024-09-16T17:17:43.872Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20785</link>
      <description>On April 20, 2022, the following vulnerability in the ClamAV scanning library versions 0.103.5 and earlier and 0.104.2 and earlier was disclosed: A vulnerability in HTML file parser of Clam AntiVirus (ClamAV) versions 0.104.0 through 0.104.2 and LTS version 0.103.5 and prior versions could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition on an affected device. For a description of this vulnerability, see the ClamAV blog. This advisory will be updated as additional information becomes available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20785|2024-09-16T17:17:43.872Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 17:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20796|2024-09-16T17:29:07.898Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20796</link>
      <description>On May 4, 2022, the following vulnerability in the ClamAV scanning library versions 0.103.5 and earlier and 0.104.2 and earlier was disclosed: A vulnerability in Clam AntiVirus (ClamAV) versions 0.103.4, 0.103.5, 0.104.1, and 0.104.2 could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause a denial of service condition on an affected device. For a description of this vulnerability, see the ClamAV blog.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20796|2024-09-16T17:29:07.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 17:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3350|2024-09-16T19:09:58.170Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3350</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the endpoint software of Cisco AMP for Endpoints and Clam AntiVirus could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause the running software to delete arbitrary files on the system. The vulnerability is due to a race condition that could occur when scanning malicious files. An attacker with local shell access could exploit this vulnerability by executing a script that could trigger the race condition. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files on the system that the attacker would not normally have privileges to delete, producing system instability or causing the endpoint software to stop working.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3350|2024-09-16T19:09:58.170Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 02:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1386|2024-09-16T22:31:25.089Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1386</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the dynamic link library (DLL) loading mechanism in Cisco Advanced Malware Protection (AMP) for Endpoints Windows Connector, ClamAV for Windows, and Immunet could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform a DLL hijacking attack on an affected Windows system. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid credentials on the system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of directory search paths at run time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by placing a malicious DLL file on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1386|2024-09-16T22:31:25.089Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 04:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15437|2024-09-16T18:23:23.732Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15437</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the system scanning component of Cisco Immunet and Cisco Advanced Malware Protection (AMP) for Endpoints running on Microsoft Windows could allow a local attacker to disable the scanning functionality of the product. This could allow executable files to be launched on the system without being analyzed for threats. The vulnerability is due to improper process resource handling. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by gaining local access to a system running Microsoft Windows and protected by Cisco Immunet or Cisco AMP for Endpoints and executing a malicious file. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to prevent the scanning services from functioning properly and ultimately prevent the system from being protected from further intrusion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15437|2024-09-16T18:23:23.732Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1280|2024-09-16T18:07:52.277Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1280</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the loading mechanism of specific DLLs of Cisco Advanced Malware Protection (AMP) for Endpoints for Windows and Immunet for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform a DLL hijacking attack. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid credentials on the Windows system. This vulnerability is due to incorrect handling of directory search paths at run time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by placing a malicious DLL file on the targeted system. This file will execute when the vulnerable application launches. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the targeted system with SYSTEM privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1280|2024-09-16T18:07:52.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:56:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20770|2024-09-16T18:48:27.201Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20770</link>
      <description>On April 20, 2022, the following vulnerability in the ClamAV scanning library versions 0.103.5 and earlier and 0.104.2 and earlier was disclosed: A vulnerability in CHM file parser of Clam AntiVirus (ClamAV) versions 0.104.0 through 0.104.2 and LTS version 0.103.5 and prior versions could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition on an affected device. For a description of this vulnerability, see the ClamAV blog. This advisory will be updated as additional information becomes available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20770|2024-09-16T18:48:27.201Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 17:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3343|2024-09-16T22:09:00.050Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3343</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco AMP for Endpoints Linux Connector Software and Cisco AMP for Endpoints Mac Connector Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause a buffer overflow on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Cisco AMP for Endpoints service to crash and restart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3343|2024-09-16T22:09:00.050Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 05:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
