<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Jabber IM for Android</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20jabber%20im%20for%20android.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Jabber IM for Android</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3155|2024-08-04T07:24:00.623Z -- cisco -- cisco%20jabber%20im%20for%20android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3155</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSL implementation of the Cisco Intelligent Proximity solution could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to view or alter information shared on Cisco Webex video devices and Cisco collaboration endpoints if the products meet the conditions described in the Vulnerable Products section. The vulnerability is due to a lack of validation of the SSL server certificate received when establishing a connection to a Cisco Webex video device or a Cisco collaboration endpoint. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using man in the middle (MITM) techniques to intercept the traffic between the affected client and an endpoint, and then using a forged certificate to impersonate the endpoint. Depending on the configuration of the endpoint, an exploit could allow the attacker to view presentation content shared on it, modify any content being presented by the victim, or have access to call controls. This vulnerability does not affect cloud registered collaboration endpoints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3155|2024-08-04T07:24:00.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
