<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN Solution</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20sd-wan%20solution.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN Solution</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:42:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1614|2024-09-16T16:18:27.417Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1614</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Multiprotocol Label Switching (MPLS) packet handling function of Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain access to information stored in MPLS buffer memory. This vulnerability is due to insufficient handling of malformed MPLS packets that are processed by a device that is running Cisco SD-WAN Software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted MPLS packet to an affected device that is running Cisco SD-WAN Software or Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain unauthorized access to sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1614|2024-09-16T16:18:27.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 15:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1137|2024-09-16T16:48:46.591Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1137</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code or allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain escalated privileges on an affected system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1137|2024-09-16T16:48:46.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 04:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1279|2024-09-16T16:47:58.028Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1279</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN products could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute denial of service (DoS) attacks against an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1279|2024-09-16T16:47:58.028Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3444|2024-09-16T20:32:41.107Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3444</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the packet filtering features of Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass L3 and L4 traffic filters. The vulnerability is due to improper traffic filtering conditions on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting a malicious TCP packet with specific characteristics and sending it to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the L3 and L4 traffic filters and inject an arbitrary packet into the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3444|2024-09-16T20:32:41.107Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 18:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1528|2024-09-16T18:38:44.180Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1528</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain elevated privileges on an affected system. This vulnerability exists because the affected software does not properly restrict access to privileged processes. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by invoking a privileged process in the affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform actions with the privileges of the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1528|2024-09-16T18:38:44.180Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 16:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1626|2024-09-16T17:22:57.753Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1626</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the vManage web-based UI (Web UI) of the Cisco SD-WAN Solution could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to gain elevated privileges on an affected vManage device. The vulnerability is due to a failure to properly authorize certain user actions in the device configuration. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to the vManage Web UI and sending crafted HTTP requests to vManage. A successful exploit could allow attackers to gain elevated privileges and make changes to the configuration that they would not normally be authorized to make.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1626|2024-09-16T17:22:57.753Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 02:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1624|2024-09-16T18:23:16.758Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1624</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the vManage web-based UI (Web UI) in the Cisco SD-WAN Solution could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary commands that are executed with root privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and submitting crafted input to the vManage Web UI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1624|2024-09-16T18:23:16.758Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 02:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0434|2024-09-16T18:02:53.485Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0434</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Zero Touch Provisioning feature of the Cisco SD-WAN Solution could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain unauthorized access to sensitive data by using an invalid certificate. The vulnerability is due to insufficient certificate validation by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a crafted certificate to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct man-in-the-middle attacks to decrypt confidential information on user connections to the affected software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0434|2024-09-16T18:02:53.485Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1299|2024-09-16T18:33:18.162Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1299</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN products could allow an authenticated attacker to perform command injection attacks against an affected device, which could allow the attacker to take certain actions with root privileges on the device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1299|2024-09-16T18:33:18.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3594|2024-09-16T20:06:57.561Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3594</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to root on the underlying operating system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by providing crafted options to a specific command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3594|2024-09-16T20:06:57.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 18:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0432|2024-09-16T19:31:53.140Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0432</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the error reporting feature of the Cisco SD-WAN Solution could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to gain elevated privileges on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a failure to properly validate certain parameters included within the error reporting application configuration. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted command to the error reporting feature. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain root-level privileges and take full control of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0432|2024-09-16T19:31:53.140Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1263|2024-09-16T19:09:05.222Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1263</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN products could allow an authenticated attacker to perform command injection attacks against an affected device, which could allow the attacker to take certain actions with root privileges on the device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1263|2024-09-16T19:09:05.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20818|2024-09-16T18:59:35.795Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20818</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI of Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain elevated privileges. These vulnerabilities are due to improper access controls on commands within the application CLI. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by running a malicious command on the application CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20818|2024-09-16T18:59:35.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 18:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1951|2024-09-16T18:03:30.138Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1951</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the packet filtering features of Cisco SD-WAN Solution could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass L3 and L4 traffic filters. The vulnerability is due to improper traffic filtering conditions on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting a malicious TCP packet with specific characteristics and sending it to a target device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the L3 and L4 traffic filters and inject an arbitrary packet in the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1951|2024-09-16T18:03:30.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 07:25:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1261|2024-09-16T19:35:08.478Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1261</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN products could allow an authenticated attacker to perform command injection attacks against an affected device, which could allow the attacker to take certain actions with root privileges on the device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1261|2024-09-16T19:35:08.478Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0433|2024-09-16T19:41:47.757Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0433</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the command-line interface (CLI) in the Cisco SD-WAN Solution could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject arbitrary commands that are executed with root privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and submitting crafted input to the CLI utility. The attacker must be authenticated to access the CLI utility. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0433|2024-09-16T19:41:47.757Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1650|2024-09-16T18:19:39.073Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1650</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco SD-WAN Solution could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to overwrite arbitrary files on the underlying operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation of the save command in the CLI of the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by modifying the save command in the CLI of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite arbitrary files on the underlying operating system of an affected device and escalate their privileges to the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1650|2024-09-16T18:19:39.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1480|2024-09-16T18:24:34.143Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1480</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code or allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain escalated privileges on an affected system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1480|2024-09-16T18:24:34.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 04:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1241|2024-09-16T19:46:08.270Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1241</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN products could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute denial of service (DoS) attacks against an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1241|2024-09-16T19:46:08.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 20:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20716|2024-09-16T18:18:23.701Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20716</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain escalated privileges. This vulnerability is due to improper access control on files within the affected system. A local attacker could exploit this vulnerability by modifying certain files on the vulnerable device. If successful, the attacker could gain escalated privileges and take actions on the system with the privileges of the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20716|2024-09-16T18:18:23.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1514|2024-09-16T19:35:49.514Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1514</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject arbitrary commands to be executed with Administrator privileges on the underlying operating system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation on certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and submitting crafted input to the CLI. The attacker must be authenticated as a low-privileged user to execute the affected commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands with Administrator privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1514|2024-09-16T19:35:49.514Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 12:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3264|2024-09-16T18:19:42.913Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3264</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN Solution software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause a buffer overflow on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to information that they are not authorized to access and make changes to the system that they are not authorized to make.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3264|2024-09-16T18:19:42.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 15:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1274|2024-09-16T20:41:45.724Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1274</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN products could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute denial of service (DoS) attacks against an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1274|2024-09-16T20:41:45.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3265|2024-09-16T19:50:50.131Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN Solution software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to root on the underlying operating system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain root-level privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3265|2024-09-16T19:50:50.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 15:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15387|2024-09-16T16:48:53.585Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15387</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco SD-WAN Solution could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass certificate validation on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper certificate validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a system image signed with a crafted certificate to an affected device, bypassing the certificate validation. An exploit could allow an attacker to deploy a crafted system image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15387|2024-09-16T16:48:53.585Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1262|2024-09-16T16:52:48.583Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1262</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN products could allow an authenticated attacker to perform command injection attacks against an affected device, which could allow the attacker to take certain actions with root privileges on the device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1262|2024-09-16T16:52:48.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
