<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco WebEx Meetings Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco WebEx Meetings Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 18:24:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3441|2024-08-04T07:37:55.052Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3441</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings and Cisco Webex Meetings Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to view sensitive information from the meeting room lobby. This vulnerability is due to insufficient protection of sensitive participant information. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by browsing the Webex roster. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gather information about other Webex participants, such as email address and IP address, while waiting in the lobby.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3441|2024-08-04T07:37:55.052Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3342|2024-08-04T07:30:58.143Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3342</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the software update feature of Cisco Webex Meetings Desktop App for Mac could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of cryptographic protections on files that are downloaded by the application as part of a software update. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to go to a website that returns files to the client that are similar to files that are returned from a valid Webex website. The client may fail to properly validate the cryptographic protections of the provided files before executing them as part of an update. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected system with the privileges of the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3342|2024-08-04T07:30:58.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3345|2024-08-04T07:30:58.117Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3345</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in certain web pages of Cisco Webex Meetings and Cisco Webex Meetings Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to modify a web page in the context of a browser. The vulnerability is due to improper checks on parameter values within affected pages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to follow a crafted link that is designed to pass HTML code into an affected parameter. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to alter the contents of a web page to redirect the user to potentially malicious web sites, or the attacker could leverage this vulnerability to conduct further client-side attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3345|2024-08-04T07:30:58.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3471|2024-08-04T07:37:54.287Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3471</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings and Cisco Webex Meetings Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to maintain bidirectional audio despite being expelled from an active Webex session. The vulnerability is due to a synchronization issue between meeting and media services on a vulnerable Webex site. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted requests to a vulnerable Cisco Webex Meetings or Cisco Webex Meetings Server site. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to maintain the audio connection of a Webex session despite being expelled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3471|2024-08-04T07:37:54.287Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3263|2024-08-04T07:30:57.506Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3263</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings Desktop App could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute programs on an affected end-user system. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of input that is supplied to application URLs. The attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to follow a malicious URL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the application to execute other programs that are already present on the end-user system. If malicious files are planted on the system or on an accessible network file path, the attacker could execute arbitrary code on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3263|2024-08-04T07:30:57.506Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3347|2024-08-04T07:30:58.210Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3347</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings Desktop App for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain access to sensitive information on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to unsafe usage of shared memory that is used by the affected software. An attacker with permissions to view system memory could exploit this vulnerability by running an application on the local system that is designed to read shared memory. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve sensitive information from the shared memory, including usernames, meeting information, or authentication tokens that could aid the attacker in future attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3347|2024-08-04T07:30:58.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3419|2024-08-04T07:30:58.171Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3419</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings and Cisco Webex Meetings Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to join a Webex session without appearing on the participant list. This vulnerability is due to improper handling of authentication tokens by a vulnerable Webex site. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted requests to a vulnerable Cisco Webex Meetings or Cisco Webex Meetings Server site. A successful exploit requires the attacker to have access to join a Webex meeting, including applicable meeting join links and passwords. The attacker could then exploit this vulnerability to join meetings, without appearing in the participant list, while having full access to audio, video, chat, and screen sharing capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3419|2024-08-04T07:30:58.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3361|2024-08-04T07:30:58.161Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings and Cisco Webex Meetings Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain unauthorized access to a vulnerable Webex site. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of authentication tokens by a vulnerable Webex site. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted requests to a vulnerable Cisco Webex Meetings or Cisco Webex Meetings Server site. If successful, the attacker could gain the privileges of another user within the affected Webex site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3361|2024-08-04T07:30:58.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
