<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 14:23:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3134|2024-08-04T07:24:00.635Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3134</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the zip decompression engine of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of zip files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending an email message with a crafted zip-compressed attachment. A successful exploit could trigger a restart of the content-scanning process, causing a temporary DoS condition. This vulnerability affects Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco ESA releases earlier than 13.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3134|2024-08-04T07:24:00.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3132|2024-08-04T07:24:00.589Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3132</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the email message scanning feature of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a temporary denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to inadequate parsing mechanisms for specific email body components. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious email containing a high number of shortened URLs through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to consume processing resources, causing a DoS condition on an affected device. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, certain conditions beyond the control of the attacker must occur.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3132|2024-08-04T07:24:00.589Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3568|2024-08-04T07:37:55.458Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3568</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the antispam protection mechanisms of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the URL reputation filters on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of URLs. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting a URL in a particular way. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the URL reputation filters that are configured for the affected device, which could allow malicious URLs to pass through the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3568|2024-08-04T07:37:55.458Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3447|2024-08-04T07:37:54.219Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3447</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco AsyncOS for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) and Cisco AsyncOS for Cisco Content Security Management Appliance (SMA) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive information on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to excessive verbosity in certain log subscriptions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing specific log files on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain sensitive log data, which may include user credentials. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have valid credentials at the operator level or higher on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3447|2024-08-04T07:37:54.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3181|2024-08-04T07:24:00.947Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3181</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the malware detection functionality in Cisco Advanced Malware Protection (AMP) in Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliances (ESAs) could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to exhaust resources on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient control over system memory allocation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted email through the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an email attachment that contains malware to be delivered to a user and cause email processing delays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3181|2024-08-04T07:24:00.947Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3546|2024-08-04T07:37:54.867Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3546</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco AsyncOS software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive information on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of requests that are sent to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain the IP addresses that are configured on the internal interfaces of the affected device. There is a workaround that addresses this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3546|2024-08-04T07:37:54.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3370|2024-08-04T07:30:58.421Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3370</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in URL filtering of Cisco Content Security Management Appliance (SMA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass URL filtering on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted, malicious HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to redirect users to malicious sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3370|2024-08-04T07:30:58.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3368|2024-08-04T07:30:58.113Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3368</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the antispam protection mechanisms of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the URL reputation filters on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of URLs. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting the URL in a particular way. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the URL reputation filters that are configured for the affected device, which could allow malicious URLs to pass through the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3368|2024-08-04T07:30:58.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3133|2024-08-04T07:24:00.603Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3133</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the email message scanning of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured filters on the device. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of incoming emails. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted email message to a recipient protected by the ESA. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the configured content filters, which could allow malicious content to pass through the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3133|2024-08-04T07:24:00.603Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3137|2024-08-04T07:24:00.603Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3137</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface of the affected device does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or to access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3137|2024-08-04T07:24:00.603Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34741|2024-08-04T00:19:48.129Z -- cisco -- cisco%20email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34741</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the email scanning algorithm of Cisco AsyncOS software for Cisco Email Security Appliance (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to perform a denial of service (DoS) attack against an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of incoming emails. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted email through Cisco ESA. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust all the available CPU resources on an affected device for an extended period of time, preventing other emails from being processed and resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34741|2024-08-04T00:19:48.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
