<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Digital Network Architecture Center (DNA Center)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Digital Network Architecture Center (DNA Center)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:42:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1134|2024-09-16T17:47:54.216Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1134</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) integration feature of the Cisco DNA Center Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain unauthorized access to sensitive data. The vulnerability is due to an incomplete validation of the X.509 certificate used when establishing a connection between DNA Center and an ISE server. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a crafted certificate and could then intercept communications between the ISE and DNA Center. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view and alter sensitive information that the ISE maintains about clients that are connected to the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1134|2024-09-16T17:47:54.216Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 03:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1265|2024-09-16T20:36:37.568Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the configuration archive functionality of Cisco DNA Center could allow any privilege-level authenticated, remote attacker to obtain the full unmasked running configuration of managed devices. The vulnerability is due to the configuration archives files being stored in clear text, which can be retrieved by various API calls. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and executing a series of API calls. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve the full unmasked running configurations of managed devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1265|2024-09-16T20:36:37.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1130|2024-09-16T18:38:32.316Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1130</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco DNA Center software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have administrative credentials on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1130|2024-09-16T18:38:32.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 21:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3411|2024-09-16T16:17:50.479Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3411</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco DNA Center software could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker access to sensitive information on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of authentication tokens by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker access to sensitive device information, which includes configuration files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3411|2024-09-16T16:17:50.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 18:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20630|2024-09-16T16:53:54.386Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20630</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the audit log of Cisco DNA Center could allow an authenticated, local attacker to view sensitive information in clear text. This vulnerability is due to the unsecured logging of sensitive information on an affected system. An attacker with administrative privileges could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the audit logs through the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve sensitive information that includes user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20630|2024-09-16T16:53:54.386Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 17:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1303|2024-09-16T17:13:54.971Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1303</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the user management roles of Cisco DNA Center could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute unauthorized commands on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper enforcement of actions for assigned user roles. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating as a user with an Observer role and executing commands on the affected device. A successful exploit could allow a user with the Observer role to execute commands to view diagnostic information of the devices that Cisco DNA Center manages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1303|2024-09-16T17:13:54.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3466|2024-09-16T20:52:04.837Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3466</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco DNA Center software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. The vulnerabilities exist because the web-based management interface on an affected device does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3466|2024-09-16T20:52:04.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 16:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15386|2024-09-16T20:36:46.105Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15386</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Digital Network Architecture (DNA) Center could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass authentication and have direct unauthorized access to critical management functions. The vulnerability is due to an insecure default configuration of the affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by directly connecting to the exposed services. An exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve and modify critical system files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15386|2024-09-16T20:36:46.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1707|2024-09-16T20:06:53.212Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1707</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco DNA Center could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or allow the attacker to access sensitive browser-based information. Cisco DNA Center versions prior to 1.2.5 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1707|2024-09-16T20:06:53.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20333|2024-06-04T17:40:11.205Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20333</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Catalyst Center, formerly Cisco DNA Center, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to change specific data within the interface on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization enforcement. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to change a specific field within the web-based management interface, even though they should not have access to change that field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20333|2024-06-04T17:40:11.205Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20333|2024-08-01T21:59:42.856Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20333</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Catalyst Center, formerly Cisco DNA Center, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to change specific data within the interface on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization enforcement. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to change a specific field within the web-based management interface, even though they should not have access to change that field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20333|2024-08-01T21:59:42.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
