<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software for Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches ACI Mode 11.0.1b</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20nx-os%20software%20for%20nexus%209000%20series%20fabric%20switches%20aci%20mode%2011.0.1b.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software for Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches ACI Mode 11.0.1b</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 21:21:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1592|2024-08-04T18:20:28.310Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software%20for%20nexus%209000%20series%20fabric%20switches%20aci%20mode%2011.0.1b
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1592</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the background operations functionality of Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Application Centric Infrastructure (ACI) Mode Switch Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain elevated privileges as root on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied files on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to the CLI of the affected device and creating a crafted file in a specific directory on the filesystem. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary operating system commands as root on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1592|2024-08-04T18:20:28.310Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1804|2024-08-04T18:28:42.878Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software%20for%20nexus%209000%20series%20fabric%20switches%20aci%20mode%2011.0.1b
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1804</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSH key management for the Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Application Centric Infrastructure (ACI) Mode Switch Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to connect to the affected system with the privileges of the root user. The vulnerability is due to the presence of a default SSH key pair that is present in all devices. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by opening an SSH connection via IPv6 to a targeted device using the extracted key materials. An exploit could allow the attacker to access the system with the privileges of the root user. This vulnerability is only exploitable over IPv6; IPv4 is not vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1804|2024-08-04T18:28:42.878Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
