<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Digital Network Architecture Center (DNA Center)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Digital Network Architecture Center (DNA Center)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1257|2024-08-03T16:02:56.406Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1257</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco DNA Center Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack to manipulate an authenticated user into executing malicious actions without their awareness or consent. The vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a web-based management user to follow a specially crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on the device with the privileges of the authenticated user. These actions include modifying the device configuration, disconnecting the user's session, and executing Command Runner commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1257|2024-08-03T16:02:56.406Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1303|2024-08-03T16:02:56.468Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1303</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the user management roles of Cisco DNA Center could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute unauthorized commands on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper enforcement of actions for assigned user roles. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating as a user with an Observer role and executing commands on the affected device. A successful exploit could allow a user with the Observer role to execute commands to view diagnostic information of the devices that Cisco DNA Center manages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1303|2024-08-03T16:02:56.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1134|2024-08-03T16:02:55.414Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1134</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) integration feature of the Cisco DNA Center Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain unauthorized access to sensitive data. The vulnerability is due to an incomplete validation of the X.509 certificate used when establishing a connection between DNA Center and an ISE server. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a crafted certificate and could then intercept communications between the ISE and DNA Center. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view and alter sensitive information that the ISE maintains about clients that are connected to the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1134|2024-08-03T16:02:55.414Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1265|2024-08-03T16:02:56.372Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the configuration archive functionality of Cisco DNA Center could allow any privilege-level authenticated, remote attacker to obtain the full unmasked running configuration of managed devices. The vulnerability is due to the configuration archives files being stored in clear text, which can be retrieved by various API calls. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and executing a series of API calls. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve the full unmasked running configurations of managed devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1265|2024-08-03T16:02:56.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1264|2024-08-03T16:02:56.411Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1264</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Command Runner tool of Cisco DNA Center could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a command injection attack. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the Command Runner tool. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by providing crafted input during command execution or via a crafted command runner API call. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary CLI commands on devices managed by Cisco DNA Center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1264|2024-08-03T16:02:56.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1130|2024-08-03T16:02:55.403Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1130</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco DNA Center software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have administrative credentials on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1130|2024-08-03T16:02:55.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20630|2024-08-03T02:17:52.918Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20630</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the audit log of Cisco DNA Center could allow an authenticated, local attacker to view sensitive information in clear text. This vulnerability is due to the unsecured logging of sensitive information on an affected system. An attacker with administrative privileges could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the audit logs through the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve sensitive information that includes user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20630|2024-08-03T02:17:52.918Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20333|2024-06-04T17:40:11.205Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20333</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Catalyst Center, formerly Cisco DNA Center, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to change specific data within the interface on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization enforcement. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to change a specific field within the web-based management interface, even though they should not have access to change that field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20333|2024-06-04T17:40:11.205Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20333|2024-08-01T21:59:42.856Z -- cisco -- cisco%20digital%20network%20architecture%20center%20%28dna%20center%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20333</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Catalyst Center, formerly Cisco DNA Center, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to change specific data within the interface on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization enforcement. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to change a specific field within the web-based management interface, even though they should not have access to change that field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20333|2024-08-01T21:59:42.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
