<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Small Business Smart and Managed Switches</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20small%20business%20smart%20and%20managed%20switches.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Small Business Smart and Managed Switches</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 23:22:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20263|2024-08-01T21:52:31.672Z -- cisco -- cisco%20small%20business%20smart%20and%20managed%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20263</link>
      <description>A vulnerability with the access control list (ACL) management within a stacked switch configuration of Cisco Business 250 Series Smart Switches and Business 350 Series Managed Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass protection offered by a configured ACL on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of ACLs on a stacked configuration when either the primary or backup switches experience a full stack reload or power cycle. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACLs, causing traffic to be dropped or forwarded in an unexpected manner. The attacker does not have control over the conditions that result in the device being in the vulnerable state. Note: In the vulnerable state, the ACL would be correctly applied on the primary devices but could be incorrectly applied to the backup devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20263|2024-08-01T21:52:31.672Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 17:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
