<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20application%20policy%20infrastructure%20controller%20%28apic%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:21:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1577|2024-08-03T16:18:10.357Z -- cisco -- cisco%20application%20policy%20infrastructure%20controller%20%28apic%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1577</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in an API endpoint of Cisco Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC) and Cisco Cloud Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (Cloud APIC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to read or write arbitrary files on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to improper access control. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using a specific API endpoint to upload a file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read or write arbitrary files on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1577|2024-08-03T16:18:10.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1582|2024-08-03T16:18:10.312Z -- cisco -- cisco%20application%20policy%20infrastructure%20controller%20%28apic%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1582</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC) or Cisco Cloud APIC could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a stored cross-site scripting attack on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to improper input validation in the web UI. An authenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious input to the web UI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the web-based interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1582|2024-08-03T16:18:10.312Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1579|2024-08-03T16:18:10.265Z -- cisco -- cisco%20application%20policy%20infrastructure%20controller%20%28apic%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1579</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in an API endpoint of Cisco Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC) and Cisco Cloud Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (Cloud APIC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with Administrator read-only credentials to elevate privileges on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to an insufficient role-based access control (RBAC). An attacker with Administrator read-only credentials could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specific API request using an app with admin write credentials. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to Administrator with write privileges on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1579|2024-08-03T16:18:10.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1581|2024-08-03T16:18:10.335Z -- cisco -- cisco%20application%20policy%20infrastructure%20controller%20%28apic%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1581</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web UI and API endpoints of Cisco Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC) or Cisco Cloud APIC could allow a remote attacker to perform a command injection or file upload attack on an affected system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1581|2024-08-03T16:18:10.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1578|2024-08-03T16:18:10.274Z -- cisco -- cisco%20application%20policy%20infrastructure%20controller%20%28apic%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1578</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in an API endpoint of Cisco Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC) and Cisco Cloud Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (Cloud APIC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges to Administrator on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to an improper policy default setting. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using a non-privileged credential for Cisco ACI Multi-Site Orchestrator (MSO) to send a specific API request to a managed Cisco APIC or Cloud APIC device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain Administrator credentials on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1578|2024-08-03T16:18:10.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1580|2024-08-03T16:18:10.400Z -- cisco -- cisco%20application%20policy%20infrastructure%20controller%20%28apic%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1580</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web UI and API endpoints of Cisco Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC) or Cisco Cloud APIC could allow a remote attacker to perform a command injection or file upload attack on an affected system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1580|2024-08-03T16:18:10.400Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
