<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XR Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20xr%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XR Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 08:23:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34713|2024-08-04T00:19:48.108Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34713</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Layer 2 punt code of Cisco IOS XR Software running on Cisco ASR 9000 Series Aggregation Services Routers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the affected line card to reboot. This vulnerability is due to incorrect handling of specific Ethernet frames that cause a spin loop that can make the network processors unresponsive. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific types of Ethernet frames on the segment where the affected line cards are attached. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected line card to reboot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34713|2024-08-04T00:19:48.108Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34718|2024-08-04T00:19:48.124Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34718</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSH Server process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to overwrite and read arbitrary files on the local device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of arguments that are supplied by the user for a specific file transfer method. An attacker with lower-level privileges could exploit this vulnerability by specifying Secure Copy Protocol (SCP) parameters when authenticating to a device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate their privileges and retrieve and upload files on a device that they should not have access to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34718|2024-08-04T00:19:48.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34709|2024-08-04T00:19:48.103Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34709</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in image verification checks of Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) 540 Series Routers, only when running Cisco IOS XR NCS540L software images, and Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco 8000 Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34709|2024-08-04T00:19:48.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3566|2024-08-04T07:37:55.511Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3566</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Distance Vector Multicast Routing Protocol (DVMRP) feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to exhaust process memory of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient queue management for Internet Group Management Protocol (IGMP) packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted IGMP traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause memory exhaustion, resulting in instability of other processes. These processes may include, but are not limited to, interior and exterior routing protocols. Cisco will release software updates that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3566|2024-08-04T07:37:55.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34771|2024-08-04T00:19:48.259Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34771</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco IOS XR Software CLI could allow an authenticated, local attacker to view more information than their privileges allow. This vulnerability is due to insufficient application of restrictions during the execution of a specific command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a specific command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view sensitive configuration information that their privileges might not otherwise allow them to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34771|2024-08-04T00:19:48.259Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3530|2024-08-04T07:37:54.667Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3530</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in task group assignment for a specific CLI command in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute that command, even though administrative privileges should be required. The attacker must have valid credentials on the affected device. The vulnerability is due to incorrect mapping in the source code of task group assignments for a specific command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by issuing the command, which they should not be authorized to issue, on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to invalidate the integrity of the disk and cause the device to restart. This vulnerability could allow a user with read permissions to issue a specific command that should require Administrator privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3530|2024-08-04T07:37:54.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34728|2024-08-04T00:19:48.161Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34728</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with a low-privileged account to elevate privileges on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34728|2024-08-04T00:19:48.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34721|2024-08-04T00:19:48.110Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34721</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain access to the underlying root shell of an affected device and execute arbitrary commands with root privileges. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34721|2024-08-04T00:19:48.110Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3569|2024-08-04T07:37:55.472Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3569</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Distance Vector Multicast Routing Protocol (DVMRP) feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to either immediately crash the Internet Group Management Protocol (IGMP) process or make it consume available memory and eventually crash. The memory consumption may negatively impact other processes that are running on the device. These vulnerabilities are due to the incorrect handling of IGMP packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted IGMP traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to immediately crash the IGMP process or cause memory exhaustion, resulting in other processes becoming unstable. These processes may include, but are not limited to, interior and exterior routing protocols. Cisco will release software updates that address these vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3569|2024-08-04T07:37:55.472Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3284|2024-08-04T07:30:57.521Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3284</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the enhanced Preboot eXecution Environment (PXE) boot loader for Cisco IOS XR 64-bit Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute unsigned code during the PXE boot process on an affected device. The PXE boot loader is part of the BIOS and runs over the management interface of hardware platforms that are running Cisco IOS XR Software only. The vulnerability exists because internal commands that are issued when the PXE network boot process is loading a software image are not properly verified. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by compromising the PXE boot server and replacing a valid software image with a malicious one. Alternatively, the attacker could impersonate the PXE boot server and send a PXE boot reply with a malicious file. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute unsigned code on the affected device. Note: To fix this vulnerability, both the Cisco IOS XR Software and the BIOS must be upgraded. The BIOS code is included in Cisco IOS XR Software but might require additional installation steps. For further information, see the Fixed Software section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3284|2024-08-04T07:30:57.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34720|2024-08-04T00:19:48.088Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34720</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IP Service Level Agreements (IP SLA) responder and Two-Way Active Measurement Protocol (TWAMP) features of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause device packet memory to become exhausted or cause the IP SLA process to crash, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability exists because socket creation failures are mishandled during the IP SLA and TWAMP processes. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific IP SLA or TWAMP packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust the packet memory, which will impact other processes, such as routing protocols, or crash the IP SLA process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34720|2024-08-04T00:19:48.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3120|2024-08-04T07:24:00.647Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3120</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Discovery Protocol implementation for Cisco FXOS Software, Cisco IOS XR Software, and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to a missing check when the affected software processes Cisco Discovery Protocol messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious Cisco Discovery Protocol packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust system memory, causing the device to reload. Cisco Discovery Protocol is a Layer 2 protocol. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must be in the same broadcast domain as the affected device (Layer 2 adjacent).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3120|2024-08-04T07:24:00.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3449|2024-08-04T07:37:54.036Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3449</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) additional paths feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to prevent authorized users from monitoring the BGP status and cause the BGP process to stop processing new updates, resulting in a denial of service (DOS) condition. The vulnerability is due to an incorrect calculation of lexicographical order when displaying additional path information within Cisco IOS XR Software, which causes an infinite loop. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specific BGP update from a BGP neighbor peer session of an affected device; an authorized user must then issue a show bgp command for the vulnerability to be exploited. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to prevent authorized users from properly monitoring the BGP status and prevent BGP from processing new updates, resulting in outdated information in the routing and forwarding tables.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3449|2024-08-04T07:37:54.036Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34722|2024-08-04T00:19:48.254Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34722</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain access to the underlying root shell of an affected device and execute arbitrary commands with root privileges. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34722|2024-08-04T00:19:48.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34719|2024-08-04T00:19:48.125Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34719</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with a low-privileged account to elevate privileges on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34719|2024-08-04T00:19:48.125Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3118|2024-08-04T07:24:00.571Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3118</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Discovery Protocol implementation for Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to execute arbitrary code or cause a reload on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of string input from certain fields in Cisco Discovery Protocol messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious Cisco Discovery Protocol packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a stack overflow, which could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code with administrative privileges on an affected device. Cisco Discovery Protocol is a Layer 2 protocol. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must be in the same broadcast domain as the affected device (Layer 2 adjacent).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3118|2024-08-04T07:24:00.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3473|2024-08-04T07:37:54.202Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3473</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in task group assignment for a specific CLI command in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local CLI shell user to elevate privileges and gain full administrative control of the device. The vulnerability is due to incorrect mapping of a command to task groups within the source code. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by first authenticating to the local CLI shell on the device and using the CLI command to bypass the task group&amp;ndash;based checks. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges and perform actions on the device without authorization checks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3473|2024-08-04T07:37:54.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3364|2024-08-04T07:30:58.194Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3364</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) functionality of the standby route processor management interface of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to reach the configured IP addresses on the standby route processor management Gigabit Ethernet Management interface. The vulnerability is due to a logic error that was introduced in the Cisco IOS XR Software, which prevents the ACL from working when applied against the standby route processor management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to access the device through the standby route processor management interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3364|2024-08-04T07:30:58.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3217|2024-08-04T07:30:56.411Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3217</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Topology Discovery Service of Cisco One Platform Kit (onePK) in Cisco IOS Software, Cisco IOS XE Software, Cisco IOS XR Software, and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to execute arbitrary code or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient length restrictions when the onePK Topology Discovery Service parses Cisco Discovery Protocol messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious Cisco Discovery Protocol message to an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause a stack overflow, which could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code with administrative privileges, or to cause a process crash, which could result in a reload of the device and cause a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3217|2024-08-04T07:30:56.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34737|2024-08-04T00:19:48.091Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34737</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP version 4 (DHCPv4) server feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a crash of the dhcpd process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability exists because certain DHCPv4 messages are improperly validated when they are processed by an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed DHCPv4 message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a NULL pointer dereference, resulting in a crash of the dhcpd process. While the dhcpd process is restarting, which may take up to approximately two minutes, DHCPv4 server services are unavailable on the affected device. This could temporarily prevent network access to clients that join the network during that time period. Note: Only the dhcpd process crashes and eventually restarts automatically. The router does not reload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34737|2024-08-04T00:19:48.091Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34708|2024-08-04T00:19:48.164Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34708</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in image verification checks of Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) 540 Series Routers, only when running Cisco IOS XR NCS540L software images, and Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco 8000 Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34708|2024-08-04T00:19:48.164Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3190|2024-08-04T07:24:00.647Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3190</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPsec packet processor of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition for IPsec sessions to an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of packets by the IPsec packet processor. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious ICMP error messages to an affected device that get punted to the IPsec packet processor. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to deplete IPsec memory, resulting in all future IPsec packets to an affected device being dropped by the device. Manual intervention is required to recover from this situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3190|2024-08-04T07:24:00.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20322|2024-08-02T19:49:57.842Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20322</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on Pseudowire interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20322|2024-08-02T19:49:57.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20319|2024-08-01T21:59:41.556Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20319</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured management plane protection policies and access the Simple Network Management Plane (SNMP) server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect UDP forwarding programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to perform an SNMP operation using broadcast as the destination address that could be processed by an affected device that is configured with an SNMP server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to communicate to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Although an unauthenticated attacker could send UDP datagrams to the configured SNMP port, only an authenticated user can retrieve or modify data using SNMP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20319|2024-08-01T21:59:41.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20320|2024-08-01T21:59:42.846Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20320</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSH client feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco 8000 Series Routers and Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) 540 Series and 5700 Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are included with the SSH client CLI command. An attacker with low-privileged access to an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by issuing a crafted SSH client command to the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20320|2024-08-01T21:59:42.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20322|2024-08-01T21:59:41.959Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20322</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on Pseudowire interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20322|2024-08-01T21:59:41.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20327|2024-08-01T21:59:42.888Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20327</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the PPP over Ethernet (PPPoE) termination feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco ASR 9000 Series Aggregation Services Routers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the improper handling of malformed PPPoE packets that are received on a router that is running Broadband Network Gateway (BNG) functionality with PPPoE termination on a Lightspeed-based or Lightspeed-Plus-based line card. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted PPPoE packet to an affected line card interface that does not terminate PPPoE. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a DoS condition for PPPoE traffic across the router.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20327|2024-08-01T21:59:42.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20266|2024-08-01T21:52:31.683Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20266</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP version 4 (DHCPv4) server feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a crash of the dhcpd process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because certain DHCPv4 messages are improperly validated when they are processed by an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed DHCPv4 message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a crash of the dhcpd process. While the dhcpd process is restarting, which may take approximately two minutes, DHCPv4 server services are unavailable on the affected device. This could temporarily prevent network access to clients that join the network during that time period and rely on the DHCPv4 server of the affected device.
&#13; Notes: 
&#13; &#13; Only the dhcpd process crashes and eventually restarts automatically. The router does not reload.&#13; This vulnerability only applies to DHCPv4. DHCP version 6 (DHCPv6) is not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20266|2024-08-01T21:52:31.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20262|2024-08-01T21:52:31.788Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20262</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Copy Protocol (SCP) and SFTP feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to create or overwrite files in a system directory, which could lead to a denial of service (DoS) condition. The attacker would require valid user credentials to perform this attack.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper validation of SCP and SFTP CLI input parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and issuing SCP or SFTP CLI commands with specific parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to impact the functionality of the device, which could lead to a DoS condition. The device may need to be manually rebooted to recover.
&#13; Note: This vulnerability is exploitable only when a local user invokes SCP or SFTP commands at the Cisco IOS XR CLI. A local user with administrative privileges could exploit this vulnerability remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20262|2024-08-01T21:52:31.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-08-01T21:59:42.190Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-08-01T21:59:42.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20318|2024-08-01T21:59:41.382Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20318</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Layer 2 Ethernet services of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the line card network processor to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific Ethernet frames that are received on line cards that have the Layer 2 services feature enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific Ethernet frames through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ingress interface network processor to reset, resulting in a loss of traffic over the interfaces that are supported by the network processor. Multiple resets of the network processor would cause the line card to reset, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20318|2024-08-01T21:59:41.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20315|2024-08-01T21:59:41.535Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20315</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on MPLS interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20315|2024-08-01T21:59:41.535Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-12T03:55:19.039Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-12T03:55:19.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T14:40:37.931Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T14:40:37.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20318|2024-07-05T17:22:18.112Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20318</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Layer 2 Ethernet services of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the line card network processor to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific Ethernet frames that are received on line cards that have the Layer 2 services feature enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific Ethernet frames through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ingress interface network processor to reset, resulting in a loss of traffic over the interfaces that are supported by the network processor. Multiple resets of the network processor would cause the line card to reset, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20318|2024-07-05T17:22:18.112Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20319|2024-06-21T18:49:10.353Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20319</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured management plane protection policies and access the Simple Network Management Plane (SNMP) server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect UDP forwarding programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to perform an SNMP operation using broadcast as the destination address that could be processed by an affected device that is configured with an SNMP server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to communicate to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Although an unauthenticated attacker could send UDP datagrams to the configured SNMP port, only an authenticated user can retrieve or modify data using SNMP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20319|2024-06-21T18:49:10.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20266|2024-03-13T16:42:27.815Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20266</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP version 4 (DHCPv4) server feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a crash of the dhcpd process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because certain DHCPv4 messages are improperly validated when they are processed by an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed DHCPv4 message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a crash of the dhcpd process. While the dhcpd process is restarting, which may take approximately two minutes, DHCPv4 server services are unavailable on the affected device. This could temporarily prevent network access to clients that join the network during that time period and rely on the DHCPv4 server of the affected device.
&#13; Notes: 
&#13; &#13; Only the dhcpd process crashes and eventually restarts automatically. The router does not reload.&#13; This vulnerability only applies to DHCPv4. DHCP version 6 (DHCPv6) is not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20266|2024-03-13T16:42:27.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20319|2024-03-13T16:47:09.543Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20319</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured management plane protection policies and access the Simple Network Management Plane (SNMP) server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect UDP forwarding programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to perform an SNMP operation using broadcast as the destination address that could be processed by an affected device that is configured with an SNMP server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to communicate to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Although an unauthenticated attacker could send UDP datagrams to the configured SNMP port, only an authenticated user can retrieve or modify data using SNMP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20319|2024-03-13T16:47:09.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20315|2024-03-13T16:45:58.046Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20315</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on MPLS interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20315|2024-03-13T16:45:58.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20318|2024-03-13T16:46:24.113Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20318</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Layer 2 Ethernet services of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the line card network processor to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific Ethernet frames that are received on line cards that have the Layer 2 services feature enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific Ethernet frames through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ingress interface network processor to reset, resulting in a loss of traffic over the interfaces that are supported by the network processor. Multiple resets of the network processor would cause the line card to reset, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20318|2024-03-13T16:46:24.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20322|2024-03-13T16:43:53.196Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20322</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on Pseudowire interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20322|2024-03-13T16:43:53.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20262|2024-06-04T17:40:27.162Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20262</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Copy Protocol (SCP) and SFTP feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to create or overwrite files in a system directory, which could lead to a denial of service (DoS) condition. The attacker would require valid user credentials to perform this attack.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper validation of SCP and SFTP CLI input parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and issuing SCP or SFTP CLI commands with specific parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to impact the functionality of the device, which could lead to a DoS condition. The device may need to be manually rebooted to recover.
&#13; Note: This vulnerability is exploitable only when a local user invokes SCP or SFTP commands at the Cisco IOS XR CLI. A local user with administrative privileges could exploit this vulnerability remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20262|2024-06-04T17:40:27.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20327|2024-06-04T17:40:27.563Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20327</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the PPP over Ethernet (PPPoE) termination feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco ASR 9000 Series Aggregation Services Routers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the improper handling of malformed PPPoE packets that are received on a router that is running Broadband Network Gateway (BNG) functionality with PPPoE termination on a Lightspeed-based or Lightspeed-Plus-based line card. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted PPPoE packet to an affected line card interface that does not terminate PPPoE. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a DoS condition for PPPoE traffic across the router.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20327|2024-06-04T17:40:27.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20320|2024-03-13T16:41:52.488Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20320</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSH client feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco 8000 Series Routers and Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) 540 Series and 5700 Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are included with the SSH client CLI command. An attacker with low-privileged access to an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by issuing a crafted SSH client command to the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20320|2024-03-13T16:41:52.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20319|2024-07-02T16:26:46.466Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20319</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured management plane protection policies and access the Simple Network Management Plane (SNMP) server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect UDP forwarding programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to perform an SNMP operation using broadcast as the destination address that could be processed by an affected device that is configured with an SNMP server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to communicate to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Although an unauthenticated attacker could send UDP datagrams to the configured SNMP port, only an authenticated user can retrieve or modify data using SNMP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20319|2024-07-02T16:26:46.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-10T16:06:22.104Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-10T16:06:22.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T21:23:07.031Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T21:23:07.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20315|2024-07-19T17:25:44.385Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20315</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on MPLS interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20315|2024-07-19T17:25:44.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
