<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Extensible Operating System (FXOS)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20firepower%20extensible%20operating%20system%20%28fxos%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Extensible Operating System (FXOS)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:42:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1858|2024-09-16T20:22:15.411Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20extensible%20operating%20system%20%28fxos%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1858</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) input packet processor of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the SNMP application to leak system memory, which could cause an affected device to restart unexpectedly. The vulnerability is due to improper error handling when processing inbound SNMP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending multiple crafted SNMP packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the SNMP application to leak system memory because of an improperly handled error condition during packet processing. Over time, this memory leak could cause the SNMP application to restart multiple times, leading to a system-level restart and a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1858|2024-09-16T20:22:15.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 01:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3545|2024-09-16T19:50:44.911Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20extensible%20operating%20system%20%28fxos%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3545</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco FXOS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrative credentials to cause a buffer overflow condition. The vulnerability is due to incorrect bounds checking of values that are parsed from a specific file. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a crafted file that, when it is processed, may cause a stack-based buffer overflow. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system with root privileges. An attacker would need to have valid administrative credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3545|2024-09-16T19:50:44.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 02:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3169|2024-09-16T16:39:17.080Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20extensible%20operating%20system%20%28fxos%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3169</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco FXOS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with a privilege level of root on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a specific CLI command on the affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with root privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3169|2024-09-16T16:39:17.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 16:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3166|2024-09-16T16:32:51.091Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20extensible%20operating%20system%20%28fxos%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3166</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco FXOS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to read or write arbitrary files on the underlying operating system (OS). The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted arguments to a specific CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read or write to arbitrary files on the underlying OS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3166|2024-09-16T16:32:51.091Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 16:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12699|2024-09-16T19:52:32.139Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20extensible%20operating%20system%20%28fxos%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12699</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute commands on the underlying operating system (OS) with root privileges. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by including crafted arguments to specific CLI commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands on the underlying OS with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12699|2024-09-16T19:52:32.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
