<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20nx-os%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:21:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1783|2024-09-16T22:08:44.252Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1783</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator credentials to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with the privilege level of root. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a specific CLI command on the affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1783|2024-09-16T22:08:44.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 20:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1229|2024-09-16T21:56:39.860Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1229</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in ICMP Version 6 (ICMPv6) processing in Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a slow system memory leak, which over time could lead to a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper error handling when an IPv6-configured interface receives a specific type of ICMPv6 packet. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a sustained rate of crafted ICMPv6 packets to a local IPv6 address on a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a system memory leak in the ICMPv6 process on the device. As a result, the ICMPv6 process could run out of system memory and stop processing traffic. The device could then drop all ICMPv6 packets, causing traffic instability on the device. Restoring device functionality would require a device reboot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1229|2024-09-16T21:56:39.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 19:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1368|2024-09-16T18:33:33.478Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1368</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Unidirectional Link Detection (UDLD) feature of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to execute arbitrary code with administrative privileges or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted Cisco UDLD protocol packets to a directly connected, affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code with administrative privileges or cause the Cisco UDLD process to crash and restart multiple times, causing the affected device to reload and resulting in a DoS condition. Note: The UDLD feature is disabled by default, and the conditions to exploit this vulnerability are strict. The attacker needs full control of a directly connected device. That device must be connected over a port channel that has UDLD enabled. To trigger arbitrary code execution, both the UDLD-enabled port channel and specific system conditions must exist. In the absence of either the UDLD-enabled port channel or the system conditions, attempts to exploit this vulnerability will result in a DoS condition. It is possible, but highly unlikely, that an attacker could control the necessary conditions for exploitation. The CVSS score reflects this possibility. However, given the complexity of exploitation, Cisco has assigned a Medium Security Impact Rating (SIR) to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1368|2024-09-16T18:33:33.478Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 19:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1728|2024-09-16T21:57:48.859Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1728</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Configuration Validation functionality of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to run arbitrary commands at system boot time with the privileges of root. The vulnerability is due to a lack of proper validation of system files when the persistent configuration information is read from the file system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and overwriting the persistent configuration storage with malicious executable files. An exploit could allow the attacker to run arbitrary commands at system startup and those commands will run as the root user. The attacker must have valid administrative credentials for the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1728|2024-09-16T21:57:48.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 16:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1769|2024-09-16T22:30:44.056Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1769</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator credentials to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system of an attached line card with the privilege level of root. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a specific CLI command on the affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system of an attached line card with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1769|2024-09-16T22:30:44.056Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 19:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1767|2024-09-16T19:10:19.880Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1767</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of a specific CLI command for Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator credentials to cause a buffer overflow condition or perform command injection. This could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileges on the underlying operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a certain CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of the affected CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit these vulnerabilities. NX-OS versions prior to 8.3(1) are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1767|2024-09-16T19:10:19.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 18:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20624|2024-09-16T22:30:34.699Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20624</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Fabric Services over IP (CFSoIP) feature of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of incoming CFSoIP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted CFSoIP packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20624|2024-09-16T22:30:34.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1778|2024-09-16T20:12:08.177Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1778</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with the privilege level of root. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a specific CLI command on the affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1778|2024-09-16T20:12:08.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 19:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1587|2024-09-16T20:37:55.543Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1587</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the VXLAN Operation, Administration, and Maintenance (OAM) feature of Cisco NX-OS Software, known as NGOAM, could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper handling of specific packets with a Transparent Interconnection of Lots of Links (TRILL) OAM EtherType. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted packets, including the TRILL OAM EtherType of 0x8902, to a device that is part of a VXLAN Ethernet VPN (EVPN) fabric. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an affected device to experience high CPU usage and consume excessive system resources, which may result in overall control plane instability and cause the affected device to reload. Note: The NGOAM feature is disabled by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1587|2024-09-16T20:37:55.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 19:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1227|2024-09-16T16:27:43.675Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1227</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NX-API feature of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the NX-API on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the NX-API to follow a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privilege level of the affected user. The attacker could view and modify the device configuration. Note: The NX-API feature is disabled by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1227|2024-09-16T16:27:43.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 19:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1813|2024-09-16T22:02:19.521Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1813</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Image Signature Verification feature of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator-level credentials to install a malicious software image on an affected device. The vulnerability exists because software digital signatures are not properly verified during CLI command execution. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to install an unsigned software image on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1813|2024-09-16T22:02:19.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1361|2024-09-16T17:15:17.942Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of an internal file management service for Cisco Nexus 3000 Series Switches and Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Switches in standalone NX-OS mode that are running Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to create, delete, or overwrite arbitrary files with root privileges on the device. This vulnerability exists because TCP port 9075 is incorrectly configured to listen and respond to external connection requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted TCP packets to an IP address that is configured on a local interface on TCP port 9075. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to create, delete, or overwrite arbitrary files, including sensitive files that are related to the device configuration. For example, the attacker could add a user account without the device administrator knowing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1361|2024-09-16T17:15:17.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 19:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1774|2024-09-16T17:59:13.240Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1774</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1774|2024-09-16T17:59:13.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 19:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1967|2024-09-16T20:03:19.157Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1967</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Network Time Protocol (NTP) feature of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to excessive use of system resources when the affected device is logging a drop action for received MODE_PRIVATE (Mode 7) NTP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by flooding the device with a steady stream of Mode 7 NTP packets. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause high CPU and memory usage on the affected device, which could cause internal system processes to restart or cause the affected device to unexpectedly reload. Note: The NTP feature is enabled by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1967|2024-09-16T20:03:19.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 21:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3517|2024-09-16T18:24:48.482Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3517</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Fabric Services component of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated attacker to cause process crashes, which could result in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The attack vector is configuration dependent and could be remote or adjacent. For more information about the attack vector, see the Details section of this advisory. The vulnerability is due to insufficient error handling when the affected software parses Cisco Fabric Services messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious Cisco Fabric Services messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a reload of an affected device, which could result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3517|2024-09-16T18:24:48.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 15:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3165|2024-09-16T22:09:31.074Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3165</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) Message Digest 5 (MD5) authentication in Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass MD5 authentication and establish a BGP connection with the device. The vulnerability occurs because the BGP MD5 authentication is bypassed if the peer does not have MD5 authentication configured, the NX-OS device does have BGP MD5 authentication configured, and the NX-OS BGP virtual routing and forwarding (VRF) name is configured to be greater than 19 characters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to establish a BGP session with the NX-OS peer. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to establish a BGP session with the NX-OS device without MD5 authentication. The Cisco implementation of the BGP protocol accepts incoming BGP traffic only from explicitly configured peers. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must send the malicious packets over a TCP connection that appears to come from a trusted BGP peer. To do so, the attacker must obtain information about the BGP peers in the affected system&amp;rsquo;s trusted network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3165|2024-09-16T22:09:31.074Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 16:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1732|2024-09-16T22:55:29.879Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1732</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Remote Package Manager (RPM) subsystem of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator credentials to leverage a time-of-check, time-of-use (TOCTOU) race condition to corrupt local variables, which could lead to arbitrary command injection. The vulnerability is due to the lack of a proper locking mechanism on critical variables that need to stay static until used. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to an affected device and issuing a set of RPM-related CLI commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary command injection. The attacker would need administrator credentials for the targeted device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1732|2024-09-16T22:55:29.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 16:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1795|2024-09-16T16:32:55.121Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1795</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with the privilege level of root. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a specific CLI command on the affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1795|2024-09-16T16:32:55.121Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 20:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1791|2024-09-16T20:17:32.844Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1791</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator credentials to execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileges on the underlying operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1791|2024-09-16T20:17:32.844Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 20:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1591|2024-09-16T22:25:20.356Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1591</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the EtherChannel port subscription logic of Cisco Nexus 9500 Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass access control list (ACL) rules that are configured on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to oversubscription of resources that occurs when applying ACLs to port channel interfaces. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to access network resources that are protected by the ACL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access network resources that would be protected by the ACL that was applied on the port channel interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1591|2024-09-16T22:25:20.356Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 19:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1734|2024-09-16T16:58:10.911Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1734</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of a CLI diagnostic command in Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to view sensitive system files that should be restricted. The attacker could use this information to conduct additional reconnaissance attacks. The vulnerability is due to incomplete role-based access control (RBAC) verification. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and issuing a specific CLI diagnostic command with crafted user-input parameters. An exploit could allow the attacker to perform an arbitrary read of a file on the device, and the file may contain sensitive information. The attacker needs valid device credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1734|2024-09-16T16:58:10.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 19:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1726|2024-09-16T16:39:15.111Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1726</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access internal services that should be restricted on an affected device, such as the NX-API. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a certain CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument to the affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass intended restrictions and access internal services of the device. An attacker would need valid device credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1726|2024-09-16T16:39:15.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 16:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1735|2024-09-16T21:09:08.636Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1735</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileges on the underlying operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid user credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1735|2024-09-16T21:09:08.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 18:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1780|2024-09-16T16:34:04.695Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1780</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator credentials to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device with elevated privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability. NX-OS versions prior to 8.3(1) are affected. NX-OS versions prior to 8.3(1) are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1780|2024-09-16T16:34:04.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1779|2024-09-16T18:08:07.250Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1779</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device with elevated privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid device credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1779|2024-09-16T18:08:07.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 19:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1775|2024-09-16T21:02:37.443Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1775</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1775|2024-09-16T21:02:37.443Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 19:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3398|2024-09-16T22:36:12.195Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3398</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) Multicast VPN (MVPN) implementation of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a BGP session to repeatedly reset, causing a partial denial of service (DoS) condition due to the BGP session being down. The vulnerability is due to incorrect parsing of a specific type of BGP MVPN update message. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending this BGP MVPN update message to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the BGP peer connections to reset, which could lead to BGP route instability and impact traffic. The incoming BGP MVPN update message is valid but is parsed incorrectly by the NX-OS device, which could send a corrupted BGP update to the configured BGP peer. Note: The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP traffic from only explicitly configured peers. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must send a specific BGP MVPN update message over an established TCP connection that appears to come from a trusted BGP peer. To do so, the attacker must obtain information about the BGP peers in the trusted network of the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3398|2024-09-16T22:36:12.195Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1808|2024-09-16T16:37:43.267Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1808</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Image Signature Verification feature of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator-level credentials to install a malicious software patch on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper verification of digital signatures for patch images. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by loading an unsigned software patch on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to boot a malicious software patch image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1808|2024-09-16T16:37:43.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1367|2024-09-16T20:38:10.175Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1367</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Protocol Independent Multicast (PIM) feature of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted PIM packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a traffic loop, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1367|2024-09-16T20:38:10.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 19:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3394|2024-09-16T17:48:14.615Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3394</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Enable Secret feature of Cisco Nexus 3000 Series Switches and Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Switches in standalone NX-OS mode could allow an authenticated, local attacker to issue the enable command and get full administrative privileges. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have valid credentials for the affected device. The vulnerability is due to a logic error in the implementation of the enable command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to the device and issuing the enable command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain full administrative privileges without using the enable password. Note: The Enable Secret feature is disabled by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3394|2024-09-16T17:48:14.615Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1809|2024-09-16T19:31:11.155Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1809</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Image Signature Verification feature of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator-level credentials to install a malicious software patch on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper verification of digital signatures for patch images. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting an unsigned software patch to bypass signature checks and loading it on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to boot a malicious software patch image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1809|2024-09-16T19:31:11.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1810|2024-09-16T20:43:08.057Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1810</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Image Signature Verification feature used in an NX-OS CLI command in Cisco Nexus 3000 Series and 9000 Series Switches could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator-level credentials to install a malicious software image on an affected device. The vulnerability exists because software digital signatures are not properly verified during CLI command execution. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to install an unsigned software image on an affected device. Note: If the device has not been patched for the vulnerability previously disclosed in the Cisco Security Advisory cisco-sa-20190306-nxos-sig-verif, a successful exploit could allow the attacker to boot a malicious software image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1810|2024-09-16T20:43:08.057Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20625|2024-09-16T22:03:25.867Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20625</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Discovery Protocol service of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the service to restart, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper handling of Cisco Discovery Protocol messages that are processed by the Cisco Discovery Protocol service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of malicious Cisco Discovery Protocol messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Cisco Discovery Protocol service to fail and restart. In rare conditions, repeated failures of the process could occur, which could cause the entire device to restart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20625|2024-09-16T22:03:25.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20446|2024-08-28T18:49:32.927Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20446</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCPv6 relay agent of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper handling of specific fields in a DHCPv6 RELAY-REPLY message. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCPv6 packet to any IPv6 address that is configured on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the dhcp_snoop process to crash and restart multiple times, causing the affected device to reload and resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20446|2024-08-28T18:49:32.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 16:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20285|2024-08-28T16:37:27.149Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20285</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Python interpreter of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to escape the Python sandbox and gain unauthorized access to the underlying operating system of the device.

The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating specific functions within the Python interpreter. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to escape the Python sandbox and execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of the authenticated user.&amp;nbsp;
Note: An attacker must be authenticated with Python execution privileges to exploit these vulnerabilities. For more information regarding Python execution privileges, see product-specific documentation, such as the  section of the Cisco Nexus 9000 Series NX-OS Programmability Guide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20285|2024-08-28T16:37:27.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 16:37:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20413|2024-08-28T16:27:29.365Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20413</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with privileges to access the Bash shell to elevate privileges to network-admin on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient security restrictions when executing application arguments from the Bash shell. An attacker with privileges to access the Bash shell could exploit this vulnerability by executing crafted commands on the underlying operating system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to create new users with the privileges of network-admin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20413|2024-08-28T16:27:29.365Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 16:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20289|2024-08-28T16:31:23.856Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20289</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device.&amp;nbsp;

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments for a specific CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of the affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of the currently logged-in user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20289|2024-08-28T16:31:23.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 16:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20411|2024-08-28T16:27:38.420Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20411</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with privileges to access the Bash shell to&amp;nbsp;execute arbitrary code as root on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient security restrictions when executing commands from the Bash shell. An attacker with privileges to access the Bash shell could exploit this vulnerability by executing a specific crafted command on the underlying operating system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code with the privileges of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20411|2024-08-28T16:27:38.420Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 16:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20286|2024-08-28T16:37:17.319Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20286</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Python interpreter of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to escape the Python sandbox and gain unauthorized access to the underlying operating system of the device.

The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating specific functions within the Python interpreter. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to escape the Python sandbox and execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of the authenticated user.&amp;nbsp;
Note: An attacker must be authenticated with Python execution privileges to exploit these vulnerabilities. For more information regarding Python execution privileges, see product-specific documentation, such as the  section of the Cisco Nexus 9000 Series NX-OS Programmability Guide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20286|2024-08-28T16:37:17.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 16:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20446|2024-08-28T16:31:32.514Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20446</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCPv6 relay agent of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper handling of specific fields in a DHCPv6 RELAY-REPLY message. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCPv6 packet to any IPv6 address that is configured on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the dhcp_snoop process to crash and restart multiple times, causing the affected device to reload and resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20446|2024-08-28T16:31:32.514Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 16:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20284|2024-08-28T16:37:35.281Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20284</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Python interpreter of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to escape the Python sandbox and gain unauthorized access to the underlying operating system of the device.

The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating specific functions within the Python interpreter. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to escape the Python sandbox and execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of the authenticated user.&amp;nbsp;
Note: An attacker must be authenticated with Python execution privileges to exploit these vulnerabilities. For more information regarding Python execution privileges, see product-specific documentation, such as the  section of the Cisco Nexus 9000 Series NX-OS Programmability Guide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20284|2024-08-28T16:37:35.281Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 16:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T20:40:44.265Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T20:40:44.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T15:08:18.404Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T15:08:18.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-01T18:57:52.266Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-01T18:57:52.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-01T16:11:44.028Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-01T16:11:44.028Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T03:55:37.582Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T03:55:37.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T16:20:21.935Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T16:20:21.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-08-01T21:59:42.407Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-08-01T21:59:42.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20284|2024-08-28T17:19:17.361Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20284</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Python interpreter of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to escape the Python sandbox and gain unauthorized access to the underlying operating system of the device.

The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating specific functions within the Python interpreter. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to escape the Python sandbox and execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of the authenticated user.&amp;nbsp;
Note: An attacker must be authenticated with Python execution privileges to exploit these vulnerabilities. For more information regarding Python execution privileges, see product-specific documentation, such as the  section of the Cisco Nexus 9000 Series NX-OS Programmability Guide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20284|2024-08-28T17:19:17.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 16:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20286|2024-08-28T17:23:56.426Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20286</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Python interpreter of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to escape the Python sandbox and gain unauthorized access to the underlying operating system of the device.

The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating specific functions within the Python interpreter. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to escape the Python sandbox and execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of the authenticated user.&amp;nbsp;
Note: An attacker must be authenticated with Python execution privileges to exploit these vulnerabilities. For more information regarding Python execution privileges, see product-specific documentation, such as the  section of the Cisco Nexus 9000 Series NX-OS Programmability Guide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20286|2024-08-28T17:23:56.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 16:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20411|2024-08-28T17:45:10.000Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20411</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with privileges to access the Bash shell to&amp;nbsp;execute arbitrary code as root on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient security restrictions when executing commands from the Bash shell. An attacker with privileges to access the Bash shell could exploit this vulnerability by executing a specific crafted command on the underlying operating system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code with the privileges of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20411|2024-08-28T17:45:10.000Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 16:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20289|2024-08-28T17:24:18.101Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20289</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device.&amp;nbsp;

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments for a specific CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of the affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of the currently logged-in user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20289|2024-08-28T17:24:18.101Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 16:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20413|2024-08-28T17:46:26.021Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20413</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with privileges to access the Bash shell to elevate privileges to network-admin on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient security restrictions when executing application arguments from the Bash shell. An attacker with privileges to access the Bash shell could exploit this vulnerability by executing crafted commands on the underlying operating system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to create new users with the privileges of network-admin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20413|2024-08-28T17:46:26.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 16:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20285|2024-08-28T17:19:57.207Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20285</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Python interpreter of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to escape the Python sandbox and gain unauthorized access to the underlying operating system of the device.

The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating specific functions within the Python interpreter. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to escape the Python sandbox and execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of the authenticated user.&amp;nbsp;
Note: An attacker must be authenticated with Python execution privileges to exploit these vulnerabilities. For more information regarding Python execution privileges, see product-specific documentation, such as the  section of the Cisco Nexus 9000 Series NX-OS Programmability Guide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20285|2024-08-28T17:19:57.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 16:37:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20411|2024-08-30T03:56:02.446Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20411</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with privileges to access the Bash shell to&amp;nbsp;execute arbitrary code as root on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient security restrictions when executing commands from the Bash shell. An attacker with privileges to access the Bash shell could exploit this vulnerability by executing a specific crafted command on the underlying operating system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code with the privileges of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20411|2024-08-30T03:56:02.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 16:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20413|2024-08-30T03:56:03.888Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20413</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with privileges to access the Bash shell to elevate privileges to network-admin on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient security restrictions when executing application arguments from the Bash shell. An attacker with privileges to access the Bash shell could exploit this vulnerability by executing crafted commands on the underlying operating system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to create new users with the privileges of network-admin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20413|2024-08-30T03:56:03.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 16:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
