<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Meeting Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20meeting%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Meeting Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:42:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1676|2024-09-16T18:40:07.340Z -- cisco -- cisco%20meeting%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1676</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) call processing of Cisco Meeting Server (CMS) software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of the Cisco Meeting Server. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of Session Description Protocol (SDP) messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SDP message to the CMS call bridge. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the CMS to reload, causing a DoS condition for all connected clients. Versions prior to 2.3.9 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1676|2024-09-16T18:40:07.340Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15446|2024-09-16T20:46:52.465Z -- cisco -- cisco%20meeting%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15446</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Meeting Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain access to sensitive information. The vulnerability is due to improper protections on data that is returned from user meeting requests when the Guest access via ID and passcode option is set to Legacy mode. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending meeting requests to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to determine the values of meeting room unique identifiers, possibly allowing the attacker to conduct further exploits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15446|2024-09-16T20:46:52.465Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1623|2024-09-16T18:13:50.594Z -- cisco -- cisco%20meeting%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1623</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI configuration shell of Cisco Meeting Server could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject arbitrary commands as the root user. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation during the execution of a vulnerable CLI command. An attacker with administrator-level credentials could exploit this vulnerability by injecting crafted arguments during command execution. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary code execution as root on an affected product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1623|2024-09-16T18:13:50.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 02:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
