<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 11:20:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15388|2024-08-05T09:54:02.601Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15388</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the WebVPN login process of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause increased CPU utilization on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to excessive processing load for existing WebVPN login operations. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending multiple WebVPN login requests to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to increase CPU load on the device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15388|2024-08-05T09:54:02.601Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15454|2024-08-05T09:54:03.520Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15454</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) inspection engine of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload or trigger high CPU, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of SIP traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending SIP requests designed to specifically trigger this issue at a high rate across an affected device. Software updates that address this vulnerability are not yet available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15454|2024-08-05T09:54:03.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0472|2024-08-05T03:28:10.859Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0472</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPsec driver code of multiple Cisco IOS XE Software platforms and the Cisco ASA 5500-X Series Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload. The vulnerability is due to improper processing of malformed IPsec Authentication Header (AH) or Encapsulating Security Payload (ESP) packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malformed IPsec packets to be processed by an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause a reload of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0472|2024-08-05T03:28:10.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15992|2024-08-05T01:03:32.832Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15992</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the Lua interpreter integrated in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the underlying Linux operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient restrictions on the allowed Lua function calls within the context of user-supplied Lua scripts. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to trigger a heap overflow condition and execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the underlying Linux operating system of an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15992|2024-08-05T01:03:32.832Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15383|2024-08-05T09:54:02.337Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15383</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the cryptographic hardware accelerator driver of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload, resulting in a temporary denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability exists because the affected devices have a limited amount of Direct Memory Access (DMA) memory and the affected software improperly handles resources in low-memory conditions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a sustained, high rate of malicious traffic to an affected device to exhaust memory on the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust DMA memory on the affected device, which could cause the device to reload and result in a temporary DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15383|2024-08-05T09:54:02.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15465|2024-08-05T09:54:03.481Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15465</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the authorization subsystem of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow an authenticated, but unprivileged (levels 0 and 1), remote attacker to perform privileged actions by using the web management interface. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of user privileges when using the web management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific HTTP requests via HTTPS to an affected device as an unprivileged user. An exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve files (including the running configuration) from the device or to upload and replace software images on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15465|2024-08-05T09:54:03.481Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15256|2024-08-05T00:42:03.653Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15256</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Internet Key Exchange version 1 (IKEv1) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to improper management of system memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious IKEv1 traffic to an affected device. The attacker does not need valid credentials to authenticate the VPN session, nor does the attacker's source address need to match a peer statement in the crypto map applied to the ingress interface of the affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust system memory resources, leading to a reload of an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15256|2024-08-05T00:42:03.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15398|2024-08-05T09:54:03.333Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15398</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the per-user-override feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass an access control list (ACL) that is configured for an interface of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to errors that could occur when the affected software constructs and applies per-user-override rules. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to a network through an affected device that has a vulnerable configuration. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources that are behind the affected device and would typically be protected by the interface ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15398|2024-08-05T09:54:03.333Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15397|2024-08-05T09:54:03.022Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15397</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of Traffic Flow Confidentiality (TFC) over IPsec functionality in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to restart unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to an error that may occur if the affected software renegotiates the encryption key for an IPsec tunnel when certain TFC traffic is in flight. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious stream of TFC traffic through an established IPsec tunnel on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a daemon process on the affected device to crash, which could cause the device to crash and result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15397|2024-08-05T09:54:03.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15399|2024-08-05T09:54:02.914Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TCP syslog module of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to exhaust the 1550-byte buffers on an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to a missing boundary check in an internal function. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing a man-in-the-middle position between an affected device and its configured TCP syslog server and then maliciously modifying the TCP header in segments that are sent from the syslog server to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust buffer on the affected device and cause all TCP-based features to stop functioning, resulting in a DoS condition. The affected TCP-based features include AnyConnect SSL VPN, clientless SSL VPN, and management connections such as Secure Shell (SSH), Telnet, and HTTPS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15399|2024-08-05T09:54:02.914Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20353|2024-08-01T21:59:41.487Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20353</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the management and VPN web servers for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incomplete error checking when parsing an HTTP header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to a targeted web server on a device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition when the device reloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20353|2024-08-01T21:59:41.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20358|2024-08-01T21:59:42.299Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20358</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) restore functionality that is available in Cisco ASA Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because the contents of a backup file are improperly sanitized at restore time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20358|2024-08-01T21:59:42.299Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20293|2024-08-01T21:59:41.290Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the activation of an access control list (ACL) on Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the protection that is offered by a configured ACL on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an ACL changes from inactive to active in the running configuration of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device that should be denied by the configured ACL. The reverse condition is also true—traffic that should be permitted could be denied by the configured ACL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL protections on the affected device, allowing the attacker to access trusted networks that the device might be protecting. Note: This vulnerability applies to both IPv4 and IPv6 traffic as well as dual-stack ACL configurations in which both IPv4 and IPv6 ACLs are configured on an interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20293|2024-08-01T21:59:41.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20359|2024-08-01T21:59:42.379Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20359</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a legacy capability that allowed for the preloading of VPN clients and plug-ins and that has been available in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of a file when it is read from system flash memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by copying a crafted file to the disk0: file system of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected device after the next reload of the device, which could alter system behavior. Because the injected code could persist across device reboots, Cisco has raised the Security Impact Rating (SIR) of this advisory from Medium to High.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20359|2024-08-01T21:59:42.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20355|2024-08-01T21:59:42.284Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20355</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of SAML 2.0 single sign-on (SSO) for remote access VPN services in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to successfully establish a VPN session on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper separation of authorization domains when using SAML authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using valid credentials to successfully authenticate using their designated connection profile (tunnel group), intercepting the SAML SSO token that is sent back from the Cisco ASA device, and then submitting the same SAML SSO token to a different tunnel group for authentication. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to establish a remote access VPN session using a connection profile that they are not authorized to use and connect to secured networks behind the affected device that they are not authorized to access. For successful exploitation, the attacker must have valid remote access VPN user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20355|2024-08-01T21:59:42.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20353|2024-06-04T17:40:15.708Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20353</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the management and VPN web servers for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incomplete error checking when parsing an HTTP header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to a targeted web server on a device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition when the device reloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20353|2024-06-04T17:40:15.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20359|2024-06-04T17:40:02.581Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20359</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a legacy capability that allowed for the preloading of VPN clients and plug-ins and that has been available in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of a file when it is read from system flash memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by copying a crafted file to the disk0: file system of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected device after the next reload of the device, which could alter system behavior. Because the injected code could persist across device reboots, Cisco has raised the Security Impact Rating (SIR) of this advisory from Medium to High.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20359|2024-06-04T17:40:02.581Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20355|2024-06-04T17:39:58.380Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20355</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of SAML 2.0 single sign-on (SSO) for remote access VPN services in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to successfully establish a VPN session on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper separation of authorization domains when using SAML authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using valid credentials to successfully authenticate using their designated connection profile (tunnel group), intercepting the SAML SSO token that is sent back from the Cisco ASA device, and then submitting the same SAML SSO token to a different tunnel group for authentication. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to establish a remote access VPN session using a connection profile that they are not authorized to use and connect to secured networks behind the affected device that they are not authorized to access. For successful exploitation, the attacker must have valid remote access VPN user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20355|2024-06-04T17:39:58.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20293|2024-06-04T17:39:54.684Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the activation of an access control list (ACL) on Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the protection that is offered by a configured ACL on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an ACL changes from inactive to active in the running configuration of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device that should be denied by the configured ACL. The reverse condition is also true—traffic that should be permitted could be denied by the configured ACL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL protections on the affected device, allowing the attacker to access trusted networks that the device might be protecting. Note: This vulnerability applies to both IPv4 and IPv6 traffic as well as dual-stack ACL configurations in which both IPv4 and IPv6 ACLs are configured on an interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20293|2024-06-04T17:39:54.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20358|2024-04-24T19:38:23.689Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20358</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) restore functionality that is available in Cisco ASA Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because the contents of a backup file are improperly sanitized at restore time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20358|2024-04-24T19:38:23.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20293|2024-07-02T15:36:56.903Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the activation of an access control list (ACL) on Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the protection that is offered by a configured ACL on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an ACL changes from inactive to active in the running configuration of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device that should be denied by the configured ACL. The reverse condition is also true—traffic that should be permitted could be denied by the configured ACL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL protections on the affected device, allowing the attacker to access trusted networks that the device might be protecting. Note: This vulnerability applies to both IPv4 and IPv6 traffic as well as dual-stack ACL configurations in which both IPv4 and IPv6 ACLs are configured on an interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20293|2024-07-02T15:36:56.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
