<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN vManage</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN vManage</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:24:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20261|2024-08-02T09:05:36.960Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20261</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco Catalyst SD-WAN Manager could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to retrieve arbitrary files from an affected system.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of parameters that are sent to the web UI. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to Cisco Catalyst SD-WAN Manager and issuing crafted requests using the web UI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain arbitrary files from the underlying Linux file system of an affected system. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must be an authenticated user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20261|2024-08-02T09:05:36.960Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 16:27:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20098|2024-08-02T08:57:35.560Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20098</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco SDWAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to delete arbitrary files.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper filtering of directory traversal character sequences within system commands. An attacker with administrative privileges could exploit this vulnerability by running a system command containing directory traversal character sequences to target an arbitrary file. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files from the system, including files owned by root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20098|2024-08-02T08:57:35.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20253|2024-08-02T09:05:35.890Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20253</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the command line interface (cli) management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage could allow an authenticated, local attacker to bypass authorization and allow the attacker to roll back the configuration on vManage controllers and edge router device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper access control in the cli-management interface of an affected system. An attacker with low-privilege (read only) access to the cli could exploit this vulnerability by sending a request to roll back the configuration on for other controller and devices managed by an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to to roll back the configuration on for other controller and devices managed by an affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20253|2024-08-02T09:05:35.890Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20034|2024-08-02T08:57:35.874Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20034</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Elasticsearch database used in the of Cisco SD-WAN vManage software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access the Elasticsearch configuration database of an affected device with the privileges of the elasticsearch user.&#13;
&#13; These vulnerability is due to the presence of a static username and password configured on the vManage. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to a reachable vManage on port 9200. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view the Elasticsearch database content.&#13;
&#13;   There are workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20034|2024-08-02T08:57:35.874Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20214|2024-08-02T09:05:36.165Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20214</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the request authentication validation for the REST API of Cisco SD-WAN vManage software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain read permissions or limited write permissions to the configuration of an affected Cisco SD-WAN vManage instance.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient request validation when using the REST API feature. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted API request to an affected vManage instance. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve information from and send information to the configuration of the affected Cisco vManage instance. This vulnerability only affects the REST API and does not affect the web-based management interface or the CLI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20214|2024-08-02T09:05:36.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 21:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20252|2024-08-02T09:05:36.846Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20252</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) APIs of Cisco Catalyst SD-WAN Manager Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain unauthorized access to the application as an arbitrary user.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper authentication checks for SAML APIs. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending requests directly to the SAML API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to generate an authorization token sufficient to gain access to the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20252|2024-08-02T09:05:36.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20113|2024-08-02T08:57:35.713Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20113</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privilege level of the affected user. These actions could include modifying the system configuration and deleting accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20113|2024-08-02T08:57:35.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20254|2024-08-02T09:05:36.889Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20254</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the session management system of the Cisco Catalyst SD-WAN Manager multi-tenant feature could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to access another tenant that is being managed by the same Cisco Catalyst SD-WAN Manager instance. This vulnerability requires the multi-tenant feature to be enabled.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient user session management within the Cisco Catalyst SD-WAN Manager system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain unauthorized access to information about another tenant, make configuration changes, or possibly take a tenant offline causing a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20254|2024-08-02T09:05:36.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20179|2024-08-02T09:05:35.783Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20179</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Catalyst SD-WAN Manager, formerly Cisco SD-WAN vManage, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject HTML content.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied data in element fields. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting malicious content within requests and persuading a user to view a page that contains injected content. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify pages within the web-based management interface, possibly leading to further browser-based attacks against users of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20179|2024-08-02T09:05:35.783Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
