<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XR Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20xr%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XR Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 11:20:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20049|2024-08-02T08:57:35.607Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20049</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the bidirectional forwarding detection (BFD) hardware offload feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco ASR 9000 Series Aggregation Services Routers, ASR 9902 Compact High-Performance Routers, and ASR 9903 Compact High-Performance Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a line card to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of malformed BFD packets that are received on line cards where the BFD hardware offload feature is enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPv4 BFD packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause line card exceptions or a hard reset, resulting in loss of traffic over that line card while the line card reloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20049|2024-08-02T08:57:35.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20191|2024-08-02T09:05:35.459Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20191</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on MPLS interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incomplete support for this feature. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass an ACL on the affected device.&#13;
&#13;   There are workarounds that address this vulnerability.&#13;
&#13;   &#13;
&#13; &#13; This advisory is part of the September 2023 release of the Cisco IOS XR Software Security Advisory Bundled Publication. For a complete list of the advisories and links to them, see Cisco Event Response: September 2023 Semiannual Cisco IOS XR Software Security Advisory Bundled Publication .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20191|2024-08-02T09:05:35.459Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 16:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20190|2024-08-02T09:05:35.387Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20190</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the classic access control list (ACL) compression feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the protection that is offered by a configured ACL on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect destination address range encoding in the compression module of an ACL that is applied to an interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device that should be denied by the configured ACL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL protections on the affected device, allowing the attacker to access trusted networks that the device might be protecting.&#13;
&#13;   There are workarounds that address this vulnerability.&#13;
&#13;   &#13;
&#13; &#13; This advisory is part of the September 2023 release of the Cisco IOS XR Software Security Advisory Bundled Publication. For a complete list of the advisories and links to them, see Cisco Event Response: September 2023 Semiannual Cisco IOS XR Software Security Advisory Bundled Publication .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20190|2024-08-02T09:05:35.387Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 16:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20064|2024-08-02T08:57:35.558Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20064</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the GRand Unified Bootloader (GRUB) for Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated attacker with physical access to the device to view sensitive files on the console using the GRUB bootloader command line. This vulnerability is due to the inclusion of unnecessary commands within the GRUB environment that allow sensitive files to be viewed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by being connected to the console port of the Cisco IOS XR device when the device is power-cycled. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view sensitive files that could be used to conduct additional attacks against the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20064|2024-08-02T08:57:35.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20135|2024-08-02T08:57:36.157Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20135</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco IOS XR Software image verification checks could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a time-of-check, time-of-use (TOCTOU) race condition when an install query regarding an ISO image is performed during an install operation that uses an ISO image. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by modifying an ISO image and then carrying out install requests in parallel. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20135|2024-08-02T08:57:36.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 16:38:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20233|2024-08-02T09:05:36.620Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20233</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Connectivity Fault Management (CFM) feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of invalid continuity check messages (CCMs). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted CCMs to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the CFM service to crash when a user displays information about maintenance end points (MEPs) for peer MEPs on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20233|2024-08-02T09:05:36.620Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 16:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20236|2024-08-02T09:05:35.905Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20236</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the iPXE boot function of Cisco IOS XR software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to install an unverified software image on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient image verification. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the boot parameters for image verification during the iPXE boot process on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to boot an unverified software image on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20236|2024-08-02T09:05:35.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 16:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20315|2024-07-19T17:25:44.385Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20315</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on MPLS interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20315|2024-07-19T17:25:44.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T21:23:07.031Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T21:23:07.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-10T16:06:22.104Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-10T16:06:22.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20319|2024-07-02T16:26:46.466Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20319</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured management plane protection policies and access the Simple Network Management Plane (SNMP) server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect UDP forwarding programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to perform an SNMP operation using broadcast as the destination address that could be processed by an affected device that is configured with an SNMP server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to communicate to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Although an unauthenticated attacker could send UDP datagrams to the configured SNMP port, only an authenticated user can retrieve or modify data using SNMP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20319|2024-07-02T16:26:46.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20320|2024-03-13T16:41:52.488Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20320</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSH client feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco 8000 Series Routers and Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) 540 Series and 5700 Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are included with the SSH client CLI command. An attacker with low-privileged access to an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by issuing a crafted SSH client command to the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20320|2024-03-13T16:41:52.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20327|2024-06-04T17:40:27.563Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20327</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the PPP over Ethernet (PPPoE) termination feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco ASR 9000 Series Aggregation Services Routers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the improper handling of malformed PPPoE packets that are received on a router that is running Broadband Network Gateway (BNG) functionality with PPPoE termination on a Lightspeed-based or Lightspeed-Plus-based line card. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted PPPoE packet to an affected line card interface that does not terminate PPPoE. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a DoS condition for PPPoE traffic across the router.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20327|2024-06-04T17:40:27.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20262|2024-06-04T17:40:27.162Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20262</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Copy Protocol (SCP) and SFTP feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to create or overwrite files in a system directory, which could lead to a denial of service (DoS) condition. The attacker would require valid user credentials to perform this attack.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper validation of SCP and SFTP CLI input parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and issuing SCP or SFTP CLI commands with specific parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to impact the functionality of the device, which could lead to a DoS condition. The device may need to be manually rebooted to recover.
&#13; Note: This vulnerability is exploitable only when a local user invokes SCP or SFTP commands at the Cisco IOS XR CLI. A local user with administrative privileges could exploit this vulnerability remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20262|2024-06-04T17:40:27.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20322|2024-03-13T16:43:53.196Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20322</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on Pseudowire interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20322|2024-03-13T16:43:53.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20318|2024-03-13T16:46:24.113Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20318</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Layer 2 Ethernet services of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the line card network processor to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific Ethernet frames that are received on line cards that have the Layer 2 services feature enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific Ethernet frames through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ingress interface network processor to reset, resulting in a loss of traffic over the interfaces that are supported by the network processor. Multiple resets of the network processor would cause the line card to reset, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20318|2024-03-13T16:46:24.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20315|2024-03-13T16:45:58.046Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20315</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on MPLS interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20315|2024-03-13T16:45:58.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20319|2024-03-13T16:47:09.543Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20319</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured management plane protection policies and access the Simple Network Management Plane (SNMP) server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect UDP forwarding programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to perform an SNMP operation using broadcast as the destination address that could be processed by an affected device that is configured with an SNMP server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to communicate to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Although an unauthenticated attacker could send UDP datagrams to the configured SNMP port, only an authenticated user can retrieve or modify data using SNMP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20319|2024-03-13T16:47:09.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20266|2024-03-13T16:42:27.815Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20266</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP version 4 (DHCPv4) server feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a crash of the dhcpd process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because certain DHCPv4 messages are improperly validated when they are processed by an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed DHCPv4 message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a crash of the dhcpd process. While the dhcpd process is restarting, which may take approximately two minutes, DHCPv4 server services are unavailable on the affected device. This could temporarily prevent network access to clients that join the network during that time period and rely on the DHCPv4 server of the affected device.
&#13; Notes: 
&#13; &#13; Only the dhcpd process crashes and eventually restarts automatically. The router does not reload.&#13; This vulnerability only applies to DHCPv4. DHCP version 6 (DHCPv6) is not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20266|2024-03-13T16:42:27.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20319|2024-06-21T18:49:10.353Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20319</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured management plane protection policies and access the Simple Network Management Plane (SNMP) server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect UDP forwarding programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to perform an SNMP operation using broadcast as the destination address that could be processed by an affected device that is configured with an SNMP server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to communicate to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Although an unauthenticated attacker could send UDP datagrams to the configured SNMP port, only an authenticated user can retrieve or modify data using SNMP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20319|2024-06-21T18:49:10.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20318|2024-07-05T17:22:18.112Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20318</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Layer 2 Ethernet services of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the line card network processor to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific Ethernet frames that are received on line cards that have the Layer 2 services feature enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific Ethernet frames through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ingress interface network processor to reset, resulting in a loss of traffic over the interfaces that are supported by the network processor. Multiple resets of the network processor would cause the line card to reset, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20318|2024-07-05T17:22:18.112Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T14:40:37.931Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T14:40:37.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-12T03:55:19.039Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-12T03:55:19.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20315|2024-08-01T21:59:41.535Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20315</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on MPLS interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20315|2024-08-01T21:59:41.535Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20318|2024-08-01T21:59:41.382Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20318</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Layer 2 Ethernet services of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the line card network processor to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific Ethernet frames that are received on line cards that have the Layer 2 services feature enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific Ethernet frames through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ingress interface network processor to reset, resulting in a loss of traffic over the interfaces that are supported by the network processor. Multiple resets of the network processor would cause the line card to reset, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20318|2024-08-01T21:59:41.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-08-01T21:59:42.190Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-08-01T21:59:42.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20262|2024-08-01T21:52:31.788Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20262</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Copy Protocol (SCP) and SFTP feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to create or overwrite files in a system directory, which could lead to a denial of service (DoS) condition. The attacker would require valid user credentials to perform this attack.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper validation of SCP and SFTP CLI input parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and issuing SCP or SFTP CLI commands with specific parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to impact the functionality of the device, which could lead to a DoS condition. The device may need to be manually rebooted to recover.
&#13; Note: This vulnerability is exploitable only when a local user invokes SCP or SFTP commands at the Cisco IOS XR CLI. A local user with administrative privileges could exploit this vulnerability remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20262|2024-08-01T21:52:31.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20266|2024-08-01T21:52:31.683Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20266</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP version 4 (DHCPv4) server feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a crash of the dhcpd process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because certain DHCPv4 messages are improperly validated when they are processed by an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed DHCPv4 message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a crash of the dhcpd process. While the dhcpd process is restarting, which may take approximately two minutes, DHCPv4 server services are unavailable on the affected device. This could temporarily prevent network access to clients that join the network during that time period and rely on the DHCPv4 server of the affected device.
&#13; Notes: 
&#13; &#13; Only the dhcpd process crashes and eventually restarts automatically. The router does not reload.&#13; This vulnerability only applies to DHCPv4. DHCP version 6 (DHCPv6) is not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20266|2024-08-01T21:52:31.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20327|2024-08-01T21:59:42.888Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20327</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the PPP over Ethernet (PPPoE) termination feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco ASR 9000 Series Aggregation Services Routers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the improper handling of malformed PPPoE packets that are received on a router that is running Broadband Network Gateway (BNG) functionality with PPPoE termination on a Lightspeed-based or Lightspeed-Plus-based line card. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted PPPoE packet to an affected line card interface that does not terminate PPPoE. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a DoS condition for PPPoE traffic across the router.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20327|2024-08-01T21:59:42.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20322|2024-08-01T21:59:41.959Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20322</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on Pseudowire interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20322|2024-08-01T21:59:41.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20320|2024-08-01T21:59:42.846Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20320</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSH client feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco 8000 Series Routers and Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) 540 Series and 5700 Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are included with the SSH client CLI command. An attacker with low-privileged access to an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by issuing a crafted SSH client command to the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20320|2024-08-01T21:59:42.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20319|2024-08-01T21:59:41.556Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20319</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured management plane protection policies and access the Simple Network Management Plane (SNMP) server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect UDP forwarding programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to perform an SNMP operation using broadcast as the destination address that could be processed by an affected device that is configured with an SNMP server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to communicate to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Although an unauthenticated attacker could send UDP datagrams to the configured SNMP port, only an authenticated user can retrieve or modify data using SNMP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20319|2024-08-01T21:59:41.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
