<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software for Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches ACI Mode</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20nx-os%20software%20for%20nexus%209000%20series%20fabric%20switches%20aci%20mode.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software for Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches ACI Mode</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 19:20:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1585|2024-09-17T01:25:45.666Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software%20for%20nexus%209000%20series%20fabric%20switches%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1585</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the controller authorization functionality of Cisco Nexus 9000 Series ACI Mode Switch Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to escalate standard users with root privilege on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a misconfiguration of certain sudoers files for the bashroot component on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the affected device with a crafted user ID, which may allow temporary administrative access to escalate privileges. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to escalate privileges on an affected device. This Vulnerability has been fixed in version 4.0(1h)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1585|2024-09-17T01:25:45.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1589|2024-09-17T01:45:59.198Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software%20for%20nexus%209000%20series%20fabric%20switches%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1589</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Trusted Platform Module (TPM) functionality of software for Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches in Application Centric Infrastructure (ACI) mode could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker with physical access to view sensitive information on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a lack of proper data-protection mechanisms for disk encryption keys that are used within the partitions on an affected device hard drive. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by obtaining physical access to the affected device to view certain cleartext keys. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute a custom boot process or conduct further attacks on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1589|2024-09-17T01:45:59.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 14:50:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1591|2024-09-17T02:01:45.457Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software%20for%20nexus%209000%20series%20fabric%20switches%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1591</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a specific CLI command implementation of Cisco Nexus 9000 Series ACI Mode Switch Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to escape a restricted shell on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied input when issuing a specific CLI command with parameters on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device CLI and issuing certain commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to escape the restricted shell and execute arbitrary commands with root-level privileges on the affected device. This vulnerability only affects Cisco Nexus 9000 Series ACI Mode Switches that are running a release prior to 14.0(3d).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1591|2024-09-17T02:01:45.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
