<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Extensible Operating System (FXOS)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20firepower%20extensible%20operating%20system%20%28fxos%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Extensible Operating System (FXOS)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 13:23:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3459|2024-08-04T07:37:54.127Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20extensible%20operating%20system%20%28fxos%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3459</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco FXOS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject arbitrary commands that are executed with root privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of commands supplied by the user. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to a device and submitting crafted input to the affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands on the underlying operating system with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3459|2024-08-04T07:37:54.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3545|2024-08-04T07:37:54.889Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20extensible%20operating%20system%20%28fxos%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3545</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco FXOS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrative credentials to cause a buffer overflow condition. The vulnerability is due to incorrect bounds checking of values that are parsed from a specific file. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a crafted file that, when it is processed, may cause a stack-based buffer overflow. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system with root privileges. An attacker would need to have valid administrative credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3545|2024-08-04T07:37:54.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3455|2024-08-04T07:37:54.973Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20extensible%20operating%20system%20%28fxos%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3455</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the secure boot process of Cisco FXOS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to bypass the secure boot mechanisms. The vulnerability is due to insufficient protections of the secure boot process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting code into a specific file that is then referenced during the device boot process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to break the chain of trust and inject code into the boot process of the device which would be executed at each boot and maintain persistence across reboots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3455|2024-08-04T07:37:54.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3166|2024-08-04T07:24:00.654Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20extensible%20operating%20system%20%28fxos%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3166</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco FXOS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to read or write arbitrary files on the underlying operating system (OS). The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted arguments to a specific CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read or write to arbitrary files on the underlying OS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3166|2024-08-04T07:24:00.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3169|2024-08-04T07:24:00.671Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20extensible%20operating%20system%20%28fxos%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3169</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco FXOS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with a privilege level of root on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to a specific CLI command on the affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system with root privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3169|2024-08-04T07:24:00.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
