<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Contact Center Express</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20unified%20contact%20center%20express.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Unified Contact Center Express</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:22:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1254|2024-08-03T16:02:56.386Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20contact%20center%20express
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1254</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Finesse could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of the affected software. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by injecting malicious code into the web-based management interface and persuading a user to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. An attacker needs valid administrator credentials to inject the malicious script code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1254|2024-08-03T16:02:56.386Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1395|2024-08-03T16:11:17.024Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20contact%20center%20express
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1395</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unified Intelligence Center could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1395|2024-08-03T16:11:17.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1463|2024-08-03T16:11:17.322Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20contact%20center%20express
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1463</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unified Intelligence Center Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of an affected interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1463|2024-08-03T16:11:17.322Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1358|2024-08-03T16:11:16.969Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unified%20contact%20center%20express
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1358</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Finesse could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to redirect a user to an undesired web page. This vulnerability is due to improper input validation of the URL parameters in an HTTP request that is sent to an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the interface to redirect the user to a specific, malicious URL. This type of vulnerability is known as an open redirect and is used in phishing attacks that get users to unknowingly visit malicious sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1358|2024-08-03T16:11:16.969Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
