<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN Solution</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20sd-wan%20solution.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN Solution</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 03:24:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1546|2024-09-17T01:37:07.805Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1546</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access sensitive information. This vulnerability is due to improper protections on file access through the CLI. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a CLI command that targets an arbitrary file on the local system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to return portions of an arbitrary file, possibly resulting in the disclosure of sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1546|2024-09-17T01:37:07.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3379|2024-09-17T00:20:54.041Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3379</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN Solution Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to Administrator on the underlying operating system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain administrative privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3379|2024-09-17T00:20:54.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3266|2024-09-17T01:40:45.440Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3266</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco SD-WAN Solution software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject arbitrary commands that are executed with root privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and submitting crafted input to the CLI utility. The attacker must be authenticated to access the CLI utility. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3266|2024-09-17T01:40:45.440Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 15:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1648|2024-09-17T00:10:35.021Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1648</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the user group configuration of the Cisco SD-WAN Solution could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain elevated privileges on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a failure to properly validate certain parameters included within the group configuration. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by writing a crafted file to the directory where the user group configuration is located in the underlying operating system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain root-level privileges and take full control of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1648|2024-09-17T00:10:35.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1647|2024-09-17T01:20:48.880Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1647</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco SD-WAN Solution could allow an authenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass authentication and have direct unauthorized access to other vSmart containers. The vulnerability is due to an insecure default configuration of the affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by directly connecting to the exposed services. An exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve and modify critical system files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1647|2024-09-17T01:20:48.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1278|2024-09-17T02:36:21.605Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1278</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN products could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute denial of service (DoS) attacks against an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1278|2024-09-17T02:36:21.605Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3351|2024-09-17T01:35:44.103Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3351</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN Solution Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of fields in Cisco SD-WAN peering messages that are encapsulated in UDP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted UDP messages to the targeted system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause services on the device to fail, resulting in a DoS condition that could impact the targeted device and other devices that depend on it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3351|2024-09-17T01:35:44.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1301|2024-09-17T01:16:01.672Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1301</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN products could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute attacks against an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1301|2024-09-17T01:16:01.672Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1298|2024-09-17T02:05:58.131Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1298</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN products could allow an authenticated attacker to perform command injection attacks against an affected device, which could allow the attacker to take certain actions with root privileges on the device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1298|2024-09-17T02:05:58.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
