<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Prime Infrastructure</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20prime%20infrastructure.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Prime Infrastructure</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 22:22:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15433|2024-09-17T01:27:07.584Z -- cisco -- cisco%20prime%20infrastructure
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15433</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the server backup function of Cisco Prime Infrastructure could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to view sensitive information. The vulnerability is due to the transmission of sensitive information as part of a GET request. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a GET request to a vulnerable device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15433|2024-09-17T01:27:07.584Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1820|2024-09-17T02:26:19.533Z -- cisco -- cisco%20prime%20infrastructure
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1820</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Prime Infrastructure and Cisco Evolved Programmable Network (EPN) Manager software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to download and view files within the application that should be restricted. This vulnerability is due to improper sanitization of user-supplied input in HTTP request parameters that describe filenames. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using directory traversal techniques to submit a path to a desired file location. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view application files that may contain sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1820|2024-09-17T02:26:19.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 01:10:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1818|2024-09-17T03:28:46.215Z -- cisco -- cisco%20prime%20infrastructure
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1818</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Prime Infrastructure and Cisco Evolved Programmable Network (EPN) Manager software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to download and view files within the application that should be restricted. This vulnerability is due to improper sanitization of user-supplied input in HTTP request parameters that describe filenames. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using directory traversal techniques to submit a path to a desired file location. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view application files that may contain sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1818|2024-09-17T03:28:46.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 01:10:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1825|2024-09-17T00:40:43.855Z -- cisco -- cisco%20prime%20infrastructure
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1825</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Prime Infrastructure (PI) and Cisco Evolved Programmable Network (EPN) Manager could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries. This vulnerability exist because the software improperly validates user-supplied input in SQL queries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request that contains malicious SQL statements to the affected application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view or modify entries in some database tables, affecting the integrity of the data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1825|2024-09-17T00:40:43.855Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 01:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1643|2024-09-17T03:02:22.185Z -- cisco -- cisco%20prime%20infrastructure
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1643</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Prime Infrastructure could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of the affected software. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a maliciously crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1643|2024-09-17T03:02:22.185Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20659|2024-09-17T00:45:29.739Z -- cisco -- cisco%20prime%20infrastructure
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20659</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Prime Infrastructure and Cisco Evolved Programmable Network (EPN) Manager could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of an affected interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20659|2024-09-17T00:45:29.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 15:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1659|2024-09-17T02:10:33.421Z -- cisco -- cisco%20prime%20infrastructure
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1659</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Identity Services Engine (ISE) integration feature of Cisco Prime Infrastructure (PI) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to perform a man-in-the-middle attack against the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) tunnel established between ISE and PI. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of the server SSL certificate when establishing the SSL tunnel with ISE. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using a crafted SSL certificate and could then intercept communications between the ISE and PI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view and alter potentially sensitive information that the ISE maintains about clients that are connected to the network. This vulnerability affects Cisco Prime Infrastructure Software Releases 2.2 through 3.4.0 when the PI server is integrated with ISE, which is disabled by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1659|2024-09-17T02:10:33.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
