<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN vEdge router</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20sd-wan%20vedge%20router.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN vEdge router</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 12:25:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3385|2024-08-04T07:30:58.394Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vedge%20router
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3385</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the deep packet inspection (DPI) engine of Cisco SD-WAN vEdge Routers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient handling of malformed packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reboot, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3385|2024-08-04T07:30:58.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3369|2024-08-04T07:30:58.160Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vedge%20router
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3369</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the deep packet inspection (DPI) engine of Cisco SD-WAN vEdge Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper processing of FTP traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted FTP packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to make the device reboot continuously, causing a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3369|2024-08-04T07:30:58.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
