<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Prime Infrastructure</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20prime%20infrastructure.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Prime Infrastructure</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 05:22:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34733|2024-08-04T00:19:48.123Z -- cisco -- cisco%20prime%20infrastructure
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34733</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco Prime Infrastructure and Cisco Evolved Programmable Network (EPN) Manager could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access sensitive information stored on the underlying file system of an affected system. This vulnerability exists because sensitive information is not sufficiently secured when it is stored. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by gaining unauthorized access to sensitive information on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to create forged authentication requests and gain unauthorized access to the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34733|2024-08-04T00:19:48.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34784|2024-08-04T00:19:48.219Z -- cisco -- cisco%20prime%20infrastructure
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34784</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Prime Infrastructure (PI) and Cisco Evolved Programmable Network Manager (EPNM) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of an affected interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34784|2024-08-04T00:19:48.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
