<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Intersight Virtual Appliance</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20intersight%20virtual%20appliance.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Intersight Virtual Appliance</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:43:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1600|2024-09-16T16:33:22.588Z -- cisco -- cisco%20intersight%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1600</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Intersight Virtual Appliance could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to access sensitive internal services from an external interface. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient restrictions for IPv4 or IPv6 packets that are received on the external management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending specific traffic to this interface on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access sensitive internal services and make configuration changes on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1600|2024-09-16T16:33:22.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 15:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1617|2024-09-16T17:42:58.807Z -- cisco -- cisco%20intersight%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1617</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Intersight Virtual Appliance could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a path traversal or command injection attack on an affected system. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by using the web-based management interface to do one or both of the following: Execute a command using crafted input Upload a file that has been altered using path traversal techniques A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read and write arbitrary files or execute arbitrary commands as root on an affected system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1617|2024-09-16T17:42:58.807Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 15:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
