<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software 3.8.0S</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%203.8.0s.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software 3.8.0S</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 21:22:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3213|2024-09-17T02:15:42.048Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%203.8.0s
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3213</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the ROMMON of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to those of the root user of the underlying operating system. The vulnerability is due to the ROMMON allowing for special parameters to be passed to the device at initial boot up. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending parameters to the device at initial boot up. An exploit could allow the attacker to elevate from a Priv15 user to the root user and execute arbitrary commands with the privileges of the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3213|2024-09-17T02:15:42.048Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 17:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3215|2024-09-17T00:55:29.501Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%203.8.0s
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3215</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Virtual Services Container of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain root-level privileges on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of a user-supplied open virtual appliance (OVA). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by installing a malicious OVA on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3215|2024-09-17T00:55:29.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 17:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
