<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco RV130W Wireless-N Multifunction VPN Router Firmware</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20rv130w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router%20firmware.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco RV130W Wireless-N Multifunction VPN Router Firmware</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 22:22:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3332|2024-09-16T20:32:13.672Z -- cisco -- cisco%20rv130w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3332</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Small Business RV110W, RV130, RV130W, and RV215W Series Routers could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary shell commands that are executed by an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of user-supplied data. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the web-based management interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary shell commands or scripts with root privileges on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3332|2024-09-16T20:32:13.672Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1898|2024-09-16T17:17:44.831Z -- cisco -- cisco%20rv130w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1898</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco RV110W, RV130W, and RV215W Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access the syslog file on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper authorization of an HTTP request. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the URL for the syslog file. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access the information contained in the file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1898|2024-09-16T17:17:44.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 03:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3268|2024-09-16T18:13:23.035Z -- cisco -- cisco%20rv130w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3268</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco RV110W, RV130, RV130W, and RV215W Series Routers could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary commands. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3268|2024-09-16T18:13:23.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 02:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0425|2024-09-16T20:28:07.781Z -- cisco -- cisco%20rv130w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0425</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of the Cisco RV110W Wireless-N VPN Firewall, Cisco RV130W Wireless-N Multifunction VPN Router, and Cisco RV215W Wireless-N VPN Router could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain access to sensitive information. The vulnerability is due to improper access control to files within the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to sensitive configuration information, including user authentication credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0425|2024-09-16T20:28:07.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3269|2024-09-16T18:04:02.934Z -- cisco -- cisco%20rv130w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3269</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco RV110W, RV130, RV130W, and RV215W Series Routers could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary commands. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3269|2024-09-16T18:04:02.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 02:21:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3146|2024-09-16T21:04:11.545Z -- cisco -- cisco%20rv130w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3146</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of the Cisco RV110W Wireless-N VPN Firewall, RV130 VPN Router, RV130W Wireless-N Multifunction VPN Router, and RV215W Wireless-N VPN Router could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device. The vulnerabilities are due to improper validation of user-supplied data in the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending malicious HTTP requests to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system of the affected device as a high-privilege user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3146|2024-09-16T21:04:11.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1843|2024-09-16T17:48:23.755Z -- cisco -- cisco%20rv130w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1843</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of the Cisco RV110W Wireless-N VPN Firewall, Cisco RV130W Wireless-N Multifunction VPN Router, and Cisco RV215W Wireless-N VPN Router could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied data in the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious HTTP requests to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to reload the device and causing a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1843|2024-09-16T17:48:23.755Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 02:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3145|2024-09-16T20:32:33.644Z -- cisco -- cisco%20rv130w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3145</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of the Cisco RV110W Wireless-N VPN Firewall, RV130 VPN Router, RV130W Wireless-N Multifunction VPN Router, and RV215W Wireless-N VPN Router could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device. The vulnerabilities are due to improper validation of user-supplied data in the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending malicious HTTP requests to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system of the affected device as a high-privilege user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3145|2024-09-16T20:32:33.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1899|2024-09-16T20:43:15.640Z -- cisco -- cisco%20rv130w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1899</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web interface of Cisco RV110W, RV130W, and RV215W Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to acquire the list of devices that are connected to the guest network. The vulnerability is due to improper authorization of an HTTP request. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing a specific URI on the web interface of the router.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1899|2024-09-16T20:43:15.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 03:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3144|2024-09-16T19:10:52.070Z -- cisco -- cisco%20rv130w%20wireless-n%20multifunction%20vpn%20router%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3144</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of the Cisco RV110W Wireless-N VPN Firewall, RV130 VPN Router, RV130W Wireless-N Multifunction VPN Router, and RV215W Wireless-N VPN Router could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass authentication and execute arbitrary commands with administrative commands on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper session management on affected devices. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain administrative access on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3144|2024-09-16T19:10:52.070Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
