<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20xe%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 09:23:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0470|2024-08-05T03:28:10.883Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0470</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web framework of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a buffer overflow condition on an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to the affected software improperly parsing malformed HTTP packets that are destined to a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed HTTP packet to an affected device for processing. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a buffer overflow condition on the affected device, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0470|2024-08-05T03:28:10.883Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0481|2024-08-05T03:28:10.753Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0481</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI parser of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute commands on the underlying Linux shell of an affected device with root privileges. The vulnerability exist because the affected software improperly sanitizes command arguments, failing to prevent access to certain internal data structures on an affected device. An attacker who has privileged EXEC mode (privilege level 15) access to an affected device could exploit these vulnerabilities on the device by executing CLI commands that contain custom arguments. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0481|2024-08-05T03:28:10.753Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0469|2024-08-05T03:28:10.956Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0469</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web user interface of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload. The vulnerability is due to a double-free-in-memory handling by the affected software when specific HTTP requests are processed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific HTTP requests to the web user interface of the affected software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have access to the management interface of the affected software, which is typically connected to a restricted management network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0469|2024-08-05T03:28:10.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0476|2024-08-05T03:28:10.327Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0476</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Network Address Translation (NAT) Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) Application Layer Gateway (ALG) of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload. The vulnerability is due to improper processing of SIP packets in transit while NAT is performed on an affected device. An unauthenticated, remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted SIP packets via UDP port 5060 through an affected device that is performing NAT for SIP packets. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0476|2024-08-05T03:28:10.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0471|2024-08-05T03:28:10.713Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0471</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Discovery Protocol (CDP) module of Cisco IOS XE Software Releases 16.6.1 and 16.6.2 could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a memory leak that may lead to a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of certain CDP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain CDP packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could cause an affected device to continuously consume memory and eventually result in a memory allocation failure that leads to a crash, triggering a reload of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0471|2024-08-05T03:28:10.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0477|2024-08-05T03:28:11.019Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0477</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI parser of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute commands on the underlying Linux shell of an affected device with root privileges. The vulnerability exist because the affected software improperly sanitizes command arguments, failing to prevent access to certain internal data structures on an affected device. An attacker who has privileged EXEC mode (privilege level 15) access to an affected device could exploit these vulnerabilities on the device by executing CLI commands that contain custom arguments. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0477|2024-08-05T03:28:11.019Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0480|2024-08-05T03:28:10.476Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0480</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the errdisable per VLAN feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the device to crash, leading to a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to a race condition that occurs when the VLAN and port enter an errdisabled state, resulting in an incorrect state in the software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending frames that trigger the errdisable condition. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash, leading to a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0480|2024-08-05T03:28:10.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T15:33:37.498Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T15:33:37.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-06-20T20:52:30.286Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-06-20T20:52:30.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-06-20T20:50:12.348Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-06-20T20:50:12.348Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-03-27T17:03:54.505Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-03-27T17:03:54.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-03-27T16:49:03.113Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-03-27T16:49:03.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20306|2024-03-27T16:58:22.583Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Unified Threat Defense (UTD) configuration CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying host operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have level 15 privileges on the affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20306|2024-03-27T16:58:22.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-04-03T16:36:06.520Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-04-03T16:36:06.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20259|2024-03-27T16:53:53.073Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP snooping feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a crafted IPv4 DHCP request packet being mishandled when endpoint analytics are enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCP request through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; Note: The attack vector is listed as network because a DHCP relay anywhere on the network could allow exploits from networks other than the adjacent one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20259|2024-03-27T16:53:53.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20278|2024-03-27T16:59:12.963Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20278</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NETCONF feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input over NETCONF to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges from Administrator to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20278|2024-03-27T16:59:12.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20324|2024-03-27T16:55:53.837Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20324</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to access WLAN configuration details including passwords.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper privilege checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the show and show tech wireless CLI commands to access configuration details, including passwords. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access configuration details that they are not authorized to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20324|2024-03-27T16:55:53.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20309|2024-03-27T17:02:19.749Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in auxiliary asynchronous port (AUX) functions of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause an affected device to reload or stop responding.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific ingress traffic when flow control hardware is enabled on the AUX port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by reverse telnetting to the AUX port and sending specific data after connecting. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reset or stop responding, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20309|2024-03-27T17:02:19.749Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20313|2024-04-24T20:42:10.379Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20313</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of OSPF updates that are processed by a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF update to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20313|2024-04-24T20:42:10.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-03-27T16:57:27.974Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-03-27T16:57:27.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20303|2024-06-04T17:39:55.892Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20303</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multicast DNS (mDNS) gateway feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Wireless LAN Controllers (WLCs) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper management of mDNS client entries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the wireless network and sending a continuous stream of specific mDNS packets. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the wireless controller to have high CPU utilization, which could lead to access points (APs) losing their connection to the controller and result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20303|2024-06-04T17:39:55.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-06-20T17:42:35.196Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-06-20T17:42:35.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-07-02T16:25:58.752Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-07-02T16:25:58.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-07-02T16:25:13.272Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-07-02T16:25:13.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-07-02T16:23:39.427Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-07-02T16:23:39.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20309|2024-08-01T21:59:41.337Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in auxiliary asynchronous port (AUX) functions of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause an affected device to reload or stop responding.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific ingress traffic when flow control hardware is enabled on the AUX port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by reverse telnetting to the AUX port and sending specific data after connecting. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reset or stop responding, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20309|2024-08-01T21:59:41.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20259|2024-08-01T21:52:31.719Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP snooping feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a crafted IPv4 DHCP request packet being mishandled when endpoint analytics are enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCP request through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; Note: The attack vector is listed as network because a DHCP relay anywhere on the network could allow exploits from networks other than the adjacent one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20259|2024-08-01T21:52:31.719Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20324|2024-08-01T21:59:41.715Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20324</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to access WLAN configuration details including passwords.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper privilege checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the show and show tech wireless CLI commands to access configuration details, including passwords. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access configuration details that they are not authorized to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20324|2024-08-01T21:59:41.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20303|2024-08-01T21:59:41.376Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20303</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multicast DNS (mDNS) gateway feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Wireless LAN Controllers (WLCs) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper management of mDNS client entries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the wireless network and sending a continuous stream of specific mDNS packets. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the wireless controller to have high CPU utilization, which could lead to access points (APs) losing their connection to the controller and result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20303|2024-08-01T21:59:41.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-08-01T21:59:42.311Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-08-01T21:59:42.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-08-01T21:59:42.197Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-08-01T21:59:42.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T21:52:31.616Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T21:52:31.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20278|2024-08-01T21:59:41.100Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20278</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NETCONF feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input over NETCONF to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges from Administrator to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20278|2024-08-01T21:59:41.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20306|2024-08-01T21:59:41.650Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Unified Threat Defense (UTD) configuration CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying host operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have level 15 privileges on the affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20306|2024-08-01T21:59:41.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-08-01T21:59:41.851Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-08-01T21:59:41.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20313|2024-08-01T21:59:42.856Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20313</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of OSPF updates that are processed by a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF update to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20313|2024-08-01T21:59:42.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
