<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0282|2024-08-05T03:21:14.918Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0282</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TCP socket code of Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload. The vulnerability is due to a state condition between the socket state and the transmission control block (TCB) state. While this vulnerability potentially affects all TCP applications, the only affected application observed so far is the HTTP server. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific HTTP requests at a sustained rate to a reachable IP address of the affected software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0282|2024-08-05T03:21:14.918Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0484|2024-08-05T03:28:11.002Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0484</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control logic of the Secure Shell (SSH) server of Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software may allow connections sourced from a virtual routing and forwarding (VRF) instance despite the absence of the vrf-also keyword in the access-class configuration. The vulnerability is due to a missing check in the SSH server. An attacker could use this vulnerability to open an SSH connection to an affected Cisco IOS or IOS XE device with a source address belonging to a VRF instance. Once connected, the attacker would still need to provide valid credentials to access the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0484|2024-08-05T03:28:11.002Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
