<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:22:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1704|2024-08-04T18:28:41.709Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1704</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Server Message Block (SMB) Protocol preprocessor detection engine for Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent or remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1704|2024-08-04T18:28:41.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1970|2024-08-04T18:35:52.019Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1970</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL)/Transport Layer Security (TLS) protocol inspection engine of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured file policies on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to errors when handling specific SSL/TLS messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets that would flow through an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the configured file policies and deliver a malicious payload to the protected network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1970|2024-08-04T18:35:52.019Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3299|2024-08-04T07:30:57.923Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3299</link>
      <description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort detection engine that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured File Policy for HTTP. The vulnerability is due to incorrect detection of modified HTTP packets used in chunked responses. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass a configured File Policy for HTTP packets and deliver a malicious payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3299|2024-08-04T07:30:57.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1691|2024-08-04T18:28:41.097Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1691</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the detection engine of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the unexpected restart of the SNORT detection engine, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to the incomplete error handling of the SSL or TLS packet header during the connection establishment. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SSL or TLS packet during the connection handshake. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the SNORT detection engine to unexpectedly restart, resulting in a partial DoS condition while the detection engine restarts. Versions prior to 6.2.3.4 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1691|2024-08-04T18:28:41.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34754|2024-08-04T00:19:48.159Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34754</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the payload inspection for Ethernet Industrial Protocol (ENIP) traffic for Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured rules for ENIP traffic. These vulnerabilities are due to incomplete processing during deep packet inspection for ENIP packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a crafted ENIP packet to the targeted interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access control and intrusion policies that should be activated for the ENIP packet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34754|2024-08-04T00:19:48.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3186|2024-08-04T07:24:00.636Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3186</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the management access list configuration of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured management interface access list on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to the configuration of different management access lists, with ports allowed in one access list and denied in another. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted remote management traffic to the local IP address of an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the configured management access list policies, and traffic to the management interface would not be properly denied.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3186|2024-08-04T07:24:00.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40116|2024-08-04T02:27:31.552Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40116</link>
      <description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in Snort rules that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.The vulnerability is due to improper handling of the Block with Reset or Interactive Block with Reset actions if a rule is configured without proper constraints. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IP packet to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause through traffic to be dropped. Note: Only products with Snort3 configured and either a rule with Block with Reset or Interactive Block with Reset actions configured are vulnerable. Products configured with Snort2 are not vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40116|2024-08-04T02:27:31.552Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3308|2024-08-04T07:30:57.461Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3308</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Image Signature Verification feature of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrator-level credentials to install a malicious software patch on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper verification of digital signatures for patch images. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting an unsigned software patch to bypass signature checks and loading it on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to boot a malicious software patch image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3308|2024-08-04T07:30:57.461Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1703|2024-08-04T18:28:42.326Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1703</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the internal packet-processing functionality of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software for the Cisco Firepower 2100 Series could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to stop processing traffic, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to a logic error, which may prevent ingress buffers from being replenished under specific traffic conditions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of crafted packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to consume all input buffers, which are shared between all interfaces, leading to a queue wedge condition in all active interfaces. This situation would cause an affected device to stop processing any incoming traffic and result in a DoS condition until the device is reloaded manually.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1703|2024-08-04T18:28:42.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40114|2024-08-04T02:27:31.905Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40114</link>
      <description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the way the Snort detection engine processes ICMP traffic that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper memory resource management while the Snort detection engine is processing ICMP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of ICMP packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust resources on the affected device, causing the device to reload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40114|2024-08-04T02:27:31.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1669|2024-08-04T18:20:28.366Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1669</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data acquisition (DAQ) component of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured access control policies or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability exists because the affected software improperly manages system memory resources when inspecting traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by generating specific traffic patterns for the software to inspect. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust system memory resources used for traffic inspection. Depending on the configuration, the FTD Software could fail open and cease to inspect traffic or fail closed and result in a DoS condition. This vulnerability may require manual intervention to restore the software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1669|2024-08-04T18:20:28.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3255|2024-08-04T07:30:58.159Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3255</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the packet processing functionality of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to inefficient memory management. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high rate of IPv4 or IPv6 traffic through an affected device. This traffic would need to match a configured block action in an access control policy. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause a memory exhaustion condition on the affected device, which would result in a DoS for traffic transiting the device, as well as sluggish performance of the management interface. Once the flood is stopped, performance should return to previous states.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3255|2024-08-04T07:30:58.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3253|2024-08-04T07:30:58.105Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3253</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the support tunnel feature of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access the shell of an affected device even though expert mode is disabled. The vulnerability is due to improper configuration of the support tunnel feature. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by enabling the support tunnel, setting a key, and deriving the tunnel password. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to run any system command with root access on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3253|2024-08-04T07:30:58.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34761|2024-08-04T00:19:48.218Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34761</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to overwrite or append arbitrary data to system files using root-level privileges. The attacker must have administrative credentials on the device. This vulnerability is due to incomplete validation of user input for a specific CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device with administrative privileges and issuing a CLI command with crafted user parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite or append arbitrary data to system files using root-level privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34761|2024-08-04T00:19:48.218Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3565|2024-08-04T07:37:55.034Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3565</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TCP Intercept functionality of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured Access Control Policies (including Geolocation) and Service Polices on an affected system. The vulnerability exists because TCP Intercept is invoked when the embryonic connection limit is reached, which can cause the underlying detection engine to process the packet incorrectly. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted stream of traffic that matches a policy on which TCP Intercept is configured. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to match on an incorrect policy, which could allow the traffic to be forwarded when it should be dropped. In addition, the traffic could incorrectly be dropped.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3565|2024-08-04T07:37:55.034Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3352|2024-08-04T07:30:58.147Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3352</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access hidden commands. The vulnerability is due to the presence of undocumented configuration commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by performing specific steps that make the hidden commands accessible. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to make configuration changes to various sections of an affected device that should not be exposed to CLI access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3352|2024-08-04T07:30:58.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1709|2024-08-04T18:28:42.298Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1709</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform a command injection attack. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting commands into arguments for a specific command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1709|2024-08-04T18:28:42.298Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3563|2024-08-04T07:37:54.980Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3563</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the packet processing functionality of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to inefficient memory management. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of TCP packets to a specific port on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust system memory, which could cause the device to reload unexpectedly. No manual intervention is needed to recover the device after it has reloaded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3563|2024-08-04T07:37:54.980Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3283|2024-08-04T07:30:57.723Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3283</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL)/Transport Layer Security (TLS) handler of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software when running on the Cisco Firepower 1000 Series platform could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a communication error between internal functions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SSL/TLS message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a buffer underrun, which leads to a crash. The crash causes the affected device to reload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3283|2024-08-04T07:30:57.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34755|2024-08-04T00:19:48.221Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34755</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34755|2024-08-04T00:19:48.221Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3317|2024-08-04T07:30:57.600Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3317</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the ssl_inspection component of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to crash Snort instances. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation in the ssl_inspection component. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed TLS packet through a Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA). A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash a Snort instance, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3317|2024-08-04T07:30:57.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3310|2024-08-04T07:30:58.100Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the XML parser code of Cisco Firepower Device Manager On-Box software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected system to become unstable or reload. The vulnerability is due to insufficient hardening of the XML parser configuration. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability in multiple ways using a malicious file: An attacker with administrative privileges could upload a malicious XML file on the system and cause the XML code to parse the malicious file. An attacker with Clientless Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) VPN access could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted XML file. A successful exploit would allow the attacker to crash the XML parser process, which could cause system instability, memory exhaustion, and in some cases lead to a reload of the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3310|2024-08-04T07:30:58.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1832|2024-08-04T18:28:42.865Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1832</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the detection engine of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured access control policies. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of ICMP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted ICMP packets to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access control policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1832|2024-08-04T18:28:42.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3309|2024-08-04T07:30:57.583Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Firepower Device Manager (FDM) On-Box software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to overwrite arbitrary files on the underlying operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a malicious file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite arbitrary files on as well as modify the underlying operating system of an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3309|2024-08-04T07:30:57.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1833|2024-08-04T18:28:42.820Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1833</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL)/Transport Layer Security (TLS) protocol parser of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured policies. The vulnerability is due to improper parsing of specific attributes in a TLS packet header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious TLS messages to the affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the configured policies for the system, which could allow traffic to flow through without being inspected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1833|2024-08-04T18:28:42.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3189|2024-08-04T07:24:00.626Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3189</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the VPN System Logging functionality for Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a memory leak that can deplete system memory over time, which can cause unexpected system behaviors or device crashes. The vulnerability is due to the system memory not being properly freed for a VPN System Logging event generated when a VPN session is created or deleted. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by repeatedly creating or deleting a VPN tunnel connection, which could leak a small amount of system memory for each logging event. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause system memory depletion, which can lead to a systemwide denial of service (DoS) condition. The attacker does not have any control of whether VPN System Logging is configured or not on the device, but it is enabled by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3189|2024-08-04T07:24:00.626Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1981|2024-08-04T18:35:52.366Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1981</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the normalization functionality of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software, Cisco FirePOWER Services Software for ASA, and Cisco Firepower Management Center Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass filtering protections. The vulnerability is due to insufficient normalization of a text-based payload. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic that contains specifically obfuscated payloads through an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to bypass filtering and deliver malicious payloads to protected systems that would otherwise be blocked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1981|2024-08-04T18:35:52.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1978|2024-08-04T18:35:52.426Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1978</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the stream reassembly component of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software, Cisco FirePOWER Services Software for ASA, and Cisco Firepower Management Center Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass filtering protections. The vulnerability is due to improper reassembly of traffic streams. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted streams through an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to bypass filtering and deliver malicious requests to protected systems that would otherwise be blocked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1978|2024-08-04T18:35:52.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3188|2024-08-04T07:24:00.646Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3188</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in how Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software handles session timeouts for management connections could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a buildup of remote management connections to an affected device, which could result in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability exists because the default session timeout period for specific to-the-box remote management connections is too long. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large and sustained number of crafted remote management connections to an affected device, resulting in a buildup of those connections over time. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the remote management interface or Cisco Firepower Device Manager (FDM) to stop responding and cause other management functions to go offline, resulting in a DoS condition. The user traffic that is flowing through the device would not be affected, and the DoS condition would be isolated to remote management only.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3188|2024-08-04T07:24:00.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3562|2024-08-04T07:37:55.507Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3562</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSL/TLS inspection of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software for Cisco Firepower 2100 Series firewalls could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation for certain fields of specific SSL/TLS messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed SSL/TLS message through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition. No manual intervention is needed to recover the device after it has reloaded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3562|2024-08-04T07:37:55.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1980|2024-08-04T18:35:52.346Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1980</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the protocol detection component of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software, Cisco FirePOWER Services Software for ASA, and Cisco Firepower Management Center Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass filtering protections. The vulnerability is due to improper detection of the initial use of a protocol on a nonstandard port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic on a nonstandard port for the protocol in use through an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to bypass filtering and deliver malicious requests to protected systems that would otherwise be blocked. Once the initial protocol flow on the nonstandard port is detected, future flows on the nonstandard port will be successfully detected and handled as configured by the applied policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1980|2024-08-04T18:35:52.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3514|2024-08-04T07:37:54.656Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3514</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multi-instance feature of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to escape the container for their Cisco FTD instance and execute commands with root privileges in the host namespace. The attacker must have valid credentials on the device.The vulnerability exists because a configuration file that is used at container startup has insufficient protections. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by modifying a specific container configuration file on the underlying file system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands with root privileges within the host namespace. This could allow the attacker to impact other running Cisco FTD instances or the host Cisco FXOS device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3514|2024-08-04T07:37:54.656Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3315|2024-08-04T07:30:57.819Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3315</link>
      <description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort detection engine that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured file policies on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to errors in how the Snort detection engine handles specific HTTP responses. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets that would flow through an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the configured file policies and deliver a malicious payload to the protected network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3315|2024-08-04T07:30:57.819Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3571|2024-08-04T07:37:55.489Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3571</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the ICMP ingress packet processing of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software for Cisco Firepower 4110 appliances could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to incomplete input validation upon receiving ICMP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high number of crafted ICMP or ICMPv6 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a memory exhaustion condition that may result in an unexpected reload. No manual intervention is needed to recover the device after the reload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3571|2024-08-04T07:37:55.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3533|2024-08-04T07:37:54.983Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3533</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) input packet processor of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to restart unexpectedly. The vulnerability is due to a lack of sufficient memory management protections under heavy SNMP polling loads. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high rate of SNMP requests to the SNMP daemon through the management interface on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the SNMP daemon process to consume a large amount of system memory over time, which could then lead to an unexpected device restart, causing a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability affects all versions of SNMP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3533|2024-08-04T07:37:54.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34756|2024-08-04T00:19:48.202Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34756</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34756|2024-08-04T00:19:48.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3285|2024-08-04T07:30:57.955Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3285</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Transport Layer Security version 1.3 (TLS 1.3) policy with URL category functionality for Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured TLS 1.3 policy to block traffic for a specific URL. The vulnerability is due to a logic error with Snort handling of the connection with the TLS 1.3 policy and URL category configuration. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted TLS 1.3 connections to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the TLS 1.3 policy and access URLs that are outside the affected device and normally would be dropped.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3285|2024-08-04T07:30:57.955Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3577|2024-08-04T07:37:55.494Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3577</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the ingress packet processing path of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software for interfaces that are configured either as Inline Pair or in Passive mode could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation when Ethernet frames are processed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious Ethernet frames through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker do either of the following: Fill the /ngfw partition on the device: A full /ngfw partition could result in administrators being unable to log in to the device (including logging in through the console port) or the device being unable to boot up correctly. Note: Manual intervention is required to recover from this situation. Customers are advised to contact the Cisco Technical Assistance Center (TAC) to help recover a device in this condition. Cause a process crash: The process crash would cause the device to reload. No manual intervention is necessary to recover the device after the reload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3577|2024-08-04T07:37:55.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1696|2024-08-04T18:28:41.083Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1696</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Server Message Block (SMB) Protocol preprocessor detection engine for Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent or remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1696|2024-08-04T18:28:41.083Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3312|2024-08-04T07:30:58.016Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3312</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the application policy configuration of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain unauthorized read access to sensitive data on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient application identification. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain unauthorized read access to sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3312|2024-08-04T07:30:58.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3179|2024-08-04T07:24:00.727Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3179</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the generic routing encapsulation (GRE) tunnel decapsulation feature of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a memory handling error when GRE over IPv6 traffic is processed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted GRE over IPv6 packets with either IPv4 or IPv6 payload through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to crash, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3179|2024-08-04T07:24:00.727Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20363|2024-08-01T21:59:42.321Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20363</link>
      <description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort Intrusion Prevention System (IPS) rule engine that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured rules on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to incorrect HTTP packet handling. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured IPS rules and allow uninspected traffic onto the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20363|2024-08-01T21:59:42.321Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20261|2024-08-01T21:52:31.751Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20261</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the file policy feature that is used to inspect encrypted archive files of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured file policy to block an encrypted archive file. This vulnerability exists because of a logic error when a specific class of encrypted archive files is inspected. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted, encrypted archive file through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send an encrypted archive file, which could contain malware and should have been blocked and dropped at the Cisco FTD device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20261|2024-08-01T21:52:31.751Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20261|2024-05-22T16:53:27.346Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20261</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the file policy feature that is used to inspect encrypted archive files of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured file policy to block an encrypted archive file. This vulnerability exists because of a logic error when a specific class of encrypted archive files is inspected. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted, encrypted archive file through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send an encrypted archive file, which could contain malware and should have been blocked and dropped at the Cisco FTD device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20261|2024-05-22T16:53:27.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20363|2024-06-04T17:40:03.436Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20363</link>
      <description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort Intrusion Prevention System (IPS) rule engine that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured rules on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to incorrect HTTP packet handling. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured IPS rules and allow uninspected traffic onto the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20363|2024-06-04T17:40:03.436Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20261|2024-07-02T16:00:57.104Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20261</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the file policy feature that is used to inspect encrypted archive files of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured file policy to block an encrypted archive file. This vulnerability exists because of a logic error when a specific class of encrypted archive files is inspected. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted, encrypted archive file through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send an encrypted archive file, which could contain malware and should have been blocked and dropped at the Cisco FTD device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20261|2024-07-02T16:00:57.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
