<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20nx-os%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 10:23:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3398|2024-08-04T07:30:58.383Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3398</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) Multicast VPN (MVPN) implementation of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a BGP session to repeatedly reset, causing a partial denial of service (DoS) condition due to the BGP session being down. The vulnerability is due to incorrect parsing of a specific type of BGP MVPN update message. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending this BGP MVPN update message to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the BGP peer connections to reset, which could lead to BGP route instability and impact traffic. The incoming BGP MVPN update message is valid but is parsed incorrectly by the NX-OS device, which could send a corrupted BGP update to the configured BGP peer. Note: The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP traffic from only explicitly configured peers. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must send a specific BGP MVPN update message over an established TCP connection that appears to come from a trusted BGP peer. To do so, the attacker must obtain information about the BGP peers in the trusted network of the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3398|2024-08-04T07:30:58.383Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3415|2024-08-04T07:30:58.399Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3415</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Data Management Engine (DME) of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to execute arbitrary code with administrative privileges or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted Cisco Discovery Protocol packet to a Layer 2-adjacent affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code with administrative privileges or cause the Cisco Discovery Protocol process to crash and restart multiple times, causing the affected device to reload and resulting in a DoS condition. Note: Cisco Discovery Protocol is a Layer 2 protocol. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must be in the same broadcast domain as the affected device (Layer 2 adjacent). Exploitation of this vulnerability also requires jumbo frames to be enabled on the interface that receives the crafted Cisco Discovery Protocol packets on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3415|2024-08-04T07:30:58.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3517|2024-08-04T07:37:54.679Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3517</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Fabric Services component of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated attacker to cause process crashes, which could result in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The attack vector is configuration dependent and could be remote or adjacent. For more information about the attack vector, see the Details section of this advisory. The vulnerability is due to insufficient error handling when the affected software parses Cisco Fabric Services messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious Cisco Fabric Services messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a reload of an affected device, which could result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3517|2024-08-04T07:37:54.679Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3165|2024-08-04T07:24:00.707Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3165</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) Message Digest 5 (MD5) authentication in Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass MD5 authentication and establish a BGP connection with the device. The vulnerability occurs because the BGP MD5 authentication is bypassed if the peer does not have MD5 authentication configured, the NX-OS device does have BGP MD5 authentication configured, and the NX-OS BGP virtual routing and forwarding (VRF) name is configured to be greater than 19 characters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to establish a BGP session with the NX-OS peer. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to establish a BGP session with the NX-OS device without MD5 authentication. The Cisco implementation of the BGP protocol accepts incoming BGP traffic only from explicitly configured peers. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must send the malicious packets over a TCP connection that appears to come from a trusted BGP peer. To do so, the attacker must obtain information about the BGP peers in the affected system&amp;rsquo;s trusted network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3165|2024-08-04T07:24:00.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3397|2024-08-04T07:30:58.213Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3397</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) Multicast VPN (MVPN) implementation of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to unexpectedly reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to incomplete input validation of a specific type of BGP MVPN update message. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending this specific, valid BGP MVPN update message to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause one of the BGP-related routing applications to restart multiple times, leading to a system-level restart. Note: The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP traffic from only explicitly configured peers. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must send a specific BGP MVPN update message over an established TCP connection that appears to come from a trusted BGP peer. To do so, the attacker must obtain information about the BGP peers in the trusted network of the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3397|2024-08-04T07:30:58.213Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3394|2024-08-04T07:30:58.161Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3394</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Enable Secret feature of Cisco Nexus 3000 Series Switches and Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Switches in standalone NX-OS mode could allow an authenticated, local attacker to issue the enable command and get full administrative privileges. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have valid credentials for the affected device. The vulnerability is due to a logic error in the implementation of the enable command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to the device and issuing the enable command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain full administrative privileges without using the enable password. Note: The Enable Secret feature is disabled by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3394|2024-08-04T07:30:58.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3168|2024-08-04T07:24:00.707Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3168</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Login Enhancements capability of Cisco Nexus 1000V Switch for VMware vSphere could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected Nexus 1000V Virtual Supervisor Module (VSM) to become inaccessible to users through the CLI. The vulnerability is due to improper resource allocation during failed CLI login attempts when login parameters that are part of the Secure Login Enhancements capability are configured on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by performing a high amount of login attempts against the affected device. A successful exploit could cause the affected device to become inaccessible to other users, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition requiring a manual power cycle of the VSM to recover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3168|2024-08-04T07:24:00.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T20:40:44.265Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T20:40:44.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T15:08:18.404Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T15:08:18.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-01T18:57:52.266Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-01T18:57:52.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20291|2024-02-28T16:16:33.950Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20291</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) programming for port channel subinterfaces of Cisco Nexus 3000 and 9000 Series Switches in standalone NX-OS mode could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to send traffic that should be blocked through an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect hardware programming that occurs when configuration changes are made to port channel member ports. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access network resources that should be protected by an ACL that was applied on port channel subinterfaces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20291|2024-02-28T16:16:33.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20321|2024-02-28T16:14:28.992Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20321</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the External Border Gateway Protocol (eBGP) implementation of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because eBGP traffic is mapped to a shared hardware rate-limiter queue. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending large amounts of network traffic with certain characteristics through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause eBGP neighbor sessions to be dropped, leading to a DoS condition in the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20321|2024-02-28T16:14:28.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20294|2024-06-04T17:40:18.434Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20294</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Link Layer Discovery Protocol (LLDP) feature of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of specific fields in an LLDP frame. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted LLDP packet to an interface of an affected device and having an authenticated user retrieve LLDP statistics from the affected device through CLI show commands or Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) requests. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the LLDP service to crash and stop running on the affected device. In certain situations, the LLDP crash may result in a reload of the affected device.
&#13; Note: LLDP is a Layer 2 link protocol. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to be directly connected to an interface of an affected device, either physically or logically (for example, through a Layer 2 Tunnel configured to transport the LLDP protocol).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20294|2024-06-04T17:40:18.434Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20267|2024-02-28T16:15:18.044Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20267</link>
      <description>A vulnerability with the handling of MPLS traffic for Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the netstack process to unexpectedly restart, which could cause the device to stop processing network traffic or to reload. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to lack of proper error checking when processing an ingress MPLS frame. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPv6 packet that is encapsulated within an MPLS frame to an MPLS-enabled interface of the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; Note: The IPv6 packet can be generated multiple hops away from the targeted device and then encapsulated within MPLS. The DoS condition may occur when the NX-OS device processes the packet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20267|2024-02-28T16:15:18.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-01T16:11:44.028Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-01T16:11:44.028Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T03:55:37.582Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T03:55:37.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T16:20:21.935Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-07-02T16:20:21.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20399|2024-08-01T21:59:42.407Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of root.
&#13; Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability on a Cisco NX-OS device, an attacker must have Administrator credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20399|2024-08-01T21:59:42.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20294|2024-08-01T21:59:41.160Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20294</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Link Layer Discovery Protocol (LLDP) feature of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of specific fields in an LLDP frame. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted LLDP packet to an interface of an affected device and having an authenticated user retrieve LLDP statistics from the affected device through CLI show commands or Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) requests. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the LLDP service to crash and stop running on the affected device. In certain situations, the LLDP crash may result in a reload of the affected device.
&#13; Note: LLDP is a Layer 2 link protocol. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to be directly connected to an interface of an affected device, either physically or logically (for example, through a Layer 2 Tunnel configured to transport the LLDP protocol).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20294|2024-08-01T21:59:41.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20291|2024-08-01T21:59:41.713Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20291</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) programming for port channel subinterfaces of Cisco Nexus 3000 and 9000 Series Switches in standalone NX-OS mode could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to send traffic that should be blocked through an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect hardware programming that occurs when configuration changes are made to port channel member ports. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access network resources that should be protected by an ACL that was applied on port channel subinterfaces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20291|2024-08-01T21:59:41.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20321|2024-08-01T21:59:41.467Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20321</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the External Border Gateway Protocol (eBGP) implementation of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because eBGP traffic is mapped to a shared hardware rate-limiter queue. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending large amounts of network traffic with certain characteristics through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause eBGP neighbor sessions to be dropped, leading to a DoS condition in the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20321|2024-08-01T21:59:41.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20267|2024-08-01T21:52:31.664Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20267</link>
      <description>A vulnerability with the handling of MPLS traffic for Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the netstack process to unexpectedly restart, which could cause the device to stop processing network traffic or to reload. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to lack of proper error checking when processing an ingress MPLS frame. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPv6 packet that is encapsulated within an MPLS frame to an MPLS-enabled interface of the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; Note: The IPv6 packet can be generated multiple hops away from the targeted device and then encapsulated within MPLS. The DoS condition may occur when the NX-OS device processes the packet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20267|2024-08-01T21:52:31.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
