<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Prime Collaboration Assurance</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20prime%20collaboration%20assurance.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Prime Collaboration Assurance</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1856|2024-08-04T18:28:42.900Z -- cisco -- cisco%20prime%20collaboration%20assurance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1856</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Prime Collaboration Assurance (PCA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to the insufficient validation of data supplied by external devices to the web-based management interface of an affected PCA device. An attacker in control of devices integrated with an affected PCA device could exploit this vulnerability by using crafted data in certain fields of the controlled devices. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the PCA web-based management interface or allow the attacker to access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1856|2024-08-04T18:28:42.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1662|2024-08-04T18:20:28.377Z -- cisco -- cisco%20prime%20collaboration%20assurance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1662</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Quality of Voice Reporting (QOVR) service of Cisco Prime Collaboration Assurance (PCA) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access the system as a valid user. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authentication controls. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the QOVR service with a valid username. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform actions with the privileges of the user that is used for access. This vulnerability affects Cisco PCA Software Releases prior to 12.1 SP2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1662|2024-08-04T18:20:28.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
