<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 03:23:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40118|2024-08-04T02:27:31.540Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40118</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web services interface of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper input validation when parsing HTTPS requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious HTTPS request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40118|2024-08-04T02:27:31.540Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34792|2024-08-04T00:19:48.259Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34792</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the memory management of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper resource management when connection rates are high. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by opening a significant number of connections on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34792|2024-08-04T00:19:48.259Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34783|2024-08-04T00:19:48.253Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34783</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the software-based SSL/TLS message handler of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of SSL/TLS messages when the device performs software-based SSL/TLS decryption. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SSL/TLS message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition. Note: Datagram TLS (DTLS) messages cannot be used to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34783|2024-08-04T00:19:48.253Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40117|2024-08-04T02:27:31.839Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40117</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in SSL/TLS message handler for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability exists because incoming SSL/TLS packets are not properly processed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SSL/TLS packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40117|2024-08-04T02:27:31.839Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34787|2024-08-04T00:19:48.219Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34787</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the identity-based firewall (IDFW) rule processing feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass security protections. This vulnerability is due to improper handling of network requests by affected devices configured to use object group search. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted network request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass access control list (ACL) rules on the device, bypass security protections, and send network traffic to unauthorized hosts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34787|2024-08-04T00:19:48.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34793|2024-08-04T00:19:48.210Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34793</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TCP Normalizer of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software operating in transparent mode could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to poison MAC address tables, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) vulnerability. This vulnerability is due to incorrect handling of certain TCP segments when the affected device is operating in transparent mode. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted TCP segment through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to poison the MAC address tables in adjacent devices, resulting in network disruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34793|2024-08-04T00:19:48.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34791|2024-08-04T00:19:48.252Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34791</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Application Level Gateway (ALG) for the Network Address Translation (NAT) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the ALG and open unauthorized connections with a host located behind the ALG. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory. Note: These vulnerabilities have been publicly discussed as NAT Slipstreaming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34791|2024-08-04T00:19:48.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34781|2024-08-04T00:19:48.142Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34781</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the processing of SSH connections for multi-instance deployments of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the affected device. This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper error handling when an SSH session fails to be established. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high rate of crafted SSH connections to the instance. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause resource exhaustion, which causes a DoS condition on the affected device. The device must be manually reloaded to recover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34781|2024-08-04T00:19:48.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34790|2024-08-04T00:19:48.263Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34790</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Application Level Gateway (ALG) for the Network Address Translation (NAT) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the ALG and open unauthorized connections with a host located behind the ALG. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory. Note: These vulnerabilities have been publicly discussed as NAT Slipstreaming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34790|2024-08-04T00:19:48.263Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34794|2024-08-04T00:19:48.189Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34794</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Simple Network Management Protocol version 3 (SNMPv3) access control functionality of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to query SNMP data. This vulnerability is due to ineffective access control. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending an SNMPv3 query to an affected device from a host that is not permitted by the SNMPv3 access control list. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send an SNMP query to an affected device and retrieve information from the device. The attacker would need valid credentials to perform the SNMP query.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34794|2024-08-04T00:19:48.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40125|2024-08-04T02:27:31.867Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40125</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Internet Key Exchange Version 2 (IKEv2) implementation of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper control of a resource. An attacker with the ability to spoof a trusted IKEv2 site-to-site VPN peer and in possession of valid IKEv2 credentials for that peer could exploit this vulnerability by sending malformed, authenticated IKEv2 messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to trigger a reload of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40125|2024-08-04T02:27:31.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20293|2024-07-02T15:36:56.903Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the activation of an access control list (ACL) on Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the protection that is offered by a configured ACL on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an ACL changes from inactive to active in the running configuration of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device that should be denied by the configured ACL. The reverse condition is also true—traffic that should be permitted could be denied by the configured ACL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL protections on the affected device, allowing the attacker to access trusted networks that the device might be protecting. Note: This vulnerability applies to both IPv4 and IPv6 traffic as well as dual-stack ACL configurations in which both IPv4 and IPv6 ACLs are configured on an interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20293|2024-07-02T15:36:56.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20358|2024-04-24T19:38:23.689Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20358</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) restore functionality that is available in Cisco ASA Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because the contents of a backup file are improperly sanitized at restore time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20358|2024-04-24T19:38:23.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20293|2024-06-04T17:39:54.684Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the activation of an access control list (ACL) on Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the protection that is offered by a configured ACL on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an ACL changes from inactive to active in the running configuration of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device that should be denied by the configured ACL. The reverse condition is also true—traffic that should be permitted could be denied by the configured ACL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL protections on the affected device, allowing the attacker to access trusted networks that the device might be protecting. Note: This vulnerability applies to both IPv4 and IPv6 traffic as well as dual-stack ACL configurations in which both IPv4 and IPv6 ACLs are configured on an interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20293|2024-06-04T17:39:54.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20355|2024-06-04T17:39:58.380Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20355</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of SAML 2.0 single sign-on (SSO) for remote access VPN services in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to successfully establish a VPN session on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper separation of authorization domains when using SAML authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using valid credentials to successfully authenticate using their designated connection profile (tunnel group), intercepting the SAML SSO token that is sent back from the Cisco ASA device, and then submitting the same SAML SSO token to a different tunnel group for authentication. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to establish a remote access VPN session using a connection profile that they are not authorized to use and connect to secured networks behind the affected device that they are not authorized to access. For successful exploitation, the attacker must have valid remote access VPN user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20355|2024-06-04T17:39:58.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20359|2024-06-04T17:40:02.581Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20359</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a legacy capability that allowed for the preloading of VPN clients and plug-ins and that has been available in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of a file when it is read from system flash memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by copying a crafted file to the disk0: file system of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected device after the next reload of the device, which could alter system behavior. Because the injected code could persist across device reboots, Cisco has raised the Security Impact Rating (SIR) of this advisory from Medium to High.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20359|2024-06-04T17:40:02.581Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20353|2024-06-04T17:40:15.708Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20353</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the management and VPN web servers for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incomplete error checking when parsing an HTTP header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to a targeted web server on a device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition when the device reloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20353|2024-06-04T17:40:15.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20355|2024-08-01T21:59:42.284Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20355</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of SAML 2.0 single sign-on (SSO) for remote access VPN services in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to successfully establish a VPN session on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper separation of authorization domains when using SAML authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using valid credentials to successfully authenticate using their designated connection profile (tunnel group), intercepting the SAML SSO token that is sent back from the Cisco ASA device, and then submitting the same SAML SSO token to a different tunnel group for authentication. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to establish a remote access VPN session using a connection profile that they are not authorized to use and connect to secured networks behind the affected device that they are not authorized to access. For successful exploitation, the attacker must have valid remote access VPN user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20355|2024-08-01T21:59:42.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20359|2024-08-01T21:59:42.379Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20359</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a legacy capability that allowed for the preloading of VPN clients and plug-ins and that has been available in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of a file when it is read from system flash memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by copying a crafted file to the disk0: file system of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected device after the next reload of the device, which could alter system behavior. Because the injected code could persist across device reboots, Cisco has raised the Security Impact Rating (SIR) of this advisory from Medium to High.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20359|2024-08-01T21:59:42.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20293|2024-08-01T21:59:41.290Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the activation of an access control list (ACL) on Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the protection that is offered by a configured ACL on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an ACL changes from inactive to active in the running configuration of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device that should be denied by the configured ACL. The reverse condition is also true—traffic that should be permitted could be denied by the configured ACL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL protections on the affected device, allowing the attacker to access trusted networks that the device might be protecting. Note: This vulnerability applies to both IPv4 and IPv6 traffic as well as dual-stack ACL configurations in which both IPv4 and IPv6 ACLs are configured on an interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20293|2024-08-01T21:59:41.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20358|2024-08-01T21:59:42.299Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20358</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) restore functionality that is available in Cisco ASA Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because the contents of a backup file are improperly sanitized at restore time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20358|2024-08-01T21:59:42.299Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20353|2024-08-01T21:59:41.487Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20353</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the management and VPN web servers for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incomplete error checking when parsing an HTTP header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to a targeted web server on a device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition when the device reloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20353|2024-08-01T21:59:41.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
