<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS System Software in ACI Mode 11.0(1b)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20nx-os%20system%20software%20in%20aci%20mode%2011.0%281b%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS System Software in ACI Mode 11.0(1b)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 04:24:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1228|2024-09-17T01:41:37.379Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20system%20software%20in%20aci%20mode%2011.0%281b%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1228</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the fabric infrastructure VLAN connection establishment of Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches in Application Centric Infrastructure (ACI) Mode could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass security validations and connect an unauthorized server to the infrastructure VLAN. This vulnerability is due to insufficient security requirements during the Link Layer Discovery Protocol (LLDP) setup phase of the infrastructure VLAN. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted LLDP packet on the adjacent subnet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to connect an unauthorized server to the infrastructure VLAN, which is highly privileged. With a connection to the infrastructure VLAN, the attacker can make unauthorized connections to Cisco Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC) services or join other host endpoints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1228|2024-09-17T01:41:37.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 19:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
