<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco BroadWorks</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20broadworks.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco BroadWorks</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:19:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1562|2024-08-03T16:18:10.314Z -- cisco -- cisco%20broadworks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1562</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the XSI-Actions interface of Cisco BroadWorks Application Server could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive information on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to improper input validation and authorization of specific commands that a user can execute within the XSI-Actions interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to an affected device and issuing a specific set of commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to join a Call Center instance and have calls that they do not have permissions to access distributed to them from the Call Center queue. At the time of publication, Cisco had not released updates that address this vulnerability for Cisco BroadWorks Application Server. However, firmware patches are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1562|2024-08-03T16:18:10.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20869|2024-08-03T02:24:50.289Z -- cisco -- cisco%20broadworks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20869</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco BroadWorks Application Delivery Platform Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting attack against a user of the interface. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20869|2024-08-03T02:24:50.289Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1530|2024-08-03T16:11:17.685Z -- cisco -- cisco%20broadworks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1530</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco BroadWorks Messaging Server Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive information or cause a partial denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to improper handling of XML External Entity (XXE) entries when parsing certain XML files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a crafted XML file that contains references to external entities. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve files from the local system, resulting in the disclosure of sensitive information, or cause the application to consume available resources, resulting in a partial DoS condition on an affected system. There are workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1530|2024-08-03T16:11:17.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20951|2024-08-03T02:31:58.349Z -- cisco -- cisco%20broadworks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20951</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco BroadWorks CommPilot application could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the web interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain confidential information from the BroadWorks server and other device on the network.&#13;
&#13;    &#13;
&#13;  {{value}} ["%7b%7bvalue%7d%7d"])}]]&#13;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20951|2024-08-03T02:31:58.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 19:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20958|2024-08-03T02:31:58.862Z -- cisco -- cisco%20broadworks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20958</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco BroadWorks CommPilot application could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to perform a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the web interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain confidential information from the BroadWorks server and other device on the network.&#13;
&#13;    &#13;
&#13;  {{value}} ["%7b%7bvalue%7d%7d"])}]]&#13;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20958|2024-08-03T02:31:58.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 19:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
