<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco BroadWorks</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20broadworks.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco BroadWorks</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:23:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20204|2024-08-02T09:05:35.986Z -- cisco -- cisco%20broadworks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20204</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco BroadWorks CommPilot Application Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20204|2024-08-02T09:05:35.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 21:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20216|2024-08-02T09:05:36.141Z -- cisco -- cisco%20broadworks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20216</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the privilege management functionality of all Cisco BroadWorks server types could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected system. &#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect implementation of user role permissions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application as a user with the BWORKS or BWSUPERADMIN role and issuing crafted commands on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands beyond the sphere of their intended access level, including initiating installs or running operating system commands with elevated permissions.&#13;
&#13;   There are workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20216|2024-08-02T09:05:36.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 21:18:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20238|2024-08-02T09:05:36.796Z -- cisco -- cisco%20broadworks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20238</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the single sign-on (SSO) implementation of Cisco BroadWorks Application Delivery Platform and Cisco BroadWorks Xtended Services Platform could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to forge the credentials required to access an affected system.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the method used to validate SSO tokens. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application with forged credentials. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to commit toll fraud or to execute commands at the privilege level of the forged account. If that account is an Administrator account, the attacker would have the ability to view confidential information, modify customer settings, or modify settings for other users. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need a valid user ID that is associated with an affected Cisco BroadWorks system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20238|2024-08-02T09:05:36.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 17:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20019|2024-08-02T08:57:35.601Z -- cisco -- cisco%20broadworks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20019</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco BroadWorks Application Delivery Platform, Cisco BroadWorks Application Server, and Cisco BroadWorks Xtended Services Platform could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20019|2024-08-02T08:57:35.601Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 01:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20210|2024-08-02T09:05:36.936Z -- cisco -- cisco%20broadworks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20210</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco BroadWorks could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to the root user on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the operating system CLI. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by issuing a crafted command to the affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands as the root user. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have valid BroadWorks administrative privileges on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20210|2024-08-02T09:05:36.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 13:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20020|2024-08-02T08:57:35.651Z -- cisco -- cisco%20broadworks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20020</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Device Management Servlet application of Cisco BroadWorks Application Delivery Platform and Cisco BroadWorks Xtended Services Platform could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation when parsing HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a sustained stream of crafted requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause all subsequent requests to be dropped, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20020|2024-08-02T08:57:35.651Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 01:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
