<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN vManage</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN vManage</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 18:24:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27128|2024-08-04T16:11:35.676Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27128</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the application data endpoints of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to write arbitrary files to an affected system. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of requests to APIs. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests to an API within the affected application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct directory traversal attacks and write files to an arbitrary location on the targeted system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27128|2024-08-04T16:11:35.676Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3180|2024-08-04T07:24:00.870Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3180</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN Solution Software could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker to access an affected device by using an account that has a default, static password. This account has root privileges. The vulnerability exists because the affected software has a user account with a default, static password. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by remotely connecting to an affected system by using this account. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to log in by using this account with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3180|2024-08-04T07:24:00.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3372|2024-08-04T07:30:58.418Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3372</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to consume excessive system memory and cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to inefficient memory management. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of crafted HTTP requests to the affected web-based management interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust system memory, which could cause the system to stop processing new connections and could result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3372|2024-08-04T07:30:58.418Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34700|2024-08-04T00:19:48.141Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34700</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to read arbitrary files on the underlying file system of an affected system. This vulnerability exists because access to sensitive information on an affected system is not sufficiently controlled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by gaining unauthorized access to sensitive information on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to create forged authentication requests and gain unauthorized access to the web UI of an affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34700|2024-08-04T00:19:48.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3437|2024-08-04T07:37:53.976Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3437</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to read arbitrary files on the underlying filesystem of the device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient file scope limiting. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by creating a specific file reference on the filesystem and then accessing it through the web-based management interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read arbitrary files from the filesystem of the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3437|2024-08-04T07:37:53.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3590|2024-08-04T07:37:55.565Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3590</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of the Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3590|2024-08-04T07:37:55.565Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26064|2024-08-04T15:49:06.698Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26064</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to gain read and write access to information that is stored on an affected system.&#13;
 The vulnerability is due to improper handling of XML External Entity (XXE) entries when parsing certain XML files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to import a crafted XML file with malicious entries. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read and write files within the affected application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26064|2024-08-04T15:49:06.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 20:52:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3592|2024-08-04T07:37:55.693Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3592</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to bypass authorization and modify the configuration of an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization checking on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to the web-based management interface of an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain privileges beyond what would normally be authorized for their configured user authorization level. This could allow the attacker to modify the configuration of an affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3592|2024-08-04T07:37:55.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27129|2024-08-04T16:11:35.401Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27129</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the remote management feature of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject arbitrary commands and potentially gain elevated privileges. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of commands to the remote management CLI of the affected application. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests to the affected application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to inject arbitrary commands and potentially gain elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27129|2024-08-04T16:11:35.401Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3579|2024-08-04T07:37:55.467Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3579</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3579|2024-08-04T07:37:55.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3591|2024-08-04T07:37:55.721Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3591</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of the Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3591|2024-08-04T07:37:55.721Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3388|2024-08-04T07:30:58.382Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3388</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject arbitrary commands that are executed with root privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and submitting crafted input to the CLI. The attacker must be authenticated to access the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3388|2024-08-04T07:30:58.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26065|2024-08-04T15:49:07.107Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26065</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct path traversal attacks and obtain read access to sensitive files on an affected system.&#13;
 The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request that contains directory traversal character sequences to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view arbitrary files on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26065|2024-08-04T15:49:07.107Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 20:51:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34712|2024-08-04T00:19:48.126Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34712</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct cypher query language injection attacks on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to the interface of an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34712|2024-08-04T00:19:48.126Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3401|2024-08-04T07:30:58.404Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3401</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct path traversal attacks and obtain read access to sensitive files on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request that contains directory traversal character sequences to the affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view arbitrary files on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3401|2024-08-04T07:30:58.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3374|2024-08-04T07:30:58.167Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3374</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to bypass authorization, enabling them to access sensitive information, modify the system configuration, or impact the availability of the affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization checking on the affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to the web-based management interface of an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain privileges beyond what would normally be authorized for their configured user authorization level. The attacker may be able to access sensitive information, modify the system configuration, or impact the availability of the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3374|2024-08-04T07:30:58.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3375|2024-08-04T07:30:58.207Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3375</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN Solution Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a buffer overflow on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to information that they are not authorized to access, make changes to the system that they are not authorized to make, and execute commands on an affected system with privileges of the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3375|2024-08-04T07:30:58.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3405|2024-08-04T07:30:58.382Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3405</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to gain read and write access to information that is stored on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of XML External Entity (XXE) entries when parsing certain XML files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to import a crafted XML file with malicious entries. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read and write files within the affected application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3405|2024-08-04T07:30:58.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3387|2024-08-04T07:30:58.197Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3387</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute code with root privileges on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input sanitization during user authentication processing. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted response to the Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access the software and execute commands they should not be authorized to execute.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3387|2024-08-04T07:30:58.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3587|2024-08-04T07:37:55.602Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3587</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of the Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3587|2024-08-04T07:37:55.602Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3536|2024-08-04T07:37:54.975Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3536</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting malicious data into a specific data field in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3536|2024-08-04T07:37:54.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3406|2024-08-04T07:30:58.164Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3406</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of the Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3406|2024-08-04T07:30:58.164Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3381|2024-08-04T07:30:58.206Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3381</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct directory traversal attacks and obtain read and write access to sensitive files on a targeted system. The vulnerability is due to a lack of proper validation of files that are uploaded to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a crafted file to an affected system. An exploit could allow the attacker to view or modify arbitrary files on the targeted system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3381|2024-08-04T07:30:58.206Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3378|2024-08-04T07:30:58.207Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3378</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface for Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to impact the integrity of an affected system by executing arbitrary SQL queries. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input that includes SQL statements to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify entries in some database tables, affecting the integrity of the data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3378|2024-08-04T07:30:58.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3468|2024-08-04T07:37:54.873Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3468</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface improperly validates values within SQL queries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application and sending malicious SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify values on or return values from the underlying database or the operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3468|2024-08-04T07:37:54.873Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
