<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XR Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20xr%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XR Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:19:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20714|2024-08-03T02:24:49.450Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20714</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data plane microcode of Lightspeed-Plus line cards for Cisco ASR 9000 Series Aggregation Services Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the line card to reset. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of malformed packets that are received on the Lightspeed-Plus line cards. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPv4 or IPv6 packet through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Lightspeed-Plus line card to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition for any traffic that traverses that line card.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20714|2024-08-03T02:24:49.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1128|2024-08-03T16:02:55.389Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1128</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI parser of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to view more information than their privileges allow. The vulnerability is due to insufficient application of restrictions during the execution of a specific command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using a specific command at the command line. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain sensitive information within the configuration that otherwise might not have been accessible beyond the privileges of the invoking user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1128|2024-08-03T16:02:55.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1389|2024-08-03T16:11:17.022Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1389</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv6 traffic processing of Cisco IOS XR Software and Cisco NX-OS Software for certain Cisco devices could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass an IPv6 access control list (ACL) that is configured for an interface of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper processing of IPv6 traffic that is sent through an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted IPv6 packets that traverse the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources that would typically be protected by the interface ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1389|2024-08-03T16:11:17.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1243|2024-08-03T16:02:56.218Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1243</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Local Packet Transport Services (LPTS) programming of the SNMP with the management plane protection feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to allow connections despite the management plane protection that is configured to deny access to the SNMP server of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to incorrect LPTS programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to an affected device using SNMP. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to connect to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Valid credentials are required to execute any of the SNMP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1243|2024-08-03T16:02:56.218Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1370|2024-08-03T16:11:16.879Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1370</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a CLI command of Cisco IOS XR Software for the Cisco 8000 Series Routers and Network Convergence System 540 Series Routers running NCS540L software images could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate their privilege to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have a valid account on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of command line arguments. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and entering a crafted command at the prompt. A successful exploit could allow an attacker with low-level privileges to escalate their privilege level to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1370|2024-08-03T16:11:16.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20758|2024-08-03T02:24:49.409Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20758</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) Ethernet VPN (EVPN) functionality in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect processing of a BGP update message that contains specific EVPN attributes. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a BGP update message that contains specific EVPN attributes. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must control a BGP speaker that has an established trusted peer connection to an affected device that is configured with the address family L2VPN EVPN to receive and process the update message. This vulnerability cannot be exploited by any data that is initiated by clients on the Layer 2 network or by peers that are not configured to accept the L2VPN EVPN address family. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the BGP process to restart unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition. The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP updates only from explicitly defined peers. For this vulnerability to be exploited, the malicious BGP update message must either come from a configured, valid BGP peer or be injected by the attacker into the affected BGP network on an existing, valid TCP connection to a BGP peer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20758|2024-08-03T02:24:49.409Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1288|2024-08-03T16:02:56.384Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1288</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the ingress packet processing function of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1288|2024-08-03T16:02:56.384Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1136|2024-08-03T16:02:55.367Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1136</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) 540 Series Routers, only when running Cisco IOS XR NCS540L software images, and Cisco IOS XR Software for the Cisco 8000 Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute unsigned code during the boot process on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1136|2024-08-03T16:02:55.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1244|2024-08-03T16:02:56.352Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1244</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) 540 Series Routers, only when running Cisco IOS XR NCS540L software images, and Cisco IOS XR Software for the Cisco 8000 Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute unsigned code during the boot process on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1244|2024-08-03T16:02:56.352Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1313|2024-08-03T16:02:56.416Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1313</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the ingress packet processing function of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1313|2024-08-03T16:02:56.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20821|2024-08-03T02:24:49.991Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20821</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the health check RPM of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access the Redis instance that is running within the NOSi container. This vulnerability exists because the health check RPM opens TCP port 6379 by default upon activation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the Redis instance on the open port. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to write to the Redis in-memory database, write arbitrary files to the container filesystem, and retrieve information about the Redis database. Given the configuration of the sandboxed container that the Redis instance runs in, a remote attacker would be unable to execute remote code or abuse the integrity of the Cisco IOS XR Software host system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20821|2024-08-03T02:24:49.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1485|2024-08-03T16:11:17.330Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1485</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject arbitrary commands that are executed with root privileges on the underlying Linux operating system (OS) of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of commands that are supplied by the user. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to a device and submitting crafted input to an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands on the underlying Linux OS with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1485|2024-08-03T16:11:17.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1268|2024-08-03T16:02:56.375Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1268</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv6 protocol handling of the management interfaces of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an IPv6 flood on the management interface network of an affected device. The vulnerability exists because the software incorrectly forwards IPv6 packets that have an IPv6 node-local multicast group address destination and are received on the management interfaces. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the same network as the management interfaces and injecting IPv6 packets that have an IPv6 node-local multicast group address destination. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an IPv6 flood on the corresponding network. Depending on the number of Cisco IOS XR Software nodes on that network segment, exploitation could cause excessive network traffic, resulting in network degradation or a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1268|2024-08-03T16:02:56.375Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20322|2024-08-02T19:49:57.842Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20322</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on Pseudowire interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20322|2024-08-02T19:49:57.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20319|2024-08-01T21:59:41.556Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20319</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured management plane protection policies and access the Simple Network Management Plane (SNMP) server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect UDP forwarding programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to perform an SNMP operation using broadcast as the destination address that could be processed by an affected device that is configured with an SNMP server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to communicate to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Although an unauthenticated attacker could send UDP datagrams to the configured SNMP port, only an authenticated user can retrieve or modify data using SNMP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20319|2024-08-01T21:59:41.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20320|2024-08-01T21:59:42.846Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20320</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSH client feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco 8000 Series Routers and Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) 540 Series and 5700 Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are included with the SSH client CLI command. An attacker with low-privileged access to an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by issuing a crafted SSH client command to the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20320|2024-08-01T21:59:42.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20322|2024-08-01T21:59:41.959Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20322</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on Pseudowire interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20322|2024-08-01T21:59:41.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20327|2024-08-01T21:59:42.888Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20327</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the PPP over Ethernet (PPPoE) termination feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco ASR 9000 Series Aggregation Services Routers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the improper handling of malformed PPPoE packets that are received on a router that is running Broadband Network Gateway (BNG) functionality with PPPoE termination on a Lightspeed-based or Lightspeed-Plus-based line card. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted PPPoE packet to an affected line card interface that does not terminate PPPoE. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a DoS condition for PPPoE traffic across the router.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20327|2024-08-01T21:59:42.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20266|2024-08-01T21:52:31.683Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20266</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP version 4 (DHCPv4) server feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a crash of the dhcpd process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because certain DHCPv4 messages are improperly validated when they are processed by an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed DHCPv4 message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a crash of the dhcpd process. While the dhcpd process is restarting, which may take approximately two minutes, DHCPv4 server services are unavailable on the affected device. This could temporarily prevent network access to clients that join the network during that time period and rely on the DHCPv4 server of the affected device.
&#13; Notes: 
&#13; &#13; Only the dhcpd process crashes and eventually restarts automatically. The router does not reload.&#13; This vulnerability only applies to DHCPv4. DHCP version 6 (DHCPv6) is not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20266|2024-08-01T21:52:31.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20262|2024-08-01T21:52:31.788Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20262</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Copy Protocol (SCP) and SFTP feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to create or overwrite files in a system directory, which could lead to a denial of service (DoS) condition. The attacker would require valid user credentials to perform this attack.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper validation of SCP and SFTP CLI input parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and issuing SCP or SFTP CLI commands with specific parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to impact the functionality of the device, which could lead to a DoS condition. The device may need to be manually rebooted to recover.
&#13; Note: This vulnerability is exploitable only when a local user invokes SCP or SFTP commands at the Cisco IOS XR CLI. A local user with administrative privileges could exploit this vulnerability remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20262|2024-08-01T21:52:31.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-08-01T21:59:42.190Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-08-01T21:59:42.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20318|2024-08-01T21:59:41.382Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20318</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Layer 2 Ethernet services of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the line card network processor to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific Ethernet frames that are received on line cards that have the Layer 2 services feature enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific Ethernet frames through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ingress interface network processor to reset, resulting in a loss of traffic over the interfaces that are supported by the network processor. Multiple resets of the network processor would cause the line card to reset, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20318|2024-08-01T21:59:41.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20315|2024-08-01T21:59:41.535Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20315</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on MPLS interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20315|2024-08-01T21:59:41.535Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-12T03:55:19.039Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-12T03:55:19.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T14:40:37.931Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T14:40:37.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20318|2024-07-05T17:22:18.112Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20318</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Layer 2 Ethernet services of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the line card network processor to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific Ethernet frames that are received on line cards that have the Layer 2 services feature enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific Ethernet frames through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ingress interface network processor to reset, resulting in a loss of traffic over the interfaces that are supported by the network processor. Multiple resets of the network processor would cause the line card to reset, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20318|2024-07-05T17:22:18.112Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20319|2024-06-21T18:49:10.353Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20319</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured management plane protection policies and access the Simple Network Management Plane (SNMP) server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect UDP forwarding programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to perform an SNMP operation using broadcast as the destination address that could be processed by an affected device that is configured with an SNMP server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to communicate to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Although an unauthenticated attacker could send UDP datagrams to the configured SNMP port, only an authenticated user can retrieve or modify data using SNMP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20319|2024-06-21T18:49:10.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20266|2024-03-13T16:42:27.815Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20266</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP version 4 (DHCPv4) server feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a crash of the dhcpd process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because certain DHCPv4 messages are improperly validated when they are processed by an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed DHCPv4 message to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a crash of the dhcpd process. While the dhcpd process is restarting, which may take approximately two minutes, DHCPv4 server services are unavailable on the affected device. This could temporarily prevent network access to clients that join the network during that time period and rely on the DHCPv4 server of the affected device.
&#13; Notes: 
&#13; &#13; Only the dhcpd process crashes and eventually restarts automatically. The router does not reload.&#13; This vulnerability only applies to DHCPv4. DHCP version 6 (DHCPv6) is not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20266|2024-03-13T16:42:27.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20319|2024-03-13T16:47:09.543Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20319</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured management plane protection policies and access the Simple Network Management Plane (SNMP) server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect UDP forwarding programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to perform an SNMP operation using broadcast as the destination address that could be processed by an affected device that is configured with an SNMP server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to communicate to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Although an unauthenticated attacker could send UDP datagrams to the configured SNMP port, only an authenticated user can retrieve or modify data using SNMP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20319|2024-03-13T16:47:09.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20315|2024-03-13T16:45:58.046Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20315</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on MPLS interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20315|2024-03-13T16:45:58.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20318|2024-03-13T16:46:24.113Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20318</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Layer 2 Ethernet services of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the line card network processor to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific Ethernet frames that are received on line cards that have the Layer 2 services feature enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific Ethernet frames through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ingress interface network processor to reset, resulting in a loss of traffic over the interfaces that are supported by the network processor. Multiple resets of the network processor would cause the line card to reset, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20318|2024-03-13T16:46:24.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20322|2024-03-13T16:43:53.196Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20322</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on Pseudowire interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20322|2024-03-13T16:43:53.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20262|2024-06-04T17:40:27.162Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20262</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Copy Protocol (SCP) and SFTP feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to create or overwrite files in a system directory, which could lead to a denial of service (DoS) condition. The attacker would require valid user credentials to perform this attack.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper validation of SCP and SFTP CLI input parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and issuing SCP or SFTP CLI commands with specific parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to impact the functionality of the device, which could lead to a DoS condition. The device may need to be manually rebooted to recover.
&#13; Note: This vulnerability is exploitable only when a local user invokes SCP or SFTP commands at the Cisco IOS XR CLI. A local user with administrative privileges could exploit this vulnerability remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20262|2024-06-04T17:40:27.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20327|2024-06-04T17:40:27.563Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20327</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the PPP over Ethernet (PPPoE) termination feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco ASR 9000 Series Aggregation Services Routers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the improper handling of malformed PPPoE packets that are received on a router that is running Broadband Network Gateway (BNG) functionality with PPPoE termination on a Lightspeed-based or Lightspeed-Plus-based line card. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted PPPoE packet to an affected line card interface that does not terminate PPPoE. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the ppp_ma process, resulting in a DoS condition for PPPoE traffic across the router.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20327|2024-06-04T17:40:27.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20320|2024-03-13T16:41:52.488Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20320</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSH client feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco 8000 Series Routers and Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) 540 Series and 5700 Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are included with the SSH client CLI command. An attacker with low-privileged access to an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by issuing a crafted SSH client command to the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20320|2024-03-13T16:41:52.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20319|2024-07-02T16:26:46.466Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20319</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the UDP forwarding code of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass configured management plane protection policies and access the Simple Network Management Plane (SNMP) server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect UDP forwarding programming when using SNMP with management plane protection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to perform an SNMP operation using broadcast as the destination address that could be processed by an affected device that is configured with an SNMP server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to communicate to the device on the configured SNMP ports. Although an unauthenticated attacker could send UDP datagrams to the configured SNMP port, only an authenticated user can retrieve or modify data using SNMP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20319|2024-07-02T16:26:46.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-10T16:06:22.104Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-10T16:06:22.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T21:23:07.031Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T21:23:07.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20315|2024-07-19T17:25:44.385Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20315</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing on MPLS interfaces in the ingress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of lookup keys to internal interface contexts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources behind the affected device that were supposed to be protected by a configured ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20315|2024-07-19T17:25:44.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
