<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS System Software in ACI Mode</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20nx-os%20system%20software%20in%20aci%20mode.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS System Software in ACI Mode</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:25:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20185|2024-08-02T09:05:36.245Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20system%20software%20in%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20185</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco ACI Multi-Site CloudSec encryption feature of Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches in ACI mode could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to read or modify intersite encrypted traffic.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an issue with the implementation of the ciphers that are used by the CloudSec encryption feature on affected switches. An attacker with an on-path position between the ACI sites could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting intersite encrypted traffic and using cryptanalytic techniques to break the encryption. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read or modify the traffic that is transmitted between the sites.&#13;
&#13; Cisco has not released and will not release software updates that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20185|2024-08-02T09:05:36.245Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 13:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20089|2024-08-02T08:57:35.883Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20system%20software%20in%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20089</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Link Layer Discovery Protocol (LLDP) feature for Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches in Application Centric Infrastructure (ACI) Mode could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a memory leak, which could result in an unexpected reload of the device. This vulnerability is due to incorrect error checking when parsing ingress LLDP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a steady stream of crafted LLDP packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a memory leak, which could result in a denial of service (DoS) condition when the device unexpectedly reloads. Note: This vulnerability cannot be exploited by transit traffic through the device. The crafted LLDP packet must be targeted to a directly connected interface, and the attacker must be in the same broadcast domain as the affected device (Layer 2 adjacent). In addition, the attack surface for this vulnerability can be reduced by disabling LLDP on interfaces where it is not required.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20089|2024-08-02T08:57:35.883Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
