<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Data Center Network Manager</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20data%20center%20network%20manager.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Data Center Network Manager</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-20281|2024-04-03T16:20:04.470Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Data Center Network Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20281</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Nexus Dashboard and Cisco Nexus Dashboard hosted services could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privilege level of the affected user. If the affected user has administrative privileges, these actions could include modifying the system configuration and creating new privileged accounts.&#13;
&#13; Note: There are internal security mechanisms in place that limit the scope of this exploit, reducing the Security Impact Rating of this vulnerability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20281|2024-04-03T16:20:04.470Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:20:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20348|2024-04-03T16:25:38.367Z -- Cisco -- Cisco Data Center Network Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20348</link><description>A vulnerability in the Out-of-Band (OOB) Plug and Play (PnP) feature of Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to read arbitrary files.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an unauthenticated provisioning web server. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability through direct web requests to the provisioning server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read sensitive files in the PnP container that could facilitate further attacks on the PnP infrastructure.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20348|2024-04-03T16:25:38.367Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>