<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS System Software in ACI Mode</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20nx-os%20system%20software%20in%20aci%20mode.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS System Software in ACI Mode</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 18:24:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1586|2024-08-03T16:18:10.396Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20system%20software%20in%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1586</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Multi-Pod or Multi-Site network configurations for Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches in Application Centric Infrastructure (ACI) mode could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to unexpectedly restart the device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability exists because TCP traffic sent to a specific port on an affected device is not properly sanitized. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted TCP data to a specific port that is listening on a public-facing IP address for the Multi-Pod or Multi-Site configuration. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to restart unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1586|2024-08-03T16:18:10.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1584|2024-08-03T16:18:10.142Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20system%20software%20in%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1584</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches in Application Centric Infrastructure (ACI) mode could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient restrictions during the execution of a specific CLI command. An attacker with administrative privileges could exploit this vulnerability by performing a command injection attack on the vulnerable command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access the underlying operating system as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1584|2024-08-03T16:18:10.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1523|2024-08-03T16:11:17.669Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20system%20software%20in%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1523</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches in Application Centric Infrastructure (ACI) Mode could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a queue wedge on a leaf switch, which could result in critical control plane traffic to the device being dropped. This could result in one or more leaf switches being removed from the fabric. This vulnerability is due to mishandling of ingress TCP traffic to a specific port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a stream of TCP packets to a specific port on a Switched Virtual Interface (SVI) configured on the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a specific packet queue to queue network buffers but never process them, leading to an eventual queue wedge. This could cause control plane traffic to be dropped, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition where the leaf switches are unavailable. Note: This vulnerability requires a manual intervention to power-cycle the device to recover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1523|2024-08-03T16:11:17.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1231|2024-08-03T16:02:56.339Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20system%20software%20in%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1231</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Link Layer Discovery Protocol (LLDP) for Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches in Application Centric Infrastructure (ACI) mode could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to disable switching on a small form-factor pluggable (SFP) interface. This vulnerability is due to incomplete validation of the source of a received LLDP packet. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted LLDP packet on an SFP interface to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to disable switching on the SFP interface, which could disrupt network traffic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1231|2024-08-03T16:02:56.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1583|2024-08-03T16:18:10.371Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20system%20software%20in%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1583</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the fabric infrastructure file system access control of Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches in Application Centric Infrastructure (ACI) mode could allow an authenticated, local attacker to read arbitrary files on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to improper access control. An attacker with Administrator privileges could exploit this vulnerability by executing a specific vulnerable command on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read arbitrary files on the file system of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1583|2024-08-03T16:18:10.371Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1230|2024-08-03T16:02:56.062Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20system%20software%20in%20aci%20mode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1230</link>
      <description>A vulnerability with the Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) for Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches in Application Centric Infrastructure (ACI) mode could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a routing process to crash, which could lead to a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to an issue with the installation of routes upon receipt of a BGP update. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted BGP update to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the routing process to crash, which could cause the device to reload. This vulnerability applies to both Internal BGP (IBGP) and External BGP (EBGP). Note: The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP traffic from explicitly configured peers only. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to send a specific BGP update message over an established TCP connection that appears to come from a trusted BGP peer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1230|2024-08-03T16:02:56.062Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
