<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Webex Meetings</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20webex%20meetings.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Webex Meetings</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:42:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1526|2024-09-16T19:56:50.828Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1526</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Player for Windows and MacOS could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of values in Webex recording files that are in Webex Recording Format (WRF). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a user a malicious WRF file through a link or email attachment and persuading the user to open the file with the affected software on the local system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected system with the privileges of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1526|2024-09-16T19:56:50.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 16:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3182|2024-09-16T18:38:28.971Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3182</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multicast DNS (mDNS) protocol configuration of Cisco Webex Meetings Client for MacOS could allow an unauthenticated adjacent attacker to obtain sensitive information about the device on which the Webex client is running. The vulnerability exists because sensitive information is included in the mDNS reply. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by doing an mDNS query for a particular service against an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3182|2024-09-16T18:38:28.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 18:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3440|2024-09-16T16:33:21.587Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3440</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings Desktop App for Windows could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to overwrite arbitrary files on an end-user system. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of URL parameters that are sent from a website to the affected application. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to follow a URL to a website that is designed to submit crafted input to the affected application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite arbitrary files on the affected system, possibly corrupting or deleting critical system files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3440|2024-09-16T16:33:21.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 16:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20763|2024-09-16T20:32:18.701Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20763</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the login authorization components of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary Java code. This vulnerability is due to improper deserialization of Java code within login requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious login requests to the Cisco Webex Meetings service. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to inject arbitrary Java code and take arbitrary actions within the Cisco Webex Meetings application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20763|2024-09-16T20:32:18.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 18:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27126|2024-09-16T18:02:57.795Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27126</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in an API of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site scripting attacks. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input to an application programmatic interface (API) within Cisco Webex Meetings. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by convincing a targeted user to follow a link designed to submit malicious input to the API used by Cisco Webex Meetings. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct cross-site scripting attacks and potentially gain access to sensitive browser-based information from the system of a targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27126|2024-09-16T18:02:57.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 17:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1351|2024-09-16T18:03:27.715Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1351</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based interface of the affected service. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based interface of the affected service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a maliciously crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1351|2024-09-16T18:03:27.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 16:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3541|2024-09-16T19:51:02.206Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3541</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the media engine component of Cisco Webex Meetings Client for Windows, Cisco Webex Meetings Desktop App for Windows, and Cisco Webex Teams for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain access to sensitive information. The vulnerability is due to unsafe logging of authentication requests by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by reading log files that are stored in the application directory. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to sensitive information, which could be used in further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3541|2024-09-16T19:51:02.206Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 02:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40128|2024-09-16T19:41:46.068Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40128</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the account activation feature of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to send an account activation email with an activation link that points to an arbitrary domain. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the account activation page of Cisco Webex Meetings. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send to any recipient an account activation email that contains a tampered activation link, which could direct the user to an attacker-controlled website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40128|2024-09-16T19:41:46.068Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 15:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3413|2024-09-16T17:59:14.803Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3413</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the scheduled meeting template feature of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to delete a scheduled meeting template that belongs to another user in their organization. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization enforcement for requests to delete scheduled meeting templates. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the Webex Meetings interface to delete a scheduled meeting template. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to delete a scheduled meeting template that belongs to a user other than themselves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3413|2024-09-16T17:59:14.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 18:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
