<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XR Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20xr%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XR Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:25:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34708|2024-09-17T01:50:33.076Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34708</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in image verification checks of Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) 540 Series Routers, only when running Cisco IOS XR NCS540L software images, and Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco 8000 Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34708|2024-09-17T01:50:33.076Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 05:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1244|2024-09-17T03:07:13.696Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1244</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) 540 Series Routers, only when running Cisco IOS XR NCS540L software images, and Cisco IOS XR Software for the Cisco 8000 Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute unsigned code during the boot process on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1244|2024-09-17T03:07:13.696Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 16:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20758|2024-09-17T01:30:47.253Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20758</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) Ethernet VPN (EVPN) functionality in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect processing of a BGP update message that contains specific EVPN attributes. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a BGP update message that contains specific EVPN attributes. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must control a BGP speaker that has an established trusted peer connection to an affected device that is configured with the address family L2VPN EVPN to receive and process the update message. This vulnerability cannot be exploited by any data that is initiated by clients on the Layer 2 network or by peers that are not configured to accept the L2VPN EVPN address family. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the BGP process to restart unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition. The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP updates only from explicitly defined peers. For this vulnerability to be exploited, the malicious BGP update message must either come from a configured, valid BGP peer or be injected by the attacker into the affected BGP network on an existing, valid TCP connection to a BGP peer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20758|2024-09-17T01:30:47.253Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1918|2024-09-17T03:13:31.228Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1918</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of Intermediate System&amp;ndash;to&amp;ndash;Intermediate System (IS&amp;ndash;IS) routing protocol functionality in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated attacker who is in the same IS-IS area to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of IS&amp;ndash;IS link-state protocol data units (PDUs). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific link-state PDUs to an affected system to be processed. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause incorrect calculations used in the weighted remote shared risk link groups (SRLG) or in the IGP Flexible Algorithm. It could also cause tracebacks to the logs or potentially cause the receiving device to crash the IS&amp;ndash;IS process, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1918|2024-09-17T03:13:31.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 21:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16027|2024-09-17T03:37:41.247Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16027</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the Intermediate System&amp;ndash;to&amp;ndash;Intermediate System (IS&amp;ndash;IS) routing protocol functionality in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition in the IS&amp;ndash;IS process. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of a Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) request for specific Object Identifiers (OIDs) by the IS&amp;ndash;IS process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SNMP request to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition in the IS&amp;ndash;IS process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16027|2024-09-17T03:37:41.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 04:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16023|2024-09-17T04:03:40.756Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16023</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the implementation of Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) Ethernet VPN (EVPN) functionality in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerabilities are due to incorrect processing of BGP update messages that contain crafted EVPN attributes. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending BGP EVPN update messages with malformed attributes to be processed by an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the BGP process to restart unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition. The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP traffic only from explicitly defined peers. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the malicious BGP update message would need to come from a configured, valid BGP peer, or would need to be injected by the attacker into the victim's BGP network on an existing, valid TCP connection to a BGP peer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16023|2024-09-17T04:03:40.756Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16018|2024-09-17T03:49:16.577Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16018</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) Ethernet VPN (EVPN) functionality in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of a BGP update message that contains crafted EVPN attributes. An attacker could indirectly exploit the vulnerability by sending BGP EVPN update messages with a specific, malformed attribute to an affected system and waiting for a user on the device to display the EVPN operational routes&amp;rsquo; status. If successful, the attacker could cause the BGP process to restart unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition. The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP traffic only from explicitly defined peers. To exploit this vulnerability, the malicious BGP update message would need to come from a configured, valid BGP peer, or would need to be injected by the attacker into the victim's BGP network on an existing, valid TCP connection to a BGP peer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16018|2024-09-17T03:49:16.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 04:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34728|2024-09-17T02:27:35.219Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34728</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with a low-privileged account to elevate privileges on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34728|2024-09-17T02:27:35.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 05:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3566|2024-09-17T01:21:52.264Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3566</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Distance Vector Multicast Routing Protocol (DVMRP) feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to exhaust process memory of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient queue management for Internet Group Management Protocol (IGMP) packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted IGMP traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause memory exhaustion, resulting in instability of other processes. These processes may include, but are not limited to, interior and exterior routing protocols. Cisco will release software updates that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3566|2024-09-17T01:21:52.264Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 15:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15998|2024-09-17T04:19:13.174Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15998</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access-control logic of the NETCONF over Secure Shell (SSH) of Cisco IOS XR Software may allow connections despite an access control list (ACL) that is configured to deny access to the NETCONF over SSH of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a missing check in the NETCONF over SSH access control list (ACL). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to an affected device using NETCONF over SSH. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to connect to the device on the NETCONF port. Valid credentials are required to access the device. This vulnerability does not affect connections to the default SSH process on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15998|2024-09-17T04:19:13.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 03:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34719|2024-09-17T01:56:23.635Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34719</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with a low-privileged account to elevate privileges on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34719|2024-09-17T01:56:23.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 05:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20821|2024-09-17T01:30:49.057Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20821</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the health check RPM of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access the Redis instance that is running within the NOSi container. This vulnerability exists because the health check RPM opens TCP port 6379 by default upon activation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the Redis instance on the open port. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to write to the Redis in-memory database, write arbitrary files to the container filesystem, and retrieve information about the Redis database. Given the configuration of the sandboxed container that the Redis instance runs in, a remote attacker would be unable to execute remote code or abuse the integrity of the Cisco IOS XR Software host system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20821|2024-09-17T01:30:49.057Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 14:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20714|2024-09-17T01:25:46.603Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20714</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data plane microcode of Lightspeed-Plus line cards for Cisco ASR 9000 Series Aggregation Services Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the line card to reset. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of malformed packets that are received on the Lightspeed-Plus line cards. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPv4 or IPv6 packet through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Lightspeed-Plus line card to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition for any traffic that traverses that line card.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20714|2024-09-17T01:25:46.603Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1712|2024-09-17T00:56:45.730Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1712</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Protocol Independent Multicast (PIM) feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the PIM process to restart, resulting in a denial of service condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to the incorrect processing of crafted AutoRP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted packets to port UDP 496 on a reachable IP address on the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the PIM process to restart. Software versions prior to 6.2.3, 6.3.2, 6.4.0, and 6.5.1 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1712|2024-09-17T00:56:45.730Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 22:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15989|2024-09-17T01:25:31.603Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15989</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) functionality in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of a BGP update message that contains a specific BGP attribute. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending BGP update messages that include a specific, malformed attribute to be processed by an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the BGP process to restart unexpectedly, resulting in a DoS condition. The Cisco implementation of BGP accepts incoming BGP traffic only from explicitly defined peers. To exploit this vulnerability, the malicious BGP update message would need to come from a configured, valid BGP peer or would need to be injected by the attacker into the victim&amp;rsquo;s BGP network on an existing, valid TCP connection to a BGP peer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15989|2024-09-17T01:25:31.603Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 04:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1849|2024-09-17T03:28:31.703Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1849</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Border Gateway Patrol (BGP) Multiprotocol Label Switching (MPLS)-based Ethernet VPN (EVPN) implementation of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when the affected software processes specific EVPN routing information. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious traffic patterns into the targeted EVPN network. A successful exploit could result in a crash of the l2vpn_mgr process on Provider Edge (PE) device members of the same EVPN instance (EVI). On each of the affected devices, a crash could lead to system instability and the inability to process or forward traffic through the device, resulting in a DoS condition that would require manual intervention to restore normal operating conditions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1849|2024-09-17T03:28:31.703Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 01:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1268|2024-09-17T03:17:56.629Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1268</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv6 protocol handling of the management interfaces of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an IPv6 flood on the management interface network of an affected device. The vulnerability exists because the software incorrectly forwards IPv6 packets that have an IPv6 node-local multicast group address destination and are received on the management interfaces. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the same network as the management interfaces and injecting IPv6 packets that have an IPv6 node-local multicast group address destination. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an IPv6 flood on the corresponding network. Depending on the number of Cisco IOS XR Software nodes on that network segment, exploitation could cause excessive network traffic, resulting in network degradation or a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1268|2024-09-17T03:17:56.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 16:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3120|2024-09-17T00:10:55.655Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3120</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Discovery Protocol implementation for Cisco FXOS Software, Cisco IOS XR Software, and Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to a missing check when the affected software processes Cisco Discovery Protocol messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious Cisco Discovery Protocol packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust system memory, causing the device to reload. Cisco Discovery Protocol is a Layer 2 protocol. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must be in the same broadcast domain as the affected device (Layer 2 adjacent).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3120|2024-09-17T00:10:55.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 17:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20304|2024-09-11T20:11:14.196Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20304</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multicast traceroute version 2 (Mtrace2) feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to exhaust the UDP packet memory of an affected device.

This vulnerability exists because the Mtrace2 code does not properly handle packet memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust the incoming UDP packet memory. The affected device would not be able to process higher-level UDP-based protocols packets, possibly causing a denial of service (DoS) condition.
Note: This vulnerability can be exploited using IPv4 or IPv6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20304|2024-09-11T20:11:14.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20398|2024-09-11T20:49:51.265Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20398</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to obtain read/write file system access on the underlying operating system of an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user arguments that are passed to specific CLI commands. An attacker with a low-privileged account could exploit this vulnerability by using crafted commands at the prompt. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20398|2024-09-11T20:49:51.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20317|2024-09-11T20:38:58.530Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20317</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the handling of specific Ethernet frames by Cisco IOS XR Software for various Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) platforms could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause critical priority packets to be dropped, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.

This vulnerability is due to incorrect classification of certain types of Ethernet frames that are received on an interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific types of Ethernet frames to or through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause control plane protocol relationships to fail, resulting in a DoS condition. For more information, see the  section of this advisory.
Cisco has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20317|2024-09-11T20:38:58.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:38:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20406|2024-09-11T20:38:41.758Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20406</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the segment routing feature for the Intermediate System-to-Intermediate System (IS-IS) protocol of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of ingress IS-IS packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific IS-IS packets to an affected device after forming an adjacency. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the IS-IS process on all affected devices that are participating in the Flexible Algorithm to crash and restart, resulting in a DoS condition.
Note: The IS-IS protocol is a routing protocol. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must be Layer 2-adjacent to the affected device and must have formed an adjacency. This vulnerability affects segment routing for IS-IS over IPv4 and IPv6 control planes as well as devices that are configured as level 1, level 2, or multi-level routing IS-IS type.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20406|2024-09-11T20:38:41.758Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20489|2024-09-11T20:12:26.719Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20489</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the storage method of the PON Controller configuration file could allow an authenticated, local attacker with low privileges to obtain the MongoDB credentials.

This vulnerability is due to improper storage of the unencrypted database credentials on the device that is running Cisco IOS XR Software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the configuration files on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view MongoDB credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20489|2024-09-11T20:12:26.719Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20343|2024-09-11T20:41:38.914Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20343</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to read any file in the file system of the underlying Linux operating system. The attacker must have valid credentials on the affected device.

This vulnerability is due to incorrect validation of the arguments that are passed to a specific CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to an affected device with low-privileged credentials and using the affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker access files in read-only mode on the Linux file system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20343|2024-09-11T20:41:38.914Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20390|2024-09-11T20:53:46.046Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20390</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Dedicated XML Agent feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) on XML TCP listen port 38751.

This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper error validation of ingress XML packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a sustained, crafted stream of XML traffic to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause XML TCP port 38751 to become unreachable while the attack traffic persists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20390|2024-09-11T20:53:46.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20483|2024-09-11T20:14:01.129Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20483</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Routed PON Controller Software, which runs as a docker container on hardware that is supported by Cisco IOS XR Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with Administrator-level privileges on the PON Manager or direct access to the PON Manager MongoDB instance to perform command injection attacks on the PON Controller container and execute arbitrary commands as root.

These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration commands. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the PON controller.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20483|2024-09-11T20:14:01.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-08-01T21:59:42.190Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-08-01T21:59:42.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-12T03:55:19.039Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-12T03:55:19.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T14:40:37.931Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T14:40:37.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-10T16:06:22.104Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-10T16:06:22.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T21:23:07.031Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this successfully, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an error in the software build process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system&amp;rsquo;s configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass of the requirement to run Cisco signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20456|2024-07-11T21:23:07.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20483|2024-09-11T16:38:57.862Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20483</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Routed PON Controller Software, which runs as a docker container on hardware that is supported by Cisco IOS XR Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with Administrator-level privileges on the PON Manager or direct access to the PON Manager MongoDB instance to perform command injection attacks on the PON Controller container and execute arbitrary commands as root.

These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration commands. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the PON controller.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20483|2024-09-11T16:38:57.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20390|2024-09-11T16:38:15.320Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20390</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Dedicated XML Agent feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) on XML TCP listen port 38751.

This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper error validation of ingress XML packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a sustained, crafted stream of XML traffic to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause XML TCP port 38751 to become unreachable while the attack traffic persists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20390|2024-09-11T16:38:15.320Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20343|2024-09-11T16:38:06.326Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20343</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to read any file in the file system of the underlying Linux operating system. The attacker must have valid credentials on the affected device.

This vulnerability is due to incorrect validation of the arguments that are passed to a specific CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to an affected device with low-privileged credentials and using the affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker access files in read-only mode on the Linux file system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20343|2024-09-11T16:38:06.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20489|2024-09-11T16:39:06.449Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20489</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the storage method of the PON Controller configuration file could allow an authenticated, local attacker with low privileges to obtain the MongoDB credentials.

This vulnerability is due to improper storage of the unencrypted database credentials on the device that is running Cisco IOS XR Software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the configuration files on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view MongoDB credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20489|2024-09-11T16:39:06.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20406|2024-09-11T16:38:50.133Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20406</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the segment routing feature for the Intermediate System-to-Intermediate System (IS-IS) protocol of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of ingress IS-IS packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific IS-IS packets to an affected device after forming an adjacency. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the IS-IS process on all affected devices that are participating in the Flexible Algorithm to crash and restart, resulting in a DoS condition.
Note: The IS-IS protocol is a routing protocol. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must be Layer 2-adjacent to the affected device and must have formed an adjacency. This vulnerability affects segment routing for IS-IS over IPv4 and IPv6 control planes as well as devices that are configured as level 1, level 2, or multi-level routing IS-IS type.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20406|2024-09-11T16:38:50.133Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20317|2024-09-11T16:38:33.082Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20317</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the handling of specific Ethernet frames by Cisco IOS XR Software for various Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) platforms could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause critical priority packets to be dropped, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.

This vulnerability is due to incorrect classification of certain types of Ethernet frames that are received on an interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific types of Ethernet frames to or through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause control plane protocol relationships to fail, resulting in a DoS condition. For more information, see the  section of this advisory.
Cisco has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20317|2024-09-11T16:38:33.082Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:38:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20398|2024-09-11T16:38:23.982Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20398</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to obtain read/write file system access on the underlying operating system of an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user arguments that are passed to specific CLI commands. An attacker with a low-privileged account could exploit this vulnerability by using crafted commands at the prompt. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20398|2024-09-11T16:38:23.982Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20304|2024-09-11T16:39:54.503Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20304</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multicast traceroute version 2 (Mtrace2) feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to exhaust the UDP packet memory of an affected device.

This vulnerability exists because the Mtrace2 code does not properly handle packet memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust the incoming UDP packet memory. The affected device would not be able to process higher-level UDP-based protocols packets, possibly causing a denial of service (DoS) condition.
Note: This vulnerability can be exploited using IPv4 or IPv6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20304|2024-09-11T16:39:54.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20381|2024-09-11T16:38:42.096Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20381</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the JSON-RPC API feature in ConfD that is used by the web-based management interfaces of Cisco Crosswork Network Services Orchestrator (NSO), Cisco Optical Site Manager, and Cisco RV340 Dual WAN Gigabit VPN Routers could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to modify the configuration of an affected application or device.

This vulnerability is due to improper authorization checks on the API. An attacker with privileges sufficient to access the affected application or device could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests to the JSON-RPC API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to make unauthorized modifications to the configuration of the affected application or device, including creating new user accounts or elevating their own privileges on an affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20381|2024-09-11T16:38:42.096Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:38:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20398|2024-09-12T03:55:39.920Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xr%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20398</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to obtain read/write file system access on the underlying operating system of an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user arguments that are passed to specific CLI commands. An attacker with a low-privileged account could exploit this vulnerability by using crafted commands at the prompt. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20398|2024-09-12T03:55:39.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
