<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco TelePresence TC Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20telepresence%20tc%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco TelePresence TC Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:29:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15277|2024-08-05T00:42:00.512Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20tc%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15277</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute code with root privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating as the remote support user and sending malicious traffic to a listener who is internal to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15277|2024-08-05T00:42:00.512Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15273|2024-08-05T00:42:04.113Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20tc%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15273</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to overwrite arbitrary files. The vulnerabilities are due to insufficient permission enforcement. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by authenticating as the remote support user and submitting malicious input to specific commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite arbitrary files on the underlying filesystem. The attacker has no control over the contents of the data written to the file. Overwriting a critical file could cause the device to crash, resulting in a denial of service condition (DoS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15273|2024-08-05T00:42:04.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15275|2024-08-05T00:42:03.598Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20tc%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15275</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating as the remote support user and submitting malicious input to a specific command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system (OS) with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15275|2024-08-05T00:42:03.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15288|2024-08-05T00:42:03.684Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20tc%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15288</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE), Cisco TelePresence Codec (TC), and Cisco RoomOS Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to escalate privileges to an unrestricted user of the restricted shell. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including specific arguments when opening an SSH connection to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain unrestricted user access to the restricted shell of an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15288|2024-08-05T00:42:03.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15274|2024-08-05T00:42:03.607Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20tc%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15274</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injections. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating as an administrative level user within the restricted shell and submitting malicious input to a specific command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute previously staged code from the underlying filesystem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15274|2024-08-05T00:42:03.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15962|2024-08-05T01:03:32.417Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20tc%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15962</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to write files to the /root directory of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper permission assignment. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in as the remotesupport user and writing files to the /root directory of an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15962|2024-08-05T01:03:32.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15289|2024-08-05T00:42:04.079Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20tc%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15289</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the video service of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) and Cisco RoomOS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerabilities are due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted traffic to the video service of an affected endpoint. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the video service to crash, resulting in a DoS condition on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15289|2024-08-05T00:42:04.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15967|2024-08-05T01:03:32.660Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20tc%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15967</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) and Cisco RoomOS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to enable audio recording without notifying users. The vulnerability is due to the presence of unnecessary debug commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by gaining unrestricted access to the restricted shell and using the specific debug commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to enable the microphone of an affected device to record audio without notifying users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15967|2024-08-05T01:03:32.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
