<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Identity Services Engine Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Identity Services Engine Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 13:23:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20087|2024-08-02T08:57:35.556Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20087</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to download arbitrary files from the filesystem of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted HTTP requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to download arbitrary files from the underlying filesystem of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20087|2024-08-02T08:57:35.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20077|2024-08-02T08:57:35.817Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20077</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to download arbitrary files from the filesystem of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted HTTP requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to download arbitrary files from the underlying filesystem of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20077|2024-08-02T08:57:35.817Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20111|2024-08-02T08:57:35.734Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20111</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive information.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the improper storage of sensitive information within the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to the web-based management interface and viewing hidden fields within the application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access sensitive information, including device entry credentials, that could aid the attacker in further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20111|2024-08-02T08:57:35.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20170|2024-08-02T09:05:35.023Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20170</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a specific Cisco ISE CLI command could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have valid Administrator-level privileges on the affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20170|2024-08-02T09:05:35.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20272|2024-08-02T09:05:36.852Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20272</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload malicious files to the web root of the application. This vulnerability is due to insufficient file input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a malicious file to the web interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to replace files and gain access to sensitive server-side information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20272|2024-08-02T09:05:36.852Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:49:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20228|2024-08-02T09:05:35.864Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20228</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of an affected interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the browser of the targeted user or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20228|2024-08-02T09:05:35.864Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 20:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20243|2024-08-02T09:05:36.120Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20243</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the RADIUS message processing feature of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the affected system to stop processing RADIUS packets.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain RADIUS accounting requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted authentication request to a network access device (NAD) that uses Cisco ISE for authentication, authorization, and accounting (AAA). This would eventually result in the NAD sending a RADIUS accounting request packet to Cisco ISE. An attacker could also exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted RADIUS accounting request packet to Cisco ISE directly if the RADIUS shared secret is known. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the RADIUS process to unexpectedly restart, resulting in authentication or authorization timeouts and denying legitimate users access to the network or service. Clients already authenticated to the network would not be affected.&#13;
&#13; Note: To recover the ability to process RADIUS packets, a manual restart of the affected Policy Service Node (PSN) may be required. For more information, see the Details ["#details"] section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20243|2024-08-02T09:05:36.120Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 17:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20164|2024-08-02T09:05:35.604Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20164</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid credentials on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20164|2024-08-02T09:05:35.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20196|2024-08-02T09:05:36.920Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20196</link>
      <description>Two vulnerabilities in Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by uploading a crafted file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files in specific directories on the device. The attacker could later use those files to conduct additional attacks, including executing arbitrary code on the affected device with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20196|2024-08-02T09:05:36.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20085|2024-08-02T08:57:35.869Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20085</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20085|2024-08-02T08:57:35.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 15:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20167|2024-08-02T09:05:35.793Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20167</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated attacker to perform path traversal attacks on the underlying operating system to either elevate privileges to root or read arbitrary files. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20167|2024-08-02T09:05:35.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20171|2024-08-02T09:05:35.559Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20171</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated attacker to delete or read arbitrary files on the underlying operating system. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid credentials on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20171|2024-08-02T09:05:35.559Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20022|2024-08-02T08:57:35.837Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20022</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in specific Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) CLI commands could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid Administrator privileges on the affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by submitting a crafted CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20022|2024-08-02T08:57:35.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20193|2024-08-02T09:05:36.896Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20193</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Embedded Service Router (ESR) of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, local attacker to read, write, or delete arbitrary files on the underlying operating system and escalate their privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have valid Administrator-level privileges on the affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper privilege management in the ESR console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate their privileges to root and read, write, or delete arbitrary files from the underlying operating system of the affected device. Note: The ESR is not enabled by default and must be licensed. To verify the status of the ESR in the Admin GUI, choose Administration &gt; Settings &gt; Protocols &gt; IPSec.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20193|2024-08-02T09:05:36.896Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 19:29:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20021|2024-08-02T08:57:35.556Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20021</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in specific Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) CLI commands could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid Administrator privileges on the affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by submitting a crafted CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20021|2024-08-02T08:57:35.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20166|2024-08-02T09:05:35.024Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20166</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated attacker to perform path traversal attacks on the underlying operating system to either elevate privileges to root or read arbitrary files. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20166|2024-08-02T09:05:35.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20173|2024-08-02T09:05:35.636Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20173</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to read arbitrary files or conduct a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack through an affected device. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20173|2024-08-02T09:05:35.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20208|2024-08-02T09:05:35.585Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20208</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20208|2024-08-02T09:05:35.585Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20152|2024-08-02T09:05:35.010Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20152</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in specific Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) CLI commands could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid Administrator privileges on the affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by submitting a crafted CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20152|2024-08-02T09:05:35.010Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20023|2024-08-02T08:57:35.576Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20023</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in specific Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) CLI commands could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid Administrator privileges on the affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by submitting a crafted CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20023|2024-08-02T08:57:35.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20122|2024-08-02T08:57:35.682Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20122</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the restricted shell of Cisco Evolved Programmable Network Manager (EPNM), Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE), and Cisco Prime Infrastructure could allow an authenticated, local attacker to escape the restricted shell and gain root privileges on the underlying operating system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20122|2024-08-02T08:57:35.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20194|2024-08-02T09:05:36.240Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20194</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the ERS API of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to read arbitrary files on the underlying operating system of an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have valid Administrator-level privileges on the affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper privilege management in the ERS API. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate their privileges beyond the sphere of their intended access level, which would allow them to obtain sensitive information from the underlying operating system. Note: The ERS is not enabled by default. To verify the status of the ERS API in the Admin GUI, choose Administration &gt; Settings &gt; API Settings &gt; API Service Settings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20194|2024-08-02T09:05:36.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 19:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20195|2024-08-02T09:05:35.963Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20195</link>
      <description>Two vulnerabilities in Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by uploading a crafted file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files in specific directories on the device. The attacker could later use those files to conduct additional attacks, including executing arbitrary code on the affected device with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20195|2024-08-02T09:05:35.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20172|2024-08-02T09:05:35.028Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20172</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated attacker to delete or read arbitrary files on the underlying operating system. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid credentials on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20172|2024-08-02T09:05:35.028Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20030|2024-08-02T08:57:35.587Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20030</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive information, conduct a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack through an affected device, or negatively impact the responsiveness of the web-based management interface itself. This vulnerability is due to improper handling of XML External Entity (XXE) entries when parsing certain XML files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a crafted XML file that contains references to external entities. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve files from the local system, resulting in the disclosure of confidential information. A successful exploit could also cause the web application to perform arbitrary HTTP requests on behalf of the attacker or consume memory resources to reduce the availability of the web-based management interface. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid Super Admin or Policy Admin credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20030|2024-08-02T08:57:35.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20106|2024-08-02T08:57:35.589Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20106</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated attacker to delete or read arbitrary files on the underlying operating system. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid credentials on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20106|2024-08-02T08:57:35.589Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20153|2024-08-02T09:05:34.949Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20153</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in specific Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) CLI commands could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid Administrator privileges on the affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by submitting a crafted CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20153|2024-08-02T09:05:34.949Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20213|2024-08-02T09:05:35.481Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20213</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CDP processing feature of Cisco ISE could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of the CDP process on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient bounds checking when an affected device processes CDP traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted CDP traffic to the device. A successful exploit could cause the CDP process to crash, impacting neighbor discovery and the ability of Cisco ISE to determine the reachability of remote devices. After a crash, the CDP process must be manually restarted using the cdp enable command in interface configuration mode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20213|2024-08-02T09:05:35.481Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20174|2024-08-02T09:05:35.421Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20174</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to read arbitrary files or conduct a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack through an affected device. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid Administrator credentials on the affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20174|2024-08-02T09:05:35.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20163|2024-08-02T09:05:35.898Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20163</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker must have valid credentials on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20163|2024-08-02T09:05:35.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20121|2024-08-02T08:57:35.706Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20121</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the restricted shell of Cisco Evolved Programmable Network Manager (EPNM), Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE), and Cisco Prime Infrastructure could allow an authenticated, local attacker to escape the restricted shell and gain root privileges on the underlying operating system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20121|2024-08-02T08:57:35.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20175|2024-08-02T09:05:35.934Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20175</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a specific Cisco ISE CLI command could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have valid Read-only-level privileges or higher on the affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20175|2024-08-02T09:05:35.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20368|2024-08-01T21:59:41.799Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20368</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on the affected device with the privileges of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20368|2024-08-01T21:59:41.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20332|2024-08-01T21:59:41.923Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20332</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack through an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation for specific HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send arbitrary network requests that are sourced from the affected device. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid Super Admin credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20332|2024-08-01T21:59:41.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-08-01T21:59:41.103Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-08-01T21:59:41.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T21:20:23.314Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T21:20:23.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20332|2024-06-04T17:40:15.273Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20332</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack through an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation for specific HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send arbitrary network requests that are sourced from the affected device. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid Super Admin credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20332|2024-06-04T17:40:15.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20368|2024-06-04T17:40:10.016Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20368</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on the affected device with the privileges of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20368|2024-06-04T17:40:10.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T16:28:22.193Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T16:28:22.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-18T03:55:22.366Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-18T03:55:22.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
