<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco TelePresence Endpoint Software (TC/CE)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20telepresence%20endpoint%20software%20%28tc%2Fce%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco TelePresence Endpoint Software (TC/CE)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:21:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26086|2024-09-16T17:28:21.185Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20endpoint%20software%20%28tc%2Fce%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26086</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the video endpoint API (xAPI) of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to gain access to sensitive information on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper storage of sensitive information on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing information that should not be accessible to users with low privileges. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26086|2024-09-16T17:28:21.185Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 18:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1532|2024-09-16T19:14:12.564Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20endpoint%20software%20%28tc%2Fce%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1532</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the video endpoint API (xAPI) of Cisco TelePresence Collaboration Endpoint (CE) Software and Cisco RoomOS Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to read arbitrary files from the underlying operating system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient path validation of command arguments. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted command request to the xAPI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read the contents of any file that is located on the device filesystem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1532|2024-09-16T19:14:12.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 12:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
