<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 18:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1426|2024-09-16T16:18:29.807Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1426</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the install, uninstall, and upgrade processes of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to hijack DLL or executable files that are used by the application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device with SYSTEM privileges. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker must have valid credentials on the Windows system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1426|2024-09-16T16:18:29.807Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 12:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3153|2024-09-16T16:38:23.539Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3153</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the installer component of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Windows could allow an authenticated local attacker to copy user-supplied files to system level directories with system level privileges. The vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of directory paths. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by creating a malicious file and copying the file to a system directory. An exploit could allow the attacker to copy malicious files to arbitrary locations with system level privileges. This could include DLL pre-loading, DLL hijacking, and other related attacks. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker needs valid credentials on the Windows system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3153|2024-09-16T16:38:23.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 19:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1450|2024-09-16T17:28:18.808Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1450</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the interprocess communication (IPC) channel of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have valid credentials on the device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending one or more crafted IPC messages to the AnyConnect process on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to stop the AnyConnect process, causing a DoS condition on the device. Note: The process under attack will automatically restart so no action is needed by the user or admin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1450|2024-09-16T17:28:18.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 19:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1427|2024-09-16T17:22:54.144Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1427</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the install, uninstall, and upgrade processes of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to hijack DLL or executable files that are used by the application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device with SYSTEM privileges. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker must have valid credentials on the Windows system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1427|2024-09-16T17:22:54.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 12:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
