<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco AMP for Endpoints</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco AMP for Endpoints</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:21:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20796|2024-08-03T02:24:49.535Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20796</link>
      <description>On May 4, 2022, the following vulnerability in the ClamAV scanning library versions 0.103.5 and earlier and 0.104.2 and earlier was disclosed: A vulnerability in Clam AntiVirus (ClamAV) versions 0.103.4, 0.103.5, 0.104.1, and 0.104.2 could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause a denial of service condition on an affected device. For a description of this vulnerability, see the ClamAV blog.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20796|2024-08-03T02:24:49.535Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1280|2024-08-03T16:02:56.386Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1280</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the loading mechanism of specific DLLs of Cisco Advanced Malware Protection (AMP) for Endpoints for Windows and Immunet for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform a DLL hijacking attack. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid credentials on the Windows system. This vulnerability is due to incorrect handling of directory search paths at run time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by placing a malicious DLL file on the targeted system. This file will execute when the vulnerable application launches. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the targeted system with SYSTEM privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1280|2024-08-03T16:02:56.386Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20785|2024-08-03T02:24:49.604Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20785</link>
      <description>On April 20, 2022, the following vulnerability in the ClamAV scanning library versions 0.103.5 and earlier and 0.104.2 and earlier was disclosed: A vulnerability in HTML file parser of Clam AntiVirus (ClamAV) versions 0.104.0 through 0.104.2 and LTS version 0.103.5 and prior versions could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition on an affected device. For a description of this vulnerability, see the ClamAV blog. This advisory will be updated as additional information becomes available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20785|2024-08-03T02:24:49.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1386|2024-08-03T16:11:16.881Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1386</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the dynamic link library (DLL) loading mechanism in Cisco Advanced Malware Protection (AMP) for Endpoints Windows Connector, ClamAV for Windows, and Immunet could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform a DLL hijacking attack on an affected Windows system. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid credentials on the system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of directory search paths at run time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by placing a malicious DLL file on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1386|2024-08-03T16:11:16.881Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20771|2024-08-03T02:24:49.424Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20771</link>
      <description>On April 20, 2022, the following vulnerability in the ClamAV scanning library versions 0.103.5 and earlier and 0.104.2 and earlier was disclosed: A vulnerability in the TIFF file parser of Clam AntiVirus (ClamAV) versions 0.104.0 through 0.104.2 and LTS version 0.103.5 and prior versions could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition on an affected device. For a description of this vulnerability, see the ClamAV blog. This advisory will be updated as additional information becomes available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20771|2024-08-03T02:24:49.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20770|2024-08-03T02:24:49.339Z -- cisco -- cisco%20amp%20for%20endpoints
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20770</link>
      <description>On April 20, 2022, the following vulnerability in the ClamAV scanning library versions 0.103.5 and earlier and 0.104.2 and earlier was disclosed: A vulnerability in CHM file parser of Clam AntiVirus (ClamAV) versions 0.104.0 through 0.104.2 and LTS version 0.103.5 and prior versions could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition on an affected device. For a description of this vulnerability, see the ClamAV blog. This advisory will be updated as additional information becomes available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20770|2024-08-03T02:24:49.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
