<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Webex Meetings</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20webex%20meetings.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Webex Meetings</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:23:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20132|2024-08-02T08:57:35.857Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20132</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web interface of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack or upload arbitrary files as recordings. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20132|2024-08-02T08:57:35.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20180|2024-08-02T09:05:35.326Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20180</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web interface of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web interface on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions. These actions could include joining meetings and scheduling training sessions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20180|2024-08-02T09:05:35.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 19:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20134|2024-08-02T08:57:35.893Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20134</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web interface of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack or upload arbitrary files as recordings. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20134|2024-08-02T08:57:35.893Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20133|2024-08-02T08:57:35.975Z -- cisco -- cisco%20webex%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20133</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web interface of Cisco Webex Meetings could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability exists because of insufficient validation of user-supplied input in Webex Events (classic) programs, email templates, and survey questions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20133|2024-08-02T08:57:35.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 19:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
