<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20application%20policy%20infrastructure%20controller%20%28apic%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 17:22:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3139|2024-08-04T07:24:00.586Z -- cisco -- cisco%20application%20policy%20infrastructure%20controller%20%28apic%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3139</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the out of band (OOB) management interface IP table rule programming for Cisco Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured deny entries for specific IP ports. These IP ports would be permitted to the OOB management interface when, in fact, the packets should be dropped. The vulnerability is due to the configuration of specific IP table entries for which there is a programming logic error that results in the IP port being permitted. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic to the OOB management interface on the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured IP table rules to drop specific IP port traffic. The attacker has no control over the configuration of the device itself. This vulnerability affects Cisco APIC releases prior to the first fixed software Release 4.2(3j).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3139|2024-08-04T07:24:00.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3335|2024-08-04T07:30:57.829Z -- cisco -- cisco%20application%20policy%20infrastructure%20controller%20%28apic%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3335</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the key store of Cisco Application Services Engine Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to read sensitive information of other users on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization limitations. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to an affected device locally with valid credentials. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read the sensitive information of other users on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3335|2024-08-04T07:30:57.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3333|2024-08-04T07:30:58.016Z -- cisco -- cisco%20application%20policy%20infrastructure%20controller%20%28apic%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3333</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the API of Cisco Application Services Engine Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to update event policies on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authentication of users who modify policies on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting a malicious HTTP request to contact an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to update event policies on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3333|2024-08-04T07:30:58.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
