<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN Solution</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20sd-wan%20solution.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN Solution</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 11:20:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20818|2024-08-03T02:24:49.956Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20818</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI of Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain elevated privileges. These vulnerabilities are due to improper access controls on commands within the application CLI. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by running a malicious command on the application CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20818|2024-08-03T02:24:49.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20775|2024-08-03T02:24:49.634Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20775</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI of Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain elevated privileges. These vulnerabilities are due to improper access controls on commands within the application CLI. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by running a malicious command on the application CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20775|2024-08-03T02:24:49.634Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20716|2024-08-03T02:24:48.570Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20716</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain escalated privileges. This vulnerability is due to improper access control on files within the affected system. A local attacker could exploit this vulnerability by modifying certain files on the vulnerable device. If successful, the attacker could gain escalated privileges and take actions on the system with the privileges of the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20716|2024-08-03T02:24:48.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20850|2024-08-03T02:24:50.267Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20850</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of stand-alone Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software and Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to delete arbitrary files from the file system of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting arbitrary file path information when using commands in the CLI of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files from the file system of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20850|2024-08-03T02:24:50.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
