<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Remote PHY</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20remote%20phy.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Remote PHY</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:21:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1839|2024-09-16T16:37:49.208Z -- cisco -- cisco%20remote%20phy
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1839</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Remote PHY Device Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute commands on the underlying Linux shell of an affected device with root privileges. The vulnerability occurs because the affected software improperly sanitizes user-supplied input. An attacker who has valid administrator access to an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by supplying various CLI commands with crafted arguments. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to run arbitrary commands as the root user, allowing complete compromise of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1839|2024-09-16T16:37:49.208Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 18:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15391|2024-09-16T22:02:04.505Z -- cisco -- cisco%20remote%20phy
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15391</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in certain IPv4 fragment-processing functions of Cisco Remote PHY Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to impact traffic passing through a device, potentially causing a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to the affected software not validating and calculating certain numerical values in IPv4 packets that are sent to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malformed IPv4 traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to disrupt the flow of certain IPv4 traffic passing through an affected device, which could result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15391|2024-09-16T22:02:04.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
