<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Hosted Collaboration Mediation Fulfillment</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20hosted%20collaboration%20mediation%20fulfillment.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Hosted Collaboration Mediation Fulfillment</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 13:23:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3256|2024-08-04T07:30:57.340Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hosted%20collaboration%20mediation%20fulfillment
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3256</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Hosted Collaboration Mediation Fulfillment (HCM-F) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to gain read access to information that is stored on an affected system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need administrative privileges on the Cisco HCM-F Software. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of XML External Entity (XXE) entries when parsing certain XML files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests that contain references in XML entities to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve files from the local system, resulting in the disclosure of sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3256|2024-08-04T07:30:57.340Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3124|2024-08-04T07:24:00.629Z -- cisco -- cisco%20hosted%20collaboration%20mediation%20fulfillment
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3124</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Hosted Collaboration Mediation Fulfillment (HCM-F) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a targeted user to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send arbitrary requests that could change the password of a targeted user. An attacker could then take unauthorized actions on behalf of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3124|2024-08-04T07:24:00.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
