<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Small Business 300 Series Managed Switches</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20small%20business%20300%20series%20managed%20switches.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Small Business 300 Series Managed Switches</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:19:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1892|2024-08-04T18:35:50.769Z -- cisco -- cisco%20small%20business%20300%20series%20managed%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1892</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) input packet processor of Cisco Small Business 200, 300, and 500 Series Managed Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a memory corruption on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of HTTPS packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed HTTPS packet to the management web interface of the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an unexpected reload of the device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1892|2024-08-04T18:35:50.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3147|2024-08-04T07:24:00.646Z -- cisco -- cisco%20small%20business%20300%20series%20managed%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3147</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco Small Business Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of requests sent to the web interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious request to the web interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an unexpected reload of the device, resulting in a DoS condition. This vulnerability affects firmware releases prior than 1.3.7.18</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3147|2024-08-04T07:24:00.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1814|2024-08-04T18:28:42.813Z -- cisco -- cisco%20small%20business%20300%20series%20managed%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1814</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the interactions between the DHCP and TFTP features for Cisco Small Business 300 Series (Sx300) Managed Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to become low on system memory, which in turn could lead to an unexpected reload of the device and result in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a failure to free system memory when an unexpected DHCP request is received. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCP packet to the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an unexpected reload of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1814|2024-08-04T18:28:42.813Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1891|2024-08-04T18:35:52.041Z -- cisco -- cisco%20small%20business%20300%20series%20managed%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1891</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web interface of Cisco Small Business 200, 300, and 500 Series Managed Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of requests sent to the web interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious request to the web interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an unexpected reload of the device, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1891|2024-08-04T18:35:52.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1943|2024-08-04T18:35:51.265Z -- cisco -- cisco%20small%20business%20300%20series%20managed%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1943</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web interface of Cisco Small Business 200, 300, and 500 Series Switches software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to redirect a user to a malicious web page. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation of the parameters of an HTTP request. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting a user's HTTP request and modifying it into a request that causes the web interface to redirect the user to a specific malicious URL. This type of vulnerability is known as an open redirect attack and is used in phishing attacks that get users to unknowingly visit malicious sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1943|2024-08-04T18:35:51.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
