<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) Expressway</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20telepresence%20video%20communication%20server%20%28vcs%29%20expressway.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) Expressway</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:25:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20809|2024-09-17T03:34:14.039Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20video%20communication%20server%20%28vcs%29%20expressway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20809</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the API and web-based management interfaces of Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to write files or disclose sensitive information on an affected device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20809|2024-09-17T03:34:14.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 14:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20813|2024-09-17T00:36:07.606Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20video%20communication%20server%20%28vcs%29%20expressway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20813</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the API and in the web-based management interface of Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow a remote attacker to overwrite arbitrary files or conduct null byte poisoning attacks on an affected device. Note: Cisco Expressway Series refers to the Expressway Control (Expressway-C) device and the Expressway Edge (Expressway-E) device. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20813|2024-09-17T00:36:07.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 20:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3596|2024-09-17T02:58:15.399Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20video%20communication%20server%20%28vcs%29%20expressway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3596</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) of Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to incorrect handling of incoming SIP traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of SIP packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust memory on an affected device, causing it to crash and leading to a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3596|2024-09-17T02:58:15.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 04:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34716|2024-09-17T03:32:37.034Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20video%20communication%20server%20%28vcs%29%20expressway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34716</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system as the root user. This vulnerability is due to incorrect handling of certain crafted software images that are uploaded to the affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the system as an administrative user and then uploading specific crafted software images to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34716|2024-09-17T03:32:37.034Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 19:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20497|2024-09-04T17:33:38.771Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20video%20communication%20server%20%28vcs%29%20expressway</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20497</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Expressway Edge (Expressway-E) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to masquerade as another user on an affected system.

This vulnerability is due to inadequate authorization checks for Mobile and Remote Access (MRA) users. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a series of crafted commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to intercept calls that are destined for a particular phone number or to make phone calls and have that phone number appear on the caller ID. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must be an MRA user on an affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20497|2024-09-04T17:33:38.771Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20400|2024-08-01T21:59:41.611Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20video%20communication%20server%20%28vcs%29%20expressway</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20400</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Expressway Series could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to redirect a user to a malicious web page.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation of HTTP request parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting and modifying an HTTP request from a user. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to redirect the user to a malicious web page.
&#13; Note: Cisco Expressway Series refers to Cisco Expressway Control (Expressway-C) devices and Cisco Expressway Edge (Expressway-E) devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20400|2024-08-01T21:59:41.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:29:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20400|2024-07-17T16:52:12.586Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20video%20communication%20server%20%28vcs%29%20expressway</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20400</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Expressway Series could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to redirect a user to a malicious web page.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation of HTTP request parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting and modifying an HTTP request from a user. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to redirect the user to a malicious web page.
&#13; Note: Cisco Expressway Series refers to Cisco Expressway Control (Expressway-C) devices and Cisco Expressway Edge (Expressway-E) devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20400|2024-07-17T16:52:12.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:29:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20497|2024-09-04T16:29:13.595Z -- cisco -- cisco%20telepresence%20video%20communication%20server%20%28vcs%29%20expressway</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20497</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Expressway Edge (Expressway-E) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to masquerade as another user on an affected system.

This vulnerability is due to inadequate authorization checks for Mobile and Remote Access (MRA) users. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a series of crafted commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to intercept calls that are destined for a particular phone number or to make phone calls and have that phone number appear on the caller ID. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must be an MRA user on an affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20497|2024-09-04T16:29:13.595Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
