<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Management Center</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20firepower%20management%20center.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Management Center</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 15:23:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20471|2024-10-24T14:26:22.403Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20471</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not validate user input adequately. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application as an Administrator and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain unauthorized data from the database and make changes to the system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need Administrator-level privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20471|2024-10-24T14:26:22.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20473|2024-10-23T20:59:03.182Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20473</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system.

This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not validate user input adequately. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application as an Administrator and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain unauthorized data from the database and make changes to the system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need Administrator-level privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20473|2024-10-23T20:59:03.182Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20472|2024-10-23T21:00:40.915Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20472</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system.

This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not validate user input adequately. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application as an Administrator and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain unauthorized data from the database and make changes to the system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need Administrator-level privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20472|2024-10-23T21:00:40.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20379|2024-10-23T19:40:09.040Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20379</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Management Center Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to read arbitrary files from the underlying operating system.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read arbitrary files on the underlying operating system of the affected device. The attacker would need valid user credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20379|2024-10-23T19:40:09.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20275|2024-10-23T19:49:28.407Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20275</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the cluster backup feature of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Management Center Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user data that is supplied through the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary operating system commands on the affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid credentials for a user account with at least the role of Network Administrator. In addition, the attacker would need to persuade a legitimate user to initiate a cluster backup on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20275|2024-10-23T19:49:28.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20409|2024-10-23T17:38:10.132Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20409</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20409|2024-10-23T17:38:10.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20410|2024-10-23T17:38:43.124Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20410</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20410|2024-10-23T17:38:43.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20379|2024-10-23T17:30:52.502Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20379</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Management Center Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to read arbitrary files from the underlying operating system.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read arbitrary files on the underlying operating system of the affected device. The attacker would need valid user credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20379|2024-10-23T17:30:52.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20471|2024-10-23T17:47:42.116Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20471</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not validate user input adequately. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application as an Administrator and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain unauthorized data from the database and make changes to the system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need Administrator-level privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20471|2024-10-23T17:47:42.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20377|2024-10-23T17:30:26.541Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20377</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the web-based management interface not properly validating user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20377|2024-10-23T17:30:26.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20264|2024-10-23T17:06:48.407Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20264</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20264|2024-10-23T17:06:48.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20298|2024-10-23T17:08:03.318Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20298</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20298|2024-10-23T17:08:03.318Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20300|2024-10-23T17:08:24.248Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20300</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20300|2024-10-23T17:08:24.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20388|2024-10-23T17:35:24.772Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20388</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the password change feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to determine valid user names on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper authentication of password update responses. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by forcing a password reset on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to determine valid user names in the unauthenticated response to a forced password reset.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20388|2024-10-23T17:35:24.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:35:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20424|2024-10-23T17:46:24.274Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20424</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Management Center Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system as root.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of certain HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the web-based management interface of an affected device and then sending a crafted HTTP request to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root permissions on the underlying operating system of the Cisco FMC device or to execute commands on managed Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) devices. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid credentials for a user account with at least the role of Security Analyst (Read Only).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20424|2024-10-23T17:46:24.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20387|2024-10-23T17:34:18.768Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20387</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco FMC Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to store malicious content for use in XSS attacks. This vulnerability is due to improper input sanitization in the web-based management interface of Cisco FMC Software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct a stored XSS attack on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20387|2024-10-23T17:34:18.768Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:34:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20374|2024-10-23T17:30:06.650Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20374</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Management Center Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with Administrator-level privileges to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of certain HTTP request parameters that are sent to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the Cisco FMC web-based management interface and sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands as the root user on the affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need Administrator-level credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20374|2024-10-23T17:30:06.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20340|2024-10-23T17:09:10.266Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20340</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Management Center Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform an SQL injection attack against an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have a valid account on the device with the role of Security Approver, Intrusion Admin, Access Admin, or Network Admin.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the web-based management interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read the contents of databases on the affected device and also obtain limited read access to the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20340|2024-10-23T17:09:10.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20482|2024-10-23T17:52:08.555Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20482</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Management Center Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have a valid account on the device that is configured with a custom read-only role.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of role permissions in part of the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by performing a write operation on the affected part of the web-based management interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify certain parts of the configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20482|2024-10-23T17:52:08.555Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20364|2024-10-23T17:28:31.674Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20364</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20364|2024-10-23T17:28:31.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20275|2024-10-23T17:07:44.671Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20275</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the cluster backup feature of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Management Center Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user data that is supplied through the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary operating system commands on the affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid credentials for a user account with at least the role of Network Administrator. In addition, the attacker would need to persuade a legitimate user to initiate a cluster backup on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20275|2024-10-23T17:07:44.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20269|2024-10-23T17:07:09.355Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20269</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20269|2024-10-23T17:07:09.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20473|2024-10-23T17:51:01.385Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20473</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system.

This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not validate user input adequately. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application as an Administrator and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain unauthorized data from the database and make changes to the system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need Administrator-level privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20473|2024-10-23T17:51:01.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20403|2024-10-23T17:36:14.821Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20403</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20403|2024-10-23T17:36:14.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20415|2024-10-23T17:46:02.736Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20415</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20415|2024-10-23T17:46:02.736Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20273|2024-10-23T17:07:29.031Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20273</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20273|2024-10-23T17:07:29.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:07:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20472|2024-10-23T17:50:13.687Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20472</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system.

This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not validate user input adequately. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application as an Administrator and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain unauthorized data from the database and make changes to the system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need Administrator-level privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20472|2024-10-23T17:50:13.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20386|2024-10-23T17:33:02.801Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20386</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20386|2024-10-23T17:33:02.801Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20274|2024-10-23T17:07:36.671Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20274</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Management Center Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary HTML content into a device-generated document.

This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied data. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting malicious content to an affected device and using the device to generate a document that contains sensitive information. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to alter the standard layout of the device-generated documents, access arbitrary files from the underlying operating system, and conduct server-side request forgery (SSRF) attacks. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid credentials for a user account with policy-editing permissions, such as Network Admin, Intrusion Admin, or any custom user role with the same capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20274|2024-10-23T17:07:36.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20372|2024-10-23T17:29:39.644Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20372</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20372|2024-10-23T17:29:39.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-13T14:05:52.072Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Object Groups for Access Control Lists (ACLs) feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured access controls on managed devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect deployment of the Object Groups for ACLs feature from Cisco FMC Software to managed FTD devices in high-availability setups. After an affected device is rebooted following Object Groups for ACLs deployment, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access controls and successfully send traffic to devices that are expected to be protected by the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-13T14:05:52.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20360|2024-06-04T17:40:39.489Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20360</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not adequately validate user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain any data from the database, execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system, and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least Read Only user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20360|2024-06-04T17:40:39.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-04T17:40:51.215Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Object Groups for Access Control Lists (ACLs) feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured access controls on managed devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect deployment of the Object Groups for ACLs feature from Cisco FMC Software to managed FTD devices in high-availability setups. After an affected device is rebooted following Object Groups for ACLs deployment, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access controls and successfully send traffic to devices that are expected to be protected by the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-04T17:40:51.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20360|2024-08-01T21:59:42.328Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20360</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not adequately validate user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain any data from the database, execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system, and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least Read Only user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20360|2024-08-01T21:59:42.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20361|2024-08-01T21:59:41.652Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Object Groups for Access Control Lists (ACLs) feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured access controls on managed devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect deployment of the Object Groups for ACLs feature from Cisco FMC Software to managed FTD devices in high-availability setups. After an affected device is rebooted following Object Groups for ACLs deployment, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access controls and successfully send traffic to devices that are expected to be protected by the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20361|2024-08-01T21:59:41.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20415|2024-10-23T20:54:58.239Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20415</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20415|2024-10-23T20:54:58.239Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20482|2024-10-23T20:53:36.067Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20482</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Management Center Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have a valid account on the device that is configured with a custom read-only role.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of role permissions in part of the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by performing a write operation on the affected part of the web-based management interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify certain parts of the configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20482|2024-10-23T20:53:36.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
