<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 19:20:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1448|2024-09-16T18:29:18.141Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1448</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges on the underlying operating system of an affected device that is running in multi-instance mode. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied command arguments. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting crafted input to the affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands on the underlying operating system with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1448|2024-09-16T18:29:18.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3308|2024-09-16T16:57:45.443Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3308</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Image Signature Verification feature of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrator-level credentials to install a malicious software patch on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper verification of digital signatures for patch images. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting an unsigned software patch to bypass signature checks and loading it on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to boot a malicious software patch image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3308|2024-09-16T16:57:45.443Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20746|2024-09-16T18:17:54.767Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20746</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TCP proxy functionality of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper handling of TCP flows. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted stream of TCP traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20746|2024-09-16T18:17:54.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 03:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1224|2024-09-16T17:59:10.265Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1224</link>
      <description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability with TCP Fast Open (TFO) when used in conjunction with the Snort detection engine that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured file policy for HTTP. The vulnerability is due to incorrect detection of the HTTP payload if it is contained at least partially within the TFO connection handshake. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted TFO packets with an HTTP payload through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured file policy for HTTP packets and deliver a malicious payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1224|2024-09-16T17:59:10.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 21:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1495|2024-09-16T16:53:44.778Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1495</link>
      <description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort detection engine that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured file policy for HTTP. The vulnerability is due to incorrect handling of specific HTTP header parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass a configured file policy for HTTP packets and deliver a malicious payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1495|2024-09-16T16:53:44.778Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40114|2024-09-16T16:47:44.848Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40114</link>
      <description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the way the Snort detection engine processes ICMP traffic that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper memory resource management while the Snort detection engine is processing ICMP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of ICMP packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust resources on the affected device, causing the device to reload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40114|2024-09-16T16:47:44.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3285|2024-09-16T16:58:40.942Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3285</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Transport Layer Security version 1.3 (TLS 1.3) policy with URL category functionality for Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured TLS 1.3 policy to block traffic for a specific URL. The vulnerability is due to a logic error with Snort handling of the connection with the TLS 1.3 policy and URL category configuration. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted TLS 1.3 connections to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the TLS 1.3 policy and access URLs that are outside the affected device and normally would be dropped.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3285|2024-09-16T16:58:40.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3533|2024-09-16T16:19:05.907Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3533</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) input packet processor of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to restart unexpectedly. The vulnerability is due to a lack of sufficient memory management protections under heavy SNMP polling loads. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high rate of SNMP requests to the SNMP daemon through the management interface on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the SNMP daemon process to consume a large amount of system memory over time, which could then lead to an unexpected device restart, causing a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability affects all versions of SNMP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3533|2024-09-16T16:19:05.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3562|2024-09-16T18:39:14.785Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3562</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSL/TLS inspection of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software for Cisco Firepower 2100 Series firewalls could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation for certain fields of specific SSL/TLS messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed SSL/TLS message through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition. No manual intervention is needed to recover the device after it has reloaded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3562|2024-09-16T18:39:14.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34754|2024-09-16T16:33:19.260Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34754</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the payload inspection for Ethernet Industrial Protocol (ENIP) traffic for Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured rules for ENIP traffic. These vulnerabilities are due to incomplete processing during deep packet inspection for ENIP packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a crafted ENIP packet to the targeted interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access control and intrusion policies that should be activated for the ENIP packet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34754|2024-09-16T16:33:19.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12674|2024-09-16T18:02:56.560Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12674</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the multi-instance feature of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to escape the container for their FTD instance and execute commands with root privileges in the host namespace. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient protections on the underlying filesystem. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by modifying critical files on the underlying filesystem. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands with root privileges within the host namespace. This could allow the attacker to impact other running FTD instances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12674|2024-09-16T18:02:56.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12627|2024-09-16T18:49:36.551Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12627</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the application policy configuration of the Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain unauthorized read access to sensitive data. The vulnerability is due to insufficient application identification. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain unauthorized read access to sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12627|2024-09-16T18:49:36.551Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 18:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20261|2024-07-02T16:00:57.104Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20261</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the file policy feature that is used to inspect encrypted archive files of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured file policy to block an encrypted archive file. This vulnerability exists because of a logic error when a specific class of encrypted archive files is inspected. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted, encrypted archive file through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send an encrypted archive file, which could contain malware and should have been blocked and dropped at the Cisco FTD device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20261|2024-07-02T16:00:57.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20363|2024-06-04T17:40:03.436Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20363</link>
      <description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort Intrusion Prevention System (IPS) rule engine that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured rules on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to incorrect HTTP packet handling. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured IPS rules and allow uninspected traffic onto the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20363|2024-06-04T17:40:03.436Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20261|2024-05-22T16:53:27.346Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20261</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the file policy feature that is used to inspect encrypted archive files of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured file policy to block an encrypted archive file. This vulnerability exists because of a logic error when a specific class of encrypted archive files is inspected. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted, encrypted archive file through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send an encrypted archive file, which could contain malware and should have been blocked and dropped at the Cisco FTD device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20261|2024-05-22T16:53:27.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20261|2024-08-01T21:52:31.751Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20261</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the file policy feature that is used to inspect encrypted archive files of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured file policy to block an encrypted archive file. This vulnerability exists because of a logic error when a specific class of encrypted archive files is inspected. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted, encrypted archive file through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send an encrypted archive file, which could contain malware and should have been blocked and dropped at the Cisco FTD device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20261|2024-08-01T21:52:31.751Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20363|2024-08-01T21:59:42.321Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20threat%20defense%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20363</link>
      <description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the Snort Intrusion Prevention System (IPS) rule engine that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured rules on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to incorrect HTTP packet handling. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured IPS rules and allow uninspected traffic onto the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20363|2024-08-01T21:59:42.321Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
