<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 14:23:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3153|2024-08-04T07:24:00.700Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3153</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the installer component of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Windows could allow an authenticated local attacker to copy user-supplied files to system level directories with system level privileges. The vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of directory paths. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by creating a malicious file and copying the file to a system directory. An exploit could allow the attacker to copy malicious files to arbitrary locations with system level privileges. This could include DLL pre-loading, DLL hijacking, and other related attacks. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker needs valid credentials on the Windows system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3153|2024-08-04T07:24:00.700Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3434|2024-08-04T07:37:54.380Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3434</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the interprocess communication (IPC) channel of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have valid credentials on the Windows system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPC message to the AnyConnect process on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to stop the AnyConnect process, causing a DoS condition on the device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have valid credentials on the Windows system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3434|2024-08-04T07:37:54.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3435|2024-08-04T07:37:54.683Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3435</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the interprocess communication (IPC) channel of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to overwrite VPN profiles on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have valid credentials on the Windows system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPC message to the AnyConnect process on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify VPN profile files. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have valid credentials on the Windows system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3435|2024-08-04T07:37:54.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3433|2024-08-04T07:37:54.304Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3433</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the interprocess communication (IPC) channel of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform a DLL hijacking attack. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have valid credentials on the Windows system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of resources that are loaded by the application at run time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPC message to the AnyConnect process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected machine with SYSTEM privileges. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have valid credentials on the Windows system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3433|2024-08-04T07:37:54.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34788|2024-08-04T00:19:48.261Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34788</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the shared library loading mechanism of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Linux and Mac OS could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform a shared library hijacking attack on an affected device if the VPN Posture (HostScan) Module is installed on the AnyConnect client. This vulnerability is due to a race condition in the signature verification process for shared library files that are loaded on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of crafted interprocess communication (IPC) messages to the AnyConnect process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected device with root privileges. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have a valid account on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34788|2024-08-04T00:19:48.261Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40124|2024-08-04T02:27:31.715Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40124</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Network Access Manager (NAM) module of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to escalate privileges on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to incorrect privilege assignment to scripts executed before user logon. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by configuring a script to be executed before logon. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40124|2024-08-04T02:27:31.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3556|2024-08-04T07:37:54.975Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3556</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the interprocess communication (IPC) channel of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause a targeted AnyConnect user to execute a malicious script. The vulnerability is due to a lack of authentication to the IPC listener. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted IPC messages to the AnyConnect client IPC listener. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to cause the targeted AnyConnect user to execute a script. This script would execute with the privileges of the targeted AnyConnect user. In order to successfully exploit this vulnerability, there must be an ongoing AnyConnect session by the targeted user at the time of the attack. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would also need valid user credentials on the system upon which the AnyConnect client is being run. Cisco has not released software updates that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3556|2024-08-04T07:37:54.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
