<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Umbrella</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20umbrella.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Umbrella</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:23:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1792|2024-09-16T18:39:14.219Z -- cisco -- cisco%20umbrella
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1792</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the URL block page of Cisco Umbrella could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user in a network protected by Umbrella. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of input parameters passed to that page. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a maliciously crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive browser-based information. This vulnerability has been fixed in the current version of Cisco Umbrella. Cisco Umbrella is a cloud service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1792|2024-09-16T18:39:14.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 00:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0435|2024-09-16T18:02:59.697Z -- cisco -- cisco%20umbrella
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0435</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Umbrella API could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to view and modify data across their organization and other organizations. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authentication configurations for the API interface of Cisco Umbrella. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to view and potentially modify data for their organization or other organizations. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read or modify data across multiple organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0435|2024-09-16T18:02:59.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
