<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN vManage</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN vManage</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 18:24:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20930|2024-08-03T02:31:57.960Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20930</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to overwrite and possibly corrupt files on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting arbitrary commands that are executed as the root user account. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite arbitrary system files, which could result in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20930|2024-08-03T02:31:57.960Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20747|2024-08-03T02:24:49.306Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20747</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the History API of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to gain access to sensitive information on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient API authorization checking on the underlying operating system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted API request to Cisco vManage as a lower-privileged user and gaining access to sensitive information that they would not normally be authorized to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20747|2024-08-03T02:24:49.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1468|2024-08-03T16:11:17.322Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1468</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code or gain access to sensitive information, or allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain escalated privileges or gain unauthorized access to the application. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1468|2024-08-03T16:11:17.322Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1349|2024-08-03T16:11:16.783Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1349</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct Cypher query language injection attacks on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to the interface of an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1349|2024-08-03T16:11:16.783Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1305|2024-08-03T16:02:56.385Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1305</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to bypass authorization and modify the configuration of an affected system, gain access to sensitive information, and view information that they are not authorized to access. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1305|2024-08-03T16:02:56.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1302|2024-08-03T16:02:56.407Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1302</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to bypass authorization and modify the configuration of an affected system, gain access to sensitive information, and view information that they are not authorized to access. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1302|2024-08-03T16:02:56.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1506|2024-08-03T16:11:17.649Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1506</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code or gain access to sensitive information, or allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain escalated privileges or gain unauthorized access to the application. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1506|2024-08-03T16:11:17.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20735|2024-08-03T02:24:49.341Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20735</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privilege level of the affected user. These actions could include modifying the system configuration and deleting accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20735|2024-08-03T02:24:49.341Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1515|2024-08-03T16:11:17.769Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1515</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to gain access to sensitive information. This vulnerability is due to improper access controls on API endpoints when Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software is running in multi-tenant mode. An attacker with access to a device that is managed in the multi-tenant environment could exploit this vulnerability by sending a request to an affected API endpoint on the vManage system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to sensitive information that may include hashed credentials that could be used in future attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1515|2024-08-03T16:11:17.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20830|2024-08-03T02:24:49.961Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20830</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in authentication mechanism of Cisco Software-Defined Application Visibility and Control (SD-AVC) on Cisco vManage could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access the GUI of Cisco SD-AVC without authentication. This vulnerability exists because the GUI is accessible on self-managed cloud installations or local server installations of Cisco vManage. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the exposed GUI of Cisco SD-AVC. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view managed device names, SD-AVC logs, and SD-AVC DNS server IP addresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20830|2024-08-03T02:24:49.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1486|2024-08-03T16:11:17.768Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1486</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to enumerate user accounts. This vulnerability is due to the improper handling of HTTP headers. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending authenticated requests to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to compare the HTTP responses that are returned by the affected system to determine which accounts are valid user accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1486|2024-08-03T16:11:17.768Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20734|2024-08-03T02:24:49.315Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20734</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to view sensitive information on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient file system restrictions. An authenticated attacker with netadmin privileges could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the vshell of an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read sensitive information on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20734|2024-08-03T02:24:49.315Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1225|2024-08-03T16:02:56.196Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1225</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system. These vulnerabilities exist because the web-based management interface improperly validates values in SQL queries. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by authenticating to the application and sending malicious SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify values on or return values from the underlying database or the operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1225|2024-08-03T16:02:56.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1535|2024-08-03T16:11:17.691Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1535</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the cluster management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to view sensitive information on an affected system. To be affected by this vulnerability, the Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software must be in cluster mode. This vulnerability is due to the absence of authentication for sensitive information in the cluster management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the cluster management interface of an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to allow the attacker to view sensitive information on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1535|2024-08-03T16:11:17.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1507|2024-08-03T16:11:17.682Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1507</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in an API of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against users of the application web-based interface. This vulnerability exists because the API does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious input to the API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the web-based interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1507|2024-08-03T16:11:17.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1259|2024-08-03T16:02:56.387Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct path traversal attacks and obtain write access to sensitive files on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request that contains directory traversal character sequences to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to write arbitrary files on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1259|2024-08-03T16:02:56.387Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1304|2024-08-03T16:02:56.389Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1304</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to bypass authorization and modify the configuration of an affected system, gain access to sensitive information, and view information that they are not authorized to access. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1304|2024-08-03T16:02:56.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1275|2024-08-03T16:02:56.441Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1275</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code or gain access to sensitive information, or allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain escalated privileges or gain unauthorized access to the application. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1275|2024-08-03T16:02:56.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1235|2024-08-03T16:02:56.004Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1235</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to read sensitive database files on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient user authorization. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the vshell of an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read database files from the filesystem of the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1235|2024-08-03T16:02:56.004Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1508|2024-08-03T16:11:17.793Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1508</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code or gain access to sensitive information, or allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain escalated privileges or gain unauthorized access to the application. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1508|2024-08-03T16:11:17.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1284|2024-08-03T16:02:56.369Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1284</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based messaging service interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass authentication and authorization and modify the configuration of an affected system. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must be able to access an associated Cisco SD-WAN vEdge device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to the web-based messaging service interface of an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain unauthenticated read and write access to the affected vManage system. With this access, the attacker could access information about the affected vManage system, modify the configuration of the system, or make configuration changes to devices that are managed by the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1284|2024-08-03T16:02:56.369Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20844|2024-08-03T02:24:50.064Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20844</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in authentication mechanism of Cisco Software-Defined Application Visibility and Control (SD-AVC) on Cisco vManage could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access the GUI of Cisco SD-AVC using a default static username and password combination. This vulnerability exists because the GUI is accessible on self-managed cloud installations or local server installations of Cisco vManage. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the exposed GUI of Cisco SD-AVC. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view managed device names, SD-AVC logs, and SD-AVC DNS server IP addresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20844|2024-08-03T02:24:50.064Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20696|2024-08-03T02:24:48.467Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20696</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the binding configuration of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software containers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker who has access to the VPN0 logical network to also access the messaging service ports on an affected system. This vulnerability exists because the messaging server container ports on an affected system lack sufficient protection mechanisms. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the messaging service ports of the affected system. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must be able to send network traffic to interfaces within the VPN0 logical network. This network may be restricted to protect logical or physical adjacent networks, depending on device deployment configuration. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view and inject messages into the messaging service, which can cause configuration changes or cause the system to reload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20696|2024-08-03T02:24:48.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20739|2024-08-03T02:24:49.338Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20739</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system as the root user. The attacker must be authenticated on the affected system as a low-privileged user to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because a file leveraged by a root user is executed when a low-privileged user runs specific commands on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting arbitrary commands to a specific file as a lower-privileged user and then waiting until an admin user executes specific commands. The commands would then be executed on the device by the root user. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to escalate their privileges on the affected system from a low-privileged user to the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20739|2024-08-03T02:24:49.338Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1505|2024-08-03T16:11:17.689Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1505</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code or gain access to sensitive information, or allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain escalated privileges or gain unauthorized access to the application. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1505|2024-08-03T16:11:17.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1589|2024-08-03T16:18:10.660Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1589</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the disaster recovery feature of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to gain unauthorized access to user credentials. This vulnerability exists because access to API endpoints is not properly restricted. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a request to an API endpoint. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain unauthorized access to administrative credentials that could be used in further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1589|2024-08-03T16:18:10.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
