<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:24:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20760|2024-09-17T00:55:29.975Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20760</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DNS inspection handler of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition (DoS) on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper processing of incoming requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted DNS requests at a high rate to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to stop responding, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20760|2024-09-17T00:55:29.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1934|2024-09-17T02:26:37.071Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1934</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges and execute administrative functions on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to an affected device as a low-privileged user and then sending specific HTTPS requests to execute administrative functions using the information retrieved during initial login.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1934|2024-09-17T02:26:37.071Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 21:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1585|2024-09-17T02:20:36.501Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1585</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Adaptive Security Device Manager (ASDM) Launcher could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on a user's operating system. This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper signature verification for specific code exchanged between the ASDM and the Launcher. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by leveraging a man-in-the-middle position on the network to intercept the traffic between the Launcher and the ASDM and then inject arbitrary code. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the user's operating system with the level of privileges assigned to the ASDM Launcher. A successful exploit may require the attacker to perform a social engineering attack to persuade the user to initiate communication from the Launcher to the ASDM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1585|2024-09-17T02:20:36.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 18:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15399|2024-09-17T02:51:33.020Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TCP syslog module of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to exhaust the 1550-byte buffers on an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to a missing boundary check in an internal function. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing a man-in-the-middle position between an affected device and its configured TCP syslog server and then maliciously modifying the TCP header in segments that are sent from the syslog server to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust buffer on the affected device and cause all TCP-based features to stop functioning, resulting in a DoS condition. The affected TCP-based features include AnyConnect SSL VPN, clientless SSL VPN, and management connections such as Secure Shell (SSH), Telnet, and HTTPS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15399|2024-09-17T02:51:33.020Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34791|2024-09-17T01:15:58.093Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34791</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Application Level Gateway (ALG) for the Network Address Translation (NAT) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the ALG and open unauthorized connections with a host located behind the ALG. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory. Note: These vulnerabilities have been publicly discussed as NAT Slipstreaming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34791|2024-09-17T01:15:58.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3259|2024-09-17T04:09:29.092Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web services interface of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to retrieve memory contents on an affected device, which could lead to the disclosure of confidential information. The vulnerability is due to a buffer tracking issue when the software parses invalid URLs that are requested from the web services interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted GET request to the web services interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve memory contents, which could lead to the disclosure of confidential information. Note: This vulnerability affects only specific AnyConnect and WebVPN configurations. For more information, see the Vulnerable Products section.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3259|2024-09-17T04:09:29.092Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34790|2024-09-17T01:06:19.680Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34790</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Application Level Gateway (ALG) for the Network Address Translation (NAT) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the ALG and open unauthorized connections with a host located behind the ALG. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory. Note: These vulnerabilities have been publicly discussed as NAT Slipstreaming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34790|2024-09-17T01:06:19.680Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12695|2024-09-17T03:28:06.719Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12695</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Clientless SSL VPN (WebVPN) portal of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or allow the attacker to access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12695|2024-09-17T03:28:06.719Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1693|2024-09-17T03:42:44.718Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1693</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the WebVPN service of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper management of authenticated sessions in the WebVPN portal. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating with valid credentials and accessing a specific URL in the WebVPN portal. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a temporary DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1693|2024-09-17T03:42:44.718Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 15:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3572|2024-09-17T00:37:17.358Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3572</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSL/TLS session handler of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a memory leak when closing SSL/TLS connections in a specific state. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing several SSL/TLS sessions and ensuring they are closed under certain conditions. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust memory resources in the affected device, which would prevent it from processing new SSL/TLS connections, resulting in a DoS. Manual intervention is required to recover an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3572|2024-09-17T00:37:17.358Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3305|2024-09-17T01:21:45.574Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3305</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of the Border Gateway Protocol (BGP) module in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of certain BGP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted BGP packet. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3305|2024-09-17T01:21:45.574Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3456|2024-09-17T02:16:48.630Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Firepower Chassis Manager (FCM) of Cisco FXOS Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack against a user of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the FCM interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a targeted user to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send arbitrary requests that could take unauthorized actions on behalf of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3456|2024-09-17T02:16:48.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3555|2024-09-17T01:16:39.280Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3555</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SIP inspection process of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a crash and reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to a watchdog timeout and crash during the cleanup of threads that are associated with a SIP connection that is being deleted from the connection list. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high rate of crafted SIP traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a watchdog timeout and crash, resulting in a crash and reload of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3555|2024-09-17T01:16:39.280Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1504|2024-09-17T02:37:07.140Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1504</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to lack of proper input validation of the HTTPS request. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a crafted HTTPS request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition. Note: This vulnerability affects only specific AnyConnect and WebVPN configurations. For more information, see the Vulnerable Products section.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1504|2024-09-17T02:37:07.140Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1687|2024-09-17T03:53:35.291Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1687</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TCP proxy functionality for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to restart unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to an error in TCP-based packet inspection, which could cause the TCP packet to have an invalid Layer 2 (L2)-formatted header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted TCP packet sequence to the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1687|2024-09-17T03:53:35.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3303|2024-09-17T00:42:31.490Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3303</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Internet Key Exchange version 1 (IKEv1) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to improper management of system memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious IKEv1 traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3303|2024-09-17T00:42:31.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20745|2024-09-17T00:06:07.247Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20745</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web services interface for remote access VPN features of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper input validation when parsing HTTPS requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTPS request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20745|2024-09-17T00:06:07.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 03:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1873|2024-09-17T01:05:50.344Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1873</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the cryptographic driver for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance Software (ASA) and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reboot unexpectedly. The vulnerability is due to incomplete input validation of a Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) or Transport Layer Security (TLS) ingress packet header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted TLS/SSL packet to an interface on the targeted device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, which will result in a denial of service (DoS) condition. Note: Only traffic directed to the affected system can be used to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability affects systems configured in routed and transparent firewall mode and in single or multiple context mode. This vulnerability can be triggered by IPv4 and IPv6 traffic. A valid SSL or TLS session is required to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1873|2024-09-17T01:05:50.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 17:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1945|2024-09-17T01:46:05.956Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1945</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the smart tunnel functionality of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to the root user or load a malicious library file while the tunnel is being established. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this security advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1945|2024-09-17T01:46:05.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 21:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15398|2024-09-17T01:02:06.093Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15398</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the per-user-override feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass an access control list (ACL) that is configured for an interface of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to errors that could occur when the affected software constructs and applies per-user-override rules. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to a network through an affected device that has a vulnerable configuration. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access resources that are behind the affected device and would typically be protected by the interface ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15398|2024-09-17T01:02:06.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3436|2024-09-17T02:06:29.418Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3436</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web services interface of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary-sized files to specific folders on an affected device, which could lead to an unexpected device reload. The vulnerability exists because the affected software does not efficiently handle the writing of large files to specific folders on the local file system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading files to those specific folders. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to write a file that triggers a watchdog timeout, which would cause the device to unexpectedly reload, causing a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3436|2024-09-17T02:06:29.418Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12698|2024-09-17T00:40:40.018Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12698</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the WebVPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause increased CPU utilization on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to excessive processing load for a specific WebVPN HTTP page request. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending multiple WebVPN HTTP page load requests for a specific URL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to increase CPU load on the device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition, which could cause traffic to be delayed through the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12698|2024-09-17T00:40:40.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1476|2024-09-17T01:26:36.084Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1476</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system (OS) of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of commands that are supplied by the user. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to a device and submitting crafted input for specific commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands on the underlying OS with root privileges. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have valid administrator-level credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1476|2024-09-17T01:26:36.084Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1713|2024-09-17T03:14:10.692Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1713</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privilege level of the affected user. If the user has administrative privileges, the attacker could alter the configuration of, extract information from, or reload an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1713|2024-09-17T03:14:10.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 16:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3452|2024-09-17T01:06:57.812Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3452</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web services interface of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct directory traversal attacks and read sensitive files on a targeted system. The vulnerability is due to a lack of proper input validation of URLs in HTTP requests processed by an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request containing directory traversal character sequences to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view arbitrary files within the web services file system on the targeted device. The web services file system is enabled when the affected device is configured with either WebVPN or AnyConnect features. This vulnerability cannot be used to obtain access to ASA or FTD system files or underlying operating system (OS) files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3452|2024-09-17T01:06:57.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 20:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40125|2024-09-17T03:34:03.602Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40125</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Internet Key Exchange Version 2 (IKEv2) implementation of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper control of a resource. An attacker with the ability to spoof a trusted IKEv2 site-to-site VPN peer and in possession of valid IKEv2 credentials for that peer could exploit this vulnerability by sending malformed, authenticated IKEv2 messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to trigger a reload of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40125|2024-09-17T03:34:03.602Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15397|2024-09-17T02:16:04.264Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15397</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of Traffic Flow Confidentiality (TFC) over IPsec functionality in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to restart unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to an error that may occur if the affected software renegotiates the encryption key for an IPsec tunnel when certain TFC traffic is in flight. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious stream of TFC traffic through an established IPsec tunnel on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a daemon process on the affected device to crash, which could cause the device to crash and result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15397|2024-09-17T02:16:04.264Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1708|2024-09-17T04:15:01.566Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1708</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Internet Key Exchange Version 2 Mobility and Multihoming Protocol (MOBIKE) feature for the Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a memory leak or a reload of an affected device that leads to a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to the incorrect processing of certain MOBIKE packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted MOBIKE packets to an affected device to be processed. A successful exploit could cause an affected device to continuously consume memory and eventually reload, resulting in a DoS condition. The MOBIKE feature is supported only for IPv4 addresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1708|2024-09-17T04:15:01.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 16:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20829|2024-09-17T03:32:55.360Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20829</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the packaging of Cisco Adaptive Security Device Manager (ASDM) images and the validation of those images by Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative privileges to upload an ASDM image that contains malicious code to a device that is running Cisco ASA Software. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of the authenticity of an ASDM image during its installation on a device that is running Cisco ASA Software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by installing a crafted ASDM image on the device that is running Cisco ASA Software and then waiting for a targeted user to access that device using ASDM. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the machine of the targeted user with the privileges of that user on that machine. Notes: To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have administrative privileges on the device that is running Cisco ASA Software. Potential targets are limited to users who manage the same device that is running Cisco ASA Software using ASDM. Cisco has released and will release software updates that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20829|2024-09-17T03:32:55.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 15:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3582|2024-09-17T02:22:05.093Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3582</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web services interface of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks against a user of the web services interface of an affected device. The vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web services interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or allow the attacker to access sensitive, browser-based information. Note: These vulnerabilities affect only specific AnyConnect and WebVPN configurations. For more information, see the Vulnerable Products section.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3582|2024-09-17T02:22:05.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:36:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34793|2024-09-17T01:10:35.509Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34793</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TCP Normalizer of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software operating in transparent mode could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to poison MAC address tables, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) vulnerability. This vulnerability is due to incorrect handling of certain TCP segments when the affected device is operating in transparent mode. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted TCP segment through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to poison the MAC address tables in adjacent devices, resulting in network disruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34793|2024-09-17T01:10:35.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1714|2024-09-17T04:24:31.977Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1714</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) 2.0 Single Sign-On (SSO) for Clientless SSL VPN (WebVPN) and AnyConnect Remote Access VPN in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to successfully establish a VPN session to an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper credential management when using NT LAN Manager (NTLM) or basic authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by opening a VPN session to an affected device after another VPN user has successfully authenticated to the affected device via SAML SSO. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to connect to secured networks behind the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1714|2024-09-17T04:24:31.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 16:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15465|2024-09-17T02:47:36.834Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15465</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the authorization subsystem of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow an authenticated, but unprivileged (levels 0 and 1), remote attacker to perform privileged actions by using the web management interface. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of user privileges when using the web management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific HTTP requests via HTTPS to an affected device as an unprivileged user. An exploit could allow the attacker to retrieve files (including the running configuration) from the device or to upload and replace software images on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15465|2024-09-17T02:47:36.834Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3585|2024-09-17T00:46:42.617Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3585</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TLS handler of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software for Cisco Firepower 1000 Series firewalls could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain access to sensitive information. The vulnerability is due to improper implementation of countermeasures against the Bleichenbacher attack for cipher suites that rely on RSA for key exchange. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted TLS messages to the device, which would act as an oracle and allow the attacker to carry out a chosen-ciphertext attack. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform cryptanalytic operations that may allow decryption of previously captured TLS sessions to the affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must be able to perform both of the following actions: Capture TLS traffic that is in transit between clients and the affected device Actively establish a considerable number of TLS connections to the affected device</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3585|2024-09-17T00:46:42.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3167|2024-09-17T00:27:02.158Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3167</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco FXOS Software and Cisco UCS Manager Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system (OS). The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including crafted arguments to specific commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying OS with the privileges of the currently logged-in user for all affected platforms excluding Cisco UCS 6400 Series Fabric Interconnects. On Cisco UCS 6400 Series Fabric Interconnects, the injected commands are executed with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3167|2024-09-17T00:27:02.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 16:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3306|2024-09-17T03:42:52.334Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP module of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the affected device. The vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of certain DHCP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCP packet to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3306|2024-09-17T03:42:52.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3334|2024-09-17T02:00:38.383Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3334</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the ARP packet processing of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software for Cisco Firepower 2100 Series Security Appliances could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of ARP packets received by the management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of unicast ARP packets in a short timeframe that would reach the management interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to consume resources on an affected device, which would prevent the device from sending internal system keepalives and eventually cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3334|2024-09-17T02:00:38.383Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12676|2024-09-17T02:47:49.191Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12676</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Open Shortest Path First (OSPF) implementation of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability exists because the affected software improperly parses certain options in OSPF link-state advertisement (LSA) type 11 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted LSA type 11 OSPF packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a reload of the affected device, resulting in a DoS condition for client traffic that is traversing the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12676|2024-09-17T02:47:49.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20737|2024-09-17T02:11:58.345Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20737</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the handler for HTTP authentication for resources accessed through the Clientless SSL VPN portal of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device or to obtain portions of process memory from an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient bounds checking when parsing specific HTTP authentication messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious traffic to an affected device acting as a VPN Gateway. To send this malicious traffic, an attacker would need to control a web server that can be accessed through the Clientless SSL VPN portal. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition, or to retrieve bytes from the device process memory that may contain sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20737|2024-09-17T02:11:58.345Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34792|2024-09-17T04:14:09.924Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34792</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the memory management of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper resource management when connection rates are high. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by opening a significant number of connections on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34792|2024-09-17T04:14:09.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3304|2024-09-17T02:36:33.128Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3304</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web interface of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to a lack of proper input validation of HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition. Note: This vulnerability applies to IP Version 4 (IPv4) and IP Version 6 (IPv6) HTTP traffic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3304|2024-09-17T02:36:33.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3529|2024-09-17T02:51:58.826Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3529</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the SSL VPN negotiation process for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to inefficient direct memory access (DMA) memory management during the negotiation phase of an SSL VPN connection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a steady stream of crafted Datagram TLS (DTLS) traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust DMA memory on the device and cause a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3529|2024-09-17T02:51:58.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3599|2024-09-17T00:46:08.665Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3599</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3599|2024-09-17T00:46:08.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:37:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20742|2024-09-17T01:26:24.223Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20742</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in an IPsec VPN library of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to read or modify data within an IPsec IKEv2 VPN tunnel. This vulnerability is due to an improper implementation of Galois/Counter Mode (GCM) ciphers. An attacker in a man-in-the-middle position could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting a sufficient number of encrypted messages across an affected IPsec IKEv2 VPN tunnel and then using cryptanalytic techniques to break the encryption. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to decrypt, read, modify, and re-encrypt data that is transmitted across an affected IPsec IKEv2 VPN tunnel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20742|2024-09-17T01:26:24.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20358|2024-08-15T16:32:41.453Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20358</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) restore functionality that is available in Cisco ASA Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because the contents of a backup file are improperly sanitized at restore time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20358|2024-08-15T16:32:41.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20443|2024-08-07T18:13:18.759Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20443</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have at least a low-privileged account on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20443|2024-08-07T18:13:18.759Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20353|2024-08-01T21:59:41.487Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20353</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the management and VPN web servers for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incomplete error checking when parsing an HTTP header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to a targeted web server on a device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition when the device reloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20353|2024-08-01T21:59:41.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20358|2024-08-01T21:59:42.299Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20358</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) restore functionality that is available in Cisco ASA Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because the contents of a backup file are improperly sanitized at restore time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20358|2024-08-01T21:59:42.299Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20293|2024-08-01T21:59:41.290Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the activation of an access control list (ACL) on Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the protection that is offered by a configured ACL on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an ACL changes from inactive to active in the running configuration of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device that should be denied by the configured ACL. The reverse condition is also truetraffic that should be permitted could be denied by the configured ACL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL protections on the affected device, allowing the attacker to access trusted networks that the device might be protecting. Note: This vulnerability applies to both IPv4 and IPv6 traffic as well as dual-stack ACL configurations in which both IPv4 and IPv6 ACLs are configured on an interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20293|2024-08-01T21:59:41.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20359|2024-08-01T21:59:42.379Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20359</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a legacy capability that allowed for the preloading of VPN clients and plug-ins and that has been available in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of a file when it is read from system flash memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by copying a crafted file to the disk0: file system of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected device after the next reload of the device, which could alter system behavior. Because the injected code could persist across device reboots, Cisco has raised the Security Impact Rating (SIR) of this advisory from Medium to High.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20359|2024-08-01T21:59:42.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20355|2024-08-01T21:59:42.284Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20355</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of SAML 2.0 single sign-on (SSO) for remote access VPN services in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to successfully establish a VPN session on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper separation of authorization domains when using SAML authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using valid credentials to successfully authenticate using their designated connection profile (tunnel group), intercepting the SAML SSO token that is sent back from the Cisco ASA device, and then submitting the same SAML SSO token to a different tunnel group for authentication. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to establish a remote access VPN session using a connection profile that they are not authorized to use and connect to secured networks behind the affected device that they are not authorized to access. For successful exploitation, the attacker must have valid remote access VPN user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20355|2024-08-01T21:59:42.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20353|2024-06-04T17:40:15.708Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20353</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the management and VPN web servers for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incomplete error checking when parsing an HTTP header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to a targeted web server on a device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition when the device reloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20353|2024-06-04T17:40:15.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20359|2024-06-04T17:40:02.581Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20359</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a legacy capability that allowed for the preloading of VPN clients and plug-ins and that has been available in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of a file when it is read from system flash memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by copying a crafted file to the disk0: file system of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected device after the next reload of the device, which could alter system behavior. Because the injected code could persist across device reboots, Cisco has raised the Security Impact Rating (SIR) of this advisory from Medium to High.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20359|2024-06-04T17:40:02.581Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20355|2024-06-04T17:39:58.380Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20355</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of SAML 2.0 single sign-on (SSO) for remote access VPN services in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to successfully establish a VPN session on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper separation of authorization domains when using SAML authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using valid credentials to successfully authenticate using their designated connection profile (tunnel group), intercepting the SAML SSO token that is sent back from the Cisco ASA device, and then submitting the same SAML SSO token to a different tunnel group for authentication. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to establish a remote access VPN session using a connection profile that they are not authorized to use and connect to secured networks behind the affected device that they are not authorized to access. For successful exploitation, the attacker must have valid remote access VPN user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20355|2024-06-04T17:39:58.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20293|2024-06-04T17:39:54.684Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the activation of an access control list (ACL) on Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the protection that is offered by a configured ACL on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an ACL changes from inactive to active in the running configuration of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device that should be denied by the configured ACL. The reverse condition is also truetraffic that should be permitted could be denied by the configured ACL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL protections on the affected device, allowing the attacker to access trusted networks that the device might be protecting. Note: This vulnerability applies to both IPv4 and IPv6 traffic as well as dual-stack ACL configurations in which both IPv4 and IPv6 ACLs are configured on an interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20293|2024-06-04T17:39:54.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20358|2024-04-24T19:38:23.689Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20358</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) restore functionality that is available in Cisco ASA Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because the contents of a backup file are improperly sanitized at restore time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20358|2024-04-24T19:38:23.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20293|2024-07-02T15:36:56.903Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the activation of an access control list (ACL) on Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the protection that is offered by a configured ACL on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when an ACL changes from inactive to active in the running configuration of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device that should be denied by the configured ACL. The reverse condition is also truetraffic that should be permitted could be denied by the configured ACL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL protections on the affected device, allowing the attacker to access trusted networks that the device might be protecting. Note: This vulnerability applies to both IPv4 and IPv6 traffic as well as dual-stack ACL configurations in which both IPv4 and IPv6 ACLs are configured on an interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20293|2024-07-02T15:36:56.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20443|2024-08-07T16:42:05.023Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20443</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have at least a low-privileged account on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20443|2024-08-07T16:42:05.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20443|2024-08-08T03:55:30.688Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20443</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco ISE could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have at least a low-privileged account on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20443|2024-08-08T03:55:30.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20358|2024-08-20T03:55:11.390Z -- cisco -- cisco%20adaptive%20security%20appliance%20%28asa%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20358</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) restore functionality that is available in Cisco ASA Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because the contents of a backup file are improperly sanitized at restore time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20358|2024-08-20T03:55:11.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
