<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20xe%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:25:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0476|2024-09-17T01:21:34.212Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0476</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Network Address Translation (NAT) Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) Application Layer Gateway (ALG) of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload. The vulnerability is due to improper processing of SIP packets in transit while NAT is performed on an affected device. An unauthenticated, remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted SIP packets via UDP port 5060 through an affected device that is performing NAT for SIP packets. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0476|2024-09-17T01:21:34.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20693|2024-09-17T00:30:31.717Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20693</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform an injection attack against an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input to the web UI API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to inject commands to the underlying operating system with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20693|2024-09-17T00:30:31.717Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1742|2024-09-17T00:26:25.889Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1742</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive configuration information. The vulnerability is due to improper access control to files within the web UI. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to sensitive configuration information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1742|2024-09-17T00:26:25.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 23:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15372|2024-09-17T01:40:56.285Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15372</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the MACsec Key Agreement (MKA) using Extensible Authentication Protocol-Transport Layer Security (EAP-TLS) functionality of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass authentication and pass traffic through a Layer 3 interface of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a logic error in the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to and passing traffic through a Layer 3 interface of an affected device, if the interface is configured for MACsec MKA using EAP-TLS and is running in access-session closed mode. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass 802.1x network access controls and gain access to the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15372|2024-09-17T01:40:56.285Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12663|2024-09-17T02:06:41.649Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12663</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco TrustSec (CTS) Protected Access Credential (PAC) provisioning module of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of attributes in RADIUS messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious RADIUS message to an affected device while the device is in a specific state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12663|2024-09-17T02:06:41.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 20:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1623|2024-09-17T01:55:35.020Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1623</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) punt handling function of Cisco cBR-8 Converged Broadband Routers could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to overload a device punt path, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to the punt path being overwhelmed by large quantities of SNMP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of SNMP requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overload the device punt path, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1623|2024-09-17T01:55:35.020Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1760|2024-09-17T03:27:50.010Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1760</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Performance Routing Version 3 (PfRv3) of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the affected device to reload. The vulnerability is due to the processing of malformed smart probe packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specially crafted smart probe packets at the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to reload the device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) attack on an affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1760|2024-09-17T03:27:50.010Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3494|2024-09-17T03:33:00.044Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3494</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3494|2024-09-17T03:33:00.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:52:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1759|2024-09-17T04:28:46.756Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1759</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in access control list (ACL) functionality of the Gigabit Ethernet Management interface of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to reach the configured IP addresses on the Gigabit Ethernet Management interface. The vulnerability is due to a logic error that was introduced in the Cisco IOS XE Software 16.1.1 Release, which prevents the ACL from working when applied against the management interface. An attacker could exploit this issue by attempting to access the device via the management interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1759|2024-09-17T04:28:46.756Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1382|2024-09-17T03:59:20.493Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1382</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject arbitrary commands to be executed with root privileges on the underlying operating system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation on certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and submitting crafted input to the CLI. The attacker must be authenticated as an administrative user to execute the affected commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1382|2024-09-17T03:59:20.493Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3418|2024-09-17T00:47:01.648Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3418</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Routers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to send ICMPv6 traffic prior to the client being placed into RUN state. The vulnerability is due to an incomplete access control list (ACL) being applied prior to RUN state. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the associated service set identifier (SSID) and sending ICMPv6 traffic. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send ICMPv6 traffic prior to RUN state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3418|2024-09-17T00:47:01.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 18:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1451|2024-09-17T02:57:48.726Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1451</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Easy Virtual Switching System (VSS) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 4500 Series Switches and Cisco Catalyst 4500-X Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying Linux operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to incorrect boundary checks of certain values in Easy VSS protocol packets that are destined for an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted Easy VSS protocol packets to UDP port 5500 while the affected device is in a specific state. When the crafted packet is processed, a buffer overflow condition may occur. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition or execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the underlying Linux operating system of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1451|2024-09-17T02:57:48.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3390|2024-09-17T02:46:43.160Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3390</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) trap generation for wireless clients of the Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the device to unexpectedly reload, causing a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to the lack of input validation of the information used to generate an SNMP trap in relation to a wireless client connection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending an 802.1x packet with crafted parameters during the wireless authentication setup phase of a connection. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, causing a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3390|2024-09-17T02:46:43.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 18:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1436|2024-09-17T00:11:02.193Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1436</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to conduct path traversal attacks and obtain read access to sensitive files on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view arbitrary files on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1436|2024-09-17T00:11:02.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3428|2024-09-17T02:07:11.488Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3428</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the WLAN Local Profiling feature of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to incorrect parsing of HTTP packets while performing HTTP-based endpoint device classifications. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could cause an affected device to reboot, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3428|2024-09-17T02:07:11.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1754|2024-09-17T02:58:16.986Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1754</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the authorization subsystem of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated but unprivileged (level 1), remote attacker to run privileged Cisco IOS commands by using the web UI. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of user privileges of web UI users. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a malicious payload to a specific endpoint in the web UI. A successful exploit could allow the lower-privileged attacker to execute arbitrary commands with higher privileges on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1754|2024-09-17T02:58:16.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1383|2024-09-17T03:47:53.974Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1383</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access the underlying operating system with root privileges. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient input validation of certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by authenticating to the device and submitting crafted input to the CLI. The attacker must be authenticated as an administrative user to execute the affected commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access the underlying operating system with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1383|2024-09-17T03:47:53.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1621|2024-09-17T04:25:31.064Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1621</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Layer 2 punt code of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a queue wedge on an interface that receives specific Layer 2 frames, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain Layer 2 frames. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific Layer 2 frames on the segment the router is connected to. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a queue wedge on the interface, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1621|2024-09-17T04:25:31.064Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3509|2024-09-17T00:50:48.557Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3509</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP message handler of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco cBR-8 Converged Broadband Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the supervisor to crash, which could result in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to insufficient error handling when DHCP version 4 (DHCPv4) messages are parsed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious DHCPv4 message to or through a WAN interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a reload of the affected device. Note: On Cisco cBR-8 Converged Broadband Routers, all of the following are considered WAN interfaces: 10 Gbps Ethernet interfaces 100 Gbps Ethernet interfaces Port channel interfaces that include multiple 10 and/or 100 Gbps Ethernet interfaces</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3509|2024-09-17T00:50:48.557Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3399|2024-09-17T04:25:47.417Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation during CAPWAP packet processing. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted CAPWAP packet to an affected device, resulting in a buffer over-read. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3399|2024-09-17T04:25:47.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 18:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3497|2024-09-17T01:10:40.991Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3497</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3497|2024-09-17T01:10:40.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1441|2024-09-17T02:21:34.473Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1441</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the hardware initialization routines of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco 1100 Series Industrial Integrated Services Routers and Cisco ESR6300 Embedded Series Routers could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute unsigned code at system boot time. This vulnerability is due to incorrect validations of parameters passed to a diagnostic script that is executed when the device boots up. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by tampering with an executable file stored on a device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute unsigned code at boot time and bypass the software image verification check part of the secure boot process of an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need administrative level credentials (level 15) on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1441|2024-09-17T02:21:34.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1220|2024-09-17T03:43:34.793Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1220</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web UI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with read-only privileges to cause the web UI software to become unresponsive and consume vty line instances, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient error handling in the web UI. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending crafted HTTP packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the web UI software to become unresponsive and consume all available vty lines, preventing new session establishment and resulting in a DoS condition. Manual intervention would be required to regain web UI and vty session functionality. Note: These vulnerabilities do not affect the console connection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1220|2024-09-17T03:43:34.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1371|2024-09-17T02:47:30.037Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1371</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the role-based access control of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with read-only privileges to obtain administrative privileges by using the console port when the device is in the default SD-WAN configuration. This vulnerability occurs because the default configuration is applied for console authentication and authorization. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the console port and authenticating as a read-only user. A successful exploit could allow a user with read-only permissions to access administrative privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1371|2024-09-17T02:47:30.037Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1625|2024-09-17T02:27:51.043Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1625</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Zone-Based Policy Firewall feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to prevent the Zone-Based Policy Firewall from correctly classifying traffic. This vulnerability exists because ICMP and UDP responder-to-initiator flows are not inspected when the Zone-Based Policy Firewall has either Unified Threat Defense (UTD) or Application Quality of Experience (AppQoE) configured. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send UDP or ICMP flows through the network. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to inject traffic through the Zone-Based Policy Firewall, resulting in traffic being dropped because it is incorrectly classified or in incorrect reporting figures being produced by high-speed logging (HSL).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1625|2024-09-17T02:27:51.043Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3403|2024-09-17T04:15:09.421Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3403</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject a command to the underlying operating system that will execute with root privileges upon the next reboot of the device. The authenticated user must have privileged EXEC permissions on the device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient protection of values passed to a script that executes during device startup. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by writing values to a specific file. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands with root privileges each time the affected device is restarted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3403|2024-09-17T04:15:09.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 18:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3396|2024-09-17T03:49:18.746Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3396</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the file system on the pluggable USB 3.0 Solid State Drive (SSD) for Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, physical attacker to remove the USB 3.0 SSD and modify sensitive areas of the file system, including the namespace container protections. The vulnerability occurs because the USB 3.0 SSD control data is not stored on the internal boot flash. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by removing the USB 3.0 SSD, modifying or deleting files on the USB 3.0 SSD by using another device, and then reinserting the USB 3.0 SSD on the original device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to remove container protections and perform file actions outside the namespace of the container with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3396|2024-09-17T03:49:18.746Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 18:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3508|2024-09-17T01:31:09.450Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3508</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IP Address Resolution Protocol (ARP) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco ASR 1000 Series Aggregation Services Routers with a 20-Gbps Embedded Services Processor (ESP) installed could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service condition. The vulnerability is due to insufficient error handling when an affected device has reached platform limitations. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious series of IP ARP messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust system resources, which would eventually cause the affected device to reload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3508|2024-09-17T01:31:09.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1750|2024-09-17T02:53:34.468Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1750</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Easy Virtual Switching System (VSS) of Cisco IOS XE Software on Catalyst 4500 Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the switches to reload. The vulnerability is due to incomplete error handling when processing Cisco Discovery Protocol (CDP) packets used with the Easy Virtual Switching System. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted CDP packet. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1750|2024-09-17T02:53:34.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 23:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3510|2024-09-17T03:48:23.664Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3510</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Umbrella Connector component of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9200 Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a reload, resulting in a denial of service condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient error handling when parsing DNS requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of malicious DNS requests to an Umbrella Connector client interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a crash of the iosd process, which triggers a reload of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3510|2024-09-17T03:48:23.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1398|2024-09-17T02:31:12.936Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1398</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot logic of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with level 15 privileges or an unauthenticated attacker with physical access to execute arbitrary code on the underlying Linux operating system of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to incorrect validations of specific function arguments that are passed to the boot script. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by tampering with a specific file, which an affected device would process during the initial boot process. On systems that are protected by the Unified Extensible Firmware Interface (UEFI) secure boot feature, a successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute unsigned code at boot time and bypass the image verification check in the secure boot process of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1398|2024-09-17T02:31:12.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34696|2024-09-17T01:40:59.147Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34696</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) programming of Cisco ASR 900 and ASR 920 Series Aggregation Services Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL. This vulnerability is due to incorrect programming of hardware when an ACL is configured using a method other than the configuration CLI. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass an ACL on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34696|2024-09-17T01:40:59.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34723|2024-09-17T01:45:49.127Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34723</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a specific CLI command that is run on Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to overwrite arbitrary files in the configuration database of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of specific CLI command parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by issuing that command with specific parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite the content of the configuration database and gain root-level access to an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34723|2024-09-17T01:45:49.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3407|2024-09-17T02:15:55.704Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3407</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the RESTCONF and NETCONF-YANG access control list (ACL) function of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload. The vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of the ACL that is tied to the RESTCONF or NETCONF-YANG feature. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the device using RESTCONF or NETCONF-YANG. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3407|2024-09-17T02:15:55.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 18:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1434|2024-09-17T03:32:51.380Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1434</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to overwrite arbitrary files in the underlying file system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of the parameters of a specific CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by issuing that command with specific parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite the content of any arbitrary file that resides on the underlying host file system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1434|2024-09-17T03:32:51.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1624|2024-09-17T03:53:03.000Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1624</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Rate Limiting Network Address Translation (NAT) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization in the Cisco QuantumFlow Processor of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to mishandling of the rate limiting feature within the QuantumFlow Processor. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending large amounts of traffic that would be subject to NAT and rate limiting through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the QuantumFlow Processor utilization to reach 100 percent on the affected device, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1624|2024-09-17T03:53:03.000Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20682|2024-09-17T02:05:55.428Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20682</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Catalyst 9000 Family could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to inadequate input validation of incoming CAPWAP packets encapsulating multicast DNS (mDNS) queries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to a wireless network and sending a crafted mDNS query, which would flow through and be processed by the wireless controller. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20682|2024-09-17T02:05:55.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20847|2024-09-17T01:00:29.150Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20847</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP processing functionality of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Catalyst 9000 Family could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to the improper processing of DHCP messages. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious DHCP messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20847|2024-09-17T01:00:29.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 18:45:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0469|2024-09-17T04:14:23.831Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0469</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web user interface of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload. The vulnerability is due to a double-free-in-memory handling by the affected software when specific HTTP requests are processed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific HTTP requests to the web user interface of the affected software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have access to the management interface of the affected software, which is typically connected to a restricted management network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0469|2024-09-17T04:14:23.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0470|2024-09-17T02:06:12.780Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0470</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web framework of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a buffer overflow condition on an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to the affected software improperly parsing malformed HTTP packets that are destined to a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed HTTP packet to an affected device for processing. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a buffer overflow condition on the affected device, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0470|2024-09-17T02:06:12.780Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1394|2024-09-17T02:16:16.698Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1394</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the ingress traffic manager of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) 520 Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition in the web management interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of certain IPv4 TCP traffic that is destined to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of crafted TCP packets to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the web management interface to become unavailable, resulting in a DoS condition. Note: This vulnerability does not impact traffic that is going through the device or going to the Management Ethernet interface of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1394|2024-09-17T02:16:16.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0481|2024-09-17T03:38:31.635Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0481</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI parser of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute commands on the underlying Linux shell of an affected device with root privileges. The vulnerability exist because the affected software improperly sanitizes command arguments, failing to prevent access to certain internal data structures on an affected device. An attacker who has privileged EXEC mode (privilege level 15) access to an affected device could exploit these vulnerabilities on the device by executing CLI commands that contain custom arguments. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0481|2024-09-17T03:38:31.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12653|2024-09-17T01:00:40.043Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12653</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Raw Socket Transport feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a reload of an affected device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to improper parsing of Raw Socket Transport payloads. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing a TCP session and then sending a malicious TCP segment via IPv4 to an affected device. This cannot be exploited via IPv6, as the Raw Socket Transport feature does not support IPv6 as a network layer protocol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12653|2024-09-17T01:00:40.043Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 20:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20864|2024-09-17T00:37:06.142Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20864</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the password-recovery disable feature of Cisco IOS XE ROM Monitor (ROMMON) Software for Cisco Catalyst Switches could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker to recover the configuration or reset the enable password. This vulnerability is due to a problem with the file and boot variable permissions in ROMMON. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by rebooting the switch into ROMMON and entering specific commands through the console. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read any file or reset the enable password.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20864|2024-09-17T00:37:06.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 20:43:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15374|2024-09-17T02:15:45.142Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15374</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Image Verification feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to install a malicious software image or file on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to the affected software improperly verifying digital signatures for software images and files that are uploaded to a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a malicious software image or file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass digital signature verification checks for software images and files and install a malicious software image or file on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15374|2024-09-17T02:15:45.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20684|2024-09-17T00:37:22.200Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20684</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) trap generation for wireless clients of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Catalyst 9000 Family could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to unexpectedly reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on the device. This vulnerability is due to a lack of input validation of the information used to generate an SNMP trap related to a wireless client connection event. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending an 802.1x packet with crafted parameters during the wireless authentication setup phase of a connection. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20684|2024-09-17T00:37:22.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34768|2024-09-17T02:27:41.164Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34768</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit the vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34768|2024-09-17T02:27:41.164Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:26:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34769|2024-09-17T03:18:00.709Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34769</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit the vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34769|2024-09-17T03:18:00.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1753|2024-09-17T02:37:44.485Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1753</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated but unprivileged (level 1), remote attacker to run privileged Cisco IOS commands by using the web UI. The vulnerability is due to a failure to validate and sanitize input in Web Services Management Agent (WSMA) functions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a malicious payload to the affected device's web UI. A successful exploit could allow the lower-privileged attacker to execute arbitrary commands with higher privileges on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1753|2024-09-17T02:37:44.485Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3488|2024-09-17T02:41:45.355Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3488</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3488|2024-09-17T02:41:45.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34770|2024-09-17T04:28:54.300Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34770</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code with administrative privileges or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs during the validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code with administrative privileges or cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34770|2024-09-17T04:28:54.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-12664|2024-09-17T00:26:36.860Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-12664</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Dialer interface feature for ISDN connections in Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco 4000 Series Integrated Services Routers (ISRs) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to pass IPv4 traffic through an ISDN channel prior to successful PPP authentication. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of the state of the PPP IP Control Protocol (IPCP). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by making an ISDN call to an affected device and sending traffic through the ISDN channel prior to successful PPP authentication. Alternatively, an unauthenticated, remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through an affected device that is configured to exit via an ISDN connection for which both the Dialer interface and the Basic Rate Interface (BRI) have been configured, but the Challenge Handshake Authentication Protocol (CHAP) password for PPP does not match the remote end. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to pass IPv4 traffic through an unauthenticated ISDN connection for a few seconds, from initial ISDN call setup until PPP authentication fails.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-12664|2024-09-17T00:26:36.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 20:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3526|2024-09-17T02:27:12.274Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3526</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Common Open Policy Service (COPS) engine of Cisco IOS XE Software on Cisco cBR-8 Converged Broadband Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to crash a device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed COPS message to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3526|2024-09-17T02:27:12.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3417|2024-09-17T00:06:50.166Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3417</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute persistent code at boot time and break the chain of trust. This vulnerability is due to incorrect validations by boot scripts when specific ROM monitor (ROMMON) variables are set. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by installing code to a specific directory in the underlying operating system (OS) and setting a specific ROMMON variable. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute persistent code on the underlying OS. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need access to the root shell on the device or have physical access to the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3417|2024-09-17T00:06:50.166Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 18:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1619|2024-09-17T04:25:16.482Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1619</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the authentication, authorization, and accounting (AAA) function of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass NETCONF or RESTCONF authentication and do either of the following: Install, manipulate, or delete the configuration of an affected device Cause memory corruption that results in a denial of service (DoS) on an affected device This vulnerability is due to an uninitialized variable. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of NETCONF or RESTCONF requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to use NETCONF or RESTCONF to install, manipulate, or delete the configuration of a network device or to corrupt memory on the device, resulting a DoS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1619|2024-09-17T04:25:16.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1615|2024-09-17T03:34:03.057Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1615</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the packet processing functionality of Cisco Embedded Wireless Controller (EWC) Software for Catalyst Access Points (APs) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected AP. This vulnerability is due to insufficient buffer allocation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust available resources and cause a DoS condition on an affected AP, as well as a DoS condition for client traffic traversing the AP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1615|2024-09-17T03:34:03.057Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20259|2024-08-27T21:04:37.666Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP snooping feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a crafted IPv4 DHCP request packet being mishandled when endpoint analytics are enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCP request through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; Note: The attack vector is listed as network because a DHCP relay anywhere on the network could allow exploits from networks other than the adjacent one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20259|2024-08-27T21:04:37.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20306|2024-08-16T18:48:47.441Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Unified Threat Defense (UTD) configuration CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying host operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have level 15 privileges on the affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20306|2024-08-16T18:48:47.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20313|2024-08-09T18:34:02.110Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20313</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of OSPF updates that are processed by a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF update to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20313|2024-08-09T18:34:02.110Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20309|2024-08-09T18:34:29.824Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in auxiliary asynchronous port (AUX) functions of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause an affected device to reload or stop responding.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific ingress traffic when flow control hardware is enabled on the AUX port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by reverse telnetting to the AUX port and sending specific data after connecting. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reset or stop responding, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20309|2024-08-09T18:34:29.824Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20313|2024-08-01T21:59:42.856Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20313</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of OSPF updates that are processed by a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF update to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20313|2024-08-01T21:59:42.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-08-01T21:59:41.851Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-08-01T21:59:41.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20306|2024-08-01T21:59:41.650Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Unified Threat Defense (UTD) configuration CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying host operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have level 15 privileges on the affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20306|2024-08-01T21:59:41.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20278|2024-08-01T21:59:41.100Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20278</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NETCONF feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input over NETCONF to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges from Administrator to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20278|2024-08-01T21:59:41.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T21:52:31.616Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T21:52:31.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-08-01T21:59:42.197Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-08-01T21:59:42.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-08-01T21:59:42.311Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-08-01T21:59:42.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20303|2024-08-01T21:59:41.376Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20303</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multicast DNS (mDNS) gateway feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Wireless LAN Controllers (WLCs) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper management of mDNS client entries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the wireless network and sending a continuous stream of specific mDNS packets. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the wireless controller to have high CPU utilization, which could lead to access points (APs) losing their connection to the controller and result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20303|2024-08-01T21:59:41.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20324|2024-08-01T21:59:41.715Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20324</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to access WLAN configuration details including passwords.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper privilege checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the show and show tech wireless CLI commands to access configuration details, including passwords. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access configuration details that they are not authorized to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20324|2024-08-01T21:59:41.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20259|2024-08-01T21:52:31.719Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP snooping feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a crafted IPv4 DHCP request packet being mishandled when endpoint analytics are enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCP request through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; Note: The attack vector is listed as network because a DHCP relay anywhere on the network could allow exploits from networks other than the adjacent one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20259|2024-08-01T21:52:31.719Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20309|2024-08-01T21:59:41.337Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in auxiliary asynchronous port (AUX) functions of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause an affected device to reload or stop responding.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific ingress traffic when flow control hardware is enabled on the AUX port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by reverse telnetting to the AUX port and sending specific data after connecting. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reset or stop responding, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20309|2024-08-01T21:59:41.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-07-02T16:23:39.427Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-07-02T16:23:39.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-07-02T16:25:13.272Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-07-02T16:25:13.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-07-02T16:25:58.752Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-07-02T16:25:58.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-06-20T17:42:35.196Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-06-20T17:42:35.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20303|2024-06-04T17:39:55.892Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20303</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multicast DNS (mDNS) gateway feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Wireless LAN Controllers (WLCs) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper management of mDNS client entries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the wireless network and sending a continuous stream of specific mDNS packets. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the wireless controller to have high CPU utilization, which could lead to access points (APs) losing their connection to the controller and result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20303|2024-06-04T17:39:55.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-03-27T16:57:27.974Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-03-27T16:57:27.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20313|2024-04-24T20:42:10.379Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20313</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of OSPF updates that are processed by a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF update to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20313|2024-04-24T20:42:10.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20309|2024-03-27T17:02:19.749Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in auxiliary asynchronous port (AUX) functions of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause an affected device to reload or stop responding.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific ingress traffic when flow control hardware is enabled on the AUX port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by reverse telnetting to the AUX port and sending specific data after connecting. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reset or stop responding, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20309|2024-03-27T17:02:19.749Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20324|2024-03-27T16:55:53.837Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20324</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to access WLAN configuration details including passwords.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper privilege checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the show and show tech wireless CLI commands to access configuration details, including passwords. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access configuration details that they are not authorized to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20324|2024-03-27T16:55:53.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20278|2024-03-27T16:59:12.963Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20278</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NETCONF feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input over NETCONF to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges from Administrator to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20278|2024-03-27T16:59:12.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20259|2024-03-27T16:53:53.073Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP snooping feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a crafted IPv4 DHCP request packet being mishandled when endpoint analytics are enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCP request through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; Note: The attack vector is listed as network because a DHCP relay anywhere on the network could allow exploits from networks other than the adjacent one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20259|2024-03-27T16:53:53.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-04-03T16:36:06.520Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-04-03T16:36:06.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20306|2024-03-27T16:58:22.583Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Unified Threat Defense (UTD) configuration CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying host operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have level 15 privileges on the affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20306|2024-03-27T16:58:22.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-03-27T16:49:03.113Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-03-27T16:49:03.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-03-27T17:03:54.505Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-03-27T17:03:54.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-06-20T20:50:12.348Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-06-20T20:50:12.348Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-06-20T20:52:30.286Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-06-20T20:52:30.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T15:33:37.498Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T15:33:37.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20278|2024-08-15T16:45:09.481Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20278</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NETCONF feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input over NETCONF to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges from Administrator to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20278|2024-08-15T16:45:09.481Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20324|2024-08-27T20:50:51.192Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20324</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to access WLAN configuration details including passwords.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper privilege checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the show and show tech wireless CLI commands to access configuration details, including passwords. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access configuration details that they are not authorized to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20324|2024-08-27T20:50:51.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
