<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Identity Services Engine Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Identity Services Engine Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 08:23:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20961|2024-08-03T02:31:58.679Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20961</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on the affected device with the privileges of the target user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20961|2024-08-03T02:31:58.679Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 18:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20965|2024-08-03T02:31:58.772Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20965</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to take privileges actions within the web-based management interface.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper access control on a feature within the web-based management interface of the affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing features through direct requests, bypassing checks within the application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to take privileged actions within the web-based management interface that should be otherwise restricted.&#13;
&#13;    &#13;
&#13;  {{value}} ["%7b%7bvalue%7d%7d"])}]]&#13;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20965|2024-08-03T02:31:58.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 17:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20914|2024-08-03T02:31:57.400Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20914</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the External RESTful Services (ERS) API of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain sensitive information. This vulnerability is due to excessive verbosity in a specific REST API output. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain sensitive information, including administrative credentials for an external authentication server. Note: To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid ERS administrative credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20914|2024-08-03T02:31:57.400Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20964|2024-08-03T02:31:59.027Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20964</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user input within requests as part of the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating requests to the web-based management interface to contain operating system commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary operating system commands on the underlying operating system with the privileges of the web services user.&#13;
&#13; Cisco has not yet released software updates that address this vulnerability. </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20964|2024-08-03T02:31:59.027Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 17:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20937|2024-08-03T02:31:58.639Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20937</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a feature that monitors RADIUS requests on Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to negatively affect the performance of an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient management of system resources. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by taking actions that cause Cisco ISE Software to receive specific RADIUS traffic. A successful and sustained exploit of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to cause reduced performance of the affected device, resulting in significant delays to RADIUS authentications.&#13;
&#13;   There are workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20937|2024-08-03T02:31:58.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 19:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20756|2024-08-03T02:24:49.698Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20756</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the RADIUS feature of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the affected system to stop processing RADIUS packets. This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain RADIUS requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to authenticate to a network or a service where the access server is using Cisco ISE as the RADIUS server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause Cisco ISE to stop processing RADIUS requests, causing authentication/authorization timeouts, which would then result in legitimate requests being denied access. Note: To recover the ability to process RADIUS packets, a manual restart of the affected Policy Service Node (PSN) is required. See the Details section for more information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20756|2024-08-03T02:24:49.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20962|2024-08-03T02:31:59.694Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20962</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Localdisk Management feature of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to make unauthorized changes to the file system of an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request with absolute path sequences. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to upload malicious files to arbitrary locations within the file system. Using this method, it is possible to access the underlying operating system and execute commands with system privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20962|2024-08-03T02:31:59.694Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 19:39:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20819|2024-08-03T02:24:49.971Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20819</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain sensitive information from an affected device. This vulnerability exists because administrative privilege levels for sensitive data are not properly enforced. An attacker with read-only privileges for the web-based management interface on an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by browsing to a page that contains sensitive data. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to collect sensitive information about the system configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20819|2024-08-03T02:24:49.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20733|2024-08-03T02:24:49.188Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20733</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the login page of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to log in without credentials and access all roles without any restrictions. This vulnerability is due to exposed sensitive Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) metadata. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the exposed SAML metadata to bypass authentication to the user portal. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access all roles without any restrictions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20733|2024-08-03T02:24:49.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20966|2024-08-03T02:31:58.663Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20966</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site scripting attacks against other users of the application web-based management interface.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of input to an application feature before storage within the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by creating entries within the application interface that contain malicious HTML or script code. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious HTML or script code within the application interface for use in further cross-site scripting attacks.&#13;
&#13; Cisco has not yet released software updates that address this vulnerability. </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20966|2024-08-03T02:31:58.663Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 17:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20782|2024-08-03T02:24:49.596Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20782</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain sensitive information from an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper enforcement of administrative privilege levels for high-value sensitive data. An attacker with read-only Administrator privileges to the web-based management interface on an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by browsing to a page that contains sensitive data. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to collect sensitive information regarding the configuration of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20782|2024-08-03T02:24:49.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20822|2024-08-03T02:24:49.999Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20822</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to read and delete files on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request that contains certain character sequences to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read or delete specific files on the device that their configured administrative level should not have access to. Cisco plans to release software updates that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20822|2024-08-03T02:24:49.999Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20956|2024-08-03T02:31:59.286Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20956</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to bypass authorization and access system files.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper access control in the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to list, download, and delete certain files that they should not have access to.&#13;
&#13; Cisco plans to release software updates that address this vulnerability.  &#13;
&#13;  https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ise-access-contol-EeufSUCx ["https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ise-access-contol-EeufSUCx"]&#13;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20956|2024-08-03T02:31:59.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 19:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20963|2024-08-03T02:31:58.989Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20963</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into specific pages of the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid credentials to access the web-based management interface of an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20963|2024-08-03T02:31:58.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 19:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20967|2024-08-03T02:31:59.863Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20967</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site scripting attacks against other users of the application web-based management interface.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of input to an application feature before storage within the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by creating entries within the application interface that contain malicious HTML or script code. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious HTML or script code within the application interface for use in further cross-site scripting attacks.&#13;
&#13; Cisco has not yet released software updates that address this vulnerability. </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20967|2024-08-03T02:31:59.863Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 17:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20959|2024-08-03T02:31:59.808Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20959</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the External RESTful Services (ERS) API of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated administrator of the web-based management interface to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20959|2024-08-03T02:31:59.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20368|2024-08-01T21:59:41.799Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20368</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on the affected device with the privileges of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20368|2024-08-01T21:59:41.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20332|2024-08-01T21:59:41.923Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20332</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack through an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation for specific HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send arbitrary network requests that are sourced from the affected device. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid Super Admin credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20332|2024-08-01T21:59:41.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-08-01T21:59:41.103Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-08-01T21:59:41.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T21:20:23.314Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T21:20:23.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20332|2024-06-04T17:40:15.273Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20332</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack through an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation for specific HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send arbitrary network requests that are sourced from the affected device. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid Super Admin credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20332|2024-06-04T17:40:15.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20368|2024-06-04T17:40:10.016Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20368</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on the affected device with the privileges of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20368|2024-06-04T17:40:10.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T16:28:22.193Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T16:28:22.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-18T03:55:22.366Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-18T03:55:22.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
