<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Small Business 300 Series Managed Switches</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20small%20business%20300%20series%20managed%20switches.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Small Business 300 Series Managed Switches</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 17:22:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1892|2024-09-16T16:37:54.234Z -- cisco -- cisco%20small%20business%20300%20series%20managed%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1892</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) input packet processor of Cisco Small Business 200, 300, and 500 Series Managed Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a memory corruption on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of HTTPS packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed HTTPS packet to the management web interface of the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an unexpected reload of the device, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1892|2024-09-16T16:37:54.234Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 01:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15439|2024-09-16T16:53:17.110Z -- cisco -- cisco%20small%20business%20300%20series%20managed%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15439</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Small Business Switches software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the user authentication mechanism of an affected device. The vulnerability exists because under specific circumstances, the affected software enables a privileged user account without notifying administrators of the system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using this account to log in to an affected device and execute commands with full admin rights. Cisco has not released software updates that address this vulnerability. This advisory will be updated with fixed software information once fixed software becomes available. There is a workaround to address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15439|2024-09-16T16:53:17.110Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
