<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Vision Dynamic Signage Director</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20vision%20dynamic%20signage%20director.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Vision Dynamic Signage Director</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 08:23:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3485|2024-08-04T07:37:54.279Z -- cisco -- cisco%20vision%20dynamic%20signage%20director
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3485</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the role-based access control (RBAC) functionality of the web management software of Cisco Vision Dynamic Signage Director could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to access resources that they should not be able to access and perform actions that they should not be able to perform. The vulnerability exists because the web management software does not properly handle RBAC. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view and delete certain screen content on the system that the attacker would not normally have privileges to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3485|2024-08-04T07:37:54.279Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3484|2024-08-04T07:37:54.317Z -- cisco -- cisco%20vision%20dynamic%20signage%20director
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3484</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Vision Dynamic Signage Director could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to view potentially sensitive information on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to incorrect permissions within Apache configuration. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the web-based management interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view potentially sensitive information on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3484|2024-08-04T07:37:54.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3491|2024-08-04T07:37:54.322Z -- cisco -- cisco%20vision%20dynamic%20signage%20director
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3491</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Vision Dynamic Signage Director could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative privileges to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface on an affected device. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting malicious data into a specific data field in the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have administrative privileges on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3491|2024-08-04T07:37:54.322Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34742|2024-08-04T00:19:48.125Z -- cisco -- cisco%20vision%20dynamic%20signage%20director
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34742</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Vision Dynamic Signage Director could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34742|2024-08-04T00:19:48.125Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3598|2024-08-04T07:37:55.688Z -- cisco -- cisco%20vision%20dynamic%20signage%20director
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3598</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Vision Dynamic Signage Director could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access confidential information or make configuration changes. The vulnerability is due to missing authentication for a specific section of the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing a crafted URL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain access to a section of the interface, which they could use to read confidential information or make configuration changes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3598|2024-08-04T07:37:55.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3450|2024-08-04T07:37:53.974Z -- cisco -- cisco%20vision%20dynamic%20signage%20director
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3450</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Vision Dynamic Signage Director could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative credentials to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-submitted parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the web-based management interface and sending malicious requests to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain data that is stored in the underlying database, including hashed user credentials. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid administrative credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3450|2024-08-04T07:37:53.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3490|2024-08-04T07:37:54.454Z -- cisco -- cisco%20vision%20dynamic%20signage%20director
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3490</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Vision Dynamic Signage Director could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative privileges to conduct directory traversal attacks and obtain read access to sensitive files on an affected system. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request that contains directory traversal character sequences to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read files on the underlying operating system with root privileges. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have administrative privileges on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3490|2024-08-04T07:37:54.454Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
