<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software 5.0(1a)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20nx-os%20software%205.0%281a%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco NX-OS Software 5.0(1a)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 18:24:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3454|2024-08-04T07:37:54.101Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software%205.0%281a%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3454</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Call Home feature of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary commands that could be executed with root privileges on the underlying operating system (OS). The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of specific Call Home configuration parameters when the software is configured for transport method HTTP. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by modifying parameters within the Call Home configuration on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges on the underlying OS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3454|2024-08-04T07:37:54.101Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3175|2024-08-04T07:24:00.704Z -- cisco -- cisco%20nx-os%20software%205.0%281a%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3175</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the resource handling system of Cisco NX-OS Software for Cisco MDS 9000 Series Multilayer Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper resource usage control. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic to the management interface (mgmt0) of an affected device at very high rates. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause unexpected behaviors such as high CPU usage, process crashes, or even full system reboots of an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3175|2024-08-04T07:24:00.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
