<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software 16.10.1</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%2016.10.1.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software 16.10.1</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:22:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3221|2024-08-04T07:30:57.790Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%2016.10.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3221</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Flexible NetFlow Version 9 packet processor of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of parameters in a Flexible NetFlow Version 9 record. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed Flexible NetFlow Version 9 packet to the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) data port of an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to trigger an infinite loop, resulting in a process crash that would cause a reload of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3221|2024-08-04T07:30:57.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3211|2024-08-04T07:24:00.915Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%2016.10.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3211</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges on the underlying operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper input sanitization. An attacker who has valid administrative access to an affected device could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a crafted input parameter on a form in the web UI and then submitting that form. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges on the device, which could lead to complete system compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3211|2024-08-04T07:24:00.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3206|2024-08-04T07:24:00.790Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%2016.10.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3206</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the handling of IEEE 802.11w Protected Management Frames (PMFs) of Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers that are running Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to terminate a valid user connection to an affected device. The vulnerability exists because the affected software does not properly validate 802.11w disassociation and deauthentication PMFs that it receives. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a spoofed 802.11w PMF from a valid, authenticated client on a network adjacent to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to terminate a single valid user connection to the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3206|2024-08-04T07:24:00.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3222|2024-08-04T07:30:56.518Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software%2016.10.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3222</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based user interface (web UI) of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to bypass access control restrictions on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to the presence of a proxy service at a specific endpoint of the web UI. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the proxy service. An exploit could allow the attacker to bypass access restrictions on the network by proxying their access request through the management network of the affected device. As the proxy is reached over the management virtual routing and forwarding (VRF), this could reduce the effectiveness of the bypass.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3222|2024-08-04T07:30:56.518Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
