<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Identity Services Engine Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Identity Services Engine Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:24:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15255|2024-08-05T00:42:03.945Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15255</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to bypass authorization and access sensitive information related to the device. The vulnerability exists because the software fails to sanitize URLs before it handles requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted URL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain unauthorized access to sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15255|2024-08-05T00:42:03.945Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15424|2024-08-05T09:54:03.606Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15424</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device with the privileges of the web server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15424|2024-08-05T09:54:03.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15455|2024-08-05T09:54:03.400Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15455</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the logging component of Cisco Identity Services Engine could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site scripting attacks. The vulnerability is due to the improper validation of requests stored in the system's logging database. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests to the targeted system. An exploit could allow the attacker to conduct cross-site scripting attacks when an administrator views the logs in the Admin Portal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15455|2024-08-05T09:54:03.400Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15440|2024-08-05T09:54:03.373Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15440</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web interface of an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied data that is written to log files and displayed in certain web pages of the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by convincing a user of the interface to click a specific link or view an affected log file. The injected script code may be executed in the context of the web-based management interface or allow the attacker to access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15440|2024-08-05T09:54:03.373Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15456|2024-08-05T09:54:03.418Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Admin Portal of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to view saved passwords in plain text. The vulnerability is due to the incorrect inclusion of saved passwords when loading configuration pages in the Admin Portal. An attacker with read or write access to the Admin Portal could exploit this vulnerability by browsing to a page that contains sensitive data. An exploit could allow the attacker to recover passwords for unauthorized use and expose those accounts to further attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15456|2024-08-05T09:54:03.418Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15281|2024-08-05T00:42:03.696Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15281</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device. The attacker must have valid administrator credentials. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious code into a troubleshooting file. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15281|2024-08-05T00:42:03.696Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15459|2024-08-05T09:54:03.512Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15459</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the administrative web interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to gain additional privileges on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper controls on certain pages in the web interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device with an administrator account and sending a crafted HTTP request. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to create additional Admin accounts with different user roles. An attacker could then use these accounts to perform actions within their scope. The attacker would need valid Admin credentials for the device. This vulnerability cannot be exploited to add a Super Admin account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15459|2024-08-05T09:54:03.512Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15425|2024-08-05T09:54:03.404Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15425</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device with the privileges of the web server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15425|2024-08-05T09:54:03.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15463|2024-08-05T09:54:03.611Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15463</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based interface. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of some parameters passed to the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by convincing a user of the interface to click a specific link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the web-based management interface or allow the attacker to access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15463|2024-08-05T09:54:03.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15282|2024-08-05T00:42:03.725Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15282</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker read tcpdump files generated on an affected device. The vulnerability is due an issue in the authentication logic of the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the web interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read a tcpdump file generated with a particular naming scheme.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15282|2024-08-05T00:42:03.725Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0187|2024-08-05T03:14:16.823Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0187</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Admin portal of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to obtain confidential information for privileged accounts. The vulnerability is due to the improper handling of confidential information. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging into the web interface on a vulnerable system. An exploit could allow an attacker to obtain confidential information for privileged accounts. This information could then be used to impersonate or negatively impact the privileged account on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0187|2024-08-05T03:14:16.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20368|2024-08-01T21:59:41.799Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20368</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on the affected device with the privileges of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20368|2024-08-01T21:59:41.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20332|2024-08-01T21:59:41.923Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20332</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack through an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation for specific HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send arbitrary network requests that are sourced from the affected device. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid Super Admin credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20332|2024-08-01T21:59:41.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-08-01T21:59:41.103Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-08-01T21:59:41.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T21:20:23.314Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T21:20:23.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20332|2024-06-04T17:40:15.273Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20332</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack through an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation for specific HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send arbitrary network requests that are sourced from the affected device. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid Super Admin credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20332|2024-06-04T17:40:15.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20368|2024-06-04T17:40:10.016Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20368</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on the affected device with the privileges of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20368|2024-06-04T17:40:10.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T16:28:22.193Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T16:28:22.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-18T03:55:22.366Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-18T03:55:22.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
