<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Umbrella </title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20umbrella.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Umbrella </description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 08:24:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3337|2024-08-04T07:30:58.188Z -- cisco -- cisco%20umbrella
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3337</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web server of Cisco Umbrella could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to redirect a user to an undesired web page. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation of the URL parameters in an HTTP request that is sent to an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request that could cause the web application to redirect the request to a specified malicious URL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to redirect a user to a malicious website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3337|2024-08-04T07:30:58.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3246|2024-08-04T07:30:57.643Z -- cisco -- cisco%20umbrella
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3246</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web server of Cisco Umbrella could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to perform a carriage return line feed (CRLF) injection attack against a user of an affected service. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to access a crafted URL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to inject arbitrary HTTP headers into valid HTTP responses sent to the browser of the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3246|2024-08-04T07:30:57.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
