<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Secure Email</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20secure%20email.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Secure Email</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20075|2024-01-25T16:57:41.853Z -- cisco -- cisco%20secure%20email
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-20075</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco Secure Email Gateway could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands.&#13;
&#13; These vulnerability is due to improper input validation in the CLI. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting operating system commands into a legitimate command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to escape the restricted command prompt and execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid Administrator credentials.&#13;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20075|2024-01-25T16:57:41.853Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 15:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20009|2024-01-25T16:57:30.327Z -- cisco -- cisco%20secure%20email
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-20009</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Web UI and administrative CLI of the Cisco Secure Email Gateway (ESA) and Cisco Secure Email and Web Manager (SMA) could allow an authenticated remote attacker and or authenticated local attacker to escalate their privilege level and gain root access. The attacker has to have a valid user credential with at least a [[privilege of operator - validate actual name]].&#13;
&#13; The vulnerability is due to the processing of a specially crafted SNMP configuration file. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the targeted device and uploading a specially crafted SNMP configuration file that when uploaded could allow for the execution of commands as root. An exploit could allow the attacker to gain root access on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20009|2024-01-25T16:57:30.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 15:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20392|2024-06-04T17:40:31.712Z -- cisco -- cisco%20secure%20email
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20392</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management API of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Secure Email Gateway could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct an HTTP response splitting attack. &#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of some parameters that are passed to the web-based management API of the affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of an affected interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks, resulting in the execution of arbitrary script code in the browser of the targeted user, or could allow the attacker to access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20392|2024-06-04T17:40:31.712Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:22:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20258|2024-06-04T17:40:25.043Z -- cisco -- cisco%20secure%20email
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20258</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Secure Email and Web Manager and Secure Email Gateway could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of an affected interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20258|2024-06-04T17:40:25.043Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20257|2024-06-04T17:40:16.569Z -- cisco -- cisco%20secure%20email
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20257</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco AsyncOS Software for Cisco Secure Email Gateway could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct an XSS attack against a user of the interface.r
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of an affected interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20257|2024-06-04T17:40:16.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
