<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20xe%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS XE Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 13:22:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34723|2024-08-04T00:19:48.115Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34723</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a specific CLI command that is run on Cisco IOS XE SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to overwrite arbitrary files in the configuration database of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of specific CLI command parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by issuing that command with specific parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite the content of the configuration database and gain root-level access to an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34723|2024-08-04T00:19:48.115Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34697|2024-08-04T00:19:47.953Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34697</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Protection Against Distributed Denial of Service Attacks feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct denial of service (DoS) attacks to or through the affected device. This vulnerability is due to incorrect programming of the half-opened connections limit, TCP SYN flood limit, or TCP SYN cookie features when the features are configured in vulnerable releases of Cisco IOS XE Software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to flood traffic to or through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to initiate a DoS attack to or through an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34697|2024-08-04T00:19:47.953Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3429|2024-08-04T07:37:54.102Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3429</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the WPA2 and WPA3 security implementation of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to incorrect packet processing during the WPA2 and WPA3 authentication handshake when configured for dot1x or pre-shared key (PSK) authentication key management (AKM) with 802.11r BSS Fast Transition (FT) enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted authentication packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could cause an affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3429|2024-08-04T07:37:54.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3494|2024-08-04T07:37:54.468Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3494</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3494|2024-08-04T07:37:54.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3404|2024-08-04T07:30:58.170Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3404</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the persistent Telnet/Secure Shell (SSH) CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain shell access on an affected device and execute commands on the underlying operating system (OS) with root privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient enforcement of the consent token in authorizing shell access. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the persistent Telnet/SSH CLI on an affected device and requesting shell access. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain shell access on the affected device and execute commands on the underlying OS with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3404|2024-08-04T07:30:58.170Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3390|2024-08-04T07:30:58.395Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3390</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) trap generation for wireless clients of the Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause the device to unexpectedly reload, causing a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to the lack of input validation of the information used to generate an SNMP trap in relation to a wireless client connection. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending an 802.1x packet with crafted parameters during the wireless authentication setup phase of a connection. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, causing a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3390|2024-08-04T07:30:58.395Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3476|2024-08-04T07:37:54.337Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3476</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI implementation of a specific command of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to overwrite arbitrary files in the underlying host file system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of the parameters of a specific CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by issuing that command with specific parameters. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite the content of any arbitrary file that resides on the underlying host file system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3476|2024-08-04T07:37:54.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3489|2024-08-04T07:37:54.319Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3489</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3489|2024-08-04T07:37:54.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3527|2024-08-04T07:37:54.692Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3527</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Polaris kernel of Cisco Catalyst 9200 Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to crash the device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient packet size validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending jumbo frames or frames larger than the configured MTU size to the management interface of this device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the device fully before an automatic recovery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3527|2024-08-04T07:37:54.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34696|2024-08-04T00:19:47.976Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34696</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) programming of Cisco ASR 900 and ASR 920 Series Aggregation Services Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL. This vulnerability is due to incorrect programming of hardware when an ACL is configured using a method other than the configuration CLI. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass an ACL on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34696|2024-08-04T00:19:47.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3487|2024-08-04T07:37:54.398Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3487</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3487|2024-08-04T07:37:54.398Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3510|2024-08-04T07:37:54.621Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3510</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Umbrella Connector component of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9200 Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a reload, resulting in a denial of service condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient error handling when parsing DNS requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of malicious DNS requests to an Umbrella Connector client interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a crash of the iosd process, which triggers a reload of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3510|2024-08-04T07:37:54.621Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3418|2024-08-04T07:30:58.255Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3418</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Routers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to send ICMPv6 traffic prior to the client being placed into RUN state. The vulnerability is due to an incomplete access control list (ACL) being applied prior to RUN state. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the associated service set identifier (SSID) and sending ICMPv6 traffic. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send ICMPv6 traffic prior to RUN state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3418|2024-08-04T07:30:58.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3508|2024-08-04T07:37:54.688Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3508</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IP Address Resolution Protocol (ARP) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco ASR 1000 Series Aggregation Services Routers with a 20-Gbps Embedded Services Processor (ESP) installed could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service condition. The vulnerability is due to insufficient error handling when an affected device has reached platform limitations. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious series of IP ARP messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust system resources, which would eventually cause the affected device to reload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3508|2024-08-04T07:37:54.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34770|2024-08-04T00:19:48.166Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34770</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code with administrative privileges or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs during the validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code with administrative privileges or cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34770|2024-08-04T00:19:48.166Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3513|2024-08-04T07:37:54.658Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3513</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the initialization routines that are executed during bootup of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco ASR 900 Series Aggregation Services Routers with a Route Switch Processor 3 (RSP3) installed could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to execute persistent code at bootup and break the chain of trust. These vulnerabilities are due to incorrect validations by boot scripts when specific ROM monitor (ROMMON) variables are set. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by copying a specific file to the local file system of an affected device and defining specific ROMMON variables. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to run arbitrary code on the underlying operating system (OS) with root privileges. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker would need to have access to the root shell on the device or have physical access to the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3513|2024-08-04T07:37:54.658Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3403|2024-08-04T07:30:58.215Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3403</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject a command to the underlying operating system that will execute with root privileges upon the next reboot of the device. The authenticated user must have privileged EXEC permissions on the device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient protection of values passed to a script that executes during device startup. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by writing values to a specific file. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands with root privileges each time the affected device is restarted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3403|2024-08-04T07:30:58.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3503|2024-08-04T07:37:54.441Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3503</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the file system permissions of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to obtain read and write access to critical configuration or system files. The vulnerability is due to insufficient file system permissions on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to an affected device's guest shell, and accessing or modifying restricted files. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view or modify restricted information or configurations that are normally not accessible to system administrators.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3503|2024-08-04T07:37:54.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3486|2024-08-04T07:37:54.222Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3486</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3486|2024-08-04T07:37:54.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3516|2024-08-04T07:37:54.645Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3516</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web server authentication of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to crash the web server on the device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation during authentication. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by entering unexpected characters during a valid authentication. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the web server on the device, which must be manually recovered by disabling and re-enabling the web server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3516|2024-08-04T07:37:54.645Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3488|2024-08-04T07:37:54.459Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3488</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3488|2024-08-04T07:37:54.459Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3421|2024-08-04T07:30:58.726Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3421</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Zone-Based Firewall feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload or stop forwarding traffic through the firewall. The vulnerabilities are due to incomplete handling of Layer 4 packets through the device. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a certain sequence of traffic patterns through the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload or stop forwarding traffic through the firewall, resulting in a denial of service. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3421|2024-08-04T07:30:58.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3400|2024-08-04T07:30:58.140Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3400</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to utilize parts of the web UI for which they are not authorized.The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization of web UI access requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the web UI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to utilize parts of the web UI for which they are not authorized. This could allow a Read-Only user to perform actions of an Admin user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3400|2024-08-04T07:30:58.140Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34769|2024-08-04T00:19:48.218Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34769</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit the vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34769|2024-08-04T00:19:48.218Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3493|2024-08-04T07:37:54.304Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3493</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3493|2024-08-04T07:37:54.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3396|2024-08-04T07:30:58.382Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3396</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the file system on the pluggable USB 3.0 Solid State Drive (SSD) for Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, physical attacker to remove the USB 3.0 SSD and modify sensitive areas of the file system, including the namespace container protections. The vulnerability occurs because the USB 3.0 SSD control data is not stored on the internal boot flash. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by removing the USB 3.0 SSD, modifying or deleting files on the USB 3.0 SSD by using another device, and then reinserting the USB 3.0 SSD on the original device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to remove container protections and perform file actions outside the namespace of the container with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3396|2024-08-04T07:30:58.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3526|2024-08-04T07:37:54.684Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3526</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Common Open Policy Service (COPS) engine of Cisco IOS XE Software on Cisco cBR-8 Converged Broadband Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to crash a device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed COPS message to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3526|2024-08-04T07:37:54.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3497|2024-08-04T07:37:54.201Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3497</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3497|2024-08-04T07:37:54.201Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34768|2024-08-04T00:19:48.221Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34768</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of CAPWAP packets. An attacker could exploit the vulnerabilities by sending a malformed CAPWAP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34768|2024-08-04T00:19:48.221Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3422|2024-08-04T07:30:58.396Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3422</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IP Service Level Agreement (SLA) responder feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the IP SLA responder to reuse an existing port, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability exists because the IP SLA responder could consume a port that could be used by another feature. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific IP SLA control packets to the IP SLA responder on an affected device. The control packets must include the port number that could be used by another configured feature. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause an in-use port to be consumed by the IP SLA responder, impacting the feature that was using the port and resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3422|2024-08-04T07:30:58.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34767|2024-08-04T00:19:48.133Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34767</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in IPv6 traffic processing of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a Layer 2 (L2) loop in a configured VLAN, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition for that VLAN. The vulnerability is due to a logic error when processing specific link-local IPv6 traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPv6 packet that would flow inbound through the wired interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause traffic drops in the affected VLAN, thus triggering the DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34767|2024-08-04T00:19:48.133Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3417|2024-08-04T07:30:58.397Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3417</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute persistent code at boot time and break the chain of trust. This vulnerability is due to incorrect validations by boot scripts when specific ROM monitor (ROMMON) variables are set. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by installing code to a specific directory in the underlying operating system (OS) and setting a specific ROMMON variable. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute persistent code on the underlying OS. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need access to the root shell on the device or have physical access to the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3417|2024-08-04T07:30:58.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3407|2024-08-04T07:30:58.445Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3407</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the RESTCONF and NETCONF-YANG access control list (ACL) function of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload. The vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of the ACL that is tied to the RESTCONF or NETCONF-YANG feature. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the device using RESTCONF or NETCONF-YANG. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3407|2024-08-04T07:30:58.445Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3480|2024-08-04T07:37:54.305Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3480</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the Zone-Based Firewall feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload or stop forwarding traffic through the firewall. The vulnerabilities are due to incomplete handling of Layer 4 packets through the device. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending a certain sequence of traffic patterns through the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload or stop forwarding traffic through the firewall, resulting in a denial of service. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3480|2024-08-04T07:37:54.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3393|2024-08-04T07:30:58.334Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3393</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the application-hosting subsystem of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device. The attacker could execute IOS XE commands outside the application-hosting subsystem Docker container as well as on the underlying Linux operating system. These commands could be run as the root user. The vulnerability is due to a combination of two factors: (a) incomplete input validation of the user payload of CLI commands, and (b) improper role-based access control (RBAC) when commands are issued at the command line within the application-hosting subsystem. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using a CLI command with crafted user input. A successful exploit could allow the lower-privileged attacker to execute arbitrary CLI commands with root privileges. The attacker would need valid user credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3393|2024-08-04T07:30:58.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3359|2024-08-04T07:30:58.161Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3359</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multicast DNS (mDNS) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of mDNS packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted mDNS packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could cause a device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3359|2024-08-04T07:30:58.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3416|2024-08-04T07:30:58.670Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3416</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the initialization routines that are executed during bootup of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco ASR 900 Series Aggregation Services Routers with a Route Switch Processor 3 (RSP3) installed could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to execute persistent code at bootup and break the chain of trust. These vulnerabilities are due to incorrect validations by boot scripts when specific ROM monitor (ROMMON) variables are set. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by copying a specific file to the local file system of an affected device and defining specific ROMMON variables. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to run arbitrary code on the underlying operating system (OS) with root privileges. To exploit these vulnerabilities, an attacker would need to have access to the root shell on the device or have physical access to the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3416|2024-08-04T07:30:58.670Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3509|2024-08-04T07:37:54.644Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3509</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP message handler of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco cBR-8 Converged Broadband Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the supervisor to crash, which could result in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to insufficient error handling when DHCP version 4 (DHCPv4) messages are parsed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious DHCPv4 message to or through a WAN interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a reload of the affected device. Note: On Cisco cBR-8 Converged Broadband Routers, all of the following are considered WAN interfaces: 10 Gbps Ethernet interfaces 100 Gbps Ethernet interfaces Port channel interfaces that include multiple 10 and/or 100 Gbps Ethernet interfaces</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3509|2024-08-04T07:37:54.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3428|2024-08-04T07:37:53.973Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3428</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the WLAN Local Profiling feature of Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controller Software for the Cisco Catalyst 9000 Family could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to incorrect parsing of HTTP packets while performing HTTP-based endpoint device classifications. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP packet to an affected device. A successful exploit could cause an affected device to reboot, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3428|2024-08-04T07:37:53.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3399|2024-08-04T07:30:58.214Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3399</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Control and Provisioning of Wireless Access Points (CAPWAP) protocol processing of Cisco IOS XE Software for Cisco Catalyst 9800 Series Wireless Controllers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation during CAPWAP packet processing. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted CAPWAP packet to an affected device, resulting in a buffer over-read. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to crash and reload, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3399|2024-08-04T07:30:58.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T15:33:37.498Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T15:33:37.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-06-20T20:52:30.286Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-06-20T20:52:30.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-06-20T20:50:12.348Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-06-20T20:50:12.348Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-03-27T17:03:54.505Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-03-27T17:03:54.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-03-27T16:49:03.113Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-03-27T16:49:03.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20306|2024-03-27T16:58:22.583Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Unified Threat Defense (UTD) configuration CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying host operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have level 15 privileges on the affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20306|2024-03-27T16:58:22.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-04-03T16:36:06.520Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-04-03T16:36:06.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20259|2024-03-27T16:53:53.073Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP snooping feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a crafted IPv4 DHCP request packet being mishandled when endpoint analytics are enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCP request through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; Note: The attack vector is listed as network because a DHCP relay anywhere on the network could allow exploits from networks other than the adjacent one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20259|2024-03-27T16:53:53.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20278|2024-03-27T16:59:12.963Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20278</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NETCONF feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input over NETCONF to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges from Administrator to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20278|2024-03-27T16:59:12.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20324|2024-03-27T16:55:53.837Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20324</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to access WLAN configuration details including passwords.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper privilege checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the show and show tech wireless CLI commands to access configuration details, including passwords. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access configuration details that they are not authorized to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20324|2024-03-27T16:55:53.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20309|2024-03-27T17:02:19.749Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in auxiliary asynchronous port (AUX) functions of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause an affected device to reload or stop responding.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific ingress traffic when flow control hardware is enabled on the AUX port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by reverse telnetting to the AUX port and sending specific data after connecting. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reset or stop responding, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20309|2024-03-27T17:02:19.749Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20313|2024-04-24T20:42:10.379Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20313</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of OSPF updates that are processed by a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF update to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20313|2024-04-24T20:42:10.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-03-27T16:57:27.974Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-03-27T16:57:27.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20303|2024-06-04T17:39:55.892Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20303</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multicast DNS (mDNS) gateway feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Wireless LAN Controllers (WLCs) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper management of mDNS client entries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the wireless network and sending a continuous stream of specific mDNS packets. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the wireless controller to have high CPU utilization, which could lead to access points (APs) losing their connection to the controller and result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20303|2024-06-04T17:39:55.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-06-20T17:42:35.196Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-06-20T17:42:35.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-07-02T16:25:58.752Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-07-02T16:25:58.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-07-02T16:25:13.272Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-07-02T16:25:13.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-07-02T16:23:39.427Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-07-02T16:23:39.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20309|2024-08-01T21:59:41.337Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in auxiliary asynchronous port (AUX) functions of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause an affected device to reload or stop responding.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of specific ingress traffic when flow control hardware is enabled on the AUX port. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by reverse telnetting to the AUX port and sending specific data after connecting. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reset or stop responding, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20309|2024-08-01T21:59:41.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20259|2024-08-01T21:52:31.719Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DHCP snooping feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a crafted IPv4 DHCP request packet being mishandled when endpoint analytics are enabled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted DHCP request through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; Note: The attack vector is listed as network because a DHCP relay anywhere on the network could allow exploits from networks other than the adjacent one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20259|2024-08-01T21:52:31.719Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20324|2024-08-01T21:59:41.715Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20324</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, low-privileged, local attacker to access WLAN configuration details including passwords.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper privilege checks. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using the show and show tech wireless CLI commands to access configuration details, including passwords. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access configuration details that they are not authorized to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20324|2024-08-01T21:59:41.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20303|2024-08-01T21:59:41.376Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20303</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the multicast DNS (mDNS) gateway feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for Wireless LAN Controllers (WLCs) could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper management of mDNS client entries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the wireless network and sending a continuous stream of specific mDNS packets. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the wireless controller to have high CPU utilization, which could lead to access points (APs) losing their connection to the controller and result in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20303|2024-08-01T21:59:41.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20314|2024-08-01T21:59:42.311Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 Software-Defined Access (SD-Access) fabric edge node feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause high CPU utilization and stop all traffic processing, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of certain IPv4 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain IPv4 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to exhaust CPU resources and stop processing traffic, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20314|2024-08-01T21:59:42.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20316|2024-08-01T21:59:42.197Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the data model interface (DMI) services of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access resources that should have been protected by a configured IPv4 access control list (ACL).
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper handling of error conditions when a successfully authorized device administrator updates an IPv4 ACL using the NETCONF or RESTCONF protocol, and the update would reorder access control entries (ACEs) in the updated ACL. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing resources that should have been protected across an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20316|2024-08-01T21:59:42.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T21:52:31.616Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco Access Point (AP) Software could allow an unauthenticated, physical attacker to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot functionality and load a software image that has been tampered with on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because unnecessary commands are available during boot time at the physical console. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by interrupting the boot process and executing specific commands to bypass the Cisco Secure Boot validation checks and load an image that has been tampered with. This image would have been previously downloaded onto the targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to load the image once. The Cisco Secure Boot functionality is not permanently compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20265|2024-08-01T21:52:31.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20278|2024-08-01T21:59:41.100Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20278</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NETCONF feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges to root on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input over NETCONF to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges from Administrator to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20278|2024-08-01T21:59:41.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20306|2024-08-01T21:59:41.650Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Unified Threat Defense (UTD) configuration CLI of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying host operating system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have level 15 privileges on the affected device. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20306|2024-08-01T21:59:41.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20310|2024-08-01T21:59:41.851Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager IM &amp; Presence Service (Unified CM IM&amp;amp;P) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against an authenticated user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20310|2024-08-01T21:59:41.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20313|2024-08-01T21:59:42.856Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20xe%20software</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20313</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of OSPF updates that are processed by a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF update to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20313|2024-08-01T21:59:42.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
