<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN vManage</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN vManage</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 19:20:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3180|2024-09-16T16:58:19.167Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3180</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN Solution Software could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker to access an affected device by using an account that has a default, static password. This account has root privileges. The vulnerability exists because the affected software has a user account with a default, static password. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by remotely connecting to an affected system by using this account. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to log in by using this account with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3180|2024-09-16T16:58:19.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3468|2024-09-16T18:44:21.906Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3468</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface improperly validates values within SQL queries. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application and sending malicious SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify values on or return values from the underlying database or the operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3468|2024-09-16T18:44:21.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1535|2024-09-16T16:13:45.919Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1535</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the cluster management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to view sensitive information on an affected system. To be affected by this vulnerability, the Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software must be in cluster mode. This vulnerability is due to the absence of authentication for sensitive information in the cluster management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to the cluster management interface of an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to allow the attacker to view sensitive information on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1535|2024-09-16T16:13:45.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 12:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20739|2024-09-16T18:59:41.461Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20739</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system as the root user. The attacker must be authenticated on the affected system as a low-privileged user to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because a file leveraged by a root user is executed when a low-privileged user runs specific commands on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting arbitrary commands to a specific file as a lower-privileged user and then waiting until an admin user executes specific commands. The commands would then be executed on the device by the root user. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to escalate their privileges on the affected system from a low-privileged user to the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20739|2024-09-16T18:59:41.461Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3378|2024-09-16T17:28:37.971Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3378</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface for Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to impact the integrity of an affected system by executing arbitrary SQL queries. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted input that includes SQL statements to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify entries in some database tables, affecting the integrity of the data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3378|2024-09-16T17:28:37.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3374|2024-09-16T18:12:51.928Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3374</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to bypass authorization, enabling them to access sensitive information, modify the system configuration, or impact the availability of the affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization checking on the affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to the web-based management interface of an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain privileges beyond what would normally be authorized for their configured user authorization level. The attacker may be able to access sensitive information, modify the system configuration, or impact the availability of the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3374|2024-09-16T18:12:51.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27128|2024-09-16T16:32:53.173Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27128</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the application data endpoints of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to write arbitrary files to an affected system. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of requests to APIs. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests to an API within the affected application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct directory traversal attacks and write files to an arbitrary location on the targeted system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27128|2024-09-16T16:32:53.173Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 18:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34700|2024-09-16T16:18:10.973Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34700</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to read arbitrary files on the underlying file system of an affected system. This vulnerability exists because access to sensitive information on an affected system is not sufficiently controlled. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by gaining unauthorized access to sensitive information on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to create forged authentication requests and gain unauthorized access to the web UI of an affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34700|2024-09-16T16:18:10.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 15:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1506|2024-09-16T16:13:17.598Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1506</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code or gain access to sensitive information, or allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain escalated privileges or gain unauthorized access to the application. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1506|2024-09-16T16:13:17.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 12:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1259|2024-09-16T16:53:17.596Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct path traversal attacks and obtain write access to sensitive files on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request that contains directory traversal character sequences to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to write arbitrary files on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1259|2024-09-16T16:53:17.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:57:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1302|2024-09-16T18:43:16.394Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1302</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to bypass authorization and modify the configuration of an affected system, gain access to sensitive information, and view information that they are not authorized to access. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1302|2024-09-16T18:43:16.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3590|2024-09-16T18:29:42.727Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20vmanage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3590</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of the Cisco SD-WAN vManage Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user. The vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3590|2024-09-16T18:29:42.727Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 18:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
