<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 08:23:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3478|2024-08-04T07:37:54.221Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3478</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the REST API of Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to overwrite certain files that should be restricted on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization enforcement on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a file using the REST API. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to overwrite and upload files, which could degrade the functionality of the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3478|2024-08-04T07:37:54.221Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3236|2024-08-04T07:30:56.534Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3236</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain root shell access to the underlying operating system and overwrite or read arbitrary files. The attacker would need valid administrative credentials. This vulnerability is due to improper input validation of CLI command arguments. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using path traversal techniques when executing a vulnerable command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain root shell access to the underlying operating system and overwrite or read arbitrary files on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3236|2024-08-04T07:30:56.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3365|2024-08-04T07:30:58.174Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3365</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the directory permissions of Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a directory traversal attack on a limited set of restricted directories. The vulnerability is due to a flaw in the logic that governs directory permissions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using capabilities that are not controlled by the role-based access control (RBAC) mechanisms of the software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite files on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3365|2024-08-04T07:30:58.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34746|2024-08-04T00:19:48.132Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34746</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TACACS+ authentication, authorization and accounting (AAA) feature of Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass authentication and log in to an affected device as an administrator. This vulnerability is due to incomplete validation of user-supplied input that is passed to an authentication script. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by injecting parameters into an authentication request. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass authentication and log in as an administrator to the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34746|2024-08-04T00:19:48.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
