<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Unity Connection</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20unity%20connection.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Unity Connection</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 11:21:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15426|2024-08-05T09:54:03.316Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unity%20connection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15426</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface of Cisco Unity Connection could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based interface of the affected software. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input that is processed by the web-based interface of the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the web-based interface to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15426|2024-08-05T09:54:03.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15963|2024-08-05T01:03:32.513Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unity%20connection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15963</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unified Communications Manager could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to view sensitive information in the web-based management interface of the affected software. The vulnerability is due to insufficient protection of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of the affected service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the interface and viewing restricted portions of the software configuration. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to sensitive information or conduct further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15963|2024-08-05T01:03:32.513Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15396|2024-08-05T09:54:03.441Z -- cisco -- cisco%20unity%20connection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15396</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Bulk Administration Tool (BAT) for Cisco Unity Connection could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause high disk utilization, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability exists because the affected software does not restrict the maximum size of certain files that can be written to disk. An attacker who has valid administrator credentials for an affected system could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted, remote connection request to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to write a file that consumes most of the available disk space on the system, causing application functions to operate abnormally and leading to a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15396|2024-08-05T09:54:03.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
