<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20ios%20and%20ios%20xe%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco IOS and IOS XE Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 04:24:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0197|2024-09-17T02:21:10.694Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20and%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0197</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the VLAN Trunking Protocol (VTP) subsystem of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to corrupt the internal VTP database on an affected device and cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to a logic error in how the affected software handles a subset of VTP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending VTP packets in a sequence that triggers a timeout in the VTP message processing code of the affected software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to impact the ability to create, modify, or delete VLANs and cause a DoS condition. There are workarounds that address this vulnerability. This vulnerability affects Cisco devices that are running a vulnerable release of Cisco IOS Software or Cisco IOS XE Software, are operating in VTP client mode or VTP server mode, and do not have a VTP domain name configured. The default configuration for Cisco devices that are running Cisco IOS Software or Cisco IOS XE Software and support VTP is to operate in VTP server mode with no domain name configured.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0197|2024-09-17T02:21:10.694Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1748|2024-09-17T02:02:40.244Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20and%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1748</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Network Plug-and-Play (PnP) agent of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain unauthorized access to sensitive data. The vulnerability exists because the affected software insufficiently validates certificates. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a crafted certificate to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct man-in-the-middle attacks to decrypt and modify confidential information on user connections to the affected software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1748|2024-09-17T02:02:40.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 23:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1752|2024-09-17T01:16:09.678Z -- cisco -- cisco%20ios%20and%20ios%20xe%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1752</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the ISDN functions of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload. The vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of specific values in the Q.931 information elements. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by calling the affected device with specific Q.931 information elements being present. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1752|2024-09-17T01:16:09.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
