<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Web Security Appliance (WSA)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20web%20security%20appliance%20%28wsa%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Web Security Appliance (WSA)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 18:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1672|2024-09-16T17:14:51.322Z -- cisco -- cisco%20web%20security%20appliance%20%28wsa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1672</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Decryption Policy Default Action functionality of the Cisco Web Security Appliance (WSA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured drop policy and allow traffic onto the network that should have been denied. The vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of SSL-encrypted traffic when Decrypt for End-User Notification is disabled in the configuration. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a SSL connection through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass a configured drop policy to block specific SSL connections. Releases 10.1.x and 10.5.x are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1672|2024-09-16T17:14:51.322Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3367|2024-09-16T16:23:35.743Z -- cisco -- cisco%20web%20security%20appliance%20%28wsa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3367</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the log subscription subsystem of Cisco AsyncOS for the Cisco Secure Web Appliance (formerly Web Security Appliance) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection and elevate privileges to root. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input for the web interface and CLI. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the affected device and injecting scripting commands in the scope of the log subscription subsystem. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3367|2024-09-16T16:23:35.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 17:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
