<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Small Business 220 Series Smart Plus Switches</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20small%20business%20220%20series%20smart%20plus%20switches.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Small Business 220 Series Smart Plus Switches</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1914|2024-08-04T18:35:50.766Z -- cisco -- cisco%20small%20business%20220%20series%20smart%20plus%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1914</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web management interface of Cisco Small Business 220 Series Smart Switches could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a command injection attack. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious request to certain parts of the web management interface. To send the malicious request, the attacker needs a valid login session in the web management interface as a privilege level 15 user. Depending on the configuration of the affected switch, the malicious request must be sent via HTTP or HTTPS. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary shell commands with the privileges of the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1914|2024-08-04T18:35:50.766Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34744|2024-08-04T00:19:48.151Z -- cisco -- cisco%20small%20business%20220%20series%20smart%20plus%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34744</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Business 220 Series Smart Switches firmware could allow an attacker with Administrator privileges to access sensitive login credentials or reconfigure the passwords on the user account. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34744|2024-08-04T00:19:48.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34757|2024-08-04T00:19:48.139Z -- cisco -- cisco%20small%20business%20220%20series%20smart%20plus%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34757</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Business 220 Series Smart Switches firmware could allow an attacker with Administrator privileges to access sensitive login credentials or reconfigure the passwords on the user account. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34757|2024-08-04T00:19:48.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1912|2024-08-04T18:35:50.834Z -- cisco -- cisco%20small%20business%20220%20series%20smart%20plus%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1912</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web management interface of Cisco Small Business 220 Series Smart Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files. The vulnerability is due to incomplete authorization checks in the web management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malicious request to certain parts of the web management interface. Depending on the configuration of the affected switch, the malicious request must be sent via HTTP or HTTPS. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify the configuration of an affected device or to inject a reverse shell. This vulnerability affects Cisco Small Business 220 Series Smart Switches running firmware versions prior to 1.1.4.4 with the web management interface enabled. The web management interface is enabled via both HTTP and HTTPS by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1912|2024-08-04T18:35:50.834Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1913|2024-08-04T18:35:52.063Z -- cisco -- cisco%20small%20business%20220%20series%20smart%20plus%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1913</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web management interface of Cisco Small Business 220 Series Smart Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to overflow a buffer, which then allows the execution of arbitrary code with root privileges on the underlying operating system. The vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input and improper boundary checks when reading data into an internal buffer. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending malicious requests to the web management interface of an affected device. Depending on the configuration of the affected switch, the malicious requests must be sent via HTTP or HTTPS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1913|2024-08-04T18:35:52.063Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
