<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Connected Mobile Experiences</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20connected%20mobile%20experiences.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Connected Mobile Experiences</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 08:24:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3151|2024-09-17T03:43:53.193Z -- cisco -- cisco%20connected%20mobile%20experiences
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3151</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco Connected Mobile Experiences (CMX) could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrative credentials to bypass restrictions on the CLI. The vulnerability is due to insufficient security mechanisms in the restricted shell implementation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted commands to the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to escape the restricted shell and execute a set of normally unauthorized commands with the privileges of a non-root user. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to have valid administrative credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3151|2024-09-17T03:43:53.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 16:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1645|2024-09-17T02:01:50.302Z -- cisco -- cisco%20connected%20mobile%20experiences
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1645</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Connected Mobile Experiences (CMX) software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to access sensitive data on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to a lack of input and validation checking mechanisms for certain GET requests to API's on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending HTTP GET requests to an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to use this information to conduct additional reconnaissance attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1645|2024-09-17T02:01:50.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1522|2024-09-17T01:30:38.943Z -- cisco -- cisco%20connected%20mobile%20experiences
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1522</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the change password API of Cisco Connected Mobile Experiences (CMX) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to alter their own password to a value that does not comply with the strong authentication requirements that are configured on an affected device. This vulnerability exists because a password policy check is incomplete at the time a password is changed at server side using the API. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted API request to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to change their own password to a value that does not comply with the configured strong authentication requirements.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1522|2024-09-17T01:30:38.943Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 17:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
