<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Identity Services Engine Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Identity Services Engine Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 17:21:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T16:28:22.193Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least valid Policy Admin credentials on the affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of files that are uploaded to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading arbitrary files to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to store malicious files on the system, execute arbitrary commands on the operating system, and elevate privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20296|2024-07-17T16:28:22.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20368|2024-06-04T17:40:10.016Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20368</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack and perform arbitrary actions on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on the affected device with the privileges of the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20368|2024-06-04T17:40:10.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20332|2024-06-04T17:40:15.273Z -- cisco -- cisco%20identity%20services%20engine%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20332</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack through an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper input validation for specific HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to send arbitrary network requests that are sourced from the affected device. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid Super Admin credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20332|2024-06-04T17:40:15.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
