<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Industrial Network Director</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20industrial%20network%20director.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Industrial Network Director</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:20:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20038|2024-08-02T08:57:35.624Z -- cisco -- cisco%20industrial%20network%20director
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20038</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the monitoring application of Cisco Industrial Network Director could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access a static secret key used to store both local data and credentials for accessing remote systems.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a static key value stored in the application used to encrypt application data and remote credentials. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by gaining local access to the server Cisco Industrial Network Director is installed on. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to decrypt data allowing the attacker to access remote systems monitored by Cisco Industrial Network Director.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20038|2024-08-02T08:57:35.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 01:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20037|2024-08-02T08:57:35.842Z -- cisco -- cisco%20industrial%20network%20director
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20037</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Industrial Network Director could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks.&#13;
&#13; The vulnerability is due to improper validation of content submitted to the affected application. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending requests containing malicious values to the affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20037|2024-08-02T08:57:35.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 01:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
