<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN Solution</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20sd-wan%20solution.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco SD-WAN Solution</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 15:22:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3600|2024-08-04T07:37:55.490Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3600</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to root on the underlying operating system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient security controls on the CLI. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by using an affected CLI utility that is running on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3600|2024-08-04T07:37:55.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3595|2024-08-04T07:37:55.474Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3595</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to root group on the underlying operating system. The vulnerability is due to incorrect permissions being set when the affected command is executed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by executing the affected command on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3595|2024-08-04T07:37:55.474Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3266|2024-08-04T07:30:57.438Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3266</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco SD-WAN Solution software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject arbitrary commands that are executed with root privileges. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and submitting crafted input to the CLI utility. The attacker must be authenticated to access the CLI utility. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3266|2024-08-04T07:30:57.438Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3351|2024-08-04T07:30:58.155Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3351</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN Solution Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of fields in Cisco SD-WAN peering messages that are encapsulated in UDP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted UDP messages to the targeted system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause services on the device to fail, resulting in a DoS condition that could impact the targeted device and other devices that depend on it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3351|2024-08-04T07:30:58.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34726|2024-08-04T00:19:48.110Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34726</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to inject arbitrary commands to be executed with root-level privileges on the underlying operating system of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation on certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to an affected device and submitting crafted input to the CLI. The attacker must be authenticated as an administrative user to execute the affected commands. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands with root-level privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34726|2024-08-04T00:19:48.110Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3593|2024-08-04T07:37:55.548Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3593</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to root on the underlying operating system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to a utility that is running on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3593|2024-08-04T07:37:55.548Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3264|2024-08-04T07:30:57.587Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3264</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN Solution software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause a buffer overflow on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain access to information that they are not authorized to access and make changes to the system that they are not authorized to make.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3264|2024-08-04T07:30:57.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3444|2024-08-04T07:37:54.859Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3444</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the packet filtering features of Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass L3 and L4 traffic filters. The vulnerability is due to improper traffic filtering conditions on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting a malicious TCP packet with specific characteristics and sending it to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass the L3 and L4 traffic filters and inject an arbitrary packet into the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3444|2024-08-04T07:37:54.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3265|2024-08-04T07:30:57.454Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN Solution software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to root on the underlying operating system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain root-level privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3265|2024-08-04T07:30:57.454Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3115|2024-08-04T07:24:00.527Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3115</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of the Cisco SD-WAN Solution vManage software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to root-level privileges on the underlying operating system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted file to the affected system. An exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root-level privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3115|2024-08-04T07:24:00.527Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3594|2024-08-04T07:37:55.528Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3594</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to root on the underlying operating system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by providing crafted options to a specific command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3594|2024-08-04T07:37:55.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3379|2024-08-04T07:30:58.020Z -- cisco -- cisco%20sd-wan%20solution
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3379</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco SD-WAN Solution Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to Administrator on the underlying operating system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted request to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain administrative privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3379|2024-08-04T07:30:58.020Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
