<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:21:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20777|2024-08-03T02:24:49.662Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20777</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an attacker to escape from the guest virtual machine (VM) to the host machine, inject commands that execute at the root level, or leak system data from the host to the VM. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20777|2024-08-03T02:24:49.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1127|2024-08-03T16:02:55.418Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1127</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface. The vulnerability is due to improper input validation of log file content stored on the affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by modifying a log file with malicious code and getting a user to view the modified log file. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or to access sensitive, browser-based information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1127|2024-08-03T16:02:55.418Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20929|2024-08-03T02:31:59.544Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20929</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the upgrade signature verification of Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker to provide an unauthentic upgrade file for upload.&#13;
 This vulnerability is due to insufficient cryptographic signature verification of upgrade files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by providing an administrator with an unauthentic upgrade file. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to fully compromise the Cisco NFVIS system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20929|2024-08-03T02:31:59.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 14:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20780|2024-08-03T02:24:49.602Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20780</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an attacker to escape from the guest virtual machine (VM) to the host machine, inject commands that execute at the root level, or leak system data from the host to the VM. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20780|2024-08-03T02:24:49.602Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1421|2024-08-03T16:11:17.317Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1421</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform a command injection attack on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input to a configuration command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input during the execution of this command. A successful exploit could allow a non-privileged attacker authenticated in the restricted CLI to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system (OS) with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1421|2024-08-03T16:11:17.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20779|2024-08-03T02:24:49.619Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20nfv%20infrastructure%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20779</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Enterprise NFV Infrastructure Software (NFVIS) could allow an attacker to escape from the guest virtual machine (VM) to the host machine, inject commands that execute at the root level, or leak system data from the host to the VM. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20779|2024-08-03T02:24:49.619Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
