<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Enterprise Chat and Email</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20enterprise%20chat%20and%20email.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Enterprise Chat and Email</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 22:22:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1702|2024-09-16T20:01:42.754Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20chat%20and%20email
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1702</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Enterprise Chat and Email could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of the affected software. The vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface of the affected software. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities either by injecting malicious code in a chat window or by sending a crafted link to a user of the interface. In both cases, the attacker must persuade the user to click the crafted link or open the chat window that contains the attacker's code. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. Version 11.6(1) is affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1702|2024-09-16T20:01:42.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20802|2024-09-16T20:53:24.287Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20chat%20and%20email
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20802</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web interface of Cisco Enterprise Chat and Email (ECE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input that is processed by the web interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code in the context of the interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid agent credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20802|2024-09-16T20:53:24.287Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 14:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20367|2024-08-01T21:59:42.019Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20chat%20and%20email</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20367</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco Enterprise Chat and Email (ECE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web UI does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid agent credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20367|2024-08-01T21:59:42.019Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20367|2024-06-04T17:40:29.581Z -- cisco -- cisco%20enterprise%20chat%20and%20email</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20367</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI of Cisco Enterprise Chat and Email (ECE) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web UI does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid agent credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20367|2024-06-04T17:40:29.581Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
