<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Management Center</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20firepower%20management%20center.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Firepower Management Center</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:19:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20220|2024-08-02T09:05:35.426Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20220</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker must have valid device credentials, but does not need Administrator privileges. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input for certain configuration options. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by using crafted input within the device configuration GUI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the device, including on the underlying operating system, which could also affect the availability of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20220|2024-08-02T09:05:35.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20219|2024-08-02T09:05:36.069Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20219</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system. The attacker would need valid device credentials but does not require administrator privileges to exploit this vulnerability. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input for certain configuration options. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by using crafted input within the device configuration GUI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the device including the underlying operating system which could also affect the availability of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20219|2024-08-02T09:05:36.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20155|2024-08-02T09:05:34.875Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20155</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in a logging API in Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to become unresponsive or trigger an unexpected reload. This vulnerability could also allow an attacker with valid user credentials, but not Administrator privileges, to view a system log file that they would not normally have access to. This vulnerability is due to a lack of rate-limiting of requests that are sent to a specific API that is related to an FMC log. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high rate of HTTP requests to the API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition due to the FMC CPU spiking to 100 percent utilization or to the device reloading. CPU utilization would return to normal if the attack traffic was stopped before an unexpected reload was triggered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20155|2024-08-02T09:05:34.875Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20206|2024-08-02T09:05:35.381Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20206</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information. In some cases, it is also possible to cause a temporary availability impact to portions of the FMC Dashboard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20206|2024-08-02T09:05:35.381Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20048|2024-08-02T08:57:35.642Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20048</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web services interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute certain unauthorized configuration commands on a Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) device that is managed by the FMC Software. This vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization of configuration commands that are sent through the web service interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the FMC web services interface and sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute certain configuration commands on the targeted FTD device. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid credentials on the FMC Software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20048|2024-08-02T08:57:35.642Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20074|2024-08-02T08:57:35.827Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20074</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information. In some cases, it is also possible to cause a temporary availability impact to portions of the FMC Dashboard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20074|2024-08-02T08:57:35.827Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20041|2024-08-02T08:57:35.535Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20041</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information. In some cases, it is also possible to cause a temporary availability impact to portions of the FMC Dashboard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20041|2024-08-02T08:57:35.535Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:52:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20114|2024-08-02T08:57:35.919Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20114</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the file download feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to download arbitrary files from an affected system. This vulnerability is due to a lack of input sanitation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTPS request. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to download arbitrary files from the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20114|2024-08-02T08:57:35.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20005|2024-08-02T08:57:35.060Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20005</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information. In some cases, it is also possible to cause a temporary availability impact to portions of the FMC Dashboard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20005|2024-08-02T08:57:35.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20063|2024-08-02T08:57:35.628Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20063</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the inter-device communication mechanisms between devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software and devices that are running Cisco Firepower Management (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root permissions on the underlying operating system of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the expert mode of an affected device and submitting specific commands to a connected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code in the context of an FMC device if the attacker has administrative privileges on an associated FTD device. Alternatively, a successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code in the context of an FTD device if the attacker has administrative privileges on an associated FMC device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20063|2024-08-02T08:57:35.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-13T14:05:52.072Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Object Groups for Access Control Lists (ACLs) feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured access controls on managed devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect deployment of the Object Groups for ACLs feature from Cisco FMC Software to managed FTD devices in high-availability setups. After an affected device is rebooted following Object Groups for ACLs deployment, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access controls and successfully send traffic to devices that are expected to be protected by the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-13T14:05:52.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20360|2024-06-04T17:40:39.489Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20360</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not adequately validate user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain any data from the database, execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system, and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least Read Only user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20360|2024-06-04T17:40:39.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-04T17:40:51.215Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Object Groups for Access Control Lists (ACLs) feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured access controls on managed devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect deployment of the Object Groups for ACLs feature from Cisco FMC Software to managed FTD devices in high-availability setups. After an affected device is rebooted following Object Groups for ACLs deployment, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access controls and successfully send traffic to devices that are expected to be protected by the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20361|2024-06-04T17:40:51.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20360|2024-08-01T21:59:42.328Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20360</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system. This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not adequately validate user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain any data from the database, execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system, and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need at least Read Only user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20360|2024-08-01T21:59:42.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20361|2024-08-01T21:59:41.652Z -- cisco -- cisco%20firepower%20management%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Object Groups for Access Control Lists (ACLs) feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured access controls on managed devices that are running Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software. This vulnerability is due to the incorrect deployment of the Object Groups for ACLs feature from Cisco FMC Software to managed FTD devices in high-availability setups. After an affected device is rebooted following Object Groups for ACLs deployment, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured access controls and successfully send traffic to devices that are expected to be protected by the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20361|2024-08-01T21:59:41.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
