<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco DNA Spaces Connector</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20dna%20spaces%20connector.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco DNA Spaces Connector</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 23:24:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3586|2024-09-17T04:04:11.428Z -- cisco -- cisco%20dna%20spaces%20connector
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3586</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco DNA Spaces Connector could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input in the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to the web-based management interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underling operating system with privileges of the web-based management application, which is running as a restricted user. This could result in changes being made to pages served by the web-based management application impacting the integrity or availability of the web-based management application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3586|2024-09-17T04:04:11.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 17:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1559|2024-09-17T04:14:04.566Z -- cisco -- cisco%20dna%20spaces%20connector
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1559</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco DNA Spaces Connector could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a command injection attack on an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient input sanitization when executing affected commands. A high-privileged attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities on a Cisco DNA Spaces Connector by injecting crafted input during command execution. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root within the Connector docker container.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1559|2024-09-17T04:14:04.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 06:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1560|2024-09-17T03:12:47.554Z -- cisco -- cisco%20dna%20spaces%20connector
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1560</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco DNA Spaces Connector could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a command injection attack on an affected device. These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient input sanitization when executing affected commands. A high-privileged attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities on a Cisco DNA Spaces Connector by injecting crafted input during command execution. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root within the Connector docker container.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1560|2024-09-17T03:12:47.554Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 06:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
