<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20application%20policy%20infrastructure%20controller%20%28apic%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:23:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20011|2024-08-02T08:57:36.069Z -- cisco -- cisco%20application%20policy%20infrastructure%20controller%20%28apic%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20011</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC) and Cisco Cloud Network Controller, formerly Cisco Cloud APIC, could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privilege level of the affected user. If the affected user has administrative privileges, these actions could include modifying the system configuration and creating new privileged accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20011|2024-08-02T08:57:36.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20230|2024-08-02T09:05:35.936Z -- cisco -- cisco%20application%20policy%20infrastructure%20controller%20%28apic%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20230</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the restricted security domain implementation of Cisco Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to read, modify, or delete non-tenant policies (for example, access policies) created by users associated with a different security domain on an affected system.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper access control when restricted security domains are used to implement multi-tenancy for policies outside the tenant boundaries. An attacker with a valid user account associated with a restricted security domain could exploit this vulnerability. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read, modify, or delete policies created by users associated with a different security domain. Exploitation is not possible for policies under tenants that an attacker has no authorization to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20230|2024-08-02T09:05:35.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 18:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
