<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:22:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1427|2024-08-03T16:11:17.069Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1427</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the install, uninstall, and upgrade processes of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to hijack DLL or executable files that are used by the application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device with SYSTEM privileges. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker must have valid credentials on the Windows system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1427|2024-08-03T16:11:17.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1567|2024-08-03T16:18:10.253Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1567</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the DLL loading mechanism of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform a DLL hijacking attack on an affected device if the VPN Posture (HostScan) Module is installed on the AnyConnect client. This vulnerability is due to a race condition in the signature verification process for DLL files that are loaded on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a series of crafted interprocess communication (IPC) messages to the AnyConnect process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected device with SYSTEM privileges. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid credentials on the Windows system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1567|2024-08-03T16:18:10.253Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1366|2024-08-03T16:11:16.939Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1366</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the interprocess communication (IPC) channel of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform a DLL hijacking attack on an affected device if the VPN Posture (HostScan) Module is installed on the AnyConnect client. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of resources that are loaded by the application at run time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPC message to the AnyConnect process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected machine with SYSTEM privileges. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker needs valid credentials on the Windows system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1366|2024-08-03T16:11:16.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1426|2024-08-03T16:11:16.886Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1426</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the install, uninstall, and upgrade processes of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to hijack DLL or executable files that are used by the application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device with SYSTEM privileges. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker must have valid credentials on the Windows system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1426|2024-08-03T16:11:16.886Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1450|2024-08-03T16:11:17.333Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1450</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the interprocess communication (IPC) channel of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have valid credentials on the device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending one or more crafted IPC messages to the AnyConnect process on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to stop the AnyConnect process, causing a DoS condition on the device. Note: The process under attack will automatically restart so no action is needed by the user or admin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1450|2024-08-03T16:11:17.333Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1496|2024-08-03T16:11:17.400Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1496</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the install, uninstall, and upgrade processes of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to hijack DLL or executable files that are used by the application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device with SYSTEM privileges. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker must have valid credentials on the Windows system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1496|2024-08-03T16:11:17.400Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1568|2024-08-03T16:18:10.133Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1568</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected system. This vulnerability is due to uncontrolled memory allocation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by copying a crafted file to a specific folder on the system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to crash the VPN Agent service when the affected application is launched, causing it to be unavailable to all users of the system. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid credentials on a multiuser Windows system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1568|2024-08-03T16:18:10.133Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1258|2024-08-03T16:02:56.382Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1258</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the upgrade component of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client could allow an authenticated, local attacker with low privileges to read arbitrary files on the underlying operating system (OS) of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient file permission restrictions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted command from the local CLI to the application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read arbitrary files on the underlying OS of the affected device. The attacker would need to have valid user credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1258|2024-08-03T16:02:56.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1430|2024-08-03T16:11:17.315Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1430</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the install, uninstall, and upgrade processes of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to hijack DLL or executable files that are used by the application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device with SYSTEM privileges. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker must have valid credentials on the Windows system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1430|2024-08-03T16:11:17.315Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1428|2024-08-03T16:11:16.975Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1428</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the install, uninstall, and upgrade processes of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to hijack DLL or executable files that are used by the application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device with SYSTEM privileges. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker must have valid credentials on the Windows system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1428|2024-08-03T16:11:16.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1519|2024-08-03T16:11:17.692Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1519</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the interprocess communication (IPC) channel of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to overwrite VPN profiles on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IPC message to the AnyConnect process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify VPN profile files. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid credentials on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1519|2024-08-03T16:11:17.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1429|2024-08-03T16:11:16.927Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1429</link>
      <description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the install, uninstall, and upgrade processes of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to hijack DLL or executable files that are used by the application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device with SYSTEM privileges. To exploit these vulnerabilities, the attacker must have valid credentials on the Windows system. For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1429|2024-08-03T16:11:16.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1237|2024-08-03T16:02:56.296Z -- cisco -- cisco%20anyconnect%20secure%20mobility%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1237</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Network Access Manager and Web Security Agent components of Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform a DLL injection attack. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need to have valid credentials on the Windows system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of resources that are loaded by the application at run time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting a configuration file in a specific path in the system which, in turn, causes a malicious DLL file to be loaded when the application starts. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected machine with SYSTEM privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1237|2024-08-03T16:02:56.296Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
