<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- ClamAV</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/clamav.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- ClamAV</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:21:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1252|2024-08-03T16:02:56.276Z -- cisco -- clamav
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1252</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Excel XLM macro parsing module in Clam AntiVirus (ClamAV) Software versions 0.103.0 and 0.103.1 could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper error handling that may result in an infinite loop. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted Excel file to an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ClamAV scanning process hang, resulting in a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1252|2024-08-03T16:02:56.276Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1405|2024-08-03T16:11:16.920Z -- cisco -- clamav
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1405</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the email parsing module in Clam AntiVirus (ClamAV) Software version 0.103.1 and all prior versions could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper variable initialization that may result in an NULL pointer read. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted email to an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ClamAV scanning process crash, resulting in a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1405|2024-08-03T16:11:16.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20698|2024-08-03T02:24:48.458Z -- cisco -- clamav
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20698</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OOXML parsing module in Clam AntiVirus (ClamAV) Software version 0.104.1 and LTS version 0.103.4 and prior versions could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper checks that may result in an invalid pointer read. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted OOXML file to an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ClamAV scanning process to crash, resulting in a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20698|2024-08-03T02:24:48.458Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20803|2024-08-03T02:24:49.711Z -- cisco -- clamav
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20803</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OLE2 file parser of Clam AntiVirus (ClamAV) versions 0.104.0 through 0.104.2 could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition on an affected device.The vulnerability is due to incorrect use of the realloc function that may result in a double-free. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted OLE2 file to be scanned by ClamAV on the affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ClamAV scanning process to crash, resulting in a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20803|2024-08-03T02:24:49.711Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1404|2024-08-03T16:11:17.323Z -- cisco -- clamav
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1404</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the PDF parsing module in Clam AntiVirus (ClamAV) Software versions 0.103.0 and 0.103.1 could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper buffer size tracking that may result in a heap buffer over-read. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted PDF file to an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ClamAV scanning process to crash, resulting in a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1404|2024-08-03T16:11:17.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20380|2024-08-01T21:59:41.788Z -- cisco -- clamav</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20380</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the HTML parser of ClamAV could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
The vulnerability is due to an issue in the C to Rust foreign function interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted file containing HTML content to be scanned by ClamAV on an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ClamAV scanning process to terminate, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20380|2024-08-01T21:59:41.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 19:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20328|2024-08-01T21:59:41.779Z -- cisco -- clamav</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20328</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the VirusEvent feature of ClamAV could allow a local attacker to inject arbitrary commands with the privileges of the application service account.The vulnerability is due to unsafe handling of file names. A local attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a file name containing command-line sequences. When processed on a system using configuration options for the VirusEvent feature, the attacker could cause the application to execute arbitrary commands.
ClamAV has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20328|2024-08-01T21:59:41.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 20:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20328|2024-03-01T20:48:15.328Z -- cisco -- clamav</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20328</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the VirusEvent feature of ClamAV could allow a local attacker to inject arbitrary commands with the privileges of the application service account.The vulnerability is due to unsafe handling of file names. A local attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a file name containing command-line sequences. When processed on a system using configuration options for the VirusEvent feature, the attacker could cause the application to execute arbitrary commands.
ClamAV has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20328|2024-03-01T20:48:15.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 20:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20380|2024-06-04T17:39:59.638Z -- cisco -- clamav</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20380</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the HTML parser of ClamAV could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
The vulnerability is due to an issue in the C to Rust foreign function interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted file containing HTML content to be scanned by ClamAV on an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ClamAV scanning process to terminate, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20380|2024-06-04T17:39:59.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 19:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20328|2024-07-23T20:45:50.903Z -- cisco -- clamav</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20328</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the VirusEvent feature of ClamAV could allow a local attacker to inject arbitrary commands with the privileges of the application service account.The vulnerability is due to unsafe handling of file names. A local attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying a file name containing command-line sequences. When processed on a system using configuration options for the VirusEvent feature, the attacker could cause the application to execute arbitrary commands.
ClamAV has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20328|2024-07-23T20:45:50.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 20:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
