<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- IOS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/ios.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- IOS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 23:23:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20109|2024-10-23T18:53:42.480Z -- cisco -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20109</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Group Encrypted Transport VPN (GET VPN) feature of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker who has administrative control of either a group member or a key server to execute arbitrary code on an affected device or cause the device to crash.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of attributes in the Group Domain of Interpretation (GDOI) and G-IKEv2 protocols of the GET VPN feature. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by either compromising an installed key server or modifying the configuration of a group member to point to a key server that is controlled by the attacker. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code and gain full control of the affected system or cause the affected system to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. For more information, see the Details ["#details"] section of this advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20109|2024-10-23T18:53:42.480Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20186|2024-10-23T19:41:01.155Z -- cisco -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20186</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Authentication, Authorization, and Accounting (AAA) feature of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to bypass command authorization and copy files to or from the file system of an affected device using the Secure Copy Protocol (SCP).&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrect processing of SCP commands in AAA command authorization checks. An attacker with valid credentials and level 15 privileges could exploit this vulnerability by using SCP to connect to an affected device from an external machine. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain or change the configuration of the affected device and put files on or retrieve files from the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20186|2024-10-23T19:41:01.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20414|2024-09-25T18:00:35.918Z -- cisco -- ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20414</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI feature of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system through the web UI.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrectly accepting configuration changes through the HTTP GET method. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a currently authenticated administrator to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to change the configuration of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20414|2024-09-25T18:00:35.918Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 16:29:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20433|2024-09-25T16:26:15.651Z -- cisco -- ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20433</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Resource Reservation Protocol (RSVP) feature of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a buffer overflow when processing crafted RSVP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending RSVP traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20433|2024-09-25T16:26:15.651Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 16:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20465|2024-09-25T16:29:16.335Z -- cisco -- ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20465</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) programming of Cisco IOS Software running on Cisco Industrial Ethernet 4000, 4010, and 5000 Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of IPv4 ACLs on switched virtual interfaces when an administrator enables and disables Resilient Ethernet Protocol (REP). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass an ACL on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20465|2024-09-25T16:29:16.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 16:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20414|2024-09-25T16:29:36.509Z -- cisco -- ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20414</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web UI feature of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system through the web UI.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incorrectly accepting configuration changes through the HTTP GET method. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a currently authenticated administrator to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to change the configuration of the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20414|2024-09-25T16:29:36.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 16:29:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20433|2024-09-25T18:48:42.038Z -- cisco -- ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20433</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Resource Reservation Protocol (RSVP) feature of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a buffer overflow when processing crafted RSVP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending RSVP traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20433|2024-09-25T18:48:42.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 16:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20465|2024-09-25T18:50:16.555Z -- cisco -- ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20465</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) programming of Cisco IOS Software running on Cisco Industrial Ethernet 4000, 4010, and 5000 Series Switches could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of IPv4 ACLs on switched virtual interfaces when an administrator enables and disables Resilient Ethernet Protocol (REP). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass an ACL on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20465|2024-09-25T18:50:16.555Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 16:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
