<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- MDS 9000 Series Multilayer Switches</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/mds%209000%20series%20multilayer%20switches.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- MDS 9000 Series Multilayer Switches</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:24:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1605|2024-09-17T02:37:15.117Z -- cisco -- mds%209000%20series%20multilayer%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1605</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NX-API feature of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code as root. The vulnerability is due to incorrect input validation in the NX-API feature. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP or HTTPS request to an internal service on an affected device that has the NX-API feature enabled. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a buffer overflow and execute arbitrary code as root. Note: The NX-API feature is disabled by default. MDS 9000 Series Multilayer Switches are affected in versions prior to 8.1(1). Nexus 3000 Series Switches are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)I4(8) and 7.0(3)I7(1). Nexus 3500 Platform Switches are affected in versions prior to 6.0(2)A8(8). Nexus 3600 Platform Switches are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)F3(5). Nexus 2000, 5500, 5600, and 6000 Series Switches are affected in versions prior to 7.3(2)N1(1). Nexus 7000 and 7700 Series Switches are affected in versions prior to 7.3(3)D1(1). Nexus 9000 Series Switches in Standalone NX-OS Mode are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)I4(8) and 7.0(3)I7(1). Nexus 9500 R-Series Line Cards and Fabric Modules are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)F3(5).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1605|2024-09-17T02:37:15.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1614|2024-09-17T01:05:36.675Z -- cisco -- mds%209000%20series%20multilayer%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1614</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the NX-API feature of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges. The vulnerability is due to incorrect input validation of user-supplied data by the NX-API subsystem. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious HTTP or HTTPS packets to the management interface of an affected system that has the NX-API feature enabled. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to perform a command-injection attack and execute arbitrary commands with root privileges. Note: NX-API is disabled by default. MDS 9000 Series Multilayer Switches are affected running software versions prior to 8.1(1b) and 8.2(3). Nexus 3000 Series Switches are affected running software versions prior to 7.0(3)I4(9) and 7.0(3)I7(4). Nexus 3500 Platform Switches are affected running software versions prior to 7.0(3)I7(4). Nexus 2000, 5500, 5600, and 6000 Series Switches are affected running software versions prior to 7.3(4)N1(1). Nexus 9000 Series Switches in Standalone NX-OS Mode are affected running software versions prior to 7.0(3)I4(9) and 7.0(3)I7(4). Nexus 7000 and 7700 Series Switches are affected running software versions prior to 7.3(3)D1(1) and 8.2(3).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1614|2024-09-17T01:05:36.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1608|2024-09-17T00:51:08.242Z -- cisco -- mds%209000%20series%20multilayer%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1608</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability. MDS 9000 Series Multilayer Switches are affected in versions prior to 6.2(27), 8.1(1b), and 8.3(1). Nexus 7000 and 7700 Series Switches are affected in versions prior to 6.2(22), 7.3(3)D1(1), and 8.2(3).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1608|2024-09-17T00:51:08.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
