<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco -- Nexus 3000 Series Switches</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco/nexus%203000%20series%20switches.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco -- Nexus 3000 Series Switches</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:23:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1612|2024-08-04T18:20:28.369Z -- cisco -- nexus%203000%20series%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1612</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments passed to certain CLI commands. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by including malicious input as the argument of an affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. An attacker would need valid administrator credentials to exploit this vulnerability. Nexus 3000 Series Switches are affected running software versions prior to 7.0(3)I4(9) and 7.0(3)I7(4). Nexus 3500 Platform Switches are affected running software versions prior to 7.0(3)I7(4). Nexus 3600 Platform Switches are affected running software versions prior to 7.0(3)F3(5). Nexus 9000 Series Switches in Stand are affected running software versions prior to 7.0(3)F3(5).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1612|2024-08-04T18:20:28.369Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1602|2024-08-04T18:20:28.254Z -- cisco -- nexus%203000%20series%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1602</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the filesystem permissions of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access sensitive data that could be used to elevate their privileges to administrator. The vulnerability is due to improper implementation of filesystem permissions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to the CLI of an affected device, accessing a specific file, and leveraging this information to authenticate to the NX-API server. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to make configuration changes as administrator. Note: NX-API is disabled by default. Nexus 3000 Series Switches are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)I7(4). Nexus 3500 Platform Switches are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)I7(4). Nexus 3600 Platform Switches are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)F3(5). Nexus 9000 Series Switches-Standalone are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)I7(4). Nexus 9500 R-Series Line Cards and Fabric Modules are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)F3(5).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1602|2024-08-04T18:20:28.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1615|2024-08-04T18:20:28.347Z -- cisco -- nexus%203000%20series%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1615</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Image Signature Verification feature of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with administrator-level credentials to install a malicious software image on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to improper verification of digital signatures for software images. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by loading an unsigned software image on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to boot a malicious software image. Note: The fix for this vulnerability requires a BIOS upgrade as part of the software upgrade. For additional information, see the Details section of this advisory. Nexus 3000 Series Switches are affected running software versions prior to 7.0(3)I7(5). Nexus 9000 Series Fabric Switches in ACI Mode are affected running software versions prior to 13.2(1l). Nexus 9000 Series Switches in Standalone NX-OS Mode are affected running software versions prior to 7.0(3)I7(5). Nexus 9500 R-Series Line Cards and Fabric Modules are affected running software versions prior to 7.0(3)F3(5).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1615|2024-08-04T18:20:28.347Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1603|2024-08-04T18:20:28.374Z -- cisco -- nexus%203000%20series%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1603</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to escalate lower-level privileges to the administrator level. The vulnerability is due to insufficient authorization enforcement. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the targeted device and executing commands that could lead to elevated privileges. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to make configuration changes to the system as administrator. Nexus 3000 Series Switches are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)I7(4). Nexus 3500 Platform Switches are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)I7(4). Nexus 3600 Platform Switches are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)F3(5). Nexus 9000 Series Switches-Standalone are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)I7(4). Nexus 9500 R-Series Line Cards and Fabric Modules are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)F3(5).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1603|2024-08-04T18:20:28.374Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1593|2024-08-04T18:20:28.327Z -- cisco -- nexus%203000%20series%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1593</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Bash shell implementation for Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to escalate their privilege level by executing commands authorized to other user roles. The attacker must authenticate with valid user credentials. The vulnerability is due to the incorrect implementation of a Bash shell command that allows role-based access control (RBAC) to be bypassed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and entering a crafted command at the Bash prompt. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to escalate their privilege level by executing commands that should be restricted to other roles. For example, a dev-ops user could escalate their privilege level to admin with a successful exploit of this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1593|2024-08-04T18:20:28.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1596|2024-08-04T18:20:28.291Z -- cisco -- nexus%203000%20series%20switches
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1596</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Bash shell implementation for Cisco NX-OS Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to escalate their privilege level to root. The attacker must authenticate with valid user credentials. The vulnerability is due to incorrect permissions of a system executable. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and entering a crafted command at the Bash prompt. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to escalate their privilege level to root. Nexus 3000 Series Switches are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)I7(4). Nexus 3500 Platform Switches are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)I7(4). Nexus 3600 Platform Switches are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)F3(5). Nexus 9000 Series Switches in Standalone NX-OS Mode are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)I7(4). Nexus 9500 R-Series Line Cards and Fabric Modules are affected in versions prior to 7.0(3)F3(5).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1596|2024-08-04T18:20:28.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
