<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for innologi -- appointments Extension</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/innologi/appointments%20extension.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for innologi -- appointments Extension</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 10:23:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-25094|2024-08-05T03:00:19.369Z -- innologi -- appointments%20extension
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25094</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in innologi appointments Extension up to 2.0.5 on TYPO3. This affects an unknown part of the component Appointment Handler. The manipulation of the argument formfield leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 2.0.6 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 986d3cb34e5e086c6f04e061f600ffc5837abe7f. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-217353 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in innologi appointments Extension bis 2.0.5 für TYPO3 gefunden. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Komponente Appointment Handler. Durch Manipulation des Arguments formfield mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 2.0.6 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 986d3cb34e5e086c6f04e061f600ffc5837abe7f bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-25094|2024-08-05T03:00:19.369Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 09:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
