<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for kyverno -- kyverno</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/kyverno/kyverno.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for kyverno -- kyverno</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:22:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42813|2024-08-02T19:30:23.998Z -- kyverno -- kyverno
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42813</link>
      <description>Kyverno is a policy engine designed for Kubernetes. A security vulnerability was found in Kyverno where an attacker could cause denial of service of Kyverno. The vulnerable component in Kyvernos Notary verifier. An attacker would need control over the registry from which Kyverno would fetch attestations. With such a position, the attacker could return a malicious response to Kyverno, when Kyverno would send a request to the registry. The malicious response would cause denial of service of Kyverno, such that other users' admission requests would be blocked from being processed. This is a vulnerability in a new component released in v1.11.0. The only users affected by this are those that have been building Kyverno from source at the main branch which is not encouraged. Users consuming official Kyverno releases are not affected. There are no known cases of this vulnerability being exploited in the wild.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42813|2024-08-02T19:30:23.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 20:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42815|2024-08-02T19:30:24.650Z -- kyverno -- kyverno
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42815</link>
      <description>Kyverno is a policy engine designed for Kubernetes. A security vulnerability was found in Kyverno where an attacker could cause denial of service of Kyverno. The vulnerability was in Kyvernos Notary verifier. An attacker would need control over the registry from which Kyverno would fetch signatures. With such a position, the attacker could return a malicious response to Kyverno, when Kyverno would send a request to the registry. The malicious response would cause denial of service of Kyverno, such that other users' admission requests would be blocked from being processed. This is a vulnerability in a new component released in v1.11.0. The only users affected by this are those that have been building Kyverno from source at the main branch which is not encouraged. Users consuming official Kyverno releases are not affected. There are no known cases of this vulnerability being exploited in the wild.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42815|2024-08-02T19:30:24.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 20:33:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42816|2024-08-02T19:30:24.686Z -- kyverno -- kyverno
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42816</link>
      <description>Kyverno is a policy engine designed for Kubernetes. A security vulnerability was found in Kyverno where an attacker could cause denial of service of Kyverno. The vulnerability was in Kyvernos Notary verifier. An attacker would need control over the registry from which Kyverno would fetch signatures. With such a position, the attacker could return a malicious response to Kyverno, when Kyverno would send a request to the registry. The malicious response would cause denial of service of Kyverno, such that other users' admission requests would be blocked from being processed. This is a vulnerability in a new component released in v1.11.0. The only users affected by this are those that have been building Kyverno from source at the main branch which is not encouraged. Users consuming official Kyverno releases are not affected. There are no known cases of this vulnerability being exploited in the wild.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42816|2024-08-02T19:30:24.686Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 20:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34091|2024-08-02T16:01:53.601Z -- kyverno -- kyverno
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34091</link>
      <description>Kyverno is a policy engine designed for Kubernetes. In versions of Kyverno prior to 1.10.0, resources which have the `deletionTimestamp` field defined can bypass validate, generate, or mutate-existing policies, even in cases where the `validationFailureAction` field is set to `Enforce`. This situation occurs as resources pending deletion were being consciously exempted by Kyverno, as a way to reduce processing load as policies are typically not applied to objects which are being deleted. However, this could potentially result in allowing a malicious user to leverage the Kubernetes finalizers feature by setting a finalizer which causes the Kubernetes API server to set the `deletionTimestamp` and then not completing the delete operation as a way to explicitly to bypass a Kyverno policy. Note that this is not applicable to Kubernetes Pods but, as an example, a Kubernetes Service resource can be manipulated using an indefinite finalizer to bypass policies. This is resolved in Kyverno 1.10.0. There is no known workaround.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34091|2024-08-02T16:01:53.601Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33191|2024-08-02T15:39:35.695Z -- kyverno -- kyverno
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33191</link>
      <description>Kyverno is a policy engine designed for Kubernetes. Kyverno seccomp control can be circumvented. Users of the podSecurity `validate.podSecurity` subrule in Kyverno 1.9.2 and 1.9.3 are vulnerable. This issue was patched in version 1.9.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33191|2024-08-02T15:39:35.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 06:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42814|2024-08-02T19:30:24.296Z -- kyverno -- kyverno
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42814</link>
      <description>Kyverno is a policy engine designed for Kubernetes. A security vulnerability was found in Kyverno where an attacker could cause denial of service of Kyverno. The vulnerable component in Kyvernos Notary verifier. An attacker would need control over the registry from which Kyverno would fetch attestations. With such a position, the attacker could return a malicious response to Kyverno, when Kyverno would send a request to the registry. The malicious response would cause denial of service of Kyverno, such that other users' admission requests would be blocked from being processed. This is a vulnerability in a new component released in v1.11.0. The only users affected by this are those that have been building Kyverno from source at the main branch which is not encouraged. Users consuming official Kyverno releases are not affected. There are no known cases of this vulnerability being exploited in the wild.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42814|2024-08-02T19:30:24.296Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 20:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-47630|2024-08-02T21:16:42.282Z -- kyverno -- kyverno
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47630</link>
      <description>Kyverno is a policy engine designed for Kubernetes. An issue was found in Kyverno that allowed an attacker to control the digest of images used by Kyverno users. The issue would require the attacker to compromise the registry that the Kyverno users fetch their images from. The attacker could then return an vulnerable image to the the user and leverage that to further escalate their position. As such, the attacker would need to know which images the Kyverno user consumes and know of one of multiple exploitable vulnerabilities in previous digests of the images. Alternatively, if the attacker has compromised the registry, they could craft a malicious image with a different digest with intentionally placed vulnerabilities and deliver the image to the user.  Users pulling their images by digests and from trusted registries are not impacted by this vulnerability. There is no evidence of this being exploited in the wild. The issue has been patched in 1.10.5. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-47630|2024-08-02T21:16:42.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
