<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for LizardByte -- Sunshine</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/lizardbyte/sunshine.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for LizardByte -- Sunshine</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-31221|2024-04-08T15:10:17.071Z -- LizardByte -- Sunshine
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31221</link><description>Sunshine is a self-hosted game stream host for Moonlight. Starting in version 0.10.0 and prior to version 0.23.0, after unpairing all devices in the web UI interface and then pairing only one device, all of the previously devices will be temporarily paired. Version 0.23.0 contains a patch for the issue. As a workaround, restarting Sunshine after unpairing all devices prevents the vulnerability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31221|2024-04-08T15:10:17.071Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 15:10:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31220|2024-04-05T14:59:52.662Z -- LizardByte -- Sunshine
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31220</link><description>Sunshine is a self-hosted game stream host for Moonlight. Starting in version 0.16.0 and prior to version 0.18.0, an attacker may be able to remotely read arbitrary files without authentication due to a path traversal vulnerability. Users who exposed the Sunshine configuration web user interface outside of localhost may be affected, depending on firewall configuration. To exploit vulnerability, attacker could make an http/s request to the `node_modules` endpoint if user exposed Sunshine config web server to internet or attacker is on the LAN. Version 0.18.0 contains a patch for this issue. As a workaround, one may block access to Sunshine via firewall.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31220|2024-04-05T14:59:52.662Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 14:59:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31226|2024-05-16T18:12:57.081Z -- LizardByte -- Sunshine
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31226</link><description>Sunshine is a self-hosted game stream host for Moonlight. Users who ran Sunshine versions 0.17.0 through 0.22.2 as a service on Windows may be impacted when terminating the service if an attacked placed a file named `C:\Program.exe`, `C:\Program.bat`, or `C:\Program.cmd` on the user's computer. This attack vector isn't exploitable unless the user has manually loosened ACLs on the system drive. If the user's system locale is not English, then the name of the executable will likely vary. Version 0.23.0 contains a patch for the issue. Some workarounds are available. One may identify and block potentially malicious software executed path interception by using application control tools, like Windows Defender Application Control, AppLocker, or Software Restriction Policies where appropriate. Alternatively, ensure that proper permissions and directory access control are set to deny users the ability to write files to the top-level directory `C:`. Require that all executables be placed in write-protected directories.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31226|2024-05-16T18:12:57.081Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 18:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>