<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for NEC Corporation -- Aterm WG2600HP2</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nec%20corporation/aterm%20wg2600hp2.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for NEC Corporation -- Aterm WG2600HP2</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:23:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3332|2024-08-02T06:55:01.051Z -- nec%20corporation -- aterm%20wg2600hp2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3332</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation vulnerability in NEC Corporation Aterm Aterm WG2600HP2, WG2600HP, WG2200HP, WG1800HP2, WG1800HP, WG1400HP, WG600HP, WG300HP, WF300HP, WR9500N, WR9300N, WR8750N, WR8700N, WR8600N, WR8370N, WR8175N and WR8170N all versions allows a attacker to 

execute an arbitrary script, after obtaining a high privilege exploiting CVE-2023-3330 and CVE-2023-3331 vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3332|2024-08-02T06:55:01.051Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 01:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3330|2024-08-02T06:55:00.699Z -- nec%20corporation -- aterm%20wg2600hp2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3330</link>
      <description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory vulnerability in NEC Corporation Aterm WG2600HP2, WG2600HP, WG2200HP, WG1800HP2, WG1800HP, WG1400HP, WG600HP, WG300HP, WF300HP, WR9500N, WR9300N, WR8750N, WR8700N, WR8600N, WR8370N, WR8175N and WR8170N all versions allows a attacker to obtain specific files in the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3330|2024-08-02T06:55:00.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 01:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3331|2024-08-02T06:55:02.734Z -- nec%20corporation -- aterm%20wg2600hp2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3331</link>
      <description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory vulnerability in NEC Corporation Aterm Aterm WG2600HP2, WG2600HP, WG2200HP, WG1800HP2, WG1800HP, WG1400HP, WG600HP, WG300HP, WF300HP, WR9500N, WR9300N, WR8750N, WR8700N, WR8600N, WR8370N, WR8175N and WR8170N all versions allows a attacker to delete

 specific files in the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3331|2024-08-02T06:55:02.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 01:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3333|2024-08-02T06:55:00.761Z -- nec%20corporation -- aterm%20wg2600hp2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3333</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command vulnerability in NEC Corporation Aterm WG2600HP2, WG2600HP, WG2200HP, WG1800HP2, WG1800HP, WG1400HP, WG600HP, WG300HP, WF300HP, WR9500N, WR9300N, WR8750N, WR8700N, WR8600N, WR8370N, WR8175N and WR8170N all versions allows a attacker to execute an arbitrary OS command with the root privilege, after obtaining a high privilege exploiting CVE-2023-3330 and CVE-2023-3331 vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3333|2024-08-02T06:55:00.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 01:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
