<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for NEC Corporation -- CLUSTERPRO X</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nec%20corporation/clusterpro%20x.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for NEC Corporation -- CLUSTERPRO X</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 14:22:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34823|2024-08-03T09:22:10.122Z -- nec%20corporation -- clusterpro%20x
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34823</link>
      <description>Buffer overflow vulnerability in CLUSTERPRO X 5.0 for Windows and earlier, EXPRESSCLUSTER X 5.0 for Windows and earlier, CLUSTERPRO X 5.0 SingleServerSafe for Windows and earlier, EXPRESSCLUSTER X 5.0 SingleServerSafe for Windows and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to overwrite existing files on the file system and to potentially execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34823|2024-08-03T09:22:10.122Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34824|2024-08-03T09:22:10.309Z -- nec%20corporation -- clusterpro%20x
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34824</link>
      <description>Weak File and Folder Permissions vulnerability in CLUSTERPRO X 5.0 for Windows and earlier, EXPRESSCLUSTER X 5.0 for Windows and earlier, CLUSTERPRO X 5.0 SingleServerSafe for Windows and earlier, EXPRESSCLUSTER X 5.0 SingleServerSafe for Windows and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to overwrite existing files on the file system and to potentially execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34824|2024-08-03T09:22:10.309Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34825|2024-08-03T09:22:10.692Z -- nec%20corporation -- clusterpro%20x
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34825</link>
      <description>Uncontrolled Search Path Element in CLUSTERPRO X 5.0 for Windows and earlier, EXPRESSCLUSTER X 5.0 for Windows and earlier, CLUSTERPRO X 5.0 SingleServerSafe for Windows and earlier, EXPRESSCLUSTER X 5.0 SingleServerSafe for Windows and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to overwrite existing files on the file system and to potentially execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34825|2024-08-03T09:22:10.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34822|2024-08-03T09:22:10.570Z -- nec%20corporation -- clusterpro%20x
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34822</link>
      <description>Path traversal vulnerability in CLUSTERPRO X 5.0 for Windows and earlier, EXPRESSCLUSTER X 5.0 for Windows and earlier, CLUSTERPRO X 5.0 SingleServerSafe for Windows and earlier, EXPRESSCLUSTER X 5.0 SingleServerSafe for Windows and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to overwrite existing files on the file system and to potentially execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34822|2024-08-03T09:22:10.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
