<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for peering-manager -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/peering-manager/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for peering-manager -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-28112|2024-03-12T19:54:16.219Z -- peering-manager -- peering-manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28112</link><description>Peering Manager is a BGP session management tool. Affected versions of Peering Manager are subject to a potential stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack in the `name` attribute of AS or Platform. The XSS triggers on a routers detail page. Adversaries are able to execute arbitrary JavaScript code with the permission of a victim. XSS attacks are often used to steal credentials or login tokens of other users. This issue has been addressed in version 1.8.3. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28112|2024-03-12T19:54:16.219Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 19:54:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28113|2024-03-12T19:56:01.358Z -- peering-manager -- peering-manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28113</link><description>Peering Manager is a BGP session management tool. In Peering Manager &lt;=1.8.2, it is possible to redirect users to an arbitrary page using a crafted url. As a result users can be redirected to an unexpected location. This issue has been addressed in version 1.8.3. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28113|2024-03-12T19:56:01.358Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 19:56:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28114|2024-03-12T19:58:39.859Z -- peering-manager -- peering-manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28114</link><description>Peering Manager is a BGP session management tool. There is a Server Side Template Injection vulnerability that leads to Remote Code Execution in Peering Manager &lt;=1.8.2. As a result arbitrary commands can be executed on the operating system that is running Peering Manager. This issue has been addressed in version 1.8.3. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28114|2024-03-12T19:58:39.859Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 19:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>