<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6739, MT6761, MT6765, MT6768, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6880, MT6885, MT6886, MT6890, MT6893, MT6895, MT6897, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8676, MT8678</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mediatek%2C%20inc./mt6739%2C%20mt6761%2C%20mt6765%2C%20mt6768%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt6785%2C%20mt6789%2C%20mt6833%2C%20mt6835%2C%20mt6853%2C%20mt6855%2C%20mt6873%2C%20mt6880%2C%20mt6885%2C%20mt6886%2C%20mt6890%2C%20mt6893%2C%20mt6895%2C%20mt6897%2C%20mt6983%2C%20mt6985%2C%20mt6989%2C%20mt8666%2C%20mt8667%2C%20mt8673%2C%20mt8676%2C%20mt8678.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6739, MT6761, MT6765, MT6768, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6880, MT6885, MT6886, MT6890, MT6893, MT6895, MT6897, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8676, MT8678</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-20056|2024-05-06T02:51:47.286Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6739, MT6761, MT6765, MT6768, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6880, MT6885, MT6886, MT6890, MT6893, MT6895, MT6897, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8676, MT8678
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20056</link><description>In preloader, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08528185; Issue ID: ALPS08528185.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20056|2024-05-06T02:51:47.286Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>