<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/microsoft/windows%2010%20version%201803.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 18:23:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2020-1556|2024-05-29T16:33:10.367Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2020-1556</link><description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that the Windows WalletService handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute code with elevated permissions.
To exploit the vulnerability, a locally authenticated attacker could run a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring the Windows WalletService properly handles objects in memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1556|2024-05-29T16:33:10.367Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-1227|2024-05-29T16:51:12.625Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1227</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows kernel improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would have to log on to an affected system and run a specially crafted application. The vulnerability would not allow an attacker to execute code or to elevate user rights directly, but it could be used to obtain information that could be used to try to further compromise the affected system.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows kernel handles objects in memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1227|2024-05-29T16:51:12.625Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-1512|2024-05-29T16:33:06.478Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2020-1512</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows State Repository Service improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.
An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a specially crafted application on the victim system.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way the Windows State Repository Service handles objects in memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1512|2024-05-29T16:33:06.478Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-1184|2024-05-29T16:50:57.973Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1184</link><description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when Windows Core Shell COM Server Registrar improperly handles COM calls. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could potentially set certain items to run at a higher level and thereby elevate permissions.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to log on to the system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application that could exploit the vulnerability and take control of an affected system.
The update addresses this vulnerability by correcting unprotected COM calls.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1184|2024-05-29T16:50:57.973Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-1173|2024-05-29T16:50:31.858Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1173</link><description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that the PsmServiceExtHost.dll handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute code with elevated permissions.
To exploit the vulnerability, a locally authenticated attacker could run a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring the PsmServiceExtHost.dll properly handles objects in memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1173|2024-05-29T16:50:31.858Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-1464|2024-05-29T16:32:23.703Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2020-1464</link><description>A spoofing vulnerability exists when Windows incorrectly validates file signatures. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could bypass security features and load improperly signed files.
In an attack scenario, an attacker could bypass security features intended to prevent improperly signed files from being loaded.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Windows validates file signatures.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1464|2024-05-29T16:32:23.703Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-1587|2024-05-29T16:33:23.155Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2020-1587</link><description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock handles memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1587|2024-05-29T16:33:23.155Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-1533|2024-05-29T16:32:33.370Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2020-1533</link><description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that the Windows WalletService handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute code with elevated permissions.
To exploit the vulnerability, a locally authenticated attacker could run a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring the Windows WalletService properly handles objects in memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1533|2024-05-29T16:32:33.370Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-1524|2024-05-29T16:32:29.424Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2020-1524</link><description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Speech Shell Components improperly handle memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Speech Shell Components handle memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1524|2024-05-29T16:32:29.424Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-1513|2024-05-29T16:33:06.961Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2020-1513</link><description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows CSC Service improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows CSC Service handles memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1513|2024-05-29T16:33:06.961Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-0965|2024-05-29T16:50:25.301Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-0965</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists when Windows Hyper-V on a host server fails to properly validate input from an authenticated user on a guest operating system. To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker could run a specially crafted application on a guest operating system that could cause the Hyper-V host operating system to execute arbitrary code.
An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute arbitrary code on the host operating system.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Hyper-V validates guest operating system user input.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0965|2024-05-29T16:50:25.301Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-1578|2024-05-29T16:33:19.204Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2020-1578</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in the Windows kernel that could allow an attacker to retrieve information that could lead to a Kernel Address Space Layout Randomization (ASLR) bypass. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could retrieve the memory address of a kernel object.
To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker would have to log on to an affected system and run a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows kernel handles memory addresses.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1578|2024-05-29T16:33:19.204Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-1377|2024-05-29T16:32:45.265Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2020-1377</link><description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Kernel API improperly handles registry objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain elevated privileges on a targeted system.
A locally authenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by helping to ensure that the Windows Kernel API properly handles objects in memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1377|2024-05-29T16:32:45.265Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-1378|2024-05-29T16:32:45.756Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2020-1378</link><description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Kernel API improperly handles registry objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain elevated privileges on a targeted system.
A locally authenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by helping to ensure that the Windows Kernel API properly handles objects in memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1378|2024-05-29T16:32:45.756Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-1526|2024-05-29T16:32:30.401Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2020-1526</link><description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Network Connection Broker improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Network Connection Broker handles memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1526|2024-05-29T16:32:30.401Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-1534|2024-05-29T16:32:33.859Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2020-1534</link><description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Backup Service improperly handles file operations.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Backup Service handles file operations.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1534|2024-05-29T16:32:33.859Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-1212|2024-05-29T16:51:08.076Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1212</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the Windows Server DHCP service when processing specially crafted packets. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could cause the DHCP server service to stop responding.
To exploit the vulnerability, a remote unauthenticated attacker could send a specially crafted packet to an affected DHCP server.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how DHCP servers handle network packets.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1212|2024-05-29T16:51:08.076Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-1222|2024-05-29T16:51:10.078Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1222</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in Remote Desktop Services – formerly known as Terminal Services – when an unauthenticated attacker connects to the target system using RDP and sends specially crafted requests. This vulnerability is pre-authentication and requires no user interaction. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could execute arbitrary code on the target system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to send a specially crafted request to the target systems Remote Desktop Service via RDP.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Remote Desktop Services handles connection requests.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1222|2024-05-29T16:51:10.078Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-1224|2024-05-29T16:51:11.090Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1224</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows RDP server improperly discloses the contents of its memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the system.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would have to connect remotely to an affected system and run a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows RDP server initializes memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1224|2024-05-29T16:51:11.090Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-1223|2024-05-29T16:51:10.569Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1223</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) when an attacker connects to the target system using RDP and sends specially crafted requests. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could cause the RDP service on the target system to stop responding.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to run a specially crafted application against a server which provides Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) services.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how RDP handles connection requests.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1223|2024-05-29T16:51:10.569Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-1516|2024-05-29T16:32:25.945Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2020-1516</link><description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Work Folders Service improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Work Folders Service handles memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1516|2024-05-29T16:32:25.945Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-1226|2024-05-29T16:51:12.090Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1226</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in Remote Desktop Services – formerly known as Terminal Services – when an unauthenticated attacker connects to the target system using RDP and sends specially crafted requests. This vulnerability is pre-authentication and requires no user interaction. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could execute arbitrary code on the target system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to send a specially crafted request to the target systems Remote Desktop Service via RDP.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Remote Desktop Services handles connection requests.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1226|2024-05-29T16:51:12.090Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-1225|2024-05-29T16:51:11.595Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1225</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows RDP server improperly discloses the contents of its memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the system.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would have to connect remotely to an affected system and run a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows RDP server initializes memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1225|2024-05-29T16:51:11.595Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-1535|2024-05-29T16:32:34.354Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2020-1535</link><description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Backup Engine improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Backup Engine handles memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1535|2024-05-29T16:32:34.354Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-1522|2024-05-29T16:32:28.934Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2020-1522</link><description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Speech Runtime improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Speech Runtime handles memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1522|2024-05-29T16:32:28.934Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-1175|2024-05-29T16:50:32.889Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1175</link><description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that the psmsrv.dll handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute code with elevated permissions.
To exploit the vulnerability, a locally authenticated attacker could run a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring the psmsrv.dll properly handles objects in memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1175|2024-05-29T16:50:32.889Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-1188|2024-05-29T16:51:00.524Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1188</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in Microsoft Windows that could allow remote code execution if a .LNK file is processed.
An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the local user. Users whose accounts are configured to have fewer user rights on the system could be less impacted than users who operate with administrative user rights.
The attacker could present to the user a removable drive, or remote share, that contains a malicious .LNK file and an associated malicious binary. When the user opens this drive(or remote share) in Windows Explorer, or any other application that parses the .LNK file, the malicious binary will execute code of the attacker’s choice, on the target system.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the processing of shortcut LNK references.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1188|2024-05-29T16:51:00.524Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-1521|2024-05-29T16:32:28.443Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2020-1521</link><description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Speech Runtime improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Speech Runtime handles memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1521|2024-05-29T16:32:28.443Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-1473|2024-05-29T16:32:51.143Z -- Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2020-1473</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists when the Windows Jet Database Engine improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could execute arbitrary code on a victim system.
An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by enticing a victim to open a specially crafted file.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way the Windows Jet Database Engine handles objects in memory.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1473|2024-05-29T16:32:51.143Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>