<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/microsoft/windows%2010%20version%201803.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 19:19:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1212|2024-06-12T17:14:22.943Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1212</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the Windows Server DHCP service when processing specially crafted packets. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could cause the DHCP server service to stop responding.
To exploit the vulnerability, a remote unauthenticated attacker could send a specially crafted packet to an affected DHCP server.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how DHCP servers handle network packets.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1212|2024-06-12T17:14:22.943Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1188|2024-06-12T17:21:59.648Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-1188</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in Microsoft Windows that could allow remote code execution if a .LNK file is processed.
An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the local user. Users whose accounts are configured to have fewer user rights on the system could be less impacted than users who operate with administrative user rights.
The attacker could present to the user a removable drive, or remote share, that contains a malicious .LNK file and an associated malicious binary. When the user opens this drive(or remote share) in Windows Explorer, or any other application that parses the .LNK file, the malicious binary will execute code of the attacker’s choice, on the target system.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the processing of shortcut LNK references.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1188|2024-06-12T17:21:59.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
