<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1903 for 32-bit Systems</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/microsoft/windows%2010%20version%201903%20for%2032-bit%20systems.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1903 for 32-bit Systems</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:22:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0624|2024-08-04T06:11:04.656Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201903%20for%2032-bit%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0624</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in Windows when the Win32k component fails to properly handle objects in memory, aka 'Win32k Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability'. This CVE ID is unique from CVE-2020-0642.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0624|2024-08-04T06:11:04.656Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 23:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1430|2024-08-04T18:20:27.555Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201903%20for%2032-bit%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1430</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists when Windows Media Foundation improperly parses specially crafted QuickTime media files.An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the local user, aka 'Microsoft Windows Media Foundation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability'.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1430|2024-08-04T18:20:27.555Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 18:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1185|2024-08-04T18:13:29.478Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201903%20for%2032-bit%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1185</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists due to a stack corruption in Windows Subsystem for Linux. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute code with elevated permissions.
To exploit the vulnerability, a locally authenticated attacker could run a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Windows Subsystem for Linux handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1185|2024-08-04T18:13:29.478Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1057|2024-08-04T18:06:31.653Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201903%20for%2032-bit%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1057</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists when the Microsoft XML Core Services MSXML parser processes user input. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could run malicious code remotely to take control of the user’s system.
To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker could host a specially crafted website designed to invoke MSXML through a web browser. However, an attacker would have no way to force a user to visit such a website. Instead, an attacker would typically have to convince a user to either click a link in an email message or instant message that would then take the user to the website. When Internet Explorer parses the XML content, an attacker could run malicious code remotely to take control of the user’s system.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the MSXML parser processes user input.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1057|2024-08-04T18:06:31.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17014|2024-08-04T13:45:34.752Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201903%20for%2032-bit%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17014</link>
      <description>Windows Print Spooler Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17014|2024-08-04T13:45:34.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 06:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0636|2024-08-04T06:11:04.575Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201903%20for%2032-bit%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0636</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that the Windows Subsystem for Linux handles files, aka 'Windows Subsystem for Linux Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability'.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0636|2024-08-04T06:11:04.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 23:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1423|2024-08-04T18:20:27.492Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201903%20for%2032-bit%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1423</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that the StartTileData.dll handles file creation in protected locations, aka 'Windows Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability'. This CVE ID is unique from CVE-2019-1420, CVE-2019-1422.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1423|2024-08-04T18:20:27.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 18:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0796|2024-08-04T06:18:01.914Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201903%20for%2032-bit%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0796</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way that the Microsoft Server Message Block 3.1.1 (SMBv3) protocol handles certain requests, aka 'Windows SMBv3 Client/Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability'.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0796|2024-08-04T06:18:01.914Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 15:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
