<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1703</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/microsoft/windows%2010%20version%201703.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1703</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 21:20:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1172|2024-06-18T20:38:35.038Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201703
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1172</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in Azure Active Directory (AAD) Microsoft Account (MSA) during the login request session. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take over a user's account.
To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker would have to trick a user into browsing to a specially crafted website, allowing the attacker to steal the user's token.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how MSA handles cookies.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1172|2024-06-18T20:38:35.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1182|2024-06-18T20:42:46.392Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201703
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1182</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in Remote Desktop Services – formerly known as Terminal Services – when an unauthenticated attacker connects to the target system using RDP and sends specially crafted requests. This vulnerability is pre-authentication and requires no user interaction. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could execute arbitrary code on the target system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to send a specially crafted request to the target systems Remote Desktop Service via RDP.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Remote Desktop Services handles connection requests.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1182|2024-06-18T20:42:46.392Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1171|2024-06-18T20:37:50.966Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201703
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1171</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in SymCrypt during the OAEP decryption stage. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would have to log on to an affected system and run a specially crafted application. The vulnerability would not allow an attacker to execute code or to elevate user rights directly, but it could be used to obtain information that could be used to try to further compromise the affected system.
The update addresses the vulnerability through a software change to the OAEP decoding operations.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1171|2024-06-18T20:37:50.966Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0714|2024-06-18T20:35:00.159Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201703
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0714</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability exists when Microsoft Hyper-V Network Switch on a host server fails to properly validate input from a privileged user on a guest operating system. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could cause the host server to crash.
To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker who already has a privileged account on a guest operating system, running as a virtual machine, could run a specially crafted application that causes a host machine to crash.
The update addresses the vulnerability by modifying how virtual machines access the Hyper-V Network Switch.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0714|2024-06-18T20:35:00.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1143|2024-06-18T20:35:40.251Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201703
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1143</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows GDI component improperly discloses the contents of its memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise a user’s system.
There are multiple ways an attacker could exploit the vulnerability, such as by convincing a user to open a specially crafted document or by convincing a user to visit an untrusted webpage.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows GDI component handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1143|2024-06-18T20:35:40.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1187|2024-06-18T20:42:26.827Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201703
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1187</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability exists when the XmlLite runtime (XmlLite.dll) improperly parses XML input. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could cause a denial of service against an XML application.
A remote unauthenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability by issuing specially crafted requests to an XML application.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the XmlLite runtime parses XML input.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1187|2024-06-18T20:42:26.827Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 20:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
