<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/microsoft/windows%2010%20version%201803.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 13:22:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1578|2024-08-04T06:39:10.638Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1578</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in the Windows kernel that could allow an attacker to retrieve information that could lead to a Kernel Address Space Layout Randomization (ASLR) bypass. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could retrieve the memory address of a kernel object.
To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker would have to log on to an affected system and run a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows kernel handles memory addresses.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1578|2024-08-04T06:39:10.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1377|2024-08-04T06:32:01.249Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1377</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Kernel API improperly handles registry objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain elevated privileges on a targeted system.
A locally authenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by helping to ensure that the Windows Kernel API properly handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1377|2024-08-04T06:32:01.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1533|2024-08-04T06:39:10.523Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1533</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that the Windows WalletService handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute code with elevated permissions.
To exploit the vulnerability, a locally authenticated attacker could run a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring the Windows WalletService properly handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1533|2024-08-04T06:39:10.523Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0886|2024-08-04T06:18:03.179Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0886</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Storage Services improperly handle file operations. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could gain elevated privileges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker would first need code execution on a victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring the Windows Storage Services properly handle file operations.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0886|2024-08-04T06:18:03.179Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1129|2024-08-04T06:25:01.232Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1129</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way that Microsoft Windows Codecs Library handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could take control of the affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exploitation of the vulnerability requires that a program process a specially crafted image file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Microsoft Windows Codecs Library handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1129|2024-08-04T06:25:01.232Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1535|2024-08-04T06:39:10.892Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1535</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Backup Engine improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Backup Engine handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1535|2024-08-04T06:39:10.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1152|2024-08-04T06:25:01.287Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1152</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when Windows improperly handles calls to Win32k.sys. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain elevated privileges on a targeted system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker would have to log on to an affected system and run a specially crafted script or application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Windows handles calls to Win32k.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1152|2024-08-04T06:25:01.287Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1245|2024-08-04T06:31:59.784Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1245</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in Windows when the Win32k component fails to properly handle objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run arbitrary code in kernel mode. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to log on to the system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application that could exploit the vulnerability and take control of an affected system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses this vulnerability by correcting how Win32k handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1245|2024-08-04T06:31:59.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1091|2024-08-04T06:25:00.934Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1091</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows GDI component improperly discloses the contents of its memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise a user’s system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are multiple ways an attacker could exploit the vulnerability, such as by convincing a user to open a specially crafted document or by convincing a user to visit an untrusted webpage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows GDI component handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1091|2024-08-04T06:25:00.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1599|2024-08-04T06:39:10.810Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1599</link>
      <description>Windows Spoofing Vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1599|2024-08-04T06:39:10.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 06:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0890|2024-08-04T06:18:03.464Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0890</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A denial of service vulnerability exists when Microsoft Hyper-V on a host server fails to properly validate specific malicious data from a user on a guest operating system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker who already has a privileged account on a guest operating system, running as a virtual machine, could run a specially crafted application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by resolving the conditions where Hyper-V would fail to handle these requests.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0890|2024-08-04T06:18:03.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1378|2024-08-04T06:32:01.267Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1378</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Kernel API improperly handles registry objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain elevated privileges on a targeted system.
A locally authenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by helping to ensure that the Windows Kernel API properly handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1378|2024-08-04T06:32:01.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1074|2024-08-04T06:25:01.073Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1074</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A remote code execution vulnerability exists when the Windows Jet Database Engine improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could execute arbitrary code on a victim system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by enticing a victim to open a specially crafted file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way the Windows Jet Database Engine handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1074|2024-08-04T06:25:01.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1256|2024-08-04T06:31:59.924Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1256</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows GDI component improperly discloses the contents of its memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are multiple ways an attacker could exploit the vulnerability, such as by convincing a user to open a specially crafted document, or by convincing a user to visit an untrusted webpage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows GDI component handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1256|2024-08-04T06:31:59.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1592|2024-08-04T06:39:10.700Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1592</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows kernel improperly initializes objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an authenticated attacker could run a specially crafted application. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows kernel initializes objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1592|2024-08-04T06:39:10.700Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1556|2024-08-04T06:39:10.809Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1556</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that the Windows WalletService handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute code with elevated permissions.
To exploit the vulnerability, a locally authenticated attacker could run a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring the Windows WalletService properly handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1556|2024-08-04T06:39:10.809Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0764|2024-08-04T06:11:05.637Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0764</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Storage Services improperly handle file operations. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could gain elevated privileges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker would first need code execution on a victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring the Windows Storage Services properly handle file operations.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0764|2024-08-04T06:11:05.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 22:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1473|2024-08-04T06:39:09.800Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1473</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists when the Windows Jet Database Engine improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could execute arbitrary code on a victim system.
An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by enticing a victim to open a specially crafted file.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way the Windows Jet Database Engine handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1473|2024-08-04T06:39:09.800Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0790|2024-08-04T06:11:05.563Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0790</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A local elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in how splwow64.exe handles certain calls. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could elevate privileges on an affected system from low-integrity to medium-integrity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This vulnerability by itself does not allow arbitrary code execution; however, it could allow arbitrary code to be run if the attacker uses it in combination with another vulnerability (such as a remote code execution vulnerability or another elevation of privilege vulnerability) that is capable of leveraging the elevated privileges when code execution is attempted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring splwow64.exe properly handles these calls..&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0790|2024-08-04T06:11:05.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1083|2024-08-04T06:25:00.832Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1083</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Microsoft Windows Graphics Component improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would have to log on to an affected system and run a specially crafted application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way in which the Windows Graphics Component handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1083|2024-08-04T06:25:00.832Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0766|2024-08-04T06:11:05.547Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0766</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Microsoft Store Runtime improperly handles memory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Microsoft Store Runtime handles memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0766|2024-08-04T06:11:05.547Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1464|2024-08-04T06:39:09.825Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1464</link>
      <description>A spoofing vulnerability exists when Windows incorrectly validates file signatures. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could bypass security features and load improperly signed files.
In an attack scenario, an attacker could bypass security features intended to prevent improperly signed files from being loaded.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Windows validates file signatures.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1464|2024-08-04T06:39:09.825Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0921|2024-08-04T06:18:03.512Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0921</link>
      <description>Microsoft Graphics Component Denial of Service Vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0921|2024-08-04T06:18:03.512Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1097|2024-08-04T06:25:01.041Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1097</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows GDI component improperly discloses the contents of its memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise a user’s system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are multiple ways an attacker could exploit the vulnerability, such as by convincing a user to open a specially crafted document or by convincing a user to visit an untrusted webpage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows GDI component handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1097|2024-08-04T06:25:01.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1080|2024-08-04T06:25:01.083Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1080</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when Windows Hyper-V on a host server fails to properly handle objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited these vulnerabilities could gain elevated privileges on a target operating system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This vulnerability by itself does not allow arbitrary code to be run.  However, this vulnerability could be used in conjunction with one or more vulnerabilities (e.g. a remote code execution vulnerability and another elevation of privilege) that could take advantage of the elevated privileges when running.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerabilities by correcting how Windows Hyper-V handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1080|2024-08-04T06:25:01.083Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 22:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0989|2024-08-04T06:18:03.633Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0989</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An information disclosure vulnerability exists when Windows Mobile Device Management (MDM) Diagnostics improperly handles junctions. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could bypass access restrictions to read files.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to log on to the system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application that could exploit the vulnerability and access files.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the how Windows MDM Diagnostics handles files.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0989|2024-08-04T06:18:03.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1598|2024-08-04T06:39:10.806Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1598</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Universal Plug and Play (UPnP) service improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would have to log on to an affected system and run a specially crafted script or application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows UPnP service handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1598|2024-08-04T06:39:10.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1512|2024-08-04T06:39:10.519Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1512</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows State Repository Service improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.
An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a specially crafted application on the victim system.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way the Windows State Repository Service handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1512|2024-08-04T06:39:10.519Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0904|2024-08-04T06:18:03.465Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0904</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A denial of service vulnerability exists when Microsoft Hyper-V on a host server fails to properly validate specific malicious data from a user on a guest operating system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker who already has a privileged account on a guest operating system, running as a virtual machine, could run a specially crafted application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by resolving the conditions where Hyper-V would fail to handle these requests.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0904|2024-08-04T06:18:03.465Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1243|2024-08-04T06:31:59.966Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1243</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A denial of service vulnerability exists when Microsoft Hyper-V on a host server fails to properly validate specific malicious data from a user on a guest operating system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker who already has a privileged account on a guest operating system, running as a virtual machine, could run a specially crafted application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by resolving the conditions where Hyper-V would fail to handle these requests.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1243|2024-08-04T06:31:59.966Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 22:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1589|2024-08-04T06:39:10.631Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1589</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows kernel improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would have to log on to an affected system and run a specially crafted application. The vulnerability would not allow an attacker to execute code or to elevate user rights directly, but it could be used to obtain information that could be used to try to further compromise the affected system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows kernel handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1589|2024-08-04T06:39:10.631Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1524|2024-08-04T06:39:10.407Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1524</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Speech Shell Components improperly handle memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Speech Shell Components handle memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1524|2024-08-04T06:39:10.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1039|2024-08-04T06:25:00.698Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1039</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A remote code execution vulnerability exists when the Windows Jet Database Engine improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could execute arbitrary code on a victim system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by enticing a victim to open a specially crafted file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way the Windows Jet Database Engine handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1039|2024-08-04T06:25:00.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0922|2024-08-04T06:18:03.519Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0922</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way that Microsoft COM for Windows handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute arbitrary code on a target system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, a user would have to open a specially crafted file or lure the target to a website hosting malicious JavaScript.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Microsoft COM for Windows handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0922|2024-08-04T06:18:03.519Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1526|2024-08-04T06:39:10.496Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1526</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Network Connection Broker improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Network Connection Broker handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1526|2024-08-04T06:39:10.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1033|2024-08-04T06:25:00.992Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1033</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows kernel improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An authenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a specially crafted application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows kernel handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1033|2024-08-04T06:25:00.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1319|2024-08-04T06:32:00.532Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1319</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way that Microsoft Windows Codecs Library handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could take control of the affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exploitation of the vulnerability requires that a program process a specially crafted image file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Microsoft Windows Codecs Library handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1319|2024-08-04T06:32:00.532Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1034|2024-08-04T06:25:01.282Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1034</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that the Windows Kernel handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute code with elevated permissions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, a locally authenticated attacker could run a specially crafted application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring the Windows Kernel properly handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1034|2024-08-04T06:25:01.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0908|2024-08-04T06:18:03.492Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0908</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A remote code execution vulnerability exists when the Windows Text Service Module improperly handles memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain execution on a victim system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An attacker could host a specially crafted website that is designed to exploit the vulnerability through Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based), and then convince a user to view the website. The attacker could also take advantage of compromised websites and websites that accept or host user-provided content or advertisements by adding specially crafted content that could exploit the vulnerability. In all cases, however, an attacker would have no way to force users to view the attacker-controlled content. Instead, an attacker would have to convince users to take action, typically by way of enticement in an email or Instant Messenger message, or by getting them to open an attachment sent through email.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Text Service Module handles memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0908|2024-08-04T06:18:03.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0875|2024-08-04T06:18:03.390Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0875</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An information disclosure vulnerability exists in how splwow64.exe handles certain calls. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system (low-integrity to medium-integrity).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This vulnerability by itself does not allow arbitrary code execution; however, it could allow arbitrary code to be run if the attacker uses it in combination with another vulnerability (such as a remote code execution vulnerability or another elevation of privilege vulnerability) that is capable of leveraging the elevated privileges when code execution is attempted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring splwow64.exe properly handles these calls.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0875|2024-08-04T06:18:03.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0928|2024-08-04T06:18:03.539Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0928</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows kernel improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would have to log on to an affected system and run a specially crafted application. The vulnerability would not allow an attacker to execute code or to elevate user rights directly, but it could be used to obtain information that could be used to try to further compromise the affected system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows kernel handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0928|2024-08-04T06:18:03.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1146|2024-08-04T06:25:01.291Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1146</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Microsoft Store Runtime improperly handles memory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Microsoft Store Runtime handles memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1146|2024-08-04T06:25:01.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1047|2024-08-04T06:25:01.114Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1047</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when Windows Hyper-V on a host server fails to properly handle objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited these vulnerabilities could gain elevated privileges on a target operating system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This vulnerability by itself does not allow arbitrary code to be run.  However, this vulnerability could be used in conjunction with one or more vulnerabilities (e.g. a remote code execution vulnerability and another elevation of privilege) that could take advantage of the elevated privileges when running.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerabilities by correcting how Windows Hyper-V handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1047|2024-08-04T06:25:01.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 22:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1587|2024-08-04T06:39:10.664Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1587</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1587|2024-08-04T06:39:10.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1596|2024-08-04T06:39:10.699Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1596</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A information disclosure vulnerability exists when TLS components use weak hash algorithms. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise a users's encrypted transmission channel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker would have to conduct a man-in-the-middle attack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how TLS components use hash algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1596|2024-08-04T06:39:10.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0941|2024-08-04T06:18:03.558Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0941</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the win32k component improperly provides kernel information. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker would have to either log on locally to an affected system, or convince a locally authenticated user to execute a specially crafted application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how win32k handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0941|2024-08-04T06:18:03.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1130|2024-08-04T06:25:01.223Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1130</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Diagnostics Hub Standard Collector improperly handles data operations. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run processes in an elevated context.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a specially crafted application on the victim system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way the Diagnostics Hub Standard Collector handles data operations.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1130|2024-08-04T06:25:01.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0911|2024-08-04T06:18:03.628Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0911</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when Windows Modules Installer improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run arbitrary code in an elevated context.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a specially crafted application on the victim system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way the Windows Modules Installer handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0911|2024-08-04T06:18:03.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0914|2024-08-04T06:18:03.478Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0914</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows State Repository Service improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a specially crafted application on the victim system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way the Windows State Repository Service handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0914|2024-08-04T06:18:03.478Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1303|2024-08-04T06:32:00.553Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1303</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Runtime improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run arbitrary code in an elevated context.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a specially crafted application on the victim system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way the Windows Runtime handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1303|2024-08-04T06:32:00.553Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1521|2024-08-04T06:39:10.521Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1521</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Speech Runtime improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Speech Runtime handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1521|2024-08-04T06:39:10.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0870|2024-08-04T06:18:03.449Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0870</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Shell infrastructure component improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run processes in an elevated context.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to log on to the system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application that could exploit the vulnerability and take control of an affected system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way in which the Shell infrastructure component handles objects in memory and preventing unintended elevation from lower integrity application.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0870|2024-08-04T06:18:03.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0951|2024-08-04T06:18:03.545Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0951</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A security feature bypass vulnerability exists in Windows Defender Application Control (WDAC) which could allow an attacker to bypass WDAC enforcement. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could execute PowerShell commands that would be blocked by WDAC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker need administrator access on a local machine where PowerShell is running. The attacker could then connect to a PowerShell session and send commands to execute arbitrary code.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how PowerShell commands are validated when WDAC protection is enabled.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0951|2024-08-04T06:18:03.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1534|2024-08-04T06:39:10.631Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1534</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Backup Service improperly handles file operations.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Backup Service handles file operations.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1534|2024-08-04T06:39:10.631Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1167|2024-08-04T06:25:01.403Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1167</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way that Microsoft Graphics Components handle objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute arbitrary code on a target system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, a user would have to open a specially crafted file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Microsoft Graphics Components handle objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1167|2024-08-04T06:25:01.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 22:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1115|2024-08-04T06:25:01.077Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1115</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the &lt;a href="https://technet.microsoft.com/library/security/dn848375.aspx#CLFS"&gt;Windows Common Log File System (CLFS)&lt;/a&gt; driver improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run processes in an elevated context.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker would first have to log on to the system, and then run a specially crafted application to take control over the affected system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how CLFS handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1115|2024-08-04T06:25:01.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1250|2024-08-04T06:32:00.076Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1250</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the win32k component improperly provides kernel information. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would have to log on to an affected system and run a specially crafted application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how win32k handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1250|2024-08-04T06:32:00.076Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1516|2024-08-04T06:39:10.396Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1516</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Work Folders Service improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Work Folders Service handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1516|2024-08-04T06:39:10.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0998|2024-08-04T06:18:03.612Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0998</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Graphics Component improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run processes in an elevated context.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a local attack scenario, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a specially crafted application to take control over the affected system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way in which the Microsoft Graphics Component handles objects in memory and preventing unintended elevation from user mode.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0998|2024-08-04T06:18:03.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1285|2024-08-04T06:32:01.373Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1285</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way that the Windows Graphics Device Interface (GDI) handles objects in the memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could take control of the affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. Users whose accounts are configured to have fewer user rights on the system could be less impacted than users who operate with administrative user rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are multiple ways an attacker could exploit the vulnerability:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In a web-based attack scenario, an attacker could host a specially crafted website that is designed to exploit the vulnerability and then convince users to view the website. An attacker would have no way to force users to view the attacker-controlled content. Instead, an attacker would have to convince users to take action, typically by getting them to open an email attachment or click a link in an email or instant message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In a file-sharing attack scenario, an attacker could provide a specially crafted document file that is designed to exploit the vulnerability, and then convince users to open the document file.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way that the Windows GDI handles objects in the memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1285|2024-08-04T06:32:01.373Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1522|2024-08-04T06:39:10.385Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1522</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Speech Runtime improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Speech Runtime handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1522|2024-08-04T06:39:10.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1471|2024-08-04T06:39:10.366Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1471</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when Microsoft Windows CloudExperienceHost fails to check COM objects. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain elevated privileges on a targeted system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker would have to log on to an affected system and run a specially crafted script or application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by checking COM objects.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1471|2024-08-04T06:39:10.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0782|2024-08-04T06:11:05.967Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0782</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Cryptographic Catalog Services improperly handle objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could modify the cryptographic catalog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to log on to the system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application that could exploit the vulnerability and take control of an affected system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by addressing how the Windows Cryptographic Catalog Services handle objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0782|2024-08-04T06:11:05.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1513|2024-08-04T06:39:10.537Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1513</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows CSC Service improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows CSC Service handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1513|2024-08-04T06:39:10.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1252|2024-08-04T06:31:59.697Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1252</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A remote code execution vulnerability exists when Windows improperly handles objects in memory. To exploit the vulnerability an attacker would have to convince a user to run a specially crafted application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could execute arbitrary code and take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The updates address the vulnerability by correcting how Windows handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1252|2024-08-04T06:31:59.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1122|2024-08-04T06:25:01.245Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1122</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Language Pack Installer improperly handles file operations. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run processes in an elevated context.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a specially crafted application on the victim system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way the Windows Language Pack Installer handles file operations.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1122|2024-08-04T06:25:01.245Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1308|2024-08-04T06:31:59.998Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1308</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when DirectX improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run arbitrary code in kernel mode. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to log on to the system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application that could exploit the vulnerability and take control of an affected system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how DirectX handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1308|2024-08-04T06:31:59.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1038|2024-08-04T06:25:00.671Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1038</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A denial of service vulnerability exists when Windows Routing Utilities improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could cause a target system to stop responding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would have to log on to an affected system and run a specially crafted application. The vulnerability would not allow an attacker to execute code or to elevate user rights directly, but it could be used to cause a target system to stop responding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Windows handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1038|2024-08-04T06:25:00.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
