<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/microsoft/windows%2010%20version%201803.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 1803</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 22:23:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28333|2024-10-01T15:54:41.542Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28333</link>
      <description>Remote Procedure Call Runtime Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28333|2024-10-01T15:54:41.542Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 19:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26869|2024-10-01T15:55:31.921Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26869</link>
      <description>Windows ActiveX Installer Service Information Disclosure Vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26869|2024-10-01T15:55:31.921Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 15:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28344|2024-10-01T15:54:35.696Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28344</link>
      <description>Remote Procedure Call Runtime Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28344|2024-10-01T15:54:35.696Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 19:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1097|2024-10-01T15:57:12.774Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1097</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows GDI component improperly discloses the contents of its memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise a user’s system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are multiple ways an attacker could exploit the vulnerability, such as by convincing a user to open a specially crafted document or by convincing a user to visit an untrusted webpage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows GDI component handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1097|2024-10-01T15:57:12.774Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24107|2024-10-01T15:55:40.900Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24107</link>
      <description>Windows Event Tracing Information Disclosure Vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24107|2024-10-01T15:55:40.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 15:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1589|2024-10-01T15:57:05.829Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1589</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows kernel improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would have to log on to an affected system and run a specially crafted application. The vulnerability would not allow an attacker to execute code or to elevate user rights directly, but it could be used to obtain information that could be used to try to further compromise the affected system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows kernel handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1589|2024-10-01T15:57:05.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28356|2024-10-01T15:54:29.546Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28356</link>
      <description>Remote Procedure Call Runtime Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28356|2024-10-01T15:54:29.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 19:33:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1039|2024-10-01T15:57:18.205Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1039</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A remote code execution vulnerability exists when the Windows Jet Database Engine improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could execute arbitrary code on a victim system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by enticing a victim to open a specially crafted file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way the Windows Jet Database Engine handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1039|2024-10-01T15:57:18.205Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-16968|2024-10-01T15:56:44.985Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%201803
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-16968</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A remote code execution vulnerability exists when the Windows Camera Codec Pack improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could run arbitrary code in the context of the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker could take control of the affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. Users whose accounts are configured to have fewer user rights on the system could be less impacted than users who operate with administrative user rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exploitation of the vulnerability requires that a user open a specially crafted file with an affected version of the Windows Camera Codec Pack. In an email attack scenario, an attacker could exploit the vulnerability by sending the specially crafted file to the user and convincing the user to open the file. In a web-based attack scenario, an attacker could host a website (or leverage a compromised website that accepts or hosts user-provided content) containing a specially crafted file designed to exploit the vulnerability. An attacker would have no way to force users to visit the website. Instead, an attacker would have to convince users to click a link, typically by way of an enticement in an email or instant message, and then convince them to open the specially crafted file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Camera Codec Pack handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-16968|2024-10-01T15:56:44.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 22:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
