<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 2004</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/microsoft/windows%2010%20version%202004.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Microsoft -- Windows 10 Version 2004</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 17:21:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1560|2024-08-04T06:39:10.556Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1560</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way that Microsoft Windows Codecs Library handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could take control of the affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
Exploitation of the vulnerability requires that a program process a specially crafted image file.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Microsoft Windows Codecs Library handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1560|2024-08-04T06:39:10.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1544|2024-08-04T06:39:10.536Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1544</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Backup Engine improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Backup Engine handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1544|2024-08-04T06:39:10.536Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1574|2024-08-04T06:39:10.502Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1574</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way that Microsoft Windows Codecs Library handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute arbitrary code.
Exploitation of the vulnerability requires that a program process a specially crafted image file.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Microsoft Windows Codecs Library handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1574|2024-08-04T06:39:10.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1475|2024-08-04T06:39:10.290Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1475</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that the srmsvc.dll handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute code with elevated permissions.
To exploit the vulnerability, a locally authenticated attacker could run a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring the srmsvc.dll properly handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1475|2024-08-04T06:39:10.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1538|2024-08-04T06:39:10.549Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1538</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows UPnP Device Host improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows UPnP Device Host handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1538|2024-08-04T06:39:10.549Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17090|2024-08-04T13:53:17.456Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17090</link>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Endpoint Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17090|2024-08-04T13:53:17.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 06:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0805|2024-08-04T06:18:01.954Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0805</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A security feature bypass vulnerability exists when a Windows Projected Filesystem improperly handles file redirections. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could delete a targeted file they would not have permissions to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to log on to the system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application that could exploit the vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Windows Projected Filesystem handle file redirections.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0805|2024-08-04T06:18:01.954Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1477|2024-08-04T06:39:10.460Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1477</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists when Windows Media Foundation improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
There are multiple ways an attacker could exploit the vulnerability, such as by convincing a user to open a specially crafted document, or by convincing a user to visit a malicious webpage.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Windows Media Foundation handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1477|2024-08-04T06:39:10.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1488|2024-08-04T06:39:10.373Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1488</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows AppX Deployment Extensions improperly performs privilege management, resulting in access to system files.
To exploit this vulnerability, an authenticated attacker would need to run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how AppX Deployment Extensions manages privileges.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1488|2024-08-04T06:39:10.373Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0648|2024-08-04T06:11:05.051Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0648</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows RSoP Service Application improperly handles memory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows RSoP Service Application handles memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0648|2024-08-04T06:11:05.051Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1525|2024-08-04T06:39:10.466Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1525</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists when Windows Media Foundation improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
There are multiple ways an attacker could exploit the vulnerability, such as by convincing a user to open a specially crafted document, or by convincing a user to visit a malicious webpage.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Windows Media Foundation handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1525|2024-08-04T06:39:10.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1417|2024-08-04T06:39:09.116Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1417</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows kernel fails to properly handle objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run arbitrary code in kernel mode. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to log on to the system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to take control of an affected system.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows kernel handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1417|2024-08-04T06:39:09.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1508|2024-08-04T06:39:10.522Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1508</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A remote code execution vulnerability exists when Windows Media Audio Decoder improperly handles objects. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are multiple ways an attacker could exploit the vulnerability, such as by convincing a user to open a specially crafted document, or by convincing a user to visit a malicious webpage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Windows Media Audio Decoder handles objects.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1508|2024-08-04T06:39:10.522Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1098|2024-08-04T06:25:01.095Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1098</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Shell infrastructure component improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run processes in an elevated context.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to log on to the system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application that could exploit the vulnerability and take control of an affected system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way in which the Shell infrastructure component handles objects in memory and preventing unintended elevation from lower integrity application.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1098|2024-08-04T06:25:01.095Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1519|2024-08-04T06:39:10.394Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1519</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows UPnP Device Host improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows UPnP Device Host handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1519|2024-08-04T06:39:10.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1552|2024-08-04T06:39:10.531Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1552</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Work Folder Service improperly handles file operations. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run processes in an elevated context.
An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a specially crafted application on the victim system.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way the Windows Work Folder Service handles file operations.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1552|2024-08-04T06:39:10.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1585|2024-08-04T06:39:10.578Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1585</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way that Microsoft Windows Codecs Library handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could take control of the affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
Exploitation of the vulnerability requires that a program process a specially crafted image file.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Microsoft Windows Codecs Library handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1585|2024-08-04T06:39:10.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1518|2024-08-04T06:39:10.409Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1518</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows File Server Resource Management Service improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows File Server Resource Management Service handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1518|2024-08-04T06:39:10.409Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1053|2024-08-04T06:25:01.093Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1053</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when DirectX improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run arbitrary code in kernel mode. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to log on to the system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application that could exploit the vulnerability and take control of an affected system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how DirectX handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1053|2024-08-04T06:25:01.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1530|2024-08-04T06:39:10.388Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1530</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when Windows Remote Access improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Windows Remote Access handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1530|2024-08-04T06:39:10.388Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1383|2024-08-04T06:32:00.946Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1383</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in RPC if the server has Routing and Remote Access enabled. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to run a specially crafted application against an RPC server which has Routing and Remote Access enabled. Routing and Remote Access is a non-default configuration; systems without it enabled are not vulnerable.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Routing and Remote Access service handles requests.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1383|2024-08-04T06:32:00.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1577|2024-08-04T06:39:10.621Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1577</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists when DirectWrite improperly discloses the contents of its memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.
There are multiple ways an attacker could exploit the vulnerability, such as by convincing a user to open a specially crafted document, or by convincing a user to visit an untrusted webpage.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how DirectWrite handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1577|2024-08-04T06:39:10.621Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1379|2024-08-04T06:32:01.258Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1379</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists when Windows Media Foundation improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
There are multiple ways an attacker could exploit the vulnerability, such as by convincing a user to open a specially crafted document, or by convincing a user to visit a malicious webpage.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Windows Media Foundation handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1379|2024-08-04T06:32:01.258Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1492|2024-08-04T06:39:10.616Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1492</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists when Windows Media Foundation improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
There are multiple ways an attacker could exploit the vulnerability, such as by convincing a user to open a specially crafted document, or by convincing a user to visit a malicious webpage.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Windows Media Foundation handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1492|2024-08-04T06:39:10.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1510|2024-08-04T06:39:10.480Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1510</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the win32k component improperly provides kernel information. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would have to log on to an affected system and run a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how win32k handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1510|2024-08-04T06:39:10.480Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1579|2024-08-04T06:39:10.579Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1579</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Function Discovery SSDP Provider improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Function Discovery SSDP Provider handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1579|2024-08-04T06:39:10.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1509|2024-08-04T06:39:10.566Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1509</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the Local Security Authority Subsystem Service (LSASS) when an authenticated attacker sends a specially crafted authentication request. A remote attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could cause an elevation of privilege on the target system's LSASS service.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by changing the way that LSASS handles specially crafted authentication requests.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1509|2024-08-04T06:39:10.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1485|2024-08-04T06:39:10.363Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1485</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows Image Acquisition (WIA) Service improperly discloses contents of its memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.
To exploit the vulnerability, an authenticated attacker could connect an imaging device (camera, scanner, cellular phone) to an affected system and run a specially crafted application to disclose information.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the WIA Service handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1485|2024-08-04T06:39:10.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1564|2024-08-04T06:39:10.591Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1564</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists when the Windows Jet Database Engine improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could execute arbitrary code on a victim system.
An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by enticing a victim to open a specially crafted file.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way the Windows Jet Database Engine handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1564|2024-08-04T06:39:10.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1546|2024-08-04T06:39:10.427Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1546</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Backup Engine improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Backup Engine handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1546|2024-08-04T06:39:10.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1566|2024-08-04T06:39:10.573Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1566</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows kernel fails to properly handle objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run arbitrary code in kernel mode. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to log on to the system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to take control of an affected system.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows kernel handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1566|2024-08-04T06:39:10.573Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1520|2024-08-04T06:39:10.533Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1520</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists when the Windows Font Driver Host improperly handles memory.
An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability would gain execution on a victim system.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Font Driver Host handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1520|2024-08-04T06:39:10.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1545|2024-08-04T06:39:10.633Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1545</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Backup Engine improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Backup Engine handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1545|2024-08-04T06:39:10.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1507|2024-08-04T06:39:10.460Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1507</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that Microsoft COM for Windows handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain elevated privileges on a targeted system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, a user would have to open a specially crafted file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Microsoft COM for Windows handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1507|2024-08-04T06:39:10.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1474|2024-08-04T06:39:09.748Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1474</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows Image Acquisition (WIA) Service improperly discloses contents of its memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.
To exploit the vulnerability, an authenticated attacker could connect an imaging device (camera, scanner, cellular phone) to an affected system and run a specially crafted application to disclose information.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the WIA Service handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1474|2024-08-04T06:39:09.748Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1339|2024-08-04T06:32:01.251Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1339</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists when Windows Media Audio Codec improperly handles objects. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system.
There are multiple ways an attacker could exploit the vulnerability, such as by convincing a user to open a specially crafted document, or by convincing a user to visit a malicious webpage.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Windows Media Audio Codec handles objects.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1339|2024-08-04T06:32:01.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1491|2024-08-04T06:39:10.418Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1491</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that the Windows Function Discovery Service handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute code with elevated permissions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, a locally authenticated attacker could run a specially crafted application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring the Windows Function Discovery Service properly handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1491|2024-08-04T06:39:10.418Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1470|2024-08-04T06:39:09.972Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1470</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Work Folders Service improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Work Folders Service handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1470|2024-08-04T06:39:09.972Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1479|2024-08-04T06:39:10.389Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1479</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when DirectX improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run arbitrary code in kernel mode. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to log on to the system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application that could exploit the vulnerability and take control of an affected system.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how DirectX handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1479|2024-08-04T06:39:10.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1013|2024-08-04T06:25:00.644Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1013</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when Microsoft Windows processes group policy updates. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could potentially escalate permissions or perform additional privileged actions on the target machine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to launch a man-in-the-middle (MiTM) attack against the traffic passing between a domain controller and the target machine. An attacker could then create a group policy to grant administrator rights to a standard user.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by enforcing Kerberos authentication for certain calls over LDAP.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1013|2024-08-04T06:25:00.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1529|2024-08-04T06:39:10.526Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1529</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that the Windows Graphics Device Interface (GDI) handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run arbitrary code in kernel mode. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to log on to the system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application that could exploit the vulnerability and take control of an affected system.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how GDI handles objects in memory and by preventing instances of unintended user-mode privilege elevation.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1529|2024-08-04T06:39:10.526Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1562|2024-08-04T06:39:10.574Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1562</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way that Microsoft Graphics Components handle objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute arbitrary code on a target system.
To exploit the vulnerability, a user would have to open a specially crafted file.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Microsoft Graphics Components handle objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1562|2024-08-04T06:39:10.574Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1030|2024-08-04T06:25:00.888Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1030</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Print Spooler service improperly allows arbitrary writing to the file system. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would have to log on to an affected system and run a specially crafted script or application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Print Spooler Component writes to the file system.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1030|2024-08-04T06:25:00.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1517|2024-08-04T06:39:10.538Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1517</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows File Server Resource Management Service improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows File Server Resource Management Service handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1517|2024-08-04T06:39:10.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1484|2024-08-04T06:39:10.381Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1484</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Work Folders Service improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Work Folders Service handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1484|2024-08-04T06:39:10.381Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1548|2024-08-04T06:39:10.541Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1548</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows WaasMedic Service improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to improperly disclose memory.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows WaasMedic Service handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1548|2024-08-04T06:39:10.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1550|2024-08-04T06:39:10.454Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1550</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows CDP User Components improperly handle memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows CDP User Components handle memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1550|2024-08-04T06:39:10.454Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1553|2024-08-04T06:39:10.530Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1553</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Runtime improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run arbitrary code in an elevated context.
An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a specially crafted application on the victim system.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way the Windows Runtime handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1553|2024-08-04T06:39:10.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1515|2024-08-04T06:39:10.453Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1515</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Telephony Server improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Telephony Server handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1515|2024-08-04T06:39:10.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1565|2024-08-04T06:39:10.641Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1565</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the &amp;quot;Public Account Pictures&amp;quot; folder improperly handles junctions.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Windows handles junctions.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1565|2024-08-04T06:39:10.641Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1541|2024-08-04T06:39:10.622Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1541</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Backup Engine improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Backup Engine handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1541|2024-08-04T06:39:10.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1543|2024-08-04T06:39:10.676Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1543</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Backup Engine improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Backup Engine handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1543|2024-08-04T06:39:10.676Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1336|2024-08-04T06:32:00.946Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1336</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that the Windows Kernel handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute code with elevated permissions.
To exploit the vulnerability, a locally authenticated attacker could run a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring the Windows Kernel properly handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1336|2024-08-04T06:32:00.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 22:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1547|2024-08-04T06:39:10.648Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1547</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Backup Engine improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Backup Engine handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1547|2024-08-04T06:39:10.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1536|2024-08-04T06:39:10.428Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1536</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Backup Engine improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Backup Engine handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1536|2024-08-04T06:39:10.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1539|2024-08-04T06:39:10.539Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1539</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Backup Engine improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Backup Engine handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1539|2024-08-04T06:39:10.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1558|2024-08-04T06:39:10.528Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1558</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists when the Windows Jet Database Engine improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could execute arbitrary code on a victim system.
An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by enticing a victim to open a specially crafted file.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way the Windows Jet Database Engine handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1558|2024-08-04T06:39:10.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0912|2024-08-04T06:18:03.333Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0912</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Function Discovery SSDP Provider improperly handles memory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Function Discovery SSDP Provider handles memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0912|2024-08-04T06:18:03.333Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1528|2024-08-04T06:39:10.464Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1528</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Radio Manager API improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Radio Manager API handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1528|2024-08-04T06:39:10.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1337|2024-08-04T06:32:01.371Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1337</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Print Spooler service improperly allows arbitrary writing to the file system. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would have to log on to an affected system and run a specially crafted script or application.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Print Spooler Component writes to the file system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1337|2024-08-04T06:32:01.371Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1478|2024-08-04T06:39:09.643Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1478</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists when Windows Media Foundation improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
There are multiple ways an attacker could exploit the vulnerability, such as by convincing a user to open a specially crafted document, or by convincing a user to visit a malicious webpage.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Windows Media Foundation handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1478|2024-08-04T06:39:09.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1511|2024-08-04T06:39:10.410Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1511</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when Connected User Experiences and Telemetry Service improperly handles file operations. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run processes in an elevated context.
An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a specially crafted application on the victim system.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by  correcting how the Connected User Experiences and Telemetry Service handles file operations.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1511|2024-08-04T06:39:10.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0838|2024-08-04T06:18:03.451Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0838</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when NTFS improperly checks access. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run processes in an elevated context.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker would first have to log on to the system, and then run a specially crafted application to take control over the affected system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how NTFS checks access.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0838|2024-08-04T06:18:03.451Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-16891|2024-08-04T13:45:34.673Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-16891</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A remote code execution vulnerability exists when Windows Hyper-V on a host server fails to properly validate input from an authenticated user on a guest operating system. To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker could run a specially crafted application on a guest operating system that could cause the Hyper-V host operating system to execute arbitrary code.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute arbitrary code on the host operating system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Hyper-V validates guest operating system user input.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-16891|2024-08-04T13:45:34.673Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 22:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1559|2024-08-04T06:39:10.465Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1559</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Storage Services improperly handle file operations. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could gain elevated privileges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker would first need code execution on a victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring the Windows Storage Services properly handle file operations.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1559|2024-08-04T06:39:10.465Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1554|2024-08-04T06:39:10.440Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1554</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists when Windows Media Foundation improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
There are multiple ways an attacker could exploit the vulnerability, such as by convincing a user to open a specially crafted document, or by convincing a user to visit a malicious webpage.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Windows Media Foundation handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1554|2024-08-04T06:39:10.440Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1487|2024-08-04T06:39:10.512Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1487</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists when Media Foundation improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would have to log onto an affected system and open a specially crafted file. In a web-based attack scenario, an attacker could host a website (or leverage a compromised website that accepts or hosts user-provided content) that contains a specially crafted file that is designed to exploit the vulnerability. However, an attacker would have no way to force the user to visit the website. Instead, an attacker would have to convince the user to click a link, typically by way of an enticement in an email or Instant Messenger message, and then convince the user to open the specially crafted file.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Media Foundation handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1487|2024-08-04T06:39:10.512Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1571|2024-08-04T06:39:10.581Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1571</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in Windows Setup in the way it handles permissions.
A locally authenticated attacker could run arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. After successfully exploiting the vulnerability, an attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring Windows Setup properly handles permissions.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1571|2024-08-04T06:39:10.581Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1031|2024-08-04T06:25:00.842Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1031</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An information disclosure vulnerability exists in the way that the Windows Server DHCP service improperly discloses the contents of its memory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, an unauthenticated attacker could send a specially crafted packet to an affected DHCP server.  An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how DHCP servers initializes memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1031|2024-08-04T06:25:00.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1527|2024-08-04T06:39:10.425Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1527</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Custom Protocol Engine improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Custom Protocol Engine handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1527|2024-08-04T06:39:10.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1549|2024-08-04T06:39:10.501Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1549</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows CDP User Components improperly handle memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows CDP User Components handle memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1549|2024-08-04T06:39:10.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1169|2024-08-04T06:25:01.238Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1169</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Runtime improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run arbitrary code in an elevated context.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by running a specially crafted application on the victim system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way the Windows Runtime handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1169|2024-08-04T06:25:01.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1537|2024-08-04T06:39:10.570Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1537</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Remote Access improperly handles file operations. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could gain elevated privileges.
To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker would first need code execution on a victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring the Windows Remote Access properly handles file operations.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1537|2024-08-04T06:39:10.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1542|2024-08-04T06:39:10.638Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1542</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Backup Engine improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Backup Engine handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1542|2024-08-04T06:39:10.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1561|2024-08-04T06:39:10.600Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1561</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way that Microsoft Graphics Components handle objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute arbitrary code on a target system.
To exploit the vulnerability, a user would have to open a specially crafted file.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Microsoft Graphics Components handle objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1561|2024-08-04T06:39:10.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-16938|2024-08-04T13:45:34.489Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-16938</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An information disclosure vulnerability exists when the Windows kernel improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could obtain information to further compromise the user’s system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would have to log on to an affected system and run a specially crafted application. The vulnerability would not allow an attacker to execute code or to elevate user rights directly, but it could be used to obtain information that could be used to try to further compromise the affected system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows kernel handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-16938|2024-08-04T13:45:34.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 22:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1489|2024-08-04T06:39:10.412Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1489</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows CSC Service improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows CSC Service handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1489|2024-08-04T06:39:10.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1557|2024-08-04T06:39:10.730Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1557</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists when the Windows Jet Database Engine improperly handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could execute arbitrary code on a victim system.
An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by enticing a victim to open a specially crafted file.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting the way the Windows Jet Database Engine handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1557|2024-08-04T06:39:10.730Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1584|2024-08-04T06:39:10.670Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1584</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that the dnsrslvr.dll handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute code with elevated permissions.
To exploit the vulnerability, a locally authenticated attacker could run a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring the dnsrslvr.dll properly handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1584|2024-08-04T06:39:10.670Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1052|2024-08-04T06:25:00.978Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1052</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that the ssdpsrv.dll handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute code with elevated permissions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, a locally authenticated attacker could run a specially crafted application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring the ssdpsrv.dll properly handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1052|2024-08-04T06:25:00.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1551|2024-08-04T06:39:10.646Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1551</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Backup Engine improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Backup Engine handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1551|2024-08-04T06:39:10.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1490|2024-08-04T06:39:10.326Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1490</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Storage Service improperly handles file operations. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could gain elevated privileges on the victim system.
To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system, then run a specially crafted application.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Storage Services handles file operations.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1490|2024-08-04T06:39:10.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1376|2024-08-04T06:32:01.391Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1376</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that fdSSDP.dll handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute code with elevated permissions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, a locally authenticated attacker could run a specially crafted application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring the ssdpsrv.dll properly handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1376|2024-08-04T06:32:01.391Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1540|2024-08-04T06:39:10.791Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1540</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Backup Engine improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Backup Engine handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1540|2024-08-04T06:39:10.791Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1480|2024-08-04T06:39:09.786Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1480</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that the Windows Graphics Device Interface (GDI) handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run arbitrary code in kernel mode. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to log on to the system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application that could exploit the vulnerability and take control of an affected system.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how GDI handles objects in memory and by preventing instances of unintended user-mode privilege elevation.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1480|2024-08-04T06:39:09.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-0839|2024-08-04T06:18:03.449Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-0839</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in the way that the dnsrslvr.dll handles objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could execute code with elevated permissions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To exploit the vulnerability, a locally authenticated attacker could run a specially crafted application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by ensuring the dnsrslvr.dll properly handles objects in memory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-0839|2024-08-04T06:18:03.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1486|2024-08-04T06:39:10.353Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1486</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows kernel fails to properly handle objects in memory. An attacker who successfully exploited this vulnerability could run arbitrary code in kernel mode. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to log on to the system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to take control of an affected system.
The update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows kernel handles objects in memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1486|2024-08-04T06:39:10.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1531|2024-08-04T06:39:10.535Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1531</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists when the Windows Accounts Control improperly handles memory.
To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would first have to gain execution on the victim system. An attacker could then run a specially crafted application to elevate privileges.
The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how the Windows Accounts Control handles memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1531|2024-08-04T06:39:10.535Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1593|2024-08-04T06:39:10.663Z -- microsoft -- windows%2010%20version%202004
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1593</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A remote code execution vulnerability exists when Windows Media Audio Decoder improperly handles objects. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are multiple ways an attacker could exploit the vulnerability, such as by convincing a user to open a specially crafted document, or by convincing a user to visit a malicious webpage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security update addresses the vulnerability by correcting how Windows Media Audio Decoder handles objects.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1593|2024-08-04T06:39:10.663Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
