<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for JustSystems -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/justsystems/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for JustSystems -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2790|2024-08-05T14:02:07.698Z -- justsystems -- ichitaro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2790</link>
      <description>When processing a record type of 0x3c from a Workbook stream from an Excel file (.xls), JustSystems Ichitaro Office trusts that the size is greater than zero, subtracts one from the length, and uses this result as the size for a memcpy. This results in a heap-based buffer overflow and can lead to code execution under the context of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2790|2024-08-05T14:02:07.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2791|2024-08-05T14:02:07.798Z -- justsystems -- ichitaro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2791</link>
      <description>JustSystems Ichitaro 2016 Trial contains a vulnerability that exists when trying to open a specially crafted PowerPoint file. Due to the application incorrectly handling the error case for a function's result, the application will use this result in a pointer calculation for reading file data into. Due to this, the application will read data from the file into an invalid address thus corrupting memory. Under the right conditions, this can lead to code execution under the context of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2791|2024-08-05T14:02:07.798Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2789|2024-08-05T14:02:07.828Z -- justsystems -- ichitaro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2789</link>
      <description>When copying filedata into a buffer, JustSystems Ichitaro Office 2016 Trial will calculate two values to determine how much data to copy from the document. If both of these values are larger than the size of the buffer, the application will choose the smaller of the two and trust it to copy data from the file. This value is larger than the buffer size, which leads to a heap-based buffer overflow. This overflow corrupts an offset in the heap used in pointer arithmetic for writing data and can lead to code execution under the context of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2789|2024-08-05T14:02:07.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
