<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for cronvel -- string-kit</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cronvel/string-kit.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for cronvel -- string-kit</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4299|2024-08-03T17:23:10.350Z -- cronvel -- string-kit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4299</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in cronvel string-kit up to 0.12.7. This vulnerability affects the function naturalSort of the file lib/naturalSort.js. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 0.12.8 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 9cac4c298ee92c1695b0695951f1488884a7ca73. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-217180.
In cronvel string-kit bis 0.12.7 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht um die Funktion naturalSort der Datei lib/naturalSort.js. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine inefficient regular expression complexity-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 0.12.8 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 9cac4c298ee92c1695b0695951f1488884a7ca73 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4299|2024-08-03T17:23:10.350Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 07:57:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
