<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Foxit -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/foxit/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Foxit -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-29072|2024-05-28T13:52:58.113Z -- Foxit -- Foxit Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29072</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Foxit Reader 2024.2.0.25138. The vulnerability occurs due to improper certification validation of the updater executable before executing it. A low privilege user can trigger the update action which can result in unexpected elevation of privilege.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29072|2024-05-28T13:52:58.113Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 13:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30361|2024-04-02T20:17:53.853Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30361</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22877.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30361|2024-04-02T20:17:53.853Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30336|2024-04-02T20:10:27.749Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30336</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22642.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30336|2024-04-02T20:10:27.749Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:10:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30357|2024-04-02T20:16:10.523Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30357</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Annotation Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22818.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30357|2024-04-02T20:16:10.523Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30341|2024-04-02T20:11:57.116Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30341</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22709.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30341|2024-04-02T20:11:57.116Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30340|2024-04-02T20:11:42.967Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30340</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22707.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30340|2024-04-02T20:11:42.967Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30356|2024-04-02T20:15:57.029Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30356</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22811.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30356|2024-04-02T20:15:57.029Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30337|2024-04-02T20:10:46.578Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30337</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Acroforms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22704.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30337|2024-04-02T20:10:46.578Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:10:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30360|2024-04-02T20:17:40.995Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30360</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22797.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30360|2024-04-02T20:17:40.995Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:17:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30351|2024-04-02T20:14:37.138Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30351</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22799.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30351|2024-04-02T20:14:37.138Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30347|2024-04-02T20:13:44.724Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30347</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22910.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30347|2024-04-02T20:13:44.724Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30367|2024-04-02T20:27:37.842Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30367</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23013.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30367|2024-04-02T20:27:37.842Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30330|2024-04-03T16:22:48.825Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30330</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22636.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30330|2024-04-03T16:22:48.825Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30326|2024-04-03T16:21:52.538Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30326</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22593.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30326|2024-04-03T16:21:52.538Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30371|2024-04-02T20:28:59.183Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30371</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23355.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30371|2024-04-02T20:28:59.183Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30327|2024-04-03T16:22:11.355Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30327</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader template Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of template objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22632.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30327|2024-04-03T16:22:11.355Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30331|2024-04-03T16:23:02.442Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30331</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22637.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30331|2024-04-03T16:23:02.442Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30366|2024-04-03T16:24:26.378Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30366</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23002.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30366|2024-04-03T16:24:26.378Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:24:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30346|2024-04-02T20:13:32.142Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30346</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22745.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30346|2024-04-02T20:13:32.142Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30350|2024-04-02T20:14:25.960Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30350</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22708.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30350|2024-04-02T20:14:25.960Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:14:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30328|2024-04-03T16:22:22.251Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30328</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22633.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30328|2024-04-03T16:22:22.251Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30345|2024-04-02T20:13:20.386Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30345</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22742.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30345|2024-04-02T20:13:20.386Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30353|2024-04-02T20:15:15.599Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30353</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22807.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30353|2024-04-02T20:15:15.599Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30324|2024-04-03T16:21:19.087Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30324</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22576.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30324|2024-04-03T16:21:19.087Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30332|2024-04-03T16:23:12.387Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30332</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22638.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30332|2024-04-03T16:23:12.387Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30365|2024-04-02T20:18:43.270Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30365</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22947.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30365|2024-04-02T20:18:43.270Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30349|2024-04-02T20:14:09.849Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30349</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22912.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30349|2024-04-02T20:14:09.849Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30348|2024-04-02T20:13:57.509Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30348</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22911.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30348|2024-04-02T20:13:57.509Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30364|2024-04-02T20:18:33.776Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30364</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23009.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30364|2024-04-02T20:18:33.776Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30333|2024-04-03T16:23:28.166Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30333</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22639.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30333|2024-04-03T16:23:28.166Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30325|2024-04-03T16:21:32.080Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30325</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22592.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30325|2024-04-03T16:21:32.080Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30352|2024-04-02T20:15:02.950Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30352</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22800.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30352|2024-04-02T20:15:02.950Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30344|2024-04-02T20:12:54.900Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30344</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Acroforms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22733.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30344|2024-04-02T20:12:54.900Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30329|2024-04-03T16:22:37.379Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30329</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22634.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30329|2024-04-03T16:22:37.379Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30322|2024-04-03T16:20:39.122Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30322</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22499.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30322|2024-04-03T16:20:39.122Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30334|2024-04-03T16:24:04.350Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30334</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22640.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30334|2024-04-03T16:24:04.350Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:24:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30363|2024-04-02T20:18:20.890Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30363</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23008.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30363|2024-04-02T20:18:20.890Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:18:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30359|2024-04-02T20:17:26.652Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30359</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm 3D Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of 3D objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22888.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30359|2024-04-02T20:17:26.652Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:17:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30338|2024-04-02T20:11:07.857Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30338</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22705.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30338|2024-04-02T20:11:07.857Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30343|2024-04-02T20:12:18.694Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30343</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22721.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30343|2024-04-02T20:12:18.694Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30355|2024-04-02T20:15:37.031Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30355</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22809.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30355|2024-04-02T20:15:37.031Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30354|2024-04-02T20:15:26.857Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30354</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22808.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30354|2024-04-02T20:15:26.857Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30342|2024-04-02T20:12:08.125Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30342</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22720.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30342|2024-04-02T20:12:08.125Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:12:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30339|2024-04-02T20:11:25.499Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30339</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Acroforms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22706.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30339|2024-04-02T20:11:25.499Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30358|2024-04-02T20:17:11.501Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30358</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm User-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22821.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30358|2024-04-02T20:17:11.501Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30362|2024-04-02T20:18:04.752Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30362</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22798.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30362|2024-04-02T20:18:04.752Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30335|2024-04-02T17:48:13.134Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30335</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22641.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30335|2024-04-02T17:48:13.134Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30323|2024-04-03T16:21:07.052Z -- Foxit -- PDF Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30323</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader template Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of template objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22501.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30323|2024-04-03T16:21:07.052Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25575|2024-04-30T17:00:07.967Z -- Foxit -- Foxit Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25575</link><description>A type confusion vulnerability vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.1.0.23997 handles a Lock object. A specially crafted Javascript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger this vulnerability, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25575|2024-04-30T17:00:07.967Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25938|2024-04-30T17:00:07.157Z -- Foxit -- Foxit Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25938</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.1.0.23997 handles a Barcode widget. A specially crafted JavaScript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger reuse of a previously freed object, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25938|2024-04-30T17:00:07.157Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25648|2024-04-30T17:00:07.549Z -- Foxit -- Foxit Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25648</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.1.0.23997 handles a ComboBox widget. A specially crafted JavaScript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger reuse of a previously freed object, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25648|2024-04-30T17:00:07.549Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>