<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Foxit -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/foxit/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Foxit -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:19:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34975|2024-06-05T18:29:56.046Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2021-34975</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader transitionToState Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the transitionToState method. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15218.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34975|2024-06-05T18:29:56.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51561|2024-06-05T14:53:18.879Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51561</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22283.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51561|2024-06-05T14:53:18.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25648|2024-04-30T17:00:07.549Z -- foxit -- foxit%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25648</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.1.0.23997 handles a ComboBox widget. A specially crafted JavaScript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger reuse of a previously freed object, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25648|2024-04-30T17:00:07.549Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
