<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Foxit -- Foxit Reader</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/foxit/foxit%20reader.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Foxit -- Foxit Reader</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 20:24:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38097|2024-09-17T02:26:59.360Z -- foxit -- foxit%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38097</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the JavaScript engine of Foxit Software's PDF Reader, version 12.0.1.12430. By prematurely destroying annotation objects, a specially-crafted PDF document can trigger the reuse of previously freed memory, which can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially-crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38097|2024-09-17T02:26:59.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 16:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-37332|2024-09-17T02:36:28.821Z -- foxit -- foxit%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-37332</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the JavaScript engine of Foxit Software's PDF Reader, version 12.0.1.12430. A specially-crafted PDF document can trigger the reuse of previously freed memory via misusing media player API, which can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially-crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-37332|2024-09-17T02:36:28.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 16:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32774|2024-09-17T03:07:15.105Z -- foxit -- foxit%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32774</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the JavaScript engine of Foxit Software's PDF Reader, version 12.0.1.12430. By prematurely deleting objects associated with pages, a specially-crafted PDF document can trigger the reuse of previously freed memory, which can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially-crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32774|2024-09-17T03:07:15.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 16:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29072|2024-08-02T01:03:51.701Z -- foxit -- foxit%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29072</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Foxit Reader 2024.2.0.25138. The vulnerability occurs due to improper certification validation of the updater executable before executing it. A low privilege user can trigger the update action which can result in unexpected elevation of privilege.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29072|2024-08-02T01:03:51.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 13:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29072|2024-05-28T13:52:58.113Z -- foxit -- foxit%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29072</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Foxit Reader 2024.2.0.25138. The vulnerability occurs due to improper certification validation of the updater executable before executing it. A low privilege user can trigger the update action which can result in unexpected elevation of privilege.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29072|2024-05-28T13:52:58.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 13:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25575|2024-06-04T17:35:31.240Z -- foxit -- foxit%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25575</link>
      <description>A type confusion vulnerability vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.1.0.23997 handles a Lock object. A specially crafted Javascript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger this vulnerability, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25575|2024-06-04T17:35:31.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25938|2024-06-04T17:35:29.088Z -- foxit -- foxit%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25938</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.1.0.23997 handles a Barcode widget. A specially crafted JavaScript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger reuse of a previously freed object, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25938|2024-06-04T17:35:29.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25648|2024-06-04T17:35:16.481Z -- foxit -- foxit%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25648</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.1.0.23997 handles a ComboBox widget. A specially crafted JavaScript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger reuse of a previously freed object, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25648|2024-06-04T17:35:16.481Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
