<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Foxit -- Foxit Reader</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/foxit/foxit%20reader.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Foxit -- Foxit Reader</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-25575|2024-04-30T17:00:07.967Z -- Foxit -- Foxit Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25575</link><description>A type confusion vulnerability vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.1.0.23997 handles a Lock object. A specially crafted Javascript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger this vulnerability, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25575|2024-04-30T17:00:07.967Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25938|2024-04-30T17:00:07.157Z -- Foxit -- Foxit Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25938</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.1.0.23997 handles a Barcode widget. A specially crafted JavaScript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger reuse of a previously freed object, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25938|2024-04-30T17:00:07.157Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25648|2024-04-30T17:00:07.549Z -- Foxit -- Foxit Reader
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25648</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.1.0.23997 handles a ComboBox widget. A specially crafted JavaScript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger reuse of a previously freed object, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25648|2024-04-30T17:00:07.549Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>