<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Foxit -- PDF Editor</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/foxit/pdf%20editor.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Foxit -- PDF Editor</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 15:23:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34959|2024-08-08T14:56:28.397Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34959</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor Square Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14360.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34959|2024-08-08T14:56:28.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34961|2024-06-18T18:16:17.494Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34961</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor Ink Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14363.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34961|2024-06-18T18:16:17.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27365|2024-06-05T19:32:19.534Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27365</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor DOC File Parsing Exposed Dangerous Method Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DOC files. The issue results from the lack of proper restrictions on macro-enabled documents. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19739.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27365|2024-06-05T19:32:19.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27364|2024-06-04T17:24:54.497Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27364</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor XLS File Parsing Exposed Dangerous Method Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XLS files. The issue results from the lack of proper restrictions on macro-enabled documents. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19738.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27364|2024-06-04T17:24:54.497Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27365|2024-08-02T12:09:43.120Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27365</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor DOC File Parsing Exposed Dangerous Method Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DOC files. The issue results from the lack of proper restrictions on macro-enabled documents. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19739.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27365|2024-08-02T12:09:43.120Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27364|2024-08-02T12:09:43.354Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27364</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor XLS File Parsing Exposed Dangerous Method Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XLS files. The issue results from the lack of proper restrictions on macro-enabled documents. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19738.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27364|2024-08-02T12:09:43.354Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34960|2024-08-04T00:26:55.648Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34960</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor Circle Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14362.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34960|2024-08-04T00:26:55.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34966|2024-08-04T00:26:55.841Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34966</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor FileAttachment Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14367.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34966|2024-08-04T00:26:55.841Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34964|2024-08-04T00:26:55.650Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34964</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor Polygon Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14366.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34964|2024-08-04T00:26:55.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34956|2024-08-04T00:26:55.773Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34956</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor Underline Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14357.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34956|2024-08-04T00:26:55.773Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34962|2024-08-04T00:26:55.719Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34962</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor Caret Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14364.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34962|2024-08-04T00:26:55.719Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34963|2024-08-04T00:26:55.654Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34963</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor PolyLine Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14365.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34963|2024-08-04T00:26:55.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34968|2024-08-04T00:26:55.666Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34968</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor transitionToState Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the transitionToState method. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14370.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34968|2024-08-04T00:26:55.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34954|2024-08-04T00:26:55.657Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34954</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor StrikeOut Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14355.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34954|2024-08-04T00:26:55.657Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34958|2024-08-04T00:26:55.747Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34958</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor Text Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14359.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34958|2024-08-04T00:26:55.747Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34965|2024-08-04T00:26:55.776Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34965</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor Squiggly Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14361.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34965|2024-08-04T00:26:55.776Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34957|2024-08-04T00:26:55.666Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34957</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor Highlight Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14358.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34957|2024-08-04T00:26:55.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34961|2024-08-04T00:26:55.686Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34961</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor Ink Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14363.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34961|2024-08-04T00:26:55.686Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34959|2024-08-04T00:26:55.654Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34959</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor Square Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14360.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34959|2024-08-04T00:26:55.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34967|2024-08-04T00:26:55.714Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34967</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor Line Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14368.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34967|2024-08-04T00:26:55.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34955|2024-08-04T00:26:55.716Z -- foxit -- pdf%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34955</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Editor Stamp Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14356.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34955|2024-08-04T00:26:55.716Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
