<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Foxit -- PDF Reader</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/foxit/pdf%20reader.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Foxit -- PDF Reader</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:19:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34852|2024-08-04T00:26:54.204Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34852</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-13929.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34852|2024-08-04T00:26:54.204Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34850|2024-08-04T00:26:54.602Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34850</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14529.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34850|2024-08-04T00:26:54.602Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34849|2024-08-04T00:26:54.179Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34849</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14531.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34849|2024-08-04T00:26:54.179Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34848|2024-08-04T00:26:54.180Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34848</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14532.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34848|2024-08-04T00:26:54.180Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34842|2024-08-04T00:26:54.215Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34842</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34842|2024-08-04T00:26:54.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34834|2024-08-04T00:26:54.111Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34834</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14014.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34834|2024-08-04T00:26:54.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34844|2024-08-04T00:26:54.586Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34844</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14033.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34844|2024-08-04T00:26:54.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34847|2024-08-04T00:26:54.211Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34847</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14270.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34847|2024-08-04T00:26:54.211Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34838|2024-08-04T00:26:54.191Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34838</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14019.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34838|2024-08-04T00:26:54.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34836|2024-08-04T00:26:54.172Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34836</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14017.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34836|2024-08-04T00:26:54.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34837|2024-08-04T00:26:54.049Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34837</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14018.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34837|2024-08-04T00:26:54.049Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34833|2024-08-04T00:26:54.061Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34833</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34833|2024-08-04T00:26:54.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34845|2024-08-04T00:26:54.531Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34845</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14034.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34845|2024-08-04T00:26:54.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34853|2024-08-04T00:26:54.212Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34853</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14013.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34853|2024-08-04T00:26:54.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34840|2024-08-04T00:26:54.173Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34840</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34840|2024-08-04T00:26:54.173Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34841|2024-08-04T00:26:54.119Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34841</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34841|2024-08-04T00:26:54.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34835|2024-08-04T00:26:54.238Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34835</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14015.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34835|2024-08-04T00:26:54.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34846|2024-08-04T00:26:54.602Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34846</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14120.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34846|2024-08-04T00:26:54.602Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34843|2024-08-04T00:26:54.231Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34843</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34843|2024-08-04T00:26:54.231Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34832|2024-08-04T00:26:54.056Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34832</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the delay property. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-13928.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34832|2024-08-04T00:26:54.056Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34839|2024-08-04T00:26:54.214Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34839</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34839|2024-08-04T00:26:54.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34851|2024-08-04T00:26:54.206Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34851</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader 11.0.0.49893. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14016.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34851|2024-08-04T00:26:54.206Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34976|2024-08-04T00:26:55.718Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34976</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14659.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34976|2024-08-04T00:26:55.718Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34971|2024-08-04T00:26:55.656Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34971</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader JPG2000 File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14812.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34971|2024-08-04T00:26:55.656Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34952|2024-08-04T00:26:55.692Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34952</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14729.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34952|2024-08-04T00:26:55.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34975|2024-08-04T00:26:55.673Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34975</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader transitionToState Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the transitionToState method. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15218.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34975|2024-08-04T00:26:55.673Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34973|2024-08-04T00:26:55.940Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34973</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14968.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34973|2024-08-04T00:26:55.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34974|2024-08-04T00:26:55.722Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34974</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15167.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34974|2024-08-04T00:26:55.722Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34948|2024-08-04T00:26:55.744Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34948</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Square Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Square annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14272.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34948|2024-08-04T00:26:55.744Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34950|2024-08-04T00:26:55.651Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34950</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14396.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34950|2024-08-04T00:26:55.651Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34972|2024-08-04T00:26:55.786Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34972</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14975.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34972|2024-08-04T00:26:55.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34951|2024-08-04T00:26:55.649Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34951</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use of Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of a pointer prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14395.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34951|2024-08-04T00:26:55.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34949|2024-08-04T00:26:55.710Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34949</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14273.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34949|2024-08-04T00:26:55.710Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34953|2024-08-04T00:26:55.742Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34953</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use of Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of a pointer prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14658.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34953|2024-08-04T00:26:55.742Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34969|2024-08-04T00:26:55.745Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34969</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14622.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34969|2024-08-04T00:26:55.745Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34970|2024-08-04T00:26:55.785Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34970</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader print Method Use of Externally-Controlled Format String Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the print method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it as a format specifier. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14849.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34970|2024-08-04T00:26:55.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51552|2024-08-02T22:40:32.572Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51552</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Signature Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Signature objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22007.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51552|2024-08-02T22:40:32.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51554|2024-08-02T22:40:32.609Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51554</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Signature Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Signature objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22122.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51554|2024-08-02T22:40:32.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51562|2024-08-02T22:40:32.568Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51562</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22500.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51562|2024-08-02T22:40:32.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51561|2024-08-02T22:40:33.284Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51561</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22283.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51561|2024-08-02T22:40:33.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51553|2024-08-02T22:40:33.962Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51553</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Bookmark Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Bookmark objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22110.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51553|2024-08-02T22:40:33.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51557|2024-08-02T22:40:34.013Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51557</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Doc Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22256.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51557|2024-08-02T22:40:34.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51556|2024-08-02T22:40:33.186Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51556</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Doc Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22255.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51556|2024-08-02T22:40:33.186Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51550|2024-08-02T22:40:33.622Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51550</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader combobox Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of combobox fields. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21870.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51550|2024-08-02T22:40:33.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51551|2024-08-02T22:40:33.285Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51551</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Signature Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Signature objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22003.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51551|2024-08-02T22:40:33.285Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51555|2024-08-02T22:40:33.664Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51555</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22254.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51555|2024-08-02T22:40:33.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51559|2024-08-02T22:40:34.002Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51559</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22258.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51559|2024-08-02T22:40:34.002Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51549|2024-08-02T22:40:32.549Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51549</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21867.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51549|2024-08-02T22:40:32.549Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51558|2024-08-02T22:40:33.320Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51558</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Doc Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22257.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51558|2024-08-02T22:40:33.320Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51560|2024-08-02T22:40:32.586Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51560</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22259.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51560|2024-08-02T22:40:32.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38107|2024-08-02T17:30:14.056Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38107</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21019.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38107|2024-08-02T17:30:14.056Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38114|2024-08-02T17:30:14.051Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38114</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21085.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38114|2024-08-02T17:30:14.051Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38106|2024-08-02T17:30:13.811Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38106</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21018.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38106|2024-08-02T17:30:13.811Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38116|2024-08-02T17:30:14.037Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38116</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21292.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38116|2024-08-02T17:30:14.037Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38119|2024-08-02T17:30:14.023Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38119</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm signature Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of signature fields. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21326.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38119|2024-08-02T17:30:14.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38112|2024-08-02T17:30:14.061Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38112</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader XFA Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21062.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38112|2024-08-02T17:30:14.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38115|2024-08-02T17:30:14.186Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38115</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21256.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38115|2024-08-02T17:30:14.186Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38117|2024-08-02T17:30:13.640Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38117</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21293.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38117|2024-08-02T17:30:13.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38111|2024-08-02T17:30:14.065Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38111</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38111|2024-08-02T17:30:14.065Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38113|2024-08-02T17:30:14.072Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38113</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21083.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38113|2024-08-02T17:30:14.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38108|2024-08-02T17:30:14.098Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38108</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38108|2024-08-02T17:30:14.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38118|2024-08-02T17:30:14.118Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38118</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21325.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38118|2024-08-02T17:30:14.118Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38105|2024-08-02T17:30:14.079Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38105</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21017.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38105|2024-08-02T17:30:14.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38109|2024-08-02T17:30:13.963Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38109</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38109|2024-08-02T17:30:13.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38110|2024-08-02T17:30:14.037Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38110</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38110|2024-08-02T17:30:14.037Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30355|2024-08-02T01:32:07.277Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30355</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22809.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30355|2024-08-02T01:32:07.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30354|2024-08-02T01:32:07.280Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30354</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22808.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30354|2024-08-02T01:32:07.280Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30358|2024-08-02T01:32:07.239Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30358</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm User-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22821.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30358|2024-08-02T01:32:07.239Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30356|2024-08-02T01:32:07.127Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30356</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22811.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30356|2024-08-02T01:32:07.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30345|2024-08-02T01:32:07.060Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30345</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22742.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30345|2024-08-02T01:32:07.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30344|2024-08-02T01:32:07.189Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30344</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Acroforms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22733.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30344|2024-08-02T01:32:07.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30328|2024-08-02T01:32:06.516Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30328</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22633.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30328|2024-08-02T01:32:06.516Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30327|2024-08-02T01:32:07.219Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30327</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader template Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of template objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22632.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30327|2024-08-02T01:32:07.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30332|2024-08-02T01:32:07.224Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30332</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22638.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30332|2024-08-02T01:32:07.224Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30351|2024-08-02T01:32:07.133Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30351</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22799.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30351|2024-08-02T01:32:07.133Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30343|2024-08-02T01:32:07.056Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30343</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22721.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30343|2024-08-02T01:32:07.056Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30367|2024-08-02T01:32:07.304Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30367</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23013.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30367|2024-08-02T01:32:07.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30350|2024-08-02T01:32:07.120Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30350</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22708.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30350|2024-08-02T01:32:07.120Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30326|2024-08-02T01:32:07.046Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30326</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22593.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30326|2024-08-02T01:32:07.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30371|2024-08-02T01:32:07.236Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30371</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23355.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30371|2024-08-02T01:32:07.236Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30334|2024-08-02T01:32:07.162Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30334</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22640.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30334|2024-08-02T01:32:07.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30347|2024-08-02T01:32:07.269Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30347</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22910.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30347|2024-08-02T01:32:07.269Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30360|2024-08-02T01:32:07.215Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30360</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22797.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30360|2024-08-02T01:32:07.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30339|2024-08-02T01:32:07.154Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30339</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Acroforms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22706.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30339|2024-08-02T01:32:07.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30349|2024-08-02T01:32:07.202Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30349</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22912.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30349|2024-08-02T01:32:07.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30363|2024-08-02T01:32:07.199Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30363</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23008.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30363|2024-08-02T01:32:07.199Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30364|2024-08-02T01:32:07.134Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30364</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23009.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30364|2024-08-02T01:32:07.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30342|2024-08-02T01:32:07.107Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30342</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22720.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30342|2024-08-02T01:32:07.107Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30359|2024-08-02T01:32:07.216Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30359</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm 3D Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of 3D objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22888.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30359|2024-08-02T01:32:07.216Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30357|2024-08-02T01:32:07.168Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30357</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Annotation Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22818.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30357|2024-08-02T01:32:07.168Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30323|2024-08-02T01:32:07.024Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30323</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader template Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of template objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22501.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30323|2024-08-02T01:32:07.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30333|2024-08-02T01:32:07.061Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30333</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22639.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30333|2024-08-02T01:32:07.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30322|2024-08-02T01:32:07.277Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30322</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22499.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30322|2024-08-02T01:32:07.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30348|2024-08-02T01:32:07.173Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30348</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22911.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30348|2024-08-02T01:32:07.173Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30338|2024-08-02T01:32:07.141Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30338</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22705.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30338|2024-08-02T01:32:07.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30366|2024-08-02T01:32:07.051Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30366</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23002.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30366|2024-08-02T01:32:07.051Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30346|2024-08-02T01:32:07.288Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30346</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22745.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30346|2024-08-02T01:32:07.288Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30365|2024-08-02T01:32:07.171Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30365</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22947.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30365|2024-08-02T01:32:07.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30361|2024-08-02T01:32:07.130Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30361</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22877.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30361|2024-08-02T01:32:07.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30330|2024-08-02T01:32:07.050Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30330</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22636.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30330|2024-08-02T01:32:07.050Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30336|2024-08-02T01:32:07.160Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30336</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22642.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30336|2024-08-02T01:32:07.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30337|2024-08-02T01:32:07.114Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30337</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Acroforms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22704.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30337|2024-08-02T01:32:07.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30352|2024-08-02T01:32:07.246Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30352</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22800.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30352|2024-08-02T01:32:07.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30325|2024-08-02T01:32:06.921Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30325</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22592.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30325|2024-08-02T01:32:06.921Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30362|2024-08-02T01:32:07.262Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30362</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22798.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30362|2024-08-02T01:32:07.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30353|2024-08-02T01:32:07.264Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30353</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22807.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30353|2024-08-02T01:32:07.264Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30329|2024-08-02T01:32:07.096Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30329</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22634.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30329|2024-08-02T01:32:07.096Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30324|2024-08-02T01:32:07.171Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30324</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22576.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30324|2024-08-02T01:32:07.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30331|2024-08-02T01:32:07.269Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30331</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22637.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30331|2024-08-02T01:32:07.269Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30335|2024-08-02T01:32:07.241Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30335</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22641.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30335|2024-08-02T01:32:07.241Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30340|2024-08-02T01:32:07.160Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30340</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22707.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30340|2024-08-02T01:32:07.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30341|2024-08-02T01:32:07.269Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30341</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22709.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30341|2024-08-02T01:32:07.269Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30328|2024-07-29T14:10:04.490Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30328</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22633.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30328|2024-07-29T14:10:04.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30337|2024-07-23T17:18:52.570Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30337</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Acroforms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22704.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30337|2024-07-23T17:18:52.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27330|2024-07-05T21:07:19.996Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27330</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader XFA Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19476.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27330|2024-07-05T21:07:19.996Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38109|2024-07-05T21:00:40.754Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38109</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38109|2024-07-05T21:00:40.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30357|2024-06-19T19:12:46.634Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30357</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Annotation Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22818.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30357|2024-06-19T19:12:46.634Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30358|2024-06-19T19:18:49.578Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30358</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm User-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22821.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30358|2024-06-19T19:18:49.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30354|2024-06-19T19:13:30.713Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30354</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22808.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30354|2024-06-19T19:13:30.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30349|2024-06-19T19:15:22.729Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30349</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22912.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30349|2024-06-19T19:15:22.729Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30351|2024-06-19T19:14:38.076Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30351</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22799.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30351|2024-06-19T19:14:38.076Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30348|2024-06-19T19:15:49.632Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30348</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22911.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30348|2024-06-19T19:15:49.632Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30335|2024-06-19T19:17:39.928Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30335</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22641.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30335|2024-06-19T19:17:39.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30353|2024-06-19T19:14:24.015Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30353</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22807.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30353|2024-06-19T19:14:24.015Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30336|2024-06-19T19:16:50.237Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30336</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22642.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30336|2024-06-19T19:16:50.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30323|2024-06-19T19:18:20.667Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30323</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader template Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of template objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22501.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30323|2024-06-19T19:18:20.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30359|2024-06-19T19:12:00.656Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30359</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm 3D Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of 3D objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22888.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30359|2024-06-19T19:12:00.656Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30352|2024-06-19T19:14:30.707Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30352</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22800.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30352|2024-06-19T19:14:30.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30345|2024-06-19T17:54:45.884Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30345</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22742.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30345|2024-06-19T17:54:45.884Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30344|2024-06-19T17:54:52.781Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30344</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Acroforms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22733.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30344|2024-06-19T17:54:52.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30346|2024-06-19T17:53:26.170Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30346</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22745.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30346|2024-06-19T17:53:26.170Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30323|2024-04-03T16:21:07.052Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30323</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader template Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of template objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22501.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30323|2024-04-03T16:21:07.052Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30335|2024-04-02T17:48:13.134Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30335</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22641.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30335|2024-04-02T17:48:13.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30362|2024-04-02T20:18:04.752Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30362</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22798.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30362|2024-04-02T20:18:04.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30358|2024-04-02T20:17:11.501Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30358</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm User-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22821.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30358|2024-04-02T20:17:11.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30339|2024-04-02T20:11:25.499Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30339</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Acroforms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22706.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30339|2024-04-02T20:11:25.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30342|2024-04-02T20:12:08.125Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30342</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22720.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30342|2024-04-02T20:12:08.125Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30354|2024-04-02T20:15:26.857Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30354</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22808.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30354|2024-04-02T20:15:26.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30355|2024-06-06T19:19:08.403Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30355</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22809.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30355|2024-06-06T19:19:08.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30343|2024-04-02T20:12:18.694Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30343</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22721.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30343|2024-04-02T20:12:18.694Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30338|2024-04-02T20:11:07.857Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30338</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22705.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30338|2024-04-02T20:11:07.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30359|2024-04-02T20:17:26.652Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30359</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm 3D Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of 3D objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22888.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30359|2024-04-02T20:17:26.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30363|2024-06-04T17:38:39.086Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30363</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23008.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30363|2024-06-04T17:38:39.086Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30334|2024-04-03T16:24:04.350Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30334</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22640.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30334|2024-04-03T16:24:04.350Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30322|2024-04-03T16:20:39.122Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30322</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22499.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30322|2024-04-03T16:20:39.122Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30329|2024-04-03T16:22:37.379Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30329</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22634.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30329|2024-04-03T16:22:37.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30344|2024-04-02T20:12:54.900Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30344</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Acroforms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22733.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30344|2024-04-02T20:12:54.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30352|2024-04-02T20:15:02.950Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30352</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22800.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30352|2024-04-02T20:15:02.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30325|2024-04-03T16:21:32.080Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30325</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22592.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30325|2024-04-03T16:21:32.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30333|2024-04-03T16:23:28.166Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30333</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22639.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30333|2024-04-03T16:23:28.166Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30364|2024-06-04T17:38:50.017Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30364</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23009.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30364|2024-06-04T17:38:50.017Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30348|2024-04-02T20:13:57.509Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30348</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22911.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30348|2024-04-02T20:13:57.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30349|2024-04-02T20:14:09.849Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30349</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22912.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30349|2024-04-02T20:14:09.849Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30365|2024-04-02T20:18:43.270Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30365</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22947.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30365|2024-04-02T20:18:43.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30332|2024-04-03T16:23:12.387Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30332</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22638.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30332|2024-04-03T16:23:12.387Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30324|2024-04-03T16:21:19.087Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30324</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22576.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30324|2024-04-03T16:21:19.087Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30353|2024-04-02T20:15:15.599Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30353</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22807.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30353|2024-04-02T20:15:15.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30345|2024-04-02T20:13:20.386Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30345</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22742.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30345|2024-04-02T20:13:20.386Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30328|2024-04-03T16:22:22.251Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30328</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22633.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30328|2024-04-03T16:22:22.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30350|2024-06-04T17:39:05.203Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30350</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22708.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30350|2024-06-04T17:39:05.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30346|2024-04-02T20:13:32.142Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30346</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22745.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30346|2024-04-02T20:13:32.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30366|2024-04-03T16:24:26.378Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30366</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23002.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30366|2024-04-03T16:24:26.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30331|2024-04-03T16:23:02.442Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30331</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22637.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30331|2024-04-03T16:23:02.442Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30327|2024-04-03T16:22:11.355Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30327</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader template Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of template objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22632.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30327|2024-04-03T16:22:11.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30371|2024-04-02T20:28:59.183Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30371</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23355.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30371|2024-04-02T20:28:59.183Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30326|2024-04-03T16:21:52.538Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30326</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22593.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30326|2024-04-03T16:21:52.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30330|2024-04-03T16:22:48.825Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30330</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22636.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30330|2024-04-03T16:22:48.825Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30367|2024-04-02T20:27:37.842Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30367</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23013.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30367|2024-04-02T20:27:37.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30347|2024-06-04T17:39:27.671Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30347</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22910.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30347|2024-06-04T17:39:27.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30351|2024-04-02T20:14:37.138Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30351</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22799.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30351|2024-04-02T20:14:37.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30360|2024-04-02T20:17:40.995Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30360</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22797.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30360|2024-04-02T20:17:40.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30337|2024-04-02T20:10:46.578Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30337</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Acroforms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22704.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30337|2024-04-02T20:10:46.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30356|2024-06-04T17:39:34.564Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30356</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22811.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30356|2024-06-04T17:39:34.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30340|2024-06-04T17:39:35.832Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30340</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22707.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30340|2024-06-04T17:39:35.832Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30341|2024-06-04T17:39:43.983Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30341</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22709.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30341|2024-06-04T17:39:43.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30357|2024-04-02T20:16:10.523Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30357</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Annotation Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22818.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30357|2024-04-02T20:16:10.523Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30336|2024-04-02T20:10:27.749Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30336</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22642.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30336|2024-04-02T20:10:27.749Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30361|2024-04-02T20:17:53.853Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30361</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22877.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30361|2024-04-02T20:17:53.853Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51553|2024-06-04T17:20:12.759Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51553</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Bookmark Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Bookmark objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22110.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51553|2024-06-04T17:20:12.759Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51549|2024-06-04T17:20:16.146Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51549</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21867.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51549|2024-06-04T17:20:16.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51552|2024-06-04T17:20:23.033Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51552</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Signature Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Signature objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22007.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51552|2024-06-04T17:20:23.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51559|2024-06-04T17:20:24.727Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51559</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22258.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51559|2024-06-04T17:20:24.727Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51555|2024-06-04T17:20:28.565Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51555</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22254.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51555|2024-06-04T17:20:28.565Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51554|2024-06-04T17:20:32.279Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51554</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Signature Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Signature objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22122.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51554|2024-06-04T17:20:32.279Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51562|2024-06-04T17:20:33.899Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51562</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22500.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51562|2024-06-04T17:20:33.899Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51558|2024-06-04T17:20:35.987Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51558</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Doc Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22257.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51558|2024-06-04T17:20:35.987Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51561|2024-06-05T14:53:18.879Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51561</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22283.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51561|2024-06-05T14:53:18.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51557|2024-06-04T17:20:41.017Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51557</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Doc Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22256.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51557|2024-06-04T17:20:41.017Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51556|2024-06-04T17:20:43.112Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51556</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Doc Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22255.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51556|2024-06-04T17:20:43.112Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51560|2024-06-04T17:20:50.400Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51560</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22259.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51560|2024-06-04T17:20:50.400Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51551|2024-06-04T17:20:52.021Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51551</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Signature Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Signature objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22003.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51551|2024-06-04T17:20:52.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51550|2024-06-04T17:21:00.562Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51550</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader combobox Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of combobox fields. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21870.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51550|2024-06-04T17:21:00.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27330|2024-05-03T01:55:53.993Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27330</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader XFA Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19476.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27330|2024-05-03T01:55:53.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27366|2024-06-04T17:24:47.095Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27366</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20225.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27366|2024-06-04T17:24:47.095Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27331|2024-06-04T17:24:47.505Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27331</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19475.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27331|2024-06-04T17:24:47.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27329|2024-06-04T17:24:52.414Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27329</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19477.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27329|2024-06-04T17:24:52.414Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27363|2024-05-03T01:56:14.432Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27363</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader exportXFAData Exposed Dangerous Method Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the exportXFAData method. The application exposes a JavaScript interface that allows writing arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-19697.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27363|2024-05-03T01:56:14.432Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42095|2024-06-04T17:25:02.404Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42095</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21879.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42095|2024-06-04T17:25:02.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42098|2024-06-04T17:25:06.470Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42098</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22037.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42098|2024-06-04T17:25:06.470Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42094|2024-06-04T17:25:09.475Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42094</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21873.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42094|2024-06-04T17:25:09.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42089|2024-06-04T17:25:12.508Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42089</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader templates Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of templates. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21586.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42089|2024-06-04T17:25:12.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42093|2024-06-04T17:25:14.662Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42093</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21869.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42093|2024-06-04T17:25:14.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42092|2024-06-04T17:25:15.981Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42092</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21676.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42092|2024-06-04T17:25:15.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42091|2024-06-04T17:25:22.583Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42091</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader XFA Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21601.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42091|2024-06-04T17:25:22.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42090|2024-06-04T17:25:26.123Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42090</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader XFA Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21596.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42090|2024-06-04T17:25:26.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42097|2024-06-04T17:25:31.872Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42097</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21902.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42097|2024-06-04T17:25:31.872Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42096|2024-06-04T17:25:41.205Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42096</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21880.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42096|2024-06-04T17:25:41.205Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38108|2024-06-04T17:27:58.535Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38108</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38108|2024-06-04T17:27:58.535Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38112|2024-06-04T17:28:01.515Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38112</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader XFA Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21062.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38112|2024-06-04T17:28:01.515Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38105|2024-05-03T01:59:05.909Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38105</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21017.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38105|2024-05-03T01:59:05.909Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38113|2024-06-04T17:28:02.837Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38113</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21083.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38113|2024-06-04T17:28:02.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38109|2024-05-03T01:59:08.997Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38109</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38109|2024-05-03T01:59:08.997Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38114|2024-06-04T17:28:06.726Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38114</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21085.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38114|2024-06-04T17:28:06.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38118|2024-06-04T17:28:09.311Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38118</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21325.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38118|2024-06-04T17:28:09.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38119|2024-06-04T17:28:09.745Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38119</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm signature Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of signature fields. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21326.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38119|2024-06-04T17:28:09.745Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38115|2024-06-04T17:28:12.840Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38115</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21256.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38115|2024-06-04T17:28:12.840Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38116|2024-06-05T20:28:11.116Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38116</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21292.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38116|2024-06-05T20:28:11.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38117|2024-06-04T17:28:21.290Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38117</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21293.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38117|2024-06-04T17:28:21.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38106|2024-06-04T17:28:23.903Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38106</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21018.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38106|2024-06-04T17:28:23.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38110|2024-06-04T17:28:24.328Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38110</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38110|2024-06-04T17:28:24.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38111|2024-05-03T01:59:10.625Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38111</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38111|2024-05-03T01:59:10.625Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38107|2024-06-05T18:12:32.055Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38107</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21019.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38107|2024-06-05T18:12:32.055Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30371|2024-06-19T18:05:06.888Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30371</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23355.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30371|2024-06-19T18:05:06.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30361|2024-06-19T18:07:35.621Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30361</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22877.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30361|2024-06-19T18:07:35.621Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30331|2024-06-19T18:02:58.876Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30331</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22637.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30331|2024-06-19T18:02:58.876Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30367|2024-06-19T18:05:40.989Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30367</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23013.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30367|2024-06-19T18:05:40.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30360|2024-06-19T18:08:06.310Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30360</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22797.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30360|2024-06-19T18:08:06.310Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30362|2024-06-19T18:06:30.872Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30362</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22798.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30362|2024-06-19T18:06:30.872Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30365|2024-06-19T18:06:05.070Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30365</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22947.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30365|2024-06-19T18:06:05.070Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27363|2024-07-01T21:41:13.162Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27363</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader exportXFAData Exposed Dangerous Method Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the exportXFAData method. The application exposes a JavaScript interface that allows writing arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-19697.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27363|2024-07-01T21:41:13.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38111|2024-07-01T21:35:31.040Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38111</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38111|2024-07-01T21:35:31.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30330|2024-07-16T14:04:33.857Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30330</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22636.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30330|2024-07-16T14:04:33.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38105|2024-07-24T19:16:02.192Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38105</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21017.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38105|2024-07-24T19:16:02.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30322|2024-07-31T20:27:08.877Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30322</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22499.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30322|2024-07-31T20:27:08.877Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30334|2024-07-31T20:26:25.787Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30334</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22640.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30334|2024-07-31T20:26:25.787Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27366|2024-08-02T12:09:43.420Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27366</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20225.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27366|2024-08-02T12:09:43.420Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27331|2024-08-02T12:09:43.447Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27331</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19475.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27331|2024-08-02T12:09:43.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27329|2024-08-02T12:09:43.036Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27329</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19477.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27329|2024-08-02T12:09:43.036Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27330|2024-08-02T12:09:42.357Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27330</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader XFA Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19476.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27330|2024-08-02T12:09:42.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27363|2024-08-02T12:09:43.350Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27363</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader exportXFAData Exposed Dangerous Method Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the exportXFAData method. The application exposes a JavaScript interface that allows writing arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-19697.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27363|2024-08-02T12:09:43.350Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42097|2024-08-02T19:16:50.139Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42097</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21902.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42097|2024-08-02T19:16:50.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42089|2024-08-02T19:16:50.107Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42089</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader templates Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of templates. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21586.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42089|2024-08-02T19:16:50.107Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42091|2024-08-02T19:16:50.090Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42091</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader XFA Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21601.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42091|2024-08-02T19:16:50.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42092|2024-08-02T19:16:50.442Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42092</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21676.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42092|2024-08-02T19:16:50.442Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42095|2024-08-02T19:16:50.103Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42095</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21879.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42095|2024-08-02T19:16:50.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42094|2024-08-02T19:16:50.475Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42094</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21873.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42094|2024-08-02T19:16:50.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42090|2024-08-02T19:16:50.096Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42090</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader XFA Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21596.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42090|2024-08-02T19:16:50.096Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42093|2024-08-02T19:16:50.152Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42093</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21869.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42093|2024-08-02T19:16:50.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42096|2024-08-02T19:16:50.393Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42096</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21880.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42096|2024-08-02T19:16:50.393Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42098|2024-08-02T19:16:50.414Z -- foxit -- pdf%20reader</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42098</link>
      <description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22037.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42098|2024-08-02T19:16:50.414Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
