<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Foxit -- PhantomPDF</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/foxit/phantompdf.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Foxit -- PhantomPDF</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:24:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17135|2024-08-05T01:33:17.054Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17135</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.5.0.20723. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DXF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-8775.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17135|2024-08-05T01:33:17.054Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 23:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17142|2024-08-05T01:33:17.260Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17142</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.6.0.25114. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of script within a Keystroke action of a listbox field. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9081.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17142|2024-08-05T01:33:17.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 18:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17145|2024-08-05T01:33:17.267Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17145</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.6.0.25114. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the conversion of DXF files to PDF. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9276.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17145|2024-08-05T01:33:17.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 18:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17695|2024-08-05T10:54:10.727Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17695</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the username property of a TextField. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7145.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17695|2024-08-05T10:54:10.727Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17690|2024-08-05T10:54:10.621Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17690</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the rect property of a Link object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7103.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17690|2024-08-05T10:54:10.621Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17139|2024-08-05T01:33:17.099Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17139</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.5.0.20723. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of Javascript in the HTML2PDF plugin. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-8692.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17139|2024-08-05T01:33:17.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 18:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17694|2024-08-05T10:54:10.852Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17694</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the display property of a button. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7138.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17694|2024-08-05T10:54:10.852Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17698|2024-08-05T10:54:10.755Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17698</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the richValue property of a text field. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7067.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17698|2024-08-05T10:54:10.755Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17693|2024-08-05T10:54:10.567Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17693</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the conversion of HTML files to PDF. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7130.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17693|2024-08-05T10:54:10.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17140|2024-08-05T01:33:17.331Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17140</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.6.0.25114. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the OnFocus event. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9091.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17140|2024-08-05T01:33:17.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 18:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17144|2024-08-05T01:33:17.200Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17144</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.6.0.25114. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the conversion of DWG files to PDF. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9274.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17144|2024-08-05T01:33:17.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 18:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17141|2024-08-05T01:33:17.355Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17141</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.6.0.25114. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of script within a Calculate action of a text field. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9044.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17141|2024-08-05T01:33:17.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 18:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17143|2024-08-05T01:33:17.091Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17143</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.6.0.25114. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DWG files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9273.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17143|2024-08-05T01:33:17.091Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 18:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17687|2024-08-05T10:54:10.555Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17687</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the exportValues property of a radio button. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7068.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17687|2024-08-05T10:54:10.555Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17689|2024-08-05T10:54:10.742Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17689</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the fillColor property of a radio button. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7070.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17689|2024-08-05T10:54:10.742Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17691|2024-08-05T10:54:10.674Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17691</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the conversion of HTML files to PDF. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17691|2024-08-05T10:54:10.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17692|2024-08-05T10:54:10.708Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17692</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the conversion of HTML files to PDF. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7129.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17692|2024-08-05T10:54:10.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17136|2024-08-05T01:33:17.282Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17136</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.5.0.20723. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the conversion of DXF files to PDF. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-8776.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17136|2024-08-05T01:33:17.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 23:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17688|2024-08-05T10:54:10.611Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17688</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the setItems method of a ComboBox. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7069.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17688|2024-08-05T10:54:10.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17701|2024-08-05T10:54:10.696Z -- foxit -- phantompdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17701</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit PhantomPDF 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of JSON objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7132.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17701|2024-08-05T10:54:10.696Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
