<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Foxit -- Reader</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/foxit/reader.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Foxit -- Reader</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34831|2024-08-04T00:26:54.185Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34831</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.1.4.37651. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Document objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-13741.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34831|2024-08-04T00:26:54.185Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6727|2024-08-04T20:31:04.198Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6727</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the XFA remerge method. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7347.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6727|2024-08-04T20:31:04.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 19:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6775|2024-08-04T20:31:04.068Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6775</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.5.0.20723. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the exportValues method within a AcroForm. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-8491.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6775|2024-08-04T20:31:04.068Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 17:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6759|2024-08-04T20:31:04.252Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6759</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.3.10826. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within ConvertToPDF_x86.dll. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7614.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6759|2024-08-04T20:31:04.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10907|2024-08-04T11:14:15.761Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10907</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.1.29511. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of widgets in XFA forms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-10650.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10907|2024-08-04T11:14:15.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6763|2024-08-04T20:31:04.260Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6763</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.4.1.16828. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the ToggleFormsDesign method of the Foxit.FoxitReader.Ctl ActiveX object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7874.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6763|2024-08-04T20:31:04.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8851|2024-08-04T10:12:10.955Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8851</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.0.29455. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of JPG2000 images. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9406.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8851|2024-08-04T10:12:10.955Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 22:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8844|2024-08-04T10:12:10.993Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8844</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.6.0.25114. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPEG files within CovertToPDF. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an integer overflow before writing to memory. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9102.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8844|2024-08-04T10:12:10.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 22:20:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6769|2024-08-04T20:31:04.200Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6769</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.4.1.16828. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the removeField method when processing AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-8165.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6769|2024-08-04T20:31:04.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8849|2024-08-04T10:12:10.992Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8849</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.0.29455. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of JPEG2000 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9413.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8849|2024-08-04T10:12:10.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 22:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6729|2024-08-04T20:31:04.050Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6729</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7423.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6729|2024-08-04T20:31:04.050Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 19:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10906|2024-08-04T11:14:15.879Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10906</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.1.29511. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the resetForm method. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-10614.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10906|2024-08-04T11:14:15.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8850|2024-08-04T10:12:10.964Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8850</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.0.29455. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of JPEG2000 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9415.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8850|2024-08-04T10:12:10.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 22:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6760|2024-08-04T20:31:04.175Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6760</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.4.16811. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within ConvertToPDF_x86.dll. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7694.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6760|2024-08-04T20:31:04.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6728|2024-08-04T20:31:04.065Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6728</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7353.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6728|2024-08-04T20:31:04.065Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 19:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6757|2024-08-04T20:31:04.219Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6757</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.4.16811. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within ConvertToPDF_x86.dll. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7696.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6757|2024-08-04T20:31:04.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6758|2024-08-04T20:31:04.231Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6758</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.4.16811. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within ConvertToPDF_x86.dll. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7701.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6758|2024-08-04T20:31:04.231Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6772|2024-08-04T20:31:04.277Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6772</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 2019.010.20098. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the removeField method when processing AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-8231.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6772|2024-08-04T20:31:04.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6735|2024-08-04T20:31:04.188Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6735</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7355.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6735|2024-08-04T20:31:04.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 19:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6730|2024-08-04T20:31:04.237Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6730</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the popUpMenu method. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7368.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6730|2024-08-04T20:31:04.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 19:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8847|2024-08-04T10:12:10.991Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8847</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.0.29455. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of JPEG2000 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9414.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8847|2024-08-04T10:12:10.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 22:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6770|2024-08-04T20:31:04.192Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6770</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.4.1.16828. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the resetForm method when processing AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-8229.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6770|2024-08-04T20:31:04.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8848|2024-08-04T10:12:10.994Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8848</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.0.29455. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of JPG2000 images. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9407.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8848|2024-08-04T10:12:10.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 22:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6774|2024-08-04T20:31:04.358Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6774</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.4.1.16828. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the deleteItemAt method when processing AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-8295.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6774|2024-08-04T20:31:04.358Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 17:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17417|2024-08-04T13:53:17.421Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17417</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.0.1.35811. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11657.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17417|2024-08-04T13:53:17.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 17:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6773|2024-08-04T20:31:04.217Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6773</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.4.1.16828. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the richValue property of a Field object within AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-8272.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6773|2024-08-04T20:31:04.217Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10900|2024-08-04T11:14:15.637Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10900</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.1.29511. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-10142.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10900|2024-08-04T11:14:15.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6764|2024-08-04T20:31:04.237Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6764</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.4.1.16828. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of XFA Template objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7972.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6764|2024-08-04T20:31:04.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8857|2024-08-04T10:12:10.971Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8857</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.0.29455. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of form Annotation objects within AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9862.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8857|2024-08-04T10:12:10.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 22:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6754|2024-08-04T20:31:04.224Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6754</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.3.10826. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the localFileStorage method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7407.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6754|2024-08-04T20:31:04.224Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8852|2024-08-04T10:12:10.993Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8852</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.0.29455. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of JPEG2000 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9416.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8852|2024-08-04T10:12:10.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 22:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6766|2024-08-04T20:31:04.078Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6766</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.4.1.16828. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the removeField method when processing AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-8162.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6766|2024-08-04T20:31:04.078Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6767|2024-08-04T20:31:04.216Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6767</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.4.1.16828. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the removeField method when processing AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-8163.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6767|2024-08-04T20:31:04.216Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17416|2024-08-04T13:53:17.407Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17416</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.0.0.35798. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPEG2000 images. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11497.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17416|2024-08-04T13:53:17.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 17:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10899|2024-08-04T11:14:15.730Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10899</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.1.29511. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of XFA templates. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-10132.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10899|2024-08-04T11:14:15.730Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6771|2024-08-04T20:31:04.242Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6771</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 2019.010.20098. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the value property of a Field object within AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-8230.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6771|2024-08-04T20:31:04.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6753|2024-08-04T20:31:04.251Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6753</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.3.0.10826. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the Stuff method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an integer overflow before writing to memory. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7561.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6753|2024-08-04T20:31:04.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6755|2024-08-04T20:31:04.144Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6755</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.3.10826. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within ConvertToPDF_x86.dll. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7613.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6755|2024-08-04T20:31:04.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17414|2024-08-04T13:53:17.395Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17414</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.0.0.35798. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the configuration files used by the Foxit Reader Update Service. The issue results from incorrect permissions set on a resource used by the service. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-11229.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17414|2024-08-04T13:53:17.395Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 17:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6768|2024-08-04T20:31:04.246Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6768</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.4.1.16828. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the removeField method when processing AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-8164.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6768|2024-08-04T20:31:04.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6761|2024-08-04T20:31:04.198Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6761</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.4.0.16811. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the XFA CXFA_FFDocView object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7777.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6761|2024-08-04T20:31:04.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27860|2024-08-04T16:25:43.672Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27860</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.0.1.35811. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of XFA templates. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated data structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11727.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27860|2024-08-04T16:25:43.672Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 23:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
