<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Foxit -- Reader</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/foxit/reader.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Foxit -- Reader</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:19:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34831|2024-08-04T00:26:54.185Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34831</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.1.4.37651. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Document objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-13741.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34831|2024-08-04T00:26:54.185Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 15:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10907|2024-08-04T11:14:15.761Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10907</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.1.29511. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of widgets in XFA forms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-10650.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10907|2024-08-04T11:14:15.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8851|2024-08-04T10:12:10.955Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8851</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.0.29455. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of JPG2000 images. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9406.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8851|2024-08-04T10:12:10.955Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 22:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8844|2024-08-04T10:12:10.993Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8844</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.6.0.25114. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPEG files within CovertToPDF. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an integer overflow before writing to memory. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9102.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8844|2024-08-04T10:12:10.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 22:20:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8849|2024-08-04T10:12:10.992Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8849</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.0.29455. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of JPEG2000 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9413.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8849|2024-08-04T10:12:10.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 22:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10906|2024-08-04T11:14:15.879Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10906</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.1.29511. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the resetForm method. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-10614.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10906|2024-08-04T11:14:15.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8850|2024-08-04T10:12:10.964Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8850</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.0.29455. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of JPEG2000 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9415.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8850|2024-08-04T10:12:10.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 22:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8847|2024-08-04T10:12:10.991Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8847</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.0.29455. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of JPEG2000 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9414.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8847|2024-08-04T10:12:10.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 22:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8848|2024-08-04T10:12:10.994Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8848</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.0.29455. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of JPG2000 images. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9407.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8848|2024-08-04T10:12:10.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 22:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17417|2024-08-04T13:53:17.421Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17417</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.0.1.35811. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11657.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17417|2024-08-04T13:53:17.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 17:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10900|2024-08-04T11:14:15.637Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10900</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.1.29511. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-10142.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10900|2024-08-04T11:14:15.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8857|2024-08-04T10:12:10.971Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8857</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.0.29455. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of form Annotation objects within AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9862.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8857|2024-08-04T10:12:10.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 22:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8852|2024-08-04T10:12:10.993Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8852</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.0.29455. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of JPEG2000 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9416.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8852|2024-08-04T10:12:10.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 22:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17416|2024-08-04T13:53:17.407Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17416</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.0.0.35798. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPEG2000 images. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11497.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17416|2024-08-04T13:53:17.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 17:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10899|2024-08-04T11:14:15.730Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10899</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 9.7.1.29511. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of XFA templates. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-10132.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10899|2024-08-04T11:14:15.730Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17414|2024-08-04T13:53:17.395Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17414</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.0.0.35798. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the configuration files used by the Foxit Reader Update Service. The issue results from incorrect permissions set on a resource used by the service. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-11229.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17414|2024-08-04T13:53:17.395Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 17:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27860|2024-08-04T16:25:43.672Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27860</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.0.1.35811. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of XFA templates. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated data structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11727.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27860|2024-08-04T16:25:43.672Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 23:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
