<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Foxit -- Reader</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/foxit/reader.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Foxit -- Reader</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:23:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17649|2024-08-05T10:54:10.199Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17649</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the setAttribute method of a TimeField. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6486.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17649|2024-08-05T10:54:10.199Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17653|2024-08-05T10:54:10.333Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17653</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the resolveNode method of a TimeField. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6503.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17653|2024-08-05T10:54:10.333Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17670|2024-08-05T10:54:10.714Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17670</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the content property of a XFA object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6524.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17670|2024-08-05T10:54:10.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17697|2024-08-05T10:54:10.611Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17697</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of templates. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7170.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17697|2024-08-05T10:54:10.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17702|2024-08-05T10:54:10.761Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17702</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the richValue property of button objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7252.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17702|2024-08-05T10:54:10.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17685|2024-08-05T10:54:10.709Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17685</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6819.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17685|2024-08-05T10:54:10.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17669|2024-08-05T10:54:10.681Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17669</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the name property of a XFA object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6523.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17669|2024-08-05T10:54:10.681Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17660|2024-08-05T10:54:10.545Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17660</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the resetData method of a Host object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6512.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17660|2024-08-05T10:54:10.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17665|2024-08-05T10:54:10.582Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17665</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the currentPage property of a Host object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6519.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17665|2024-08-05T10:54:10.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17654|2024-08-05T10:54:10.432Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17654</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the insertInstance method of a Form object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6504.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17654|2024-08-05T10:54:10.432Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17673|2024-08-05T10:54:10.751Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17673</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the subtype property of a Annotation object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6820.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17673|2024-08-05T10:54:10.751Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17705|2024-08-05T10:54:10.595Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17705</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the display property of CheckBox objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7255.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17705|2024-08-05T10:54:10.595Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17684|2024-08-05T10:54:10.608Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17684</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the isPropertySpecified method. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6470.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17684|2024-08-05T10:54:10.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17639|2024-08-05T10:54:10.267Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17639</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the setElement method. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6475.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17639|2024-08-05T10:54:10.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17650|2024-08-05T10:54:10.457Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17650</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the resolveNodes method of a TimeField. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6487.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17650|2024-08-05T10:54:10.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17636|2024-08-05T10:54:10.290Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17636</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the id property of a aliasNode. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6472.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17636|2024-08-05T10:54:10.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17680|2024-08-05T10:54:10.612Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17680</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the style property of a Field object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6915.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17680|2024-08-05T10:54:10.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17664|2024-08-05T10:54:10.545Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17664</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the isCompatibleNS method of a XFA object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6518.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17664|2024-08-05T10:54:10.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17663|2024-08-05T10:54:10.588Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17663</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the importData method of a Host object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6517.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17663|2024-08-05T10:54:10.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17637|2024-08-05T10:54:10.237Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17637</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the loadXML method. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6473.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17637|2024-08-05T10:54:10.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17678|2024-08-05T10:54:10.564Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17678</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the gotoNamedDest method of a app object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6851.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17678|2024-08-05T10:54:10.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17641|2024-08-05T10:54:10.426Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17641</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the deleteItem method of a TimeField. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6478.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17641|2024-08-05T10:54:10.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17676|2024-08-05T10:54:10.761Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17676</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the removeField property of a app object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6849.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17676|2024-08-05T10:54:10.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17652|2024-08-05T10:54:10.267Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17652</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the mandatory property of a TimeField. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6502.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17652|2024-08-05T10:54:10.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17703|2024-08-05T10:54:10.611Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17703</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the defaultValue property of ComboBox objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7253.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17703|2024-08-05T10:54:10.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17625|2024-08-05T10:54:10.289Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17625</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.1.0.5096. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the setInterval() method. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6438.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17625|2024-08-05T10:54:10.289Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17632|2024-08-05T10:54:10.512Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17632</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the resolveNode event. The issue results from the lack of validation of the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6700.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17632|2024-08-05T10:54:10.512Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17677|2024-08-05T10:54:10.750Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17677</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the mailDoc method of a app object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6850.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17677|2024-08-05T10:54:10.750Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17675|2024-08-05T10:54:10.551Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17675</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the removeDataObject method of a document. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6848.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17675|2024-08-05T10:54:10.551Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17651|2024-08-05T10:54:10.476Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17651</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the getItemState method of a TimeField. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6501.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17651|2024-08-05T10:54:10.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17656|2024-08-05T10:54:10.568Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17656</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the getDisplayItem method of a TimeField. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6506.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17656|2024-08-05T10:54:10.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17633|2024-08-05T10:54:10.272Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17633</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the subject property of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6498.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17633|2024-08-05T10:54:10.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17674|2024-08-05T10:54:10.530Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17674</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the name property of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6845.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17674|2024-08-05T10:54:10.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17640|2024-08-05T10:54:10.278Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17640</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the Form count property. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6477.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17640|2024-08-05T10:54:10.278Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17667|2024-08-05T10:54:10.702Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17667</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the print method of a Host object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6521.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17667|2024-08-05T10:54:10.702Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17634|2024-08-05T10:54:10.266Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17634</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the attachIcon property of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6499.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17634|2024-08-05T10:54:10.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17683|2024-08-05T10:54:10.602Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17683</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the createIcon method of an app object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7163.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17683|2024-08-05T10:54:10.602Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17699|2024-08-05T10:54:10.667Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17699</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7073.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17699|2024-08-05T10:54:10.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17626|2024-08-05T10:54:10.319Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17626</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the Validate events of TextBox objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6439.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17626|2024-08-05T10:54:10.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17648|2024-08-05T10:54:10.399Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17648</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the rotate property of a TimeField. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6485.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17648|2024-08-05T10:54:10.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17662|2024-08-05T10:54:10.711Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17662</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the beep method of a Host object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6514.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17662|2024-08-05T10:54:10.711Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17638|2024-08-05T10:54:10.214Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17638</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the getAttribute method. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6474.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17638|2024-08-05T10:54:10.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17658|2024-08-05T10:54:10.691Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17658</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the respose property of a host object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6509.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17658|2024-08-05T10:54:10.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17635|2024-08-05T10:54:10.270Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17635</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the desc property. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6471.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17635|2024-08-05T10:54:10.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17642|2024-08-05T10:54:10.285Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17642</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the colSpan property of a TimeField. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6479.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17642|2024-08-05T10:54:10.285Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17647|2024-08-05T10:54:10.476Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17647</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the boundItem method of a TimeField. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6484.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17647|2024-08-05T10:54:10.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17681|2024-08-05T10:54:10.676Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17681</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the getPageBox method of a Form. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7141.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17681|2024-08-05T10:54:10.676Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17704|2024-08-05T10:54:10.578Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17704</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the textColor property of RadioButton objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7254.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17704|2024-08-05T10:54:10.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17630|2024-08-05T10:54:10.544Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17630</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.1.0.5096. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the openPlayer method. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6616.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17630|2024-08-05T10:54:10.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17655|2024-08-05T10:54:10.527Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17655</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the moveInstance method of a Form object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6505.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17655|2024-08-05T10:54:10.527Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17672|2024-08-05T10:54:10.565Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17672</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of array indices. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6817.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17672|2024-08-05T10:54:10.565Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17644|2024-08-05T10:54:10.242Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17644</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the addItem method of a TimeField. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6481.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17644|2024-08-05T10:54:10.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17627|2024-08-05T10:54:10.580Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17627</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the XFA mouseUp event. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6455.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17627|2024-08-05T10:54:10.580Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17671|2024-08-05T10:54:10.588Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17671</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the Lower method of a XFA object. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6617.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17671|2024-08-05T10:54:10.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17696|2024-08-05T10:54:10.591Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17696</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the dataObjects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7169.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17696|2024-08-05T10:54:10.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17645|2024-08-05T10:54:10.547Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17645</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the vAlign property of a TimeField. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6482.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17645|2024-08-05T10:54:10.547Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17682|2024-08-05T10:54:10.891Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17682</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the delay property of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7157.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17682|2024-08-05T10:54:10.891Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17657|2024-08-05T10:54:10.706Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17657</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the gotoURL method of a host object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6507.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17657|2024-08-05T10:54:10.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17646|2024-08-05T10:54:10.367Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17646</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the fillColor property of a TimeField. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6483.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17646|2024-08-05T10:54:10.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17666|2024-08-05T10:54:10.690Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17666</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the exportData method of a host object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6520.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17666|2024-08-05T10:54:10.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17686|2024-08-05T10:54:10.548Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17686</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of BMP images. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6844.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17686|2024-08-05T10:54:10.548Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17629|2024-08-05T10:54:10.212Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17629</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.1.0.5096. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of template objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6614.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17629|2024-08-05T10:54:10.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17643|2024-08-05T10:54:10.295Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17643</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the editValue property of a TimeField. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6480.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17643|2024-08-05T10:54:10.295Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17661|2024-08-05T10:54:10.561Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17661</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the messageBox method of a Host object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6513.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17661|2024-08-05T10:54:10.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17631|2024-08-05T10:54:10.300Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17631</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the removeInstance event. The issue results from the lack of validation of the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6500.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17631|2024-08-05T10:54:10.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17668|2024-08-05T10:54:10.596Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17668</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the removeAttribute method of a XFA object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6522.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17668|2024-08-05T10:54:10.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17679|2024-08-05T10:54:10.620Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17679</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF documents. By manipulating a document's elements, an attacker can cause a pointer to be reused after it has been freed. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6890.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17679|2024-08-05T10:54:10.620Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17659|2024-08-05T10:54:10.583Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17659</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Foxit Reader 9.2.0.9297. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the title property of a Host object. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-6511.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17659|2024-08-05T10:54:10.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
