<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Foxit -- Reader</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/foxit/reader.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Foxit -- Reader</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31444|2024-08-03T22:55:53.815Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31444</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.1.1.37576. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of U3D objects embedded in PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-13241.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31444|2024-08-03T22:55:53.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 20:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31446|2024-08-03T22:55:53.954Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31446</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.1.1.37576. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of U3D objects embedded in PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-13245.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31446|2024-08-03T22:55:53.954Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 20:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31448|2024-08-03T22:55:53.820Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31448</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.1.1.37576. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of U3D objects embedded in PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-13273.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31448|2024-08-03T22:55:53.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 20:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31452|2024-08-03T22:55:53.778Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31452</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.1.1.37576. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of XFA forms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated data structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-13091.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31452|2024-08-03T22:55:53.778Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 20:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31445|2024-08-03T22:55:53.782Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31445</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.1.1.37576. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of U3D objects embedded in PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-13244.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31445|2024-08-03T22:55:53.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 20:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31449|2024-08-03T22:55:53.786Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31449</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.1.1.37576. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of U3D objects embedded in PDF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing further free operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-13280.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31449|2024-08-03T22:55:53.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 20:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31442|2024-08-03T22:55:53.813Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31442</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.1.1.37576. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of U3D objects in PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated data structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-13239.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31442|2024-08-03T22:55:53.813Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 20:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31451|2024-08-03T22:55:53.794Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31451</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.1.1.37576. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-13089.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31451|2024-08-03T22:55:53.794Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 20:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31443|2024-08-03T22:55:53.792Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31443</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.1.1.37576. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of U3D objects embedded in PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-13240.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31443|2024-08-03T22:55:53.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 20:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31441|2024-08-03T22:55:53.792Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31441</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.1.1.37576. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-13101.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31441|2024-08-03T22:55:53.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 20:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31447|2024-08-03T22:55:53.604Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31447</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.1.1.37576. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of U3D objects embedded in PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-13269.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31447|2024-08-03T22:55:53.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 20:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31450|2024-08-03T22:55:53.783Z -- foxit -- reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31450</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Reader 10.1.1.37576. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of XFA forms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-13084.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31450|2024-08-03T22:55:53.783Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 20:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
