<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Foxit -- Studio Photo</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/foxit/studio%20photo.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Foxit -- Studio Photo</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31438|2024-08-03T22:55:53.727Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31438</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.931. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of PSP files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-12443.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31438|2024-08-03T22:55:53.727Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 16:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31434|2024-08-03T22:55:53.828Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31434</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.931. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-12377.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31434|2024-08-03T22:55:53.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 16:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31436|2024-08-03T22:55:53.733Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31436</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.931. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of SGI files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-12376.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31436|2024-08-03T22:55:53.733Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 16:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31433|2024-08-03T22:55:53.783Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31433</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.931. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of ARW files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated data structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-12333.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31433|2024-08-03T22:55:53.783Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 16:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31435|2024-08-03T22:55:53.779Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31435</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.931. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CMP files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-12331.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31435|2024-08-03T22:55:53.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 16:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31437|2024-08-03T22:55:53.891Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31437</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.931. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-12384.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31437|2024-08-03T22:55:53.891Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 16:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
