<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Foxit -- Studio Photo</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/foxit/studio%20photo.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Foxit -- Studio Photo</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 15:22:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8878|2024-08-04T10:12:10.958Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8878</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.916. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of PSD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9625.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8878|2024-08-04T10:12:10.958Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 18:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17429|2024-08-04T13:53:17.516Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17429</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of CMP files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11337.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17429|2024-08-04T13:53:17.516Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:46:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17423|2024-08-04T13:53:17.495Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17423</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of ARW files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11196.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17423|2024-08-04T13:53:17.495Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17421|2024-08-04T13:53:17.451Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17421</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NEF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11194.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17421|2024-08-04T13:53:17.451Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17425|2024-08-04T13:53:17.445Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17425</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11259.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17425|2024-08-04T13:53:17.445Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17432|2024-08-04T13:53:17.377Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17432</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CR2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11335.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17432|2024-08-04T13:53:17.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17435|2024-08-04T13:53:17.463Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17435</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CR2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11358.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17435|2024-08-04T13:53:17.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8870|2024-08-04T10:12:10.954Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8870</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.916. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of TIF files from the GetTIFPalette method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9931.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8870|2024-08-04T10:12:10.954Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 20:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17424|2024-08-04T13:53:17.353Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17424</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EZI files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11247.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17424|2024-08-04T13:53:17.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:46:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17430|2024-08-04T13:53:17.491Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17430</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CR2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11332.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17430|2024-08-04T13:53:17.491Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8869|2024-08-04T10:12:11.022Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8869</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.916. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9881.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8869|2024-08-04T10:12:11.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 20:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17433|2024-08-04T13:53:17.492Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17433</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CMP files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11356.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17433|2024-08-04T13:53:17.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17431|2024-08-04T13:53:17.487Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17431</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CR2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11333.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17431|2024-08-04T13:53:17.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17427|2024-08-04T13:53:17.377Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17427</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of NEF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11334.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17427|2024-08-04T13:53:17.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17434|2024-08-04T13:53:17.412Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17434</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of ARW files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11357.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17434|2024-08-04T13:53:17.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8883|2024-08-04T10:12:10.948Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8883</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.916. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of EPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9880.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8883|2024-08-04T10:12:10.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 18:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8882|2024-08-04T10:12:10.989Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8882</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.916. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the PSD files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of a pointer prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9811.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8882|2024-08-04T10:12:10.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 18:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8879|2024-08-04T10:12:10.980Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8879</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.916. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of PSD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9626.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8879|2024-08-04T10:12:10.980Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 18:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17419|2024-08-04T13:53:17.433Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17419</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NEF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11192.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17419|2024-08-04T13:53:17.433Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17420|2024-08-04T13:53:17.388Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17420</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NEF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11193.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17420|2024-08-04T13:53:17.388Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15630|2024-08-04T13:22:29.976Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15630</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of PNG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-10977.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15630|2024-08-04T13:22:29.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 20:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17404|2024-08-04T13:53:16.964Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17404</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of PSD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11191.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17404|2024-08-04T13:53:16.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 20:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17422|2024-08-04T13:53:17.479Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17422</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of EPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11195.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17422|2024-08-04T13:53:17.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17428|2024-08-04T13:53:17.416Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17428</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of CMP files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11336.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17428|2024-08-04T13:53:17.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:46:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8881|2024-08-04T10:12:10.989Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8881</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.916. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9774.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8881|2024-08-04T10:12:10.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 18:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17436|2024-08-04T13:53:17.488Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17436</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CMP files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11432.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17436|2024-08-04T13:53:17.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17403|2024-08-04T13:53:16.760Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17403</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of PSD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11003.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17403|2024-08-04T13:53:16.760Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 20:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15629|2024-08-04T13:22:30.591Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15629</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-10764.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15629|2024-08-04T13:22:30.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 20:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8877|2024-08-04T10:12:11.062Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8877</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.916. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of PSD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9624.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8877|2024-08-04T10:12:11.062Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 18:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17418|2024-08-04T13:53:17.441Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17418</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of EZIX files. A crafted id in a channel element can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11197.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17418|2024-08-04T13:53:17.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17426|2024-08-04T13:53:17.452Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17426</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.922. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of CR2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-11230.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17426|2024-08-04T13:53:17.452Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8880|2024-08-04T10:12:10.964Z -- foxit -- studio%20photo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8880</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit Studio Photo 3.6.6.916. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9773.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8880|2024-08-04T10:12:10.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 18:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
