<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Xen -- Xen</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/xen/xen.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Xen -- Xen</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46837|2024-01-05T16:36:10.881Z -- xen -- xen
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-46837</link>
      <description>Arm provides multiple helpers to clean &amp; invalidate the cache
for a given region.  This is, for instance, used when allocating
guest memory to ensure any writes (such as the ones during scrubbing)
have reached memory before handing over the page to a guest.

Unfortunately, the arithmetics in the helpers can overflow and would
then result to skip the cache cleaning/invalidation.  Therefore there
is no guarantee when all the writes will reach the memory.

This undefined behavior was meant to be addressed by XSA-437, but the
approach was not sufficient.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46837|2024-01-05T16:36:10.881Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46840|2024-03-20T10:40:18.050Z -- xen -- xen
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-46840</link>
      <description>Incorrect placement of a preprocessor directive in source code results
in logic that doesn't operate as intended when support for HVM guests is
compiled out of Xen.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46840|2024-03-20T10:40:18.050Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 10:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46841|2024-06-04T17:22:15.607Z -- xen -- xen
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-46841</link>
      <description>Recent x86 CPUs offer functionality named Control-flow Enforcement
Technology (CET).  A sub-feature of this are Shadow Stacks (CET-SS).
CET-SS is a hardware feature designed to protect against Return Oriented
Programming attacks. When enabled, traditional stacks holding both data
and return addresses are accompanied by so called "shadow stacks",
holding little more than return addresses.  Shadow stacks aren't
writable by normal instructions, and upon function returns their
contents are used to check for possible manipulation of a return address
coming from the traditional stack.

In particular certain memory accesses need intercepting by Xen.  In
various cases the necessary emulation involves kind of replaying of
the instruction.  Such replaying typically involves filling and then
invoking of a stub.  Such a replayed instruction may raise an
exceptions, which is expected and dealt with accordingly.

Unfortunately the interaction of both of the above wasn't right:
Recovery involves removal of a call frame from the (traditional) stack.
The counterpart of this operation for the shadow stack was missing.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46841|2024-06-04T17:22:15.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 10:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46836|2024-01-05T16:34:59.036Z -- xen -- xen
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-46836</link>
      <description>The fixes for XSA-422 (Branch Type Confusion) and XSA-434 (Speculative
Return Stack Overflow) are not IRQ-safe.  It was believed that the
mitigations always operated in contexts with IRQs disabled.

However, the original XSA-254 fix for Meltdown (XPTI) deliberately left
interrupts enabled on two entry paths; one unconditionally, and one
conditionally on whether XPTI was active.

As BTC/SRSO and Meltdown affect different CPU vendors, the mitigations
are not active together by default.  Therefore, there is a race
condition whereby a malicious PV guest can bypass BTC/SRSO protections
and launch a BTC/SRSO attack against Xen.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46836|2024-01-05T16:34:59.036Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46835|2024-01-05T16:34:49.531Z -- xen -- xen
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-46835</link>
      <description>The current setup of the quarantine page tables assumes that the
quarantine domain (dom_io) has been initialized with an address width
of DEFAULT_DOMAIN_ADDRESS_WIDTH (48) and hence 4 page table levels.

However dom_io being a PV domain gets the AMD-Vi IOMMU page tables
levels based on the maximum (hot pluggable) RAM address, and hence on
systems with no RAM above the 512GB mark only 3 page-table levels are
configured in the IOMMU.

On systems without RAM above the 512GB boundary
amd_iommu_quarantine_init() will setup page tables for the scratch
page with 4 levels, while the IOMMU will be configured to use 3 levels
only, resulting in the last page table directory (PDE) effectively
becoming a page table entry (PTE), and hence a device in quarantine
mode gaining write access to the page destined to be a PDE.

Due to this page table level mismatch, the sink page the device gets
read/write access to is no longer cleared between device assignment,
possibly leading to data leaks.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46835|2024-01-05T16:34:49.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46842|2024-06-04T17:22:13.355Z -- xen -- xen
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-46842</link>
      <description>Unlike 32-bit PV guests, HVM guests may switch freely between 64-bit and
other modes.  This in particular means that they may set registers used
to pass 32-bit-mode hypercall arguments to values outside of the range
32-bit code would be able to set them to.

When processing of hypercalls takes a considerable amount of time,
the hypervisor may choose to invoke a hypercall continuation.  Doing so
involves putting (perhaps updated) hypercall arguments in respective
registers.  For guests not running in 64-bit mode this further involves
a certain amount of translation of the values.

Unfortunately internal sanity checking of these translated values
assumes high halves of registers to always be clear when invoking a
hypercall.  When this is found not to be the case, it triggers a
consistency check in the hypervisor and causes a crash.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46842|2024-06-04T17:22:13.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46839|2024-03-20T10:35:52.532Z -- xen -- xen
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-46839</link>
      <description>PCI devices can make use of a functionality called phantom functions,
that when enabled allows the device to generate requests using the IDs
of functions that are otherwise unpopulated.  This allows a device to
extend the number of outstanding requests.

Such phantom functions need an IOMMU context setup, but failure to
setup the context is not fatal when the device is assigned.  Not
failing device assignment when such failure happens can lead to the
primary device being assigned to a guest, while some of the phantom
functions are assigned to a different domain.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46839|2024-03-20T10:35:52.532Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 10:35:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34325|2024-01-05T16:31:09.660Z -- xen -- xen
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34325</link>
      <description>
[This CNA information record relates to multiple CVEs; the
text explains which aspects/vulnerabilities correspond to which CVE.]

libfsimage contains parsing code for several filesystems, most of them based on
grub-legacy code.  libfsimage is used by pygrub to inspect guest disks.

Pygrub runs as the same user as the toolstack (root in a priviledged domain).

At least one issue has been reported to the Xen Security Team that allows an
attacker to trigger a stack buffer overflow in libfsimage.  After further
analisys the Xen Security Team is no longer confident in the suitability of
libfsimage when run against guest controlled input with super user priviledges.

In order to not affect current deployments that rely on pygrub patches are
provided in the resolution section of the advisory that allow running pygrub in
deprivileged mode.

CVE-2023-4949 refers to the original issue in the upstream grub
project ("An attacker with local access to a system (either through a
disk or external drive) can present a modified XFS partition to
grub-legacy in such a way to exploit a memory corruption in grub’s XFS
file system implementation.")  CVE-2023-34325 refers specifically to
the vulnerabilities in Xen's copy of libfsimage, which is decended
from a very old version of grub.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34325|2024-01-05T16:31:09.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34328|2024-01-05T16:34:11.100Z -- xen -- xen
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34328</link>
      <description>
[This CNA information record relates to multiple CVEs; the
text explains which aspects/vulnerabilities correspond to which CVE.]

AMD CPUs since ~2014 have extensions to normal x86 debugging functionality.
Xen supports guests using these extensions.

Unfortunately there are errors in Xen's handling of the guest state, leading
to denials of service.

 1) CVE-2023-34327 - An HVM vCPU can end up operating in the context of
    a previous vCPUs debug mask state.

 2) CVE-2023-34328 - A PV vCPU can place a breakpoint over the live GDT.
    This allows the PV vCPU to exploit XSA-156 / CVE-2015-8104 and lock
    up the CPU entirely.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34328|2024-01-05T16:34:11.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34323|2024-01-05T16:30:32.305Z -- xen -- xen
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34323</link>
      <description>When a transaction is committed, C Xenstored will first check
the quota is correct before attempting to commit any nodes.  It would
be possible that accounting is temporarily negative if a node has
been removed outside of the transaction.

Unfortunately, some versions of C Xenstored are assuming that the
quota cannot be negative and are using assert() to confirm it.  This
will lead to C Xenstored crash when tools are built without -DNDEBUG
(this is the default).
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34323|2024-01-05T16:30:32.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34322|2024-01-05T16:18:01.363Z -- xen -- xen
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34322</link>
      <description>For migration as well as to work around kernels unaware of L1TF (see
XSA-273), PV guests may be run in shadow paging mode.  Since Xen itself
needs to be mapped when PV guests run, Xen and shadowed PV guests run
directly the respective shadow page tables.  For 64-bit PV guests this
means running on the shadow of the guest root page table.

In the course of dealing with shortage of memory in the shadow pool
associated with a domain, shadows of page tables may be torn down.  This
tearing down may include the shadow root page table that the CPU in
question is presently running on.  While a precaution exists to
supposedly prevent the tearing down of the underlying live page table,
the time window covered by that precaution isn't large enough.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34322|2024-01-05T16:18:01.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34321|2024-01-05T16:17:17.379Z -- xen -- xen
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34321</link>
      <description>Arm provides multiple helpers to clean &amp; invalidate the cache
for a given region.  This is, for instance, used when allocating
guest memory to ensure any writes (such as the ones during scrubbing)
have reached memory before handing over the page to a guest.

Unfortunately, the arithmetics in the helpers can overflow and would
then result to skip the cache cleaning/invalidation.  Therefore there
is no guarantee when all the writes will reach the memory.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34321|2024-01-05T16:17:17.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34320|2023-12-08T20:54:06.993Z -- xen -- xen
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34320</link>
      <description>Cortex-A77 cores (r0p0 and r1p0) are affected by erratum 1508412
where software, under certain circumstances, could deadlock a core
due to the execution of either a load to device or non-cacheable memory,
and either a store exclusive or register read of the Physical
Address Register (PAR_EL1) in close proximity.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34320|2023-12-08T20:54:06.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 20:54:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34327|2024-01-05T16:34:10.958Z -- xen -- xen
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34327</link>
      <description>
[This CNA information record relates to multiple CVEs; the
text explains which aspects/vulnerabilities correspond to which CVE.]

AMD CPUs since ~2014 have extensions to normal x86 debugging functionality.
Xen supports guests using these extensions.

Unfortunately there are errors in Xen's handling of the guest state, leading
to denials of service.

 1) CVE-2023-34327 - An HVM vCPU can end up operating in the context of
    a previous vCPUs debug mask state.

 2) CVE-2023-34328 - A PV vCPU can place a breakpoint over the live GDT.
    This allows the PV vCPU to exploit XSA-156 / CVE-2015-8104 and lock
    up the CPU entirely.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34327|2024-01-05T16:34:10.958Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34326|2024-01-05T16:30:57.225Z -- xen -- xen
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34326</link>
      <description>The caching invalidation guidelines from the AMD-Vi specification (48882—Rev
3.07-PUB—Oct 2022) is incorrect on some hardware, as devices will malfunction
(see stale DMA mappings) if some fields of the DTE are updated but the IOMMU
TLB is not flushed.

Such stale DMA mappings can point to memory ranges not owned by the guest, thus
allowing access to unindented memory regions.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34326|2024-01-05T16:30:57.225Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31142|2024-06-04T17:36:07.065Z -- xen -- xen
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31142</link>
      <description>Because of a logical error in XSA-407 (Branch Type Confusion), the
mitigation is not applied properly when it is intended to be used.
XSA-434 (Speculative Return Stack Overflow) uses the same
infrastructure, so is equally impacted.

For more details, see:
  https://xenbits.xen.org/xsa/advisory-407.html
  https://xenbits.xen.org/xsa/advisory-434.html
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31142|2024-06-04T17:36:07.065Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2193|2024-03-15T21:25:07.075Z -- xen -- xen
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2193</link>
      <description>A Speculative Race Condition (SRC) vulnerability that impacts modern CPU architectures supporting speculative execution (related to Spectre V1) has been disclosed. An unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to disclose arbitrary data from the CPU using race conditions to access the speculative executable code paths.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2193|2024-03-15T21:25:07.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 18:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
