<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for FriendsOfSymfony1 -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/friendsofsymfony1/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for FriendsOfSymfony1 -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28859|2024-03-15T22:32:56.078Z -- friendsofsymfony1 -- symfony1
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28859</link>
      <description>Symfony1 is a community fork of symfony 1.4 with DIC, form enhancements, latest Swiftmailer, better performance, composer compatible and PHP 8 support. Symfony 1 has a gadget chain due to vulnerable Swift Mailer dependency that would enable an attacker to get remote code execution if a developer unserialize user input in his project. This vulnerability present no direct threat but is a vector that will enable remote code execution if a developper deserialize user untrusted data. Symfony 1 depends on Swift Mailer which is bundled by default in vendor directory in the default installation since 1.3.0. Swift Mailer classes implement some `__destruct()` methods. These methods are called when php destroys the object in memory. However, it is possible to include any object type in `$this-&gt;_keys` to make PHP access to another array/object properties than intended by the developer. In particular, it is possible to abuse the array access which is triggered on foreach($this-&gt;_keys ...) for any class implementing ArrayAccess interface. This may allow an attacker to execute any PHP command which leads to remote code execution. This issue has been addressed in version 1.5.18. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28859|2024-03-15T22:32:56.078Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 22:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28861|2024-03-22T16:43:18.453Z -- friendsofsymfony1 -- symfony1
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28861</link>
      <description>Symfony 1 is a community-driven fork of the 1.x branch of Symfony, a PHP framework for web projects. Starting in version 1.1.0 and prior to version 1.5.19, Symfony 1 has a gadget chain due to dangerous deserialization in `sfNamespacedParameterHolder` class that would enable an attacker to get remote code execution if a developer deserializes user input in their project. Version 1.5.19 contains a patch for the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28861|2024-03-22T16:43:18.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 16:43:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
