<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Filseclab -- Twister Antivirus</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/filseclab/twister%20antivirus.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Filseclab -- Twister Antivirus</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:23:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1443|2024-08-02T05:49:11.356Z -- filseclab -- twister%20antivirus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1443</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Filseclab Twister Antivirus 8. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function 0x80112053 in the library fildds.sys of the component IoControlCode Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223288.
In Filseclab Twister Antivirus 8 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um die Funktion 0x80112053 in der Bibliothek fildds.sys der Komponente IoControlCode Handler. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1443|2024-08-02T05:49:11.356Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 06:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1444|2024-08-02T05:49:11.414Z -- filseclab -- twister%20antivirus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1444</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Filseclab Twister Antivirus 8. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function 0x8011206B in the library fildds.sys of the component IoControlCode Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-223289 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Filseclab Twister Antivirus 8 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um die Funktion 0x8011206B in der Bibliothek fildds.sys der Komponente IoControlCode Handler. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1444|2024-08-02T05:49:11.414Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 06:33:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0907|2024-08-02T05:24:34.867Z -- filseclab -- twister%20antivirus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0907</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Filseclab Twister Antivirus 8.17. Affected by this issue is the function 0x220017 in the library ffsmon.sys of the component IoControlCode Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-221456.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Filseclab Twister Antivirus 8.17 entdeckt. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion 0x220017 in der Bibliothek ffsmon.sys der Komponente IoControlCode Handler. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0907|2024-08-02T05:24:34.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 07:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1445|2024-08-02T05:49:11.613Z -- filseclab -- twister%20antivirus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1445</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Filseclab Twister Antivirus 8. Affected is the function 0x80112053 in the library fildds.sys of the component IoControlCode Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-223290 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Filseclab Twister Antivirus 8 entdeckt. Es betrifft die Funktion 0x80112053 in der Bibliothek fildds.sys der Komponente IoControlCode Handler. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff hat dabei lokal zu erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1445|2024-08-02T05:49:11.613Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 06:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1096|2024-03-08T22:03:21.793Z -- filseclab -- twister%20antivirus</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1096</link>
      <description>Twister Antivirus v8.17 is vulnerable to a Denial of Service vulnerability by triggering the 0x80112067, 0x801120CB 0x801120CC 0x80112044, 0x8011204B, 0x8011204F, 0x80112057, 0x8011205B, 0x8011205F, 0x80112063, 0x8011206F, 0x80112073, 0x80112077, 0x80112078, 0x8011207C and 0x80112080 IOCTL codes of the fildds.sys driver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1096|2024-03-08T22:03:21.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1140|2024-02-13T15:05:22.732Z -- filseclab -- twister%20antivirus</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1140</link>
      <description>Twister Antivirus v8.17 is vulnerable to an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability by triggering the 0x801120B8 IOCTL code of the filmfd.sys driver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1140|2024-02-13T15:05:22.732Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1140|2024-08-01T18:26:30.606Z -- filseclab -- twister%20antivirus</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1140</link>
      <description>Twister Antivirus v8.17 is vulnerable to an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability by triggering the 0x801120B8 IOCTL code of the filmfd.sys driver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1140|2024-08-01T18:26:30.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1096|2024-08-01T18:26:30.499Z -- filseclab -- twister%20antivirus</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1096</link>
      <description>Twister Antivirus v8.17 is vulnerable to a Denial of Service vulnerability by triggering the 0x80112067, 0x801120CB 0x801120CC 0x80112044, 0x8011204B, 0x8011204F, 0x80112057, 0x8011205B, 0x8011205F, 0x80112063, 0x8011206F, 0x80112073, 0x80112077, 0x80112078, 0x8011207C and 0x80112080 IOCTL codes of the fildds.sys driver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1096|2024-08-01T18:26:30.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
