<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for tailscale -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tailscale/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for tailscale -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41924|2024-08-03T12:56:38.505Z -- tailscale -- tailscale
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41924</link>
      <description>A vulnerability identified in the Tailscale Windows client allows a malicious website to reconfigure the Tailscale daemon `tailscaled`, which can then be used to remotely execute code. In the Tailscale Windows client, the local API was bound to a local TCP socket, and communicated with the Windows client GUI in cleartext with no Host header verification. This allowed an attacker-controlled website visited by the node to rebind DNS to an attacker-controlled DNS server, and then make local API requests in the client, including changing the coordination server to an attacker-controlled coordination server. An attacker-controlled coordination server can send malicious URL responses to the client, including pushing executables or installing an SMB share. These allow the attacker to remotely execute code on the node. All Windows clients prior to version v.1.32.3 are affected. If you are running Tailscale on Windows, upgrade to v1.32.3 or later to remediate the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41924|2024-08-03T12:56:38.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41925|2024-08-03T12:56:38.535Z -- tailscale -- tailscale
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41925</link>
      <description>A vulnerability identified in the Tailscale client allows a malicious website to access the peer API, which can then be used to access Tailscale environment variables. In the Tailscale client, the peer API was vulnerable to DNS rebinding. This allowed an attacker-controlled website visited by the node to rebind DNS for the peer API to an attacker-controlled DNS server, and then making peer API requests in the client, including accessing the node’s Tailscale environment variables. An attacker with access to the peer API on a node could use that access to read the node’s environment variables, including any credentials or secrets stored in environment variables. This may include Tailscale authentication keys, which could then be used to add new nodes to the user’s tailnet. The peer API access could also be used to learn of other nodes in the tailnet or send files via Taildrop. All Tailscale clients prior to version v1.32.3 are affected. Upgrade to v1.32.3 or later to remediate the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41925|2024-08-03T12:56:38.535Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
