<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for F5 -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/f5/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for F5 -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 16:24:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34851|2024-08-03T09:22:10.730Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34851</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 17.0.x before 17.0.0.1, 16.1.x before 16.1.3.1, 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, 14.1.x before 14.1.5.1, and all versions of 13.1.x, and BIG-IQ Centralized Management all versions of 8.x, an authenticated attacker may cause iControl SOAP to become unavailable through undisclosed requests. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34851|2024-08-03T09:22:10.730Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41800|2024-08-03T12:56:38.173Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41800</link>
      <description>
In all versions of BIG-IP, when running in Appliance mode, an authenticated user assigned the Administrator role may be able to bypass Appliance mode restrictions, utilizing an undisclosed iControl REST endpoint. A successful exploit can allow the attacker to cross a security boundary.  

Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41800|2024-08-03T12:56:38.173Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 03:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41624|2024-08-03T12:49:43.526Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41624</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP versions 17.0.x before 17.0.0.1, 16.1.x before 16.1.3.2, 15.1.x before 15.1.7, 14.1.x before 14.1.5.2, and 13.1.x before 13.1.5.1, when a sideband iRule is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause an increase in memory resource utilization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41624|2024-08-03T12:49:43.526Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27878|2024-08-03T05:41:10.197Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27878</link>
      <description>On all versions of 16.1.x, 15.1.x, 14.1.x, 13.1.x, 12.1.x, and 11.6.x of F5 BIG-IP, and F5 BIG-IP Guided Configuration (GC) all versions prior to 9.0, a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of the BIG-IP Configuration utility that allows an attacker to execute JavaScript in the context of the currently logged-in user. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27878|2024-08-03T05:41:10.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35243|2024-08-03T09:29:17.511Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35243</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 16.1.x before 16.1.3, 15.1.x before 15.1.5.1, 14.1.x before 14.1.5, and all versions of 13.1.x, when running in Appliance mode, an authenticated user assigned the Administrator role may be able to bypass Appliance mode restrictions, using an undisclosed iControl REST endpoint. A successful exploit can allow the attacker to cross a security boundary. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35243|2024-08-03T09:29:17.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29263|2024-08-03T06:17:54.512Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20apm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29263</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP APM 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, and all versions of 12.1.x and 11.6.x, as well as F5 BIG-IP APM Clients 7.x versions prior to 7.2.1.5, the BIG-IP Edge Client Component Installer Service does not use best practice while saving temporary files. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29263|2024-08-03T06:17:54.512Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-25990|2024-08-03T04:56:36.938Z -- f5 -- f5os-a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25990</link>
      <description>On 1.0.x versions prior to 1.0.1, systems running F5OS-A software may expose certain registry ports externally. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-25990|2024-08-03T04:56:36.938Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26370|2024-08-03T05:03:32.883Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26370</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5, and 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, when a Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) message routing framework (MRF) application layer gateway (ALG) profile is configured on a Message Routing virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26370|2024-08-03T05:03:32.883Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34844|2024-08-03T09:22:10.818Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34844</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 16.1.x before 16.1.3.1 and 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, and all versions of BIG-IQ 8.x, when the Data Plane Development Kit (DPDK)/Elastic Network Adapter (ENA) driver is used with BIG-IP or BIG-IQ on Amazon Web Services (AWS) systems, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. Successful exploitation relies on conditions outside of the attacker's control. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34844|2024-08-03T09:22:10.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35241|2024-08-03T09:29:17.434Z -- f5 -- nginx%20instance%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35241</link>
      <description>In versions 2.x before 2.3.1 and all versions of 1.x, when NGINX Instance Manager is in use, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in disk resource utilization. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35241|2024-08-03T09:29:17.434Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29473|2024-08-03T06:26:05.160Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29473</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, and 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, when an IPSec ALG profile is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed responses can cause Traffic Management Microkernel(TMM) to terminate. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29473|2024-08-03T06:26:05.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41833|2024-08-03T12:56:38.022Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41833</link>
      <description>In all BIG-IP 13.1.x versions, when an iRule containing the HTTP::collect command is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41833|2024-08-03T12:56:38.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27495|2024-08-03T05:32:57.950Z -- f5 -- nginx%20service%20mesh
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27495</link>
      <description>On all versions 1.3.x (fixed in 1.4.0) NGINX Service Mesh control plane endpoints are exposed to the cluster overlay network. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27495|2024-08-03T05:32:57.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27634|2024-08-03T05:32:59.826Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20apm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27634</link>
      <description>On 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2 and 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, BIG-IP APM does not properly validate configurations, allowing an authenticated attacker with high privileges to manipulate the APM policy leading to privilege escalation/remote code execution. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27634|2024-08-03T05:32:59.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27662|2024-08-03T05:32:59.915Z -- f5 -- traffix%20sdc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27662</link>
      <description>On F5 Traffix SDC 5.2.x versions prior to 5.2.2 and 5.1.x versions prior to 5.1.35, a stored Cross-Site Template Injection vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of the Traffix SDC Configuration utility that allows an attacker to execute template language-specific instructions in the context of the server. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27662|2024-08-03T05:32:59.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35240|2024-08-03T09:29:17.443Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35240</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 16.1.x before 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, and 14.1.x before 14.1.5, when the Message Routing (MR) Message Queuing Telemetry Transport (MQTT) profile is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in memory resource utilization. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35240|2024-08-03T09:29:17.443Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32455|2024-08-03T07:39:51.099Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32455</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 16.1.x before 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, 14.1.x before 14.1.5, and all versions of 13.1.x, when a BIG-IP LTM Client SSL profile is configured on a virtual server to perform client certificate authentication with session tickets enabled, undisclosed requests cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32455|2024-08-03T07:39:51.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33947|2024-08-03T08:16:16.066Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20dns
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33947</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 16.1.x before 16.1.3, 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, 14.1.x before 14.1.5, and all versions of 13.1.x, a vulnerability exists in undisclosed pages of the BIG-IP DNS Traffic Management User Interface (TMUI) that allows an authenticated attacker with at least operator role privileges to cause the Tomcat process to restart and perform unauthorized DNS requests and operations through undisclosed requests. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33947|2024-08-03T08:16:16.066Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35245|2024-08-03T09:29:17.466Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20apm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35245</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 16.1.x before 16.1.3.1, 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, and 14.1.x before 14.1.5.1, when a BIG-IP APM access policy is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35245|2024-08-03T09:29:17.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27181|2024-08-03T05:25:31.057Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20apm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27181</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP APM 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, and all versions of 12.1.x and 11.6.x, when APM is configured on a virtual server and the associated access profile is configured with APM AAA NTLM Auth, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in internal resource utilization. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27181|2024-08-03T05:25:31.057Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29491|2024-08-03T06:26:05.975Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20ltm%2C%20advanced%20waf%2C%20asm%2C%20and%20apm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29491</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP LTM, Advanced WAF, ASM, or APM 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, and all versions of 13.1.x, 12.1.x, and 11.6.x, when a virtual server is configured with HTTP, TCP on one side (client/server), and DTLS on the other (server/client), undisclosed requests can cause the TMM process to terminate. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29491|2024-08-03T06:26:05.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41780|2024-08-03T12:49:44.037Z -- f5 -- f5os-a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41780</link>
      <description>In F5OS-A version 1.x before 1.1.0 and F5OS-C version 1.x before 1.4.0, a directory traversal vulnerability exists in an undisclosed location of the F5OS CLI that allows an attacker to read arbitrary files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41780|2024-08-03T12:49:44.037Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28705|2024-08-03T06:03:52.572Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28705</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, and 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, on platforms with an ePVA and the pva.fwdaccel BigDB variable enabled, undisclosed requests to a virtual server with a FastL4 profile that has ePVA acceleration enabled can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) process to terminate. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28705|2024-08-03T06:03:52.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26071|2024-08-03T04:56:37.741Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26071</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, and all versions of 12.1.x and 11.6.x, a flaw in the way reply ICMP packets are limited in the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) allows an attacker to quickly scan open UDP ports. This flaw allows an off-path remote attacker to effectively bypass source port UDP randomization. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26071|2024-08-03T04:56:37.741Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41622|2024-08-03T12:49:43.598Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41622</link>
      <description>In all versions, 

BIG-IP and BIG-IQ are vulnerable to cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks through iControl SOAP.  

Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41622|2024-08-03T12:49:43.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 03:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27182|2024-08-03T05:25:31.024Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27182</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, and 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, when BIG-IP packet filters are enabled and a virtual server is configured with the type set to Reject, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in memory resource utilization. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27182|2024-08-03T05:25:31.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28714|2024-08-03T06:03:52.638Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20apm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28714</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP APM 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, and all versions of 12.1.x and 11.6.x, as well as F5 BIG-IP APM Clients 7.x versions prior to 7.2.1.5, a DLL Hijacking vulnerability exists in the BIG-IP Edge Client Windows Installer. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28714|2024-08-03T06:03:52.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29474|2024-08-03T06:26:05.877Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29474</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, and all versions of 12.1.x and 11.6.x, a directory traversal vulnerability exists in iControl SOAP that allows an authenticated attacker with at least guest role privileges to read wsdl files in the BIG-IP file system. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29474|2024-08-03T06:26:05.877Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41770|2024-08-03T12:49:43.994Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41770</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP versions 17.0.x before 17.0.0.1, 16.1.x before 16.1.3.1, 15.1.x before 15.1.7, 14.1.x before 14.1.5.1, and all versions of 13.1.x, and BIG-IQ all versions of 8.x and 7.x, an authenticated iControl REST user can cause an increase in memory resource utilization, via undisclosed requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41770|2024-08-03T12:49:43.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34655|2024-08-03T09:15:15.647Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34655</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 16.0.x before 16.0.1.1, 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, and 14.1.x before 14.1.5, when an iRule containing the HTTP::payload command is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34655|2024-08-03T09:15:15.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26415|2024-08-03T05:03:32.815Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26415</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, and all versions of 12.1.x, when running in Appliance mode, an authenticated user assigned the Administrator role may be able to bypass Appliance mode restrictions, utilizing an undisclosed iControl REST endpoint. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26415|2024-08-03T05:03:32.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28701|2024-08-03T06:03:52.165Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28701</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, when the stream profile is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in memory resource utilization. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28701|2024-08-03T06:03:52.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35272|2024-08-03T09:36:43.329Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35272</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 17.0.x before 17.0.0.1 and 16.1.x before 16.1.3.1, when source-port preserve-strict is configured on an HTTP Message Routing Framework (MRF) virtual server, undisclosed traffic may cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to produce a core file and the connection to terminate. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35272|2024-08-03T09:36:43.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41813|2024-08-03T12:56:38.300Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20afm%20%26%20pem
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41813</link>
      <description>In versions 16.1.x before 16.1.3.1, 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, 14.1.x before 14.1.5, and all versions of 13.1.x, when BIG-IP is provisioned with PEM or AFM module, an undisclosed input can cause Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41813|2024-08-03T12:56:38.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41743|2024-08-03T12:49:43.516Z -- f5 -- nginx%20plus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41743</link>
      <description>NGINX Plus before versions R27 P1 and R26 P1 have a vulnerability in the module ngx_http_hls_module that might allow a local attacker to corrupt NGINX worker memory, resulting in its crash or potential other impact using a specially crafted audio or video file. The issue affects only NGINX Plus when the hls directive is used in the configuration file. Further, the attack is possible only if an attacker can trigger processing of a specially crafted audio or video file with the module ngx_http_hls_module.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41743|2024-08-03T12:49:43.516Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35236|2024-08-03T09:29:17.401Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35236</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 16.1.x before 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, and 14.1.x before 14.1.5, when an HTTP2 profile is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause an increase in memory resource utilization. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35236|2024-08-03T09:29:17.401Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28859|2024-08-03T06:03:53.154Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28859</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1 and 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, when installing Net HSM, the scripts (nethsm-safenet-install.sh and nethsm-thales-install.sh) expose the Net HSM partition password. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28859|2024-08-03T06:03:53.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35735|2024-08-03T09:44:22.004Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35735</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 16.1.x before 16.1.3.1, 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, 14.1.x before 14.1.5.1, and all versions of 13.1.x, an authenticated attacker with Resource Administrator or Manager privileges can create or modify existing monitor objects in the Configuration utility in an undisclosed manner leading to a privilege escalation. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35735|2024-08-03T09:44:22.004Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36795|2024-08-03T10:14:28.417Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36795</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP versions 17.0.x before 17.0.0.1, 16.1.x before 16.1.3.1, 15.1.x before 15.1.7, and 14.1.x before 14.1.5.1, when an LTM TCP profile with Auto Receive Window Enabled is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause the virtual server to stop processing new client connections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36795|2024-08-03T10:14:28.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27636|2024-08-03T05:32:59.994Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20apm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27636</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP APM 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, and all versions of 12.1.x and 11.6.x, as well as F5 BIG-IP APM Clients 7.x versions prior to 7.2.1.5, BIG-IP Edge Client may log sensitive APM session-related information when VPN is launched on a Windows system. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27636|2024-08-03T05:32:59.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-25946|2024-08-03T04:49:44.326Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20%28advanced%20waf%2C%20apm%2C%20asm%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25946</link>
      <description>On all versions of 16.1.x, 15.1.x, 14.1.x, 13.1.x, 12.1.x, and 11.6.x of F5 BIG-IP Advanced WAF, ASM, and ASM, and F5 BIG-IP Guided Configuration (GC) all versions prior to 9.0, when running in Appliance mode, an authenticated attacker with Administrator role privilege may be able to bypass Appliance mode restrictions due to a missing integrity check in F5 BIG-IP Guided Configuration. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-25946|2024-08-03T04:49:44.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27659|2024-08-03T05:32:59.991Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27659</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, and 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, an authenticated attacker can modify or delete Dashboards created by other BIG-IP users in the Traffic Management User Interface (TMUI). Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27659|2024-08-03T05:32:59.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31473|2024-08-03T07:19:06.057Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20apm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31473</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 16.1.x before 16.1.1 and 15.1.x before 15.1.4, when running in Appliance mode, an authenticated attacker may be able to bypass Appliance mode restrictions due to a directory traversal vulnerability in an undisclosed page within iApps. A successful exploit can allow the attacker to cross a security boundary. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31473|2024-08-03T07:19:06.057Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41741|2024-08-03T12:49:43.730Z -- f5 -- nginx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41741</link>
      <description>NGINX Open Source before versions 1.23.2 and 1.22.1, NGINX Open Source Subscription before versions R2 P1 and R1 P1, and NGINX Plus before versions R27 P1 and R26 P1 have a vulnerability in the module ngx_http_mp4_module that might allow a local attacker to corrupt NGINX worker memory, resulting in its termination or potential other impact using a specially crafted audio or video file. The issue affects only NGINX products that are built with the ngx_http_mp4_module, when the mp4 directive is used in the configuration file. Further, the attack is possible only if an attacker can trigger processing of a specially crafted audio or video file with the module ngx_http_mp4_module.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41741|2024-08-03T12:49:43.730Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27189|2024-08-03T05:25:31.061Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27189</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, and all versions of 12.1.x and 11.6.x, when an Internet Content Adaptation Protocol (ICAP) profile is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause an increase in Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) memory resource utilization. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27189|2024-08-03T05:25:31.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29479|2024-08-03T06:26:05.656Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29479</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, and all versions of 12.1.x and 11.6.x, and F5 BIG-IQ Centralized Management all versions of 8.x and 7.x, when an IPv6 self IP address is configured and the ipv6.strictcompliance database key is enabled (disabled by default) on a BIG-IP system, undisclosed packets may cause decreased performance. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29479|2024-08-03T06:26:05.656Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41787|2024-08-03T12:49:43.826Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20dns
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41787</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP versions 17.0.x before 17.0.0.1, 16.1.x before 16.1.3.1, 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, 14.1.x before 14.1.5.1, and 13.1.x before 13.1.5.1, when DNS profile is configured on a virtual server with DNS Express enabled, undisclosed DNS queries with DNSSEC can cause TMM to terminate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41787|2024-08-03T12:49:43.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34862|2024-08-03T09:22:10.763Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34862</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 16.1.x before 16.1.3.1, 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, 14.1.x before 14.1.5, and all versions of 13.1.x, when an LTM virtual server is configured to perform normalization, undisclosed requests can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34862|2024-08-03T09:22:10.763Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41836|2024-08-03T12:56:38.115Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20advanced%20waf%20%26%20asm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41836</link>
      <description>When an 'Attack Signature False Positive Mode' enabled security policy is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause the bd process to terminate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41836|2024-08-03T12:56:38.115Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34865|2024-08-03T09:22:10.614Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34865</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, 14.1.x before 14.1.5, and all versions of 13.1.x, Traffic Intelligence feeds, which use HTTPS, do not verify the remote endpoint identity, allowing for potential data poisoning. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34865|2024-08-03T09:22:10.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28716|2024-08-03T06:03:52.053Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28716</link>
      <description>On 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, and all versions of 12.1.x 11.6.x, a DOM-based cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of the BIG-IP AFM, CGNAT, and PEM Configuration utility that allows an attacker to execute JavaScript in the context of the currently logged-in user. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28716|2024-08-03T06:03:52.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27230|2024-08-03T05:25:32.659Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20apm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27230</link>
      <description>On all versions of 16.1.x, 15.1.x, 14.1.x, 13.1.x, 12.1.x, and 11.6.x of F5 BIG-IP APM, and F5 BIG-IP Guided Configuration (GC) all versions prior to 9.0, a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of F5 BIG-IP Guided Configuration that allows an attacker to execute JavaScript in the context of the currently logged-in user. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27230|2024-08-03T05:25:32.659Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26130|2024-08-03T04:56:37.582Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26130</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, and 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, when an Active mode-enabled FTP profile is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause the virtual server to stop processing active FTP data channel connections. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26130|2024-08-03T04:56:37.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41835|2024-08-03T12:56:38.001Z -- f5 -- f5os-a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41835</link>
      <description>In F5OS-A version 1.x before 1.1.0 and F5OS-C version 1.x before 1.5.0, excessive file permissions in F5OS allows an authenticated local attacker to execute limited set of commands in a container and impact the F5OS controller.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41835|2024-08-03T12:56:38.001Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26372|2024-08-03T05:03:32.883Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26372</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.0.2, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, and all versions of 12.1.x and 11.6.x, when a DNS listener is configured on a virtual server with DNS queueing (default), undisclosed requests can cause an increase in memory resource utilization. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26372|2024-08-03T05:03:32.883Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41983|2024-08-03T12:56:39.190Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41983</link>
      <description>On specific hardware platforms, on BIG-IP versions 16.1.x before 16.1.3.1, 15.1.x before 15.1.7, 14.1.x before 14.1.5.1, and all versions of 13.1.x, while Intel QAT (QuickAssist Technology) and the AES-GCM/CCM cipher is in use, undisclosed conditions can cause BIG-IP to send data unencrypted even with an SSL Profile applied.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41983|2024-08-03T12:56:39.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27806|2024-08-03T05:32:59.981Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20%28advanced%20waf%2C%20apm%2C%20asm%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27806</link>
      <description>On all versions of 16.1.x, 15.1.x, 14.1.x, 13.1.x, 12.1.x, and 11.6.x of F5 BIG-IP Advanced WAF, ASM, and ASM, and F5 BIG-IP Guided Configuration (GC) all versions prior to 9.0, when running in Appliance mode, an authenticated attacker assigned the Administrator role may be able to bypass Appliance mode restrictions, utilizing command injection vulnerabilities in undisclosed URIs in F5 BIG-IP Guided Configuration. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27806|2024-08-03T05:32:59.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26835|2024-08-03T05:11:44.929Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26835</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, and all versions of 12.1.x and 11.6.x, directory traversal vulnerabilities exist in undisclosed iControl REST endpoints and TMOS Shell (tmsh) commands in F5 BIG-IP Guided Configuration, which may allow an authenticated attacker with at least resource administrator role privileges to read arbitrary files. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26835|2024-08-03T05:11:44.929Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41691|2024-08-03T12:49:43.498Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20advanced%20waf%20%26%20asm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41691</link>
      <description>When a BIG-IP Advanced WAF/ASM security policy is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause the bd process to terminate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41691|2024-08-03T12:49:43.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29480|2024-08-03T06:26:06.277Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29480</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, and all versions of 12.1.x and 11.6.x, when multiple route domains are configured, undisclosed requests to big3d can cause an increase in CPU resource utilization. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29480|2024-08-03T06:26:06.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33968|2024-08-03T08:16:15.956Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33968</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 17.0.x before 17.0.0.1, 16.1.x before 16.1.3.1, 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, 14.1.x before 14.1.5.1, and all versions of 13.1.x, when an LTM monitor or APM SSO is configured on a virtual server, and NTLM challenge-response is in use, undisclosed traffic can cause a buffer over-read. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33968|2024-08-03T08:16:15.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27880|2024-08-03T05:41:10.976Z -- f5 -- traffix%20sdc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27880</link>
      <description>On F5 Traffix SDC 5.2.x versions prior to 5.2.2 and 5.1.x versions prior to 5.1.35, a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of the Traffix SDC Configuration utility that allows an attacker to execute JavaScript in the context of the currently logged-in user. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27880|2024-08-03T05:41:10.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26890|2024-08-03T05:18:38.060Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20advanced%20waf%2C%20asm%2C%20and%20apm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26890</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP Advanced WAF, ASM, and APM 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.1, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, and 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, when ASM or Advanced WAF, as well as APM, are configured on a virtual server, the ASM policy is configured with Session Awareness, and the "Use APM Username and Session ID" option is enabled, undisclosed requests can cause the bd process to terminate. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26890|2024-08-03T05:18:38.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28706|2024-08-03T06:03:52.154Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28706</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2 and 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, when the DNS resolver configuration is used, undisclosed requests can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28706|2024-08-03T06:03:52.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26517|2024-08-03T05:03:33.135Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26517</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, and 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, when the BIG-IP CGNAT Large Scale NAT (LSN) pool is configured on a virtual server and packet filtering is enabled, undisclosed requests can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26517|2024-08-03T05:03:33.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28707|2024-08-03T06:03:52.585Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28707</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, and 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of the BIG-IP Configuration utility (also referred to as the BIG-IP TMUI) that allows an attacker to execute JavaScript in the context of the currently logged-in user. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28707|2024-08-03T06:03:52.585Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26340|2024-08-03T05:03:32.879Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26340</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, and all versions of 12.1.x and 11.6.x, and F5 BIG-IQ Centralized Management all versions of 8.x and 7.x, an authenticated, high-privileged attacker with no bash access may be able to access Certificate and Key files using Secure Copy (SCP) protocol from a remote system. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26340|2024-08-03T05:03:32.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27875|2024-08-03T05:41:10.984Z -- f5 -- f5%20access%20for%20android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27875</link>
      <description>On F5 Access for Android 3.x versions prior to 3.0.8, a Task Hijacking vulnerability exists in the F5 Access for Android application, which may allow an attacker to steal sensitive user information. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27875|2024-08-03T05:41:10.984Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41832|2024-08-03T12:56:38.392Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41832</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP versions 17.0.x before 17.0.0.1, 16.1.x before 16.1.3.1, 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, 14.1.x before 14.1.5.1, and 13.1.x before 13.1.5.1, when a SIP profile is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed messages can cause an increase in memory resource utilization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41832|2024-08-03T12:56:38.392Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33962|2024-08-03T08:16:15.909Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33962</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 17.0.x before 17.0.0.1, 16.1.x before 16.1.3.1, 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, 14.1.x before 14.1.5.1, and all versions of 13.1.x, certain iRules commands may allow an attacker to bypass the access control restrictions for a self IP address, regardless of the port lockdown settings. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33962|2024-08-03T08:16:15.909Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41617|2024-08-03T12:49:43.268Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20advanced%20waf%20%26%20asm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41617</link>
      <description>In versions 16.1.x before 16.1.3.1, 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, 14.1.x before 14.1.5.1, and 13.1.x before 13.1.5.1, When the Advanced WAF / ASM module is provisioned, an authenticated remote code execution vulnerability exists in the BIG-IP iControl REST interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41617|2024-08-03T12:49:43.268Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30535|2024-08-03T06:48:36.417Z -- f5 -- nginx%20ingress%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30535</link>
      <description>In versions 2.x before 2.3.0 and all versions of 1.x, An attacker authorized to create or update ingress objects can obtain the secrets available to the NGINX Ingress Controller. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30535|2024-08-03T06:48:36.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33203|2024-08-03T08:01:20.419Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20apm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33203</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 16.1.x before 16.1.3, 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, and 14.1.x before 14.1.5, when a BIG-IP APM access policy with Service Connect agent is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in memory resource utilization. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33203|2024-08-03T08:01:20.419Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35728|2024-08-03T09:44:21.647Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35728</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 17.0.x before 17.0.0.1, 16.1.x before 16.1.3.1, 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, 14.1.x before 14.1.5.1, and all versions of 13.1.x, and BIG-IQ version 8.x before 8.2.0 and all versions of 7.x, an authenticated user's iControl REST token may remain valid for a limited time after logging out from the Configuration utility. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35728|2024-08-03T09:44:21.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34651|2024-08-03T09:15:15.611Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34651</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP Versions 16.1.x before 16.1.3.1 and 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, when an LTM Client or Server SSL profile with TLS 1.3 enabled is configured on a virtual server, along with an iRule that calls HTTP::respond, undisclosed requests can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34651|2024-08-03T09:15:15.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41742|2024-08-03T12:49:44.037Z -- f5 -- nginx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41742</link>
      <description>NGINX Open Source before versions 1.23.2 and 1.22.1, NGINX Open Source Subscription before versions R2 P1 and R1 P1, and NGINX Plus before versions R27 P1 and R26 P1 have a vulnerability in the module ngx_http_mp4_module that might allow a local attacker to cause a worker process crash, or might result in worker process memory disclosure by using a specially crafted audio or video file. The issue affects only NGINX products that are built with the module ngx_http_mp4_module, when the mp4 directive is used in the configuration file. Further, the attack is possible only if an attacker can trigger processing of a specially crafted audio or video file with the module ngx_http_mp4_module.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41742|2024-08-03T12:49:44.037Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41694|2024-08-03T12:49:43.528Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41694</link>
      <description>In BIG-IP versions 16.1.x before 16.1.3, 15.1.x before 15.1.6.1, 14.1.x before 14.1.5, and all versions of 13.1.x, and BIG-IQ versions 8.x before 8.2.0.1 and all versions of 7.x, when an SSL key is imported on a BIG-IP or BIG-IQ system, undisclosed input can cause MCPD to terminate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41694|2024-08-03T12:49:43.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28695|2024-08-03T06:03:51.975Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20afm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28695</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP AFM 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, and 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, an authenticated attacker with high privileges can upload a maliciously crafted file to the BIG-IP AFM Configuration utility, which allows an attacker to run arbitrary commands. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28695|2024-08-03T06:03:51.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41806|2024-08-03T12:56:38.087Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20afm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41806</link>
      <description>In versions 16.1.x before 16.1.3.2 and 15.1.x before 15.1.5.1, when BIG-IP AFM Network Address Translation policy with IPv6/IPv4 translation rules is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in memory resource utilization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41806|2024-08-03T12:56:38.087Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28691|2024-08-03T06:03:52.164Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28691</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2, 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5, 14.1.x versions prior to 14.1.4.6, and 13.1.x versions prior to 13.1.5, when a Real Time Streaming Protocol (RTSP) profile is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause an increase in Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) resource utilization. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28691|2024-08-03T06:03:52.164Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28708|2024-08-03T06:03:52.442Z -- f5 -- big-ip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28708</link>
      <description>On F5 BIG-IP 16.1.x versions prior to 16.1.2.2 and 15.1.x versions prior to 15.1.5.1, when a BIG-IP DNS resolver-enabled, HTTP-Explicit or SOCKS profile is configured on a virtual server, an undisclosed DNS response can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) process to terminate. Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28708|2024-08-03T06:03:52.442Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-35200|2024-08-02T03:07:46.774Z -- f5 -- nginx%20open%20source</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35200</link>
      <description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module, undisclosed HTTP/3 requests can cause NGINX worker processes to terminate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-35200|2024-08-02T03:07:46.774Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31079|2024-08-02T01:46:04.427Z -- f5 -- nginx%20open%20source</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31079</link>
      <description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module, undisclosed HTTP/3 requests can cause NGINX worker processes to terminate or cause other potential impact. This attack requires that a request be specifically timed during the connection draining process, which the attacker has no visibility and limited influence over.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31079|2024-08-02T01:46:04.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31156|2024-08-02T01:46:04.426Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31156</link>
      <description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of the BIG-IP Configuration utility that allows an attacker to run JavaScript in the context of the currently logged-in user.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31156|2024-08-02T01:46:04.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32049|2024-08-02T02:06:43.256Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20next%20central%20manager</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32049</link>
      <description>BIG-IP Next Central Manager (CM) may allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to obtain the BIG-IP Next LTM/WAF instance credentials. 

Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32049|2024-08-02T02:06:43.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22389|2024-08-01T22:43:34.665Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22389</link>
      <description>When BIG-IP is deployed in high availability (HA) and an iControl REST API token is updated, the change does not sync to the peer device.  


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22389|2024-08-01T22:43:34.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21789|2024-08-01T22:27:36.326Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21789</link>
      <description>When a BIG-IP ASM/Advanced WAF security policy is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in memory resource utilization.
 Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21789|2024-08-01T22:27:36.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21782|2024-08-01T22:27:36.311Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21782</link>
      <description>BIG-IP or BIG-IQ Resource Administrators and Certificate Managers who have access to the secure copy (scp) utility but do not have access to Advanced shell (bash) can execute arbitrary commands with a specially crafted command string. This vulnerability is due to an incomplete fix for CVE-2020-5873. 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21782|2024-08-01T22:27:36.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22093|2024-08-01T22:35:34.791Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22093</link>
      <description>When running in appliance mode, an authenticated remote command injection vulnerability exists in an undisclosed iControl REST endpoint on multi-bladed systems. A successful exploit can allow the attacker to cross a security boundary.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22093|2024-08-01T22:35:34.791Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21771|2024-08-01T22:27:36.313Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21771</link>
      <description>For unspecified traffic patterns, BIG-IP AFM IPS engine may spend an excessive amount of time matching the traffic against signatures, resulting in Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) restarting and traffic disruption.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21771|2024-08-01T22:27:36.313Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21763|2024-08-01T22:27:36.227Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21763</link>
      <description>When BIG-IP AFM Device DoS or DoS profile is configured with NXDOMAIN attack vector and bad actor detection, undisclosed queries can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  NOTE: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21763|2024-08-01T22:27:36.227Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21793|2024-08-01T22:27:36.335Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20next%20central%20manager</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21793</link>
      <description>An OData injection vulnerability exists in the BIG-IP Next Central Manager API (URI).  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21793|2024-08-01T22:27:36.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23308|2024-08-01T22:59:32.144Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23308</link>
      <description>When a BIG-IP Advanced WAF or BIG-IP ASM policy with a Request Body Handling option is attached to a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause the BD process to terminate. The condition results from setting the Request Body Handling option in the Header-Based Content Profile for an Allowed URL with "Apply value and content signatures and detect threat campaigns."  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23308|2024-08-01T22:59:32.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21849|2024-08-01T22:27:36.345Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21849</link>
      <description>When an Advanced WAF/ASM security policy and a Websockets profile are configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) process to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21849|2024-08-01T22:27:36.345Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23306|2024-08-01T22:59:32.236Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20next%20spk</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in BIG-IP Next CNF and SPK systems that may allow access to undisclosed sensitive files.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23306|2024-08-01T22:59:32.236Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23314|2024-08-01T22:59:32.204Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23314</link>
      <description>When HTTP/2 is configured on BIG-IP or BIG-IP Next SPK systems, undisclosed responses can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23314|2024-08-01T22:59:32.204Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21789|2024-07-30T17:54:23.592Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21789</link>
      <description>When a BIG-IP ASM/Advanced WAF security policy is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in memory resource utilization.
 Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21789|2024-07-30T17:54:23.592Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23976|2024-07-30T17:56:07.282Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23976</link>
      <description>When running in Appliance mode, an authenticated attacker assigned the Administrator role may be able to bypass Appliance
mode restrictions utilizing iAppsLX templates on a BIG-IP system.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23976|2024-07-30T17:56:07.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33604|2024-06-12T19:41:42.041Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33604</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exist in undisclosed page of the BIG-IP Configuration utility that allows an attacker to run JavaScript in the context of the currently logged-in user.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33604|2024-06-12T19:41:42.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-35200|2024-05-29T16:02:05.342Z -- f5 -- nginx%20open%20source</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-35200</link>
      <description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module, undisclosed HTTP/3 requests can cause NGINX worker processes to terminate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-35200|2024-05-29T16:02:05.342Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25560|2024-05-08T15:01:25.651Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25560</link>
      <description>When BIG-IP AFM is licensed and provisioned, undisclosed DNS traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.

 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25560|2024-05-08T15:01:25.651Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31079|2024-05-29T16:02:04.620Z -- f5 -- nginx%20open%20source</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31079</link>
      <description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module, undisclosed HTTP/3 requests can cause NGINX worker processes to terminate or cause other potential impact. This attack requires that a request be specifically timed during the connection draining process, which the attacker has no visibility and limited influence over.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31079|2024-05-29T16:02:04.620Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31156|2024-06-04T17:37:10.115Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31156</link>
      <description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of the BIG-IP Configuration utility that allows an attacker to run JavaScript in the context of the currently logged-in user.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31156|2024-06-04T17:37:10.115Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21763|2024-02-14T16:30:25.714Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21763</link>
      <description>When BIG-IP AFM Device DoS or DoS profile is configured with NXDOMAIN attack vector and bad actor detection, undisclosed queries can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  NOTE: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21763|2024-02-14T16:30:25.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21849|2024-06-04T17:37:56.070Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21849</link>
      <description>When an Advanced WAF/ASM security policy and a Websockets profile are configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) process to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21849|2024-06-04T17:37:56.070Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21782|2024-02-14T16:30:20.945Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21782</link>
      <description>BIG-IP or BIG-IQ Resource Administrators and Certificate Managers who have access to the secure copy (scp) utility but do not have access to Advanced shell (bash) can execute arbitrary commands with a specially crafted command string. This vulnerability is due to an incomplete fix for CVE-2020-5873. 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21782|2024-02-14T16:30:20.945Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21789|2024-02-14T16:30:24.980Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21789</link>
      <description>When a BIG-IP ASM/Advanced WAF security policy is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in memory resource utilization.
 Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21789|2024-02-14T16:30:24.980Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21793|2024-06-04T17:38:06.949Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20next%20central%20manager</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21793</link>
      <description>An OData injection vulnerability exists in the BIG-IP Next Central Manager API (URI).  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21793|2024-06-04T17:38:06.949Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21771|2024-02-14T16:30:21.300Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21771</link>
      <description>For unspecified traffic patterns, BIG-IP AFM IPS engine may spend an excessive amount of time matching the traffic against signatures, resulting in Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) restarting and traffic disruption.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21771|2024-02-14T16:30:21.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34161|2024-05-29T16:02:05.696Z -- f5 -- nginx%20open%20source</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34161</link>
      <description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module and the network infrastructure supports a Maximum Transmission Unit (MTU) of 4096 or greater without fragmentation, undisclosed QUIC packets can cause NGINX worker processes to leak previously freed memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34161|2024-05-29T16:02:05.696Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24966|2024-06-04T17:42:54.469Z -- f5 -- f5os%20-%20appliance</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24966</link>
      <description>When LDAP remote authentication is configured on F5OS, a remote user without an assigned role will be incorrectly authorized.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24966|2024-06-04T17:42:54.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24989|2024-02-14T16:30:26.081Z -- f5 -- nginx%20plus</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24989</link>
      <description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module, undisclosed requests can cause NGINX worker processes to terminate.

Note: The HTTP/3 QUIC module is not enabled by default and is considered experimental. For more information, refer to  Support for QUIC and HTTP/3 https://nginx.org/en/docs/quic.html .



NOTE: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24989|2024-02-14T16:30:26.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24775|2024-02-14T16:30:23.876Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24775</link>
      <description>When a virtual server is enabled with VLAN group and SNAT listener is configured, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24775|2024-02-14T16:30:23.876Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24990|2024-02-14T16:30:26.445Z -- f5 -- nginx%20plus</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24990</link>
      <description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module, undisclosed requests can cause NGINX worker processes to terminate.

Note: The HTTP/3 QUIC module is not enabled by default and is considered experimental. For more information, refer to  Support for QUIC and HTTP/3 https://nginx.org/en/docs/quic.html .



 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24990|2024-02-14T16:30:26.445Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33608|2024-06-04T17:45:08.235Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33608</link>
      <description>When IPsec is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33608|2024-06-04T17:45:08.235Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33604|2024-05-08T15:01:27.377Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33604</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exist in undisclosed page of the BIG-IP Configuration utility that allows an attacker to run JavaScript in the context of the currently logged-in user.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33604|2024-05-08T15:01:27.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33612|2024-06-04T17:45:15.357Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20next%20central%20manager</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33612</link>
      <description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability exists in BIG-IP Next Central Manager and may allow an attacker to impersonate an Instance Provider system. A successful exploit of this vulnerability can allow the attacker to cross a security boundary.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33612|2024-06-04T17:45:15.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23607|2024-06-04T17:45:40.018Z -- f5 -- f5os%20-%20appliance</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23607</link>
      <description>A directory traversal vulnerability exists in the F5OS QKView utility that allows an authenticated attacker to read files outside the QKView directory.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23607|2024-06-04T17:45:40.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23979|2024-06-04T17:45:40.851Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23979</link>
      <description>When SSL Client Certificate LDAP or Certificate Revocation List Distribution Point (CRLDP) authentication profile is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in CPU resource utilization. 

 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23979|2024-06-04T17:45:40.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23308|2024-06-04T17:45:44.241Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23308</link>
      <description>When a BIG-IP Advanced WAF or BIG-IP ASM policy with a Request Body Handling option is attached to a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause the BD process to terminate. The condition results from setting the Request Body Handling option in the Header-Based Content Profile for an Allowed URL with "Apply value and content signatures and detect threat campaigns."  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23308|2024-06-04T17:45:44.241Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23314|2024-06-04T17:45:54.259Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23314</link>
      <description>When HTTP/2 is configured on BIG-IP or BIG-IP Next SPK systems, undisclosed responses can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23314|2024-06-04T17:45:54.259Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23603|2024-06-04T17:46:06.523Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23603</link>
      <description>An SQL injection vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of the BIG-IP Configuration utility.

 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23603|2024-06-04T17:46:06.523Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23976|2024-02-14T16:30:20.173Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23976</link>
      <description>When running in Appliance mode, an authenticated attacker assigned the Administrator role may be able to bypass Appliance
mode restrictions utilizing iAppsLX templates on a BIG-IP system.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23976|2024-02-14T16:30:20.173Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23805|2024-03-05T21:45:19.185Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23805</link>
      <description>Undisclosed requests can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. For the Application Visibility and Reporting module, this may occur when the HTTP Analytics profile with URLs enabled under Collected Entities is configured on a virtual server and the DB variables avr.IncludeServerInURI or avr.CollectOnlyHostnameFromURI are enabled. For BIG-IP Advanced WAF and ASM, this may occur when either a DoS or Bot Defense profile is configured on a virtual server and the DB variables avr.IncludeServerInURI or avr.CollectOnlyHostnameFromURI are enabled.

Note: The DB variables avr.IncludeServerInURI and avr.CollectOnlyHostnameFromURI are not enabled by default. For more information about the HTTP Analytics profile and the Collect URLs setting, refer to  K30875743: Create a new Analytics profile and attach it to your virtual servers https://my.f5.com/manage/s/article/K30875743 .



 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23805|2024-03-05T21:45:19.185Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23306|2024-06-04T17:46:11.754Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20next%20spk</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in BIG-IP Next CNF and SPK systems that may allow access to undisclosed sensitive files.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23306|2024-06-04T17:46:11.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23982|2024-02-14T16:35:08.991Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23982</link>
      <description>When a BIG-IP PEM classification profile is configured on a UDP virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. This issue affects classification engines using signatures released between 09-08-2022 and 02-16-2023. See the table in the F5 Security Advisory for a complete list of affected classification signature files.  NOTE: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23982|2024-02-14T16:35:08.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:35:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27202|2024-06-04T17:46:33.238Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27202</link>
      <description>A DOM-based cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of the BIG-IP Configuration utility that allows an attacker to run JavaScript in the context of the currently logged-in user.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27202|2024-06-04T17:46:33.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26026|2024-06-04T17:49:06.557Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20next%20central%20manager</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-26026</link>
      <description>An SQL injection vulnerability exists in the BIG-IP Next Central Manager API (URI).  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26026|2024-06-04T17:49:06.557Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32049|2024-06-04T17:51:30.134Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20next%20central%20manager</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32049</link>
      <description>BIG-IP Next Central Manager (CM) may allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to obtain the BIG-IP Next LTM/WAF instance credentials. 

Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32049|2024-06-04T17:51:30.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32760|2024-05-29T16:02:04.985Z -- f5 -- nginx%20open%20source</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32760</link>
      <description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module, undisclosed HTTP/3 encoder instructions can cause NGINX worker processes to terminate or cause or other potential impact.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32760|2024-05-29T16:02:04.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32761|2024-06-04T17:52:21.071Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32761</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, a potential data leak may occur in the Traffic Management Microkernels (TMMs) of BIG-IP tenants running on VELOS and rSeries platforms. However, this issue cannot be exploited by an attacker because it is not consistently reproducible and is beyond an attacker's control.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32761|2024-06-04T17:52:21.071Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22093|2024-02-14T16:30:22.752Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22093</link>
      <description>When running in appliance mode, an authenticated remote command injection vulnerability exists in an undisclosed iControl REST endpoint on multi-bladed systems. A successful exploit can allow the attacker to cross a security boundary.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22093|2024-02-14T16:30:22.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22389|2024-02-14T16:30:19.797Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22389</link>
      <description>When BIG-IP is deployed in high availability (HA) and an iControl REST API token is updated, the change does not sync to the peer device.  


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22389|2024-02-14T16:30:19.797Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28883|2024-06-04T20:11:20.654Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20edge%20client</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28883</link>
      <description>An origin validation vulnerability exists in 

BIG-IP APM browser network access VPN client 



 for Windows, macOS and Linux which may allow an attacker to bypass F5 endpoint inspection. 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28883|2024-06-04T20:11:20.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28889|2024-06-04T18:03:33.549Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28889</link>
      <description>When an SSL profile with alert timeout is configured with a non-default value on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic along with conditions beyond the attacker's control can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28889|2024-06-04T18:03:33.549Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28132|2024-06-04T18:03:34.871Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20next%20cnf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28132</link>
      <description>Exposure of Sensitive Information vulnerability exists in the GSLB container, which may allow an authenticated attacker with local access to view sensitive information.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28132|2024-06-04T18:03:34.871Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25560|2024-07-23T21:02:12.590Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25560</link>
      <description>When BIG-IP AFM is licensed and provisioned, undisclosed DNS traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.

 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25560|2024-07-23T21:02:12.590Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32760|2024-07-31T20:52:45.607Z -- f5 -- nginx%20open%20source</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32760</link>
      <description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module, undisclosed HTTP/3 encoder instructions can cause NGINX worker processes to terminate or cause or other potential impact.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32760|2024-07-31T20:52:45.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-35200|2024-07-31T20:51:58.724Z -- f5 -- nginx%20open%20source</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35200</link>
      <description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module, undisclosed HTTP/3 requests can cause NGINX worker processes to terminate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-35200|2024-07-31T20:51:58.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28889|2024-08-02T01:03:50.257Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28889</link>
      <description>When an SSL profile with alert timeout is configured with a non-default value on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic along with conditions beyond the attacker's control can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28889|2024-08-02T01:03:50.257Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27202|2024-08-02T00:27:59.644Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27202</link>
      <description>A DOM-based cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of the BIG-IP Configuration utility that allows an attacker to run JavaScript in the context of the currently logged-in user.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27202|2024-08-02T00:27:59.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28883|2024-08-02T01:03:50.247Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20edge%20client</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28883</link>
      <description>An origin validation vulnerability exists in 

BIG-IP APM browser network access VPN client 



 for Windows, macOS and Linux which may allow an attacker to bypass F5 endpoint inspection. 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28883|2024-08-02T01:03:50.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28132|2024-08-02T00:48:49.036Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20next%20cnf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28132</link>
      <description>Exposure of Sensitive Information vulnerability exists in the GSLB container, which may allow an authenticated attacker with local access to view sensitive information.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28132|2024-08-02T00:48:49.036Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32760|2024-08-02T02:20:35.272Z -- f5 -- nginx%20open%20source</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32760</link>
      <description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module, undisclosed HTTP/3 encoder instructions can cause NGINX worker processes to terminate or cause or other potential impact.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32760|2024-08-02T02:20:35.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33608|2024-08-02T02:36:04.307Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33608</link>
      <description>When IPsec is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33608|2024-08-02T02:36:04.307Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33612|2024-08-02T02:36:04.361Z -- f5 -- big-ip%20next%20central%20manager</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33612</link>
      <description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability exists in BIG-IP Next Central Manager and may allow an attacker to impersonate an Instance Provider system. A successful exploit of this vulnerability can allow the attacker to cross a security boundary.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33612|2024-08-02T02:36:04.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34161|2024-08-02T02:51:10.486Z -- f5 -- nginx%20open%20source</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34161</link>
      <description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module and the network infrastructure supports a Maximum Transmission Unit (MTU) of 4096 or greater without fragmentation, undisclosed QUIC packets can cause NGINX worker processes to leak previously freed memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34161|2024-08-02T02:51:10.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33604|2024-08-02T02:36:04.349Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33604</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exist in undisclosed page of the BIG-IP Configuration utility that allows an attacker to run JavaScript in the context of the currently logged-in user.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33604|2024-08-02T02:36:04.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32761|2024-08-02T02:20:35.197Z -- f5 -- big-ip</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32761</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, a potential data leak may occur in the Traffic Management Microkernels (TMMs) of BIG-IP tenants running on VELOS and rSeries platforms. However, this issue cannot be exploited by an attacker because it is not consistently reproducible and is beyond an attacker's control.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32761|2024-08-02T02:20:35.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
