<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for RedHat -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/redhat/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for RedHat -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3834|2024-08-04T19:19:18.590Z -- redhat -- struts
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3834</link>
      <description>It was found that the fix for CVE-2014-0114 had been reverted in JBoss Operations Network 3 (JON). This flaw allows attackers to manipulate ClassLoader properties on a vulnerable server. Exploits that have been published rely on ClassLoader properties that are exposed such as those in JON 3. Additional information can be found in the Red Hat Knowledgebase article: https://access.redhat.com/site/solutions/869353. Note that while multiple products released patches for the original CVE-2014-0114 flaw, the reversion described by this CVE-2019-3834 flaw only occurred in JON 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3834|2024-08-04T19:19:18.590Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 13:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10171|2024-08-04T22:10:10.034Z -- redhat -- 389-ds-base
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10171</link>
      <description>It was found that the fix for CVE-2018-14648 in 389-ds-base, versions 1.4.0.x before 1.4.0.17, was incorrectly applied in RHEL 7.5. An attacker would still be able to provoke excessive CPU consumption leading to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10171|2024-08-04T22:10:10.034Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 13:49:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10176|2024-08-04T22:10:09.971Z -- redhat -- atomic-openshift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10176</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in OpenShift Container Platform, versions 3.11 and later, in which the CSRF tokens used in the cluster console component were found to remain static during a user's session. An attacker with the ability to observe the value of this token would be able to re-use the token to perform a CSRF attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10176|2024-08-04T22:10:09.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 13:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10202|2024-08-04T22:17:19.913Z -- redhat -- codehaus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10202</link>
      <description>A series of deserialization vulnerabilities have been discovered in Codehaus 1.9.x implemented in EAP 7. This CVE fixes CVE-2017-17485, CVE-2017-7525, CVE-2017-15095, CVE-2018-5968, CVE-2018-7489, CVE-2018-1000873, CVE-2019-12086 reported for FasterXML jackson-databind by implementing a whitelist approach that will mitigate these vulnerabilities and future ones alike.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10202|2024-08-04T22:17:19.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 14:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10212|2024-08-04T22:17:18.906Z -- redhat -- undertow
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10212</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in, all under 2.0.20, in the Undertow DEBUG log for io.undertow.request.security. If enabled, an attacker could abuse this flaw to obtain the user's credentials from the log files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10212|2024-08-04T22:17:18.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 18:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10150|2024-08-04T22:10:10.023Z -- redhat -- atomic-openshift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10150</link>
      <description>It was found that OpenShift Container Platform versions 3.6.x - 4.6.0 does not perform SSH Host Key checking when using ssh key authentication during builds. An attacker, with the ability to redirect network traffic, could use this to alter the resulting build output.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10150|2024-08-04T22:10:10.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 13:42:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10142|2024-08-04T22:10:10.016Z -- redhat -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10142</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's freescale hypervisor manager implementation, kernel versions 5.0.x up to, excluding 5.0.17. A parameter passed to an ioctl was incorrectly validated and used in size calculations for the page size calculation. An attacker can use this flaw to crash the system, corrupt memory, or create other adverse security affects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10142|2024-08-04T22:10:10.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 16:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10141|2024-08-04T22:10:09.963Z -- redhat -- openstack-ironic-inspector
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10141</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in openstack-ironic-inspector all versions excluding 5.0.2, 6.0.3, 7.2.4, 8.0.3 and 8.2.1. A SQL-injection vulnerability was found in openstack-ironic-inspector's node_cache.find_node(). This function makes a SQL query using unfiltered data from a server reporting inspection results (by a POST to the /v1/continue endpoint). Because the API is unauthenticated, the flaw could be exploited by an attacker with access to the network on which ironic-inspector is listening. Because of how ironic-inspector uses the query results, it is unlikely that data could be obtained. However, the attacker could pass malicious data and create a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10141|2024-08-04T22:10:09.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 16:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10172|2024-08-04T22:10:09.989Z -- redhat -- jackson-mapper-asl
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10172</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in org.codehaus.jackson:jackson-mapper-asl:1.9.x libraries. XML external entity vulnerabilities similar CVE-2016-3720 also affects codehaus jackson-mapper-asl libraries but in different classes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10172|2024-08-04T22:10:09.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 16:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
