<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for arvados -- arvados</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/arvados/arvados.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for arvados -- arvados</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:22:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36006|2024-08-03T09:51:59.803Z -- arvados -- arvados
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36006</link>
      <description>Arvados is an open source platform for managing, processing, and sharing genomic and other large scientific and biomedical data. A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the Arvados Workbench allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code via specially crafted JSON payloads. This exists in all versions up to 2.4.1 and is fixed in 2.4.2. This vulnerability is specific to the Ruby on Rails Workbench application (“Workbench 1”). We do not believe any other Arvados components, including the TypesScript browser-based Workbench application (“Workbench 2”) or API Server, are vulnerable to this attack. For versions of Arvados earlier than 2.4.2: remove the Ruby-based "Workbench 1" app ("apt-get remove arvados-workbench") from your installation as a workaround.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36006|2024-08-03T09:51:59.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 00:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39238|2024-08-03T12:00:43.416Z -- arvados -- arvados
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39238</link>
      <description>Arvados is an open source platform for managing and analyzing biomedical big data. In versions prior to 2.4.3, when using Portable Authentication Modules (PAM) for user authentication, if a user presented valid credentials but the account is disabled or otherwise not allowed to access the host (such as an expired password), it would still be accepted for access to Arvados. Other authentication methods (LDAP, OpenID Connect) supported by Arvados are not affected by this flaw. This issue is patched in version 2.4.3. Workaround for this issue is to migrate to a different authentication method supported by Arvados, such as LDAP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39238|2024-08-03T12:00:43.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
