<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for tigroumeow -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tigroumeow/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for tigroumeow -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-0699|2024-02-05T21:21:32.230Z -- tigroumeow -- AI Engine: Chatbots, Generators, Assistants, GPT 4 and more!
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0699</link><description>The AI Engine: Chatbots, Generators, Assistants, GPT 4 and more! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'add_image_from_url' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0699|2024-02-05T21:21:32.230Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0378|2024-03-02T09:37:32.638Z -- tigroumeow -- AI Engine
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0378</link><description>The AI Engine: Chatbots, Generators, Assistants, GPT 4 and more! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the AI chat data when discussion tracking is enabled in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0378|2024-03-02T09:37:32.638Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 09:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4386|2024-05-09T20:03:23.835Z -- tigroumeow -- Gallery Block (Meow Gallery)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4386</link><description>The Gallery Block (Meow Gallery) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘data_atts’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 5.1.3  due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4386|2024-05-09T20:03:23.835Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:03:23 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>