<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for brainstormforce -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/brainstormforce/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for brainstormforce -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 18:24:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36747|2024-08-04T17:37:06.945Z -- brainstormforce -- lightweight%20sidebar%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36747</link>
      <description>The Lightweight Sidebar Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.1.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the metabox_save() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to save metbox data via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36747|2024-08-04T17:37:06.945Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 05:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36702|2024-08-04T17:37:06.777Z -- brainstormforce -- spectra%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20gutenberg%20blocks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36702</link>
      <description>The Ultimate Addons for Gutenberg plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authenticated Settings Change in versions up to, and including, 1.14.7. This is due to missing capability checks on several AJAX actions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber+ roles to update the plugin's settings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36702|2024-08-04T17:37:06.777Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42360|2024-08-04T03:30:38.250Z -- brainstormforce -- starter%20templates%20%E2%80%94%20elementor%2C%20gutenberg%20%26%20beaver%20builder%20templates
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42360</link>
      <description>On sites that also had the Elementor plugin for WordPress installed, it was possible for users with the edit_posts capability, which includes Contributor-level users, to import blocks onto any page using the astra-page-elementor-batch-process AJAX action. An attacker could craft and host a block containing malicious JavaScript on a server they controlled, and then use it to overwrite any post or page by sending an AJAX request with the action set to astra-page-elementor-batch-process and the url parameter pointed to their remotely-hosted malicious block, as well as an id parameter containing the post or page to overwrite. Any post or page that had been built with Elementor, including published pages, could be overwritten by the imported block, and the malicious JavaScript in the imported block would then be executed in the browser of any visitors to that page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42360|2024-08-04T03:30:38.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 17:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36737|2024-08-04T17:37:06.640Z -- brainstormforce -- import%20%2F%20export%20customizer%20settings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36737</link>
      <description>The Import / Export Customizer Settings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the astra_admin_errors() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to display an import status via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36737|2024-08-04T17:37:06.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 03:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5757|2024-08-01T21:18:07.091Z -- brainstormforce -- elementor%20header%20%26%20footer%20builder</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5757</link>
      <description>The Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the url  attribute within the plugin's Site Title widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.35 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5757|2024-08-01T21:18:07.091Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 05:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5663|2024-08-01T21:18:06.840Z -- brainstormforce -- cards%20for%20beaver%20builder</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5663</link>
      <description>The Cards for Beaver Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Cards widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5663|2024-08-01T21:18:06.840Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 02:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5485|2024-08-01T21:11:12.767Z -- brainstormforce -- suretriggers%20%E2%80%93%20connect%20all%20your%20plugins%2C%20apps%2C%20tools%20%26%20automate%20everything%21</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5485</link>
      <description>The SureTriggers – Connect All Your Plugins, Apps, Tools &amp; Automate Everything! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Trigger Link shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.47 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5485|2024-08-01T21:11:12.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2142|2024-08-01T19:03:39.159Z -- brainstormforce -- ultimate%20addons%20for%20beaver%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20lite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2142</link>
      <description>The Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder – Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Info Table widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2142|2024-08-01T19:03:39.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 06:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2305|2024-08-01T19:11:53.361Z -- brainstormforce -- cards%20for%20beaver%20builder</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2305</link>
      <description>The Cards for Beaver Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the BootstrapCard link  in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2305|2024-08-01T19:11:53.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2618|2024-08-01T19:18:47.922Z -- brainstormforce -- elementor%20header%20%26%20footer%20builder</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2618</link>
      <description>The Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the size attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.26 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2618|2024-08-01T19:18:47.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 04:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2141|2024-08-01T19:03:39.176Z -- brainstormforce -- ultimate%20addons%20for%20beaver%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20lite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2141</link>
      <description>The Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder – Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Button widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2141|2024-08-01T19:03:39.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 06:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2140|2024-08-01T19:03:39.201Z -- brainstormforce -- ultimate%20addons%20for%20beaver%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20lite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2140</link>
      <description>The Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder – Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Advanced Icons widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2140|2024-08-01T19:03:39.201Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 06:44:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2619|2024-08-01T19:18:47.874Z -- brainstormforce -- elementor%20header%20%26%20footer%20builder</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2619</link>
      <description>The Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder for WordPress is vulnerable to HTML Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.26 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary HTML in pages that will be shown whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2619|2024-08-01T19:18:47.874Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2143|2024-08-01T19:03:39.002Z -- brainstormforce -- ultimate%20addons%20for%20beaver%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20lite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2143</link>
      <description>The Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder – Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Heading widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2143|2024-08-01T19:03:39.002Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 06:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3107|2024-08-01T19:32:42.699Z -- brainstormforce -- spectra%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20gutenberg%20blocks</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3107</link>
      <description>The Spectra – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in versions up to, and including, 2.12.6 via the get_block_default_attributes function. This allows authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to read the contents of any files named attributes.php on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3107|2024-08-01T19:32:42.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2144|2024-08-01T19:03:38.893Z -- brainstormforce -- ultimate%20addons%20for%20beaver%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20lite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2144</link>
      <description>The Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder – Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Separator widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2144|2024-08-01T19:03:38.893Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 06:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2347|2024-08-01T19:11:53.309Z -- brainstormforce -- astra</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2347</link>
      <description>The Astra theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a user's display name in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2347|2024-08-01T19:11:53.309Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1332|2024-07-29T18:41:14.130Z -- brainstormforce -- custom%20fonts%20%E2%80%93%20host%20your%20fonts%20locally</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1332</link>
      <description>The Custom Fonts – Host Your Fonts Locally plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via svg file upload in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author level or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1332|2024-07-29T18:41:14.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 06:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5757|2024-07-29T18:32:58.666Z -- brainstormforce -- elementor%20header%20%26%20footer%20builder</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5757</link>
      <description>The Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the url  attribute within the plugin's Site Title widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.35 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5757|2024-07-29T18:32:58.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 05:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5663|2024-06-20T16:08:27.800Z -- brainstormforce -- cards%20for%20beaver%20builder</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5663</link>
      <description>The Cards for Beaver Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Cards widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5663|2024-06-20T16:08:27.800Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 02:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6486|2024-06-04T17:16:59.204Z -- brainstormforce -- spectra%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20gutenberg%20blocks</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6486</link>
      <description>The Spectra – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Custom CSS metabox in all versions up to and including 2.10.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6486|2024-06-04T17:16:59.204Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5485|2024-06-04T18:03:04.328Z -- brainstormforce -- suretriggers%20%E2%80%93%20connect%20all%20your%20plugins%2C%20apps%2C%20tools%20%26%20automate%20everything%21</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5485</link>
      <description>The SureTriggers – Connect All Your Plugins, Apps, Tools &amp; Automate Everything! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Trigger Link shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.47 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5485|2024-06-04T18:03:04.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5663|2024-06-08T02:35:20.761Z -- brainstormforce -- cards%20for%20beaver%20builder</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5663</link>
      <description>The Cards for Beaver Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Cards widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5663|2024-06-08T02:35:20.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 02:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1815|2024-06-04T18:00:46.395Z -- brainstormforce -- spectra%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20gutenberg%20blocks</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1815</link>
      <description>The Spectra – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Image Gallery block in all versions up to, and including, 2.12.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1815|2024-06-04T18:00:46.395Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1814|2024-06-04T18:00:44.106Z -- brainstormforce -- spectra%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20gutenberg%20blocks</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1814</link>
      <description>The Spectra – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Testimonial block in all versions up to, and including, 2.12.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1814|2024-06-04T18:00:44.106Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1237|2024-03-13T15:27:00.687Z -- brainstormforce -- elementor%20header%20%26%20footer%20builder</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1237</link>
      <description>The Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the flyout_layout attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.24 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1237|2024-03-13T15:27:00.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1467|2024-06-04T17:59:34.875Z -- brainstormforce -- starter%20templates%20%E2%80%94%20elementor%2C%20wordpress%20%26%20beaver%20builder%20templates</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1467</link>
      <description>The Starter Templates — Elementor, WordPress &amp; Beaver Builder Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.6 via the ai_api_request(). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1467|2024-06-04T17:59:34.875Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1332|2024-05-24T06:42:17.541Z -- brainstormforce -- custom%20fonts%20%E2%80%93%20host%20your%20fonts%20locally</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1332</link>
      <description>The Custom Fonts – Host Your Fonts Locally plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via svg file upload in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author level or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1332|2024-05-24T06:42:17.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 06:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4630|2024-06-04T17:56:04.835Z -- brainstormforce -- starter%20templates%20%E2%80%94%20elementor%2C%20wordpress%20%26%20beaver%20builder%20templates</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4630</link>
      <description>The Starter Templates — Elementor, WordPress &amp; Beaver Builder Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘custom_upload_mimes’ function in versions up to, and including, 4.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4630|2024-06-04T17:56:04.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 04:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4634|2024-06-04T17:54:05.089Z -- brainstormforce -- elementor%20header%20%26%20footer%20builder</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4634</link>
      <description>The Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘hfe_svg_mime_types’ function in versions up to, and including, 1.6.28 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4634|2024-06-04T17:54:05.089Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4366|2024-06-04T17:53:26.461Z -- brainstormforce -- spectra%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20gutenberg%20blocks</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4366</link>
      <description>The Spectra – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘block_id’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 2.13.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4366|2024-06-04T17:53:26.461Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3107|2024-06-04T17:32:39.671Z -- brainstormforce -- spectra%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20gutenberg%20blocks</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3107</link>
      <description>The Spectra – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in versions up to, and including, 2.12.6 via the get_block_default_attributes function. This allows authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to read the contents of any files named attributes.php on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3107|2024-06-04T17:32:39.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2141|2024-06-04T17:30:50.429Z -- brainstormforce -- ultimate%20addons%20for%20beaver%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20lite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2141</link>
      <description>The Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder – Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Button widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2141|2024-06-04T17:30:50.429Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 06:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2618|2024-06-04T17:30:44.649Z -- brainstormforce -- elementor%20header%20%26%20footer%20builder</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2618</link>
      <description>The Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the size attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.26 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2618|2024-06-04T17:30:44.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 04:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2619|2024-06-04T17:30:38.513Z -- brainstormforce -- elementor%20header%20%26%20footer%20builder</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2619</link>
      <description>The Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder for WordPress is vulnerable to HTML Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.26 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary HTML in pages that will be shown whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2619|2024-06-04T17:30:38.513Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2140|2024-06-04T17:30:33.665Z -- brainstormforce -- ultimate%20addons%20for%20beaver%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20lite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2140</link>
      <description>The Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder – Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Advanced Icons widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2140|2024-06-04T17:30:33.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 06:44:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2347|2024-06-04T17:30:04.505Z -- brainstormforce -- astra</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2347</link>
      <description>The Astra theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a user's display name in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2347|2024-06-04T17:30:04.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2305|2024-06-04T17:29:47.426Z -- brainstormforce -- cards%20for%20beaver%20builder</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2305</link>
      <description>The Cards for Beaver Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the BootstrapCard link  in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2305|2024-06-04T17:29:47.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2144|2024-06-04T17:29:39.721Z -- brainstormforce -- ultimate%20addons%20for%20beaver%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20lite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2144</link>
      <description>The Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder – Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Separator widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2144|2024-06-04T17:29:39.721Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 06:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2143|2024-06-04T17:29:29.556Z -- brainstormforce -- ultimate%20addons%20for%20beaver%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20lite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2143</link>
      <description>The Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder – Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Heading widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2143|2024-06-04T17:29:29.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 06:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2142|2024-06-04T17:29:02.040Z -- brainstormforce -- ultimate%20addons%20for%20beaver%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20lite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2142</link>
      <description>The Ultimate Addons for Beaver Builder – Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Info Table widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2142|2024-06-04T17:29:02.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 06:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5757|2024-06-13T05:34:45.484Z -- brainstormforce -- elementor%20header%20%26%20footer%20builder</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5757</link>
      <description>The Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the url  attribute within the plugin's Site Title widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.35 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5757|2024-06-13T05:34:45.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 05:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1237|2024-06-24T14:57:15.567Z -- brainstormforce -- elementor%20header%20%26%20footer%20builder</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1237</link>
      <description>The Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the flyout_layout attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.24 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1237|2024-06-24T14:57:15.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1467|2024-08-01T18:40:21.081Z -- brainstormforce -- starter%20templates%20%E2%80%94%20elementor%2C%20wordpress%20%26%20beaver%20builder%20templates</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1467</link>
      <description>The Starter Templates — Elementor, WordPress &amp; Beaver Builder Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.6 via the ai_api_request(). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1467|2024-08-01T18:40:21.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1237|2024-08-01T18:33:25.334Z -- brainstormforce -- elementor%20header%20%26%20footer%20builder</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1237</link>
      <description>The Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the flyout_layout attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.24 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1237|2024-08-01T18:33:25.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1814|2024-08-01T18:48:22.115Z -- brainstormforce -- spectra%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20gutenberg%20blocks</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1814</link>
      <description>The Spectra – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Testimonial block in all versions up to, and including, 2.12.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1814|2024-08-01T18:48:22.115Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1332|2024-08-01T18:33:25.379Z -- brainstormforce -- custom%20fonts%20%E2%80%93%20host%20your%20fonts%20locally</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1332</link>
      <description>The Custom Fonts – Host Your Fonts Locally plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via svg file upload in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author level or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1332|2024-08-01T18:33:25.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 06:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1815|2024-08-01T18:48:21.997Z -- brainstormforce -- spectra%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20gutenberg%20blocks</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1815</link>
      <description>The Spectra – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Image Gallery block in all versions up to, and including, 2.12.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1815|2024-08-01T18:48:21.997Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4634|2024-08-01T20:47:41.292Z -- brainstormforce -- elementor%20header%20%26%20footer%20builder</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4634</link>
      <description>The Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘hfe_svg_mime_types’ function in versions up to, and including, 1.6.28 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4634|2024-08-01T20:47:41.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4630|2024-08-01T20:47:41.208Z -- brainstormforce -- starter%20templates%20%E2%80%94%20elementor%2C%20wordpress%20%26%20beaver%20builder%20templates</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4630</link>
      <description>The Starter Templates — Elementor, WordPress &amp; Beaver Builder Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘custom_upload_mimes’ function in versions up to, and including, 4.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4630|2024-08-01T20:47:41.208Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 04:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4366|2024-08-01T20:40:47.240Z -- brainstormforce -- spectra%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20gutenberg%20blocks</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4366</link>
      <description>The Spectra – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘block_id’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 2.13.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4366|2024-08-01T20:40:47.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6486|2024-08-02T08:28:21.812Z -- brainstormforce -- spectra%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20gutenberg%20blocks</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6486</link>
      <description>The Spectra – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Custom CSS metabox in all versions up to and including 2.10.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6486|2024-08-02T08:28:21.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
