<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for NIKON -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nikon/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for NIKON -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:19:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40657|2024-08-03T12:21:46.593Z -- nikon -- nis-elements%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40657</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NIKON NIS-Elements Viewer 1.2100.1483.0. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PSD files. Crafted data in a PSD file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15073.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40657|2024-08-03T12:21:46.593Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 15:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40663|2024-08-03T12:21:46.587Z -- nikon -- nis-elements%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40663</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NIKON NIS-Elements Viewer 1.2100.1483.0. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF images. Crafted data in a TIF image can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15697.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40663|2024-08-03T12:21:46.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 15:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40656|2024-08-03T12:21:46.580Z -- nikon -- nis-elements%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40656</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NIKON NIS-Elements Viewer 13.2.0.21165. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of ND2 files. Crafted data in a ND2 file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15072.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40656|2024-08-03T12:21:46.580Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 15:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40659|2024-08-03T12:21:46.629Z -- nikon -- nis-elements%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40659</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NIKON NIS-Elements Viewer 1.2100.1483.0. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF images. Crafted data in a TIF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15214.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40659|2024-08-03T12:21:46.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 15:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40655|2024-08-03T12:21:46.629Z -- nikon -- nis-elements%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40655</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NIKON NIS-Elements Viewer 1.2100.1483.0. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of ND2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15071.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40655|2024-08-03T12:21:46.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 15:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40662|2024-08-03T12:21:46.598Z -- nikon -- nis-elements%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40662</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NIKON NIS-Elements Viewer 1.2100.1483.0. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF images. Crafted data in a TIF image can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15351.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40662|2024-08-03T12:21:46.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 15:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40658|2024-08-03T12:21:46.683Z -- nikon -- nis-elements%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40658</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NIKON NIS-Elements Viewer 1.2100.1483.0. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF images. Crafted data in a TIF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15166.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40658|2024-08-03T12:21:46.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 15:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40661|2024-08-03T12:21:46.628Z -- nikon -- nis-elements%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40661</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NIKON NIS-Elements Viewer 1.2100.1483.0. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of BMP images. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15134.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40661|2024-08-03T12:21:46.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 15:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40660|2024-08-03T12:21:46.591Z -- nikon -- nis-elements%20viewer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40660</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NIKON NIS-Elements Viewer 1.2100.1483.0. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PSD images. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15135.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40660|2024-08-03T12:21:46.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 15:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
