<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dromara -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dromara/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dromara -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 13:24:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3276|2024-08-02T06:48:08.457Z -- dromara -- hutool
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3276</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Dromara HuTool up to 5.8.19. Affected by this issue is the function readBySax of the file XmlUtil.java of the component XML Parsing Module. The manipulation leads to xml external entity reference. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-231626 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Dromara HuTool bis 5.8.19 entdeckt. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion readBySax der Datei XmlUtil.java der Komponente XML Parsing Module. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine xml external entity reference-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3276|2024-08-02T06:48:08.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2476|2024-08-02T06:26:08.853Z -- dromara -- j2eefast
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2476</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Dromara J2eeFAST up to 2.6.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the component Announcement Handler. The manipulation of the argument 系统工具/公告管理 leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is 7a9e1a00e3329fdc0ae05f7a8257cce77037134d. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227868.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Dromara J2eeFAST bis 2.6.0 ausgemacht. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Komponente Announcement Handler. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments 系统工具/公告管理 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Der Patch wird als 7a9e1a00e3329fdc0ae05f7a8257cce77037134d bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2476|2024-08-02T06:26:08.853Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 13:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2475|2024-08-02T06:26:08.654Z -- dromara -- j2eefast
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2475</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Dromara J2eeFAST up to 2.6.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component System Message Handler. The manipulation of the argument 主题 leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is named 7a9e1a00e3329fdc0ae05f7a8257cce77037134d. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227867.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Dromara J2eeFAST bis 2.6.0 gefunden. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Komponente System Message Handler. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments 主题 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Der Patch wird als 7a9e1a00e3329fdc0ae05f7a8257cce77037134d bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2475|2024-08-02T06:26:08.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 13:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51653|2024-07-25T18:12:39.492Z -- dromara -- hertzbeat</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51653</link>
      <description>Hertzbeat is a real-time monitoring system. In the implementation of `JmxCollectImpl.java`, `JMXConnectorFactory.connect` is vulnerable to JNDI injection. The corresponding interface is `/api/monitor/detect`. If there is a URL field, the address will be used by default. When the URL is `service:jmx:rmi:///jndi/rmi://xxxxxxx:1099/localHikari`, it can be exploited to cause remote code execution. Version 1.4.1 contains a fix for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51653|2024-07-25T18:12:39.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 15:39:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3928|2024-06-06T19:44:38.894Z -- dromara -- open-capacity-platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3928</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Dromara open-capacity-platform 2.0.1. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /actuator/heapdump of the component auth-server. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261367.
In Dromara open-capacity-platform 2.0.1 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /actuator/heapdump der Komponente auth-server. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3928|2024-06-06T19:44:38.894Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 23:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51388|2024-02-22T15:53:46.458Z -- dromara -- hertzbeat</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51388</link>
      <description>Hertzbeat is a real-time monitoring system. In `CalculateAlarm.java`, `AviatorEvaluator` is used to directly execute the expression function, and no security policy is configured, resulting in AviatorScript (which can execute any static method by default) script injection. Version 1.4.1 fixes this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51388|2024-02-22T15:53:46.458Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51653|2024-02-22T15:39:49.280Z -- dromara -- hertzbeat</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51653</link>
      <description>Hertzbeat is a real-time monitoring system. In the implementation of `JmxCollectImpl.java`, `JMXConnectorFactory.connect` is vulnerable to JNDI injection. The corresponding interface is `/api/monitor/detect`. If there is a URL field, the address will be used by default. When the URL is `service:jmx:rmi:///jndi/rmi://xxxxxxx:1099/localHikari`, it can be exploited to cause remote code execution. Version 1.4.1 contains a fix for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51653|2024-02-22T15:39:49.280Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 15:39:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51389|2024-02-22T15:59:29.842Z -- dromara -- hertzbeat</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51389</link>
      <description>Hertzbeat is a real-time monitoring system. At the interface of `/define/yml`, SnakeYAML is used as a parser to parse yml content, but no security configuration is used, resulting in a YAML deserialization vulnerability. Version 1.4.1 fixes this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51389|2024-02-22T15:59:29.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 15:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3928|2024-08-01T20:26:57.269Z -- dromara -- open-capacity-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3928</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Dromara open-capacity-platform 2.0.1. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /actuator/heapdump of the component auth-server. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261367.
In Dromara open-capacity-platform 2.0.1 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /actuator/heapdump der Komponente auth-server. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3928|2024-08-01T20:26:57.269Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 23:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
