<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for dromara -- hertzbeat</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dromara/hertzbeat.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for dromara -- hertzbeat</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51389|2024-02-22T15:59:29.842Z -- dromara -- hertzbeat
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51389</link>
      <description>Hertzbeat is a real-time monitoring system. At the interface of `/define/yml`, SnakeYAML is used as a parser to parse yml content, but no security configuration is used, resulting in a YAML deserialization vulnerability. Version 1.4.1 fixes this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51389|2024-02-22T15:59:29.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 15:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51653|2024-02-22T15:39:49.280Z -- dromara -- hertzbeat
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51653</link>
      <description>Hertzbeat is a real-time monitoring system. In the implementation of `JmxCollectImpl.java`, `JMXConnectorFactory.connect` is vulnerable to JNDI injection. The corresponding interface is `/api/monitor/detect`. If there is a URL field, the address will be used by default. When the URL is `service:jmx:rmi:///jndi/rmi://xxxxxxx:1099/localHikari`, it can be exploited to cause remote code execution. Version 1.4.1 contains a fix for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51653|2024-02-22T15:39:49.280Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 15:39:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51388|2024-02-22T15:53:46.458Z -- dromara -- hertzbeat
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51388</link>
      <description>Hertzbeat is a real-time monitoring system. In `CalculateAlarm.java`, `AviatorEvaluator` is used to directly execute the expression function, and no security policy is configured, resulting in AviatorScript (which can execute any static method by default) script injection. Version 1.4.1 fixes this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51388|2024-02-22T15:53:46.458Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51387|2023-12-22T20:46:29.236Z -- dromara -- hertzbeat
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51387</link>
      <description>Hertzbeat is an open source, real-time monitoring system. Hertzbeat uses aviatorscript to evaluate alert expressions. The alert expressions are supposed to be some simple expressions. However, due to improper sanitization for alert expressions in version prior to 1.4.1, a malicious user can use a crafted alert expression to execute any command on hertzbeat server. A malicious user who has access to alert define function can execute any command in hertzbeat instance. This issue is fixed in version 1.4.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51387|2023-12-22T20:46:29.236Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 20:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51650|2023-12-22T20:56:37.097Z -- dromara -- hertzbeat
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51650</link>
      <description>Hertzbeat is an open source, real-time monitoring system. Prior to version 1.4.1, Spring Boot permission configuration issues caused unauthorized access vulnerabilities to three interfaces. This could result in disclosure of sensitive server information. Version 1.4.1 fixes this issue.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51650|2023-12-22T20:56:37.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 20:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
