<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for flusity -- CMS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/flusity/cms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for flusity -- CMS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 20:23:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5810|2024-09-09T15:28:04.862Z -- flusity -- cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5810</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in flusity CMS. This issue affects the function loadPostAddForm of the file core/tools/posts.php. The manipulation of the argument edit_post_id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The identifier of the patch is 6943991c62ed87c7a57989a0cb7077316127def8. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-243641 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in flusity CMS entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion loadPostAddForm der Datei core/tools/posts.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments edit_post_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Dieses Produkt setzt Rolling Releases ein. Aus diesem Grund sind Details zu betroffenen oder zu aktualisierende Versionen nicht verfügbar. Der Patch wird als 6943991c62ed87c7a57989a0cb7077316127def8 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5810|2024-09-09T15:28:04.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
