<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for flusity -- CMS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/flusity/cms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for flusity -- CMS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:23:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5811|2024-08-02T08:14:24.029Z -- flusity -- cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5811</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in flusity CMS. Affected is the function loadPostAddForm of the file core/tools/posts.php. The manipulation of the argument menu_id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The patch is identified as 6943991c62ed87c7a57989a0cb7077316127def8. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-243642 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in flusity CMS gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um die Funktion loadPostAddForm der Datei core/tools/posts.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments menu_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Dieses Produkt verzichtet auf eine Versionierung und verwendet stattdessen Rolling Releases. Deshalb sind keine Details zu betroffenen oder zu aktualisierende Versionen vorhanden. Der Patch wird als 6943991c62ed87c7a57989a0cb7077316127def8 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5811|2024-08-02T08:14:24.029Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5812|2024-08-02T08:14:24.284Z -- flusity -- cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5812</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in flusity CMS and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function handleFileUpload of the file core/tools/upload.php. The manipulation of the argument uploaded_file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243643.
In flusity CMS wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um die Funktion handleFileUpload der Datei core/tools/upload.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments uploaded_file mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Dieses Produkt setzt Rolling Releases ein. Aus diesem Grund sind Details zu betroffenen oder zu aktualisierende Versionen nicht verfügbar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5812|2024-08-02T08:14:24.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 01:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5793|2024-08-02T08:07:32.665Z -- flusity -- cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5793</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in flusity CMS and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function loadCustomBlocCreateForm of the file /core/tools/customblock.php of the component Dashboard. The manipulation of the argument customblock_place leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The patch is named 81252bc764e1de2422e79e36194bba1289e7a0a5. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243599.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in flusity CMS gefunden. Hierbei geht es um die Funktion loadCustomBlocCreateForm der Datei /core/tools/customblock.php der Komponente Dashboard. Durch Manipulation des Arguments customblock_place mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Dieses Produkt setzt Rolling Releases ein. Aus diesem Grund sind Details zu betroffenen oder zu aktualisierende Versionen nicht verfügbar. Der Patch wird als 81252bc764e1de2422e79e36194bba1289e7a0a5 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5793|2024-08-02T08:07:32.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5810|2024-08-02T08:14:24.110Z -- flusity -- cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5810</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in flusity CMS. This issue affects the function loadPostAddForm of the file core/tools/posts.php. The manipulation of the argument edit_post_id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The identifier of the patch is 6943991c62ed87c7a57989a0cb7077316127def8. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-243641 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in flusity CMS entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion loadPostAddForm der Datei core/tools/posts.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments edit_post_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Dieses Produkt setzt Rolling Releases ein. Aus diesem Grund sind Details zu betroffenen oder zu aktualisierende Versionen nicht verfügbar. Der Patch wird als 6943991c62ed87c7a57989a0cb7077316127def8 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5810|2024-08-02T08:14:24.110Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
