<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for drybjed -- ansible-ntp</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/drybjed/ansible-ntp.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for drybjed -- ansible-ntp</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 17:22:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125036|2024-08-06T14:10:56.665Z -- drybjed -- ansible-ntp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125036</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in drybjed ansible-ntp. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file meta/main.yml. The manipulation leads to insufficient control of network message volume. The attack can only be done within the local network. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The patch is identified as ed4ca2cf012677973c220cdba36b5c60bfa0260b. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-217190 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in drybjed ansible-ntp entdeckt. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei meta/main.yml. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine insufficient control of network message volume-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann im lokalen Netzwerk erfolgen. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie ist schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Patch wird als ed4ca2cf012677973c220cdba36b5c60bfa0260b bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125036|2024-08-06T14:10:56.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
