<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for omardabbas -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/omardabbas/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for omardabbas -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:39:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-9377|2024-10-10T02:06:08.702Z -- omardabbas -- products%2C%20order%20%26%20customers%20export%20for%20woocommerce
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9377</link>
      <description>The Products, Order &amp; Customers Export for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg &amp; remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.15. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-9377|2024-10-10T02:06:08.702Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 02:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8788|2024-09-30T15:03:48.662Z -- omardabbas -- eu%2Fuk%20vat%20manager%20for%20woocommerce</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8788</link>
      <description>The EU/UK VAT Manager for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.12.11. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8788|2024-09-30T15:03:48.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 02:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-9189|2024-09-30T15:45:18.049Z -- omardabbas -- eu%2Fuk%20vat%20manager%20for%20woocommerce</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9189</link>
      <description>The EU/UK VAT Manager for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the alg_wc_eu_vat_exempt_vat_from_admin() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.12.12. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the VAT status for any order.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-9189|2024-09-30T15:45:18.049Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 02:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
