<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Shoplazza -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/shoplazza/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Shoplazza -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:23:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4601|2024-08-03T01:41:45.710Z -- shoplazza -- lifestyle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4601</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Shoplazza LifeStyle 1.1. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/api/theme-edit/ of the component Shipping/Member Discount/Icon. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-216196.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4601|2024-08-03T01:41:45.710Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4599|2024-08-03T01:41:45.604Z -- shoplazza -- lifestyle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4599</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Shoplazza LifeStyle 1.1 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/api/theme-edit/ of the component Product Handler. The manipulation of the argument Subheading/Heading/Text/Button Text/Label leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-216194 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4599|2024-08-03T01:41:45.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4598|2024-08-03T01:41:45.793Z -- shoplazza -- lifestyle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4598</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Shoplazza LifeStyle 1.1 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/api/theme-edit/ of the component Announcement Handler. The manipulation of the argument Text/Mobile Text leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-216193 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4598|2024-08-03T01:41:45.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4600|2024-08-03T01:41:45.790Z -- shoplazza -- lifestyle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4600</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Shoplazza LifeStyle 1.1. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/api/theme-edit/ of the component Product Carousel Handler. The manipulation of the argument Heading/Description leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-216195.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4600|2024-08-03T01:41:45.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4602|2024-08-03T01:41:45.769Z -- shoplazza -- lifestyle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4602</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Shoplazza LifeStyle 1.1. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/api/theme-edit/ of the component Review Flow Handler. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-216197 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4602|2024-08-03T01:41:45.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4597|2024-08-03T01:41:45.616Z -- shoplazza -- lifestyle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4597</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Shoplazza LifeStyle 1.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/api/admin/v2_products of the component Create Product Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-216192.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4597|2024-08-03T01:41:45.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
