<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Ikea -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ikea/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Ikea -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 12:25:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39064|2024-08-03T11:10:32.467Z -- ikea -- tr%C3%A5dfri%20smart%20lighting%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39064</link>
      <description>An attacker sending a single malformed IEEE 802.15.4 (Zigbee) frame makes the TRÅDFRI bulb blink, and if they replay (i.e. resend) the same frame multiple times, the bulb performs a factory reset. This causes the bulb to lose configuration information about the Zigbee network and current brightness level. After this attack, all lights are on with full brightness, and a user cannot control the bulbs with either the IKEA Home Smart app or the TRÅDFRI remote control. The malformed Zigbee frame is an unauthenticated broadcast message, which means all vulnerable devices within radio range are affected. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.1 vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:A/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:H</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39064|2024-08-03T11:10:32.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39065|2024-08-03T11:10:32.391Z -- ikea -- tr%C3%A5dfri%20gateway%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39065</link>
      <description>A single malformed IEEE 802.15.4 (Zigbee) frame makes the TRÅDFRI gateway unresponsive, such that connected lighting cannot be controlled with the IKEA Home Smart app and TRÅDFRI remote control. The malformed Zigbee frame is an unauthenticated broadcast message, which means all vulnerable devices within radio range are affected. CVSS 3.1 Base Score: 6.5 Vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:A/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39065|2024-08-03T11:10:32.391Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
