<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Indeed Engineering -- util</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/indeed%20engineering/util.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Indeed Engineering -- util</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 18:24:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36634|2024-08-04T17:30:08.391Z -- indeed%20engineering -- util
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36634</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Indeed Engineering util up to 1.0.33. Affected is the function visit/appendTo of the file varexport/src/main/java/com/indeed/util/varexport/servlet/ViewExportedVariablesServlet.java. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 1.0.34 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is c0952a9db51a880e9544d9fac2a2218a6bfc9c63. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-216882 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Indeed Engineering util bis 1.0.33 entdeckt. Es geht dabei um die Funktion visit/appendTo der Datei varexport/src/main/java/com/indeed/util/varexport/servlet/ViewExportedVariablesServlet.java. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.0.34 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als c0952a9db51a880e9544d9fac2a2218a6bfc9c63 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36634|2024-08-04T17:30:08.391Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
