<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for graphql -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/graphql/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for graphql -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 15:22:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41249|2024-08-04T03:08:31.577Z -- graphql -- graphql-playground
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41249</link>
      <description>GraphQL Playground is a GraphQL IDE for development of graphQL focused applications. All versions of graphql-playground-react older than graphql-playground-react@1.7.28 are vulnerable to compromised HTTP schema introspection responses or schema prop values with malicious GraphQL type names, exposing a dynamic XSS attack surface that can allow code injection on operation autocomplete. In order for the attack to take place, the user must load a malicious schema in graphql-playground. There are several ways this can occur, including by specifying the URL to a malicious schema in the endpoint query parameter. If a user clicks on a link to a GraphQL Playground installation that specifies a malicious server, arbitrary JavaScript can run in the user's browser, which can be used to exfiltrate user credentials or other harmful goals. If you are using graphql-playground-react directly in your client app, upgrade to version 1.7.28 or later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41249|2024-08-04T03:08:31.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 20:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41248|2024-08-04T03:08:31.617Z -- graphql -- graphiql
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41248</link>
      <description>GraphiQL is the reference implementation of this monorepo, GraphQL IDE, an official project under the GraphQL Foundation. All versions of graphiql older than graphiql@1.4.7 are vulnerable to compromised HTTP schema introspection responses or schema prop values with malicious GraphQL type names, exposing a dynamic XSS attack surface that can allow code injection on operation autocomplete. In order for the attack to take place, the user must load a vulnerable schema in graphiql. There are a number of ways that can occur. By default, the schema URL is not attacker-controllable in graphiql or in its suggested implementations or examples, leaving only very complex attack vectors. If a custom implementation of graphiql's fetcher allows the schema URL to be set dynamically, such as a URL query parameter like ?endpoint= in graphql-playground, or a database provided value, then this custom graphiql implementation is vulnerable to phishing attacks, and thus much more readily available, low or no privelege level xss attacks. The URLs could look like any generic looking graphql schema URL. It should be noted that desktop clients such as Altair, Insomnia, Postwoman, do not appear to be impacted by this. This vulnerability does not impact codemirror-graphql, monaco-graphql or other dependents, as it exists in onHasCompletion.ts in graphiql. It does impact all forks of graphiql, and every released version of graphiql.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41248|2024-08-04T03:08:31.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 20:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
