<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TechPowerUp -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/techpowerup/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TechPowerUp -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:23:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1048|2024-08-02T05:32:46.247Z -- techpowerup -- ryzen%20dram%20calculator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1048</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TechPowerUp Ryzen DRAM Calculator 1.2.0.5. This issue affects some unknown processing in the library WinRing0x64.sys. The manipulation leads to improper initialization. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-221807.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TechPowerUp Ryzen DRAM Calculator 1.2.0.5 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil in der Bibliothek WinRing0x64.sys. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper initialization-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden muss der Angriff lokal. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1048|2024-08-02T05:32:46.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 12:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1047|2024-08-02T05:32:46.332Z -- techpowerup -- realtemp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1047</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TechPowerUp RealTemp 3.7.0.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code in the library WinRing0x64.sys. The manipulation leads to improper initialization. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-221806 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In TechPowerUp RealTemp 3.7.0.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität in der Bibliothek WinRing0x64.sys. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper initialization-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs hat dabei lokal zu erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1047|2024-08-02T05:32:46.332Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 12:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
