<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for elabftw -- elabftw</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/elabftw/elabftw.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for elabftw -- elabftw</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 09:23:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43834|2024-08-04T04:10:15.748Z -- elabftw -- elabftw
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43834</link>
      <description>eLabFTW is an electronic lab notebook manager for research teams. In versions prior to 4.2.0 there is a vulnerability which allows an attacker to authenticate as an existing user, if that user was created using a single sign-on authentication option such as LDAP or SAML. It impacts instances where LDAP or SAML is used for authentication instead of the (default) local password mechanism. Users should upgrade to at least version 4.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43834|2024-08-04T04:10:15.748Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 23:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41171|2024-08-04T02:59:31.546Z -- elabftw -- elabftw
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41171</link>
      <description>eLabFTW is an open source electronic lab notebook manager for research teams. In versions of eLabFTW before 4.1.0, it allows attackers to bypass a brute-force protection mechanism by using many different forged PHPSESSID values in HTTP Cookie header. This issue has been addressed by implementing brute force login protection, as recommended by Owasp with Device Cookies. This mechanism will not impact users and will effectively thwart any brute-force attempts at guessing passwords. The only correct way to address this is to upgrade to version 4.1.0. Adding rate limitation upstream of the eLabFTW service is of course a valid option, with or without upgrading.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41171|2024-08-04T02:59:31.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 18:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43833|2024-08-04T04:10:15.695Z -- elabftw -- elabftw
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43833</link>
      <description>eLabFTW is an electronic lab notebook manager for research teams. In versions prior to 4.2.0 there is a vulnerability which allows any authenticated user to gain access to arbitrary accounts by setting a specially crafted email address. This vulnerability impacts all instances that have not set an explicit email domain name allowlist. Note that whereas neither administrators nor targeted users are notified of a change, an attacker will need to control an account. The default settings require administrators to validate newly created accounts. The problem has been patched. Users should upgrade to at least version 4.2.0. For users unable to upgrade enabling an email domain allow list (from Sysconfig panel, Security tab) will completely resolve the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43833|2024-08-04T04:10:15.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 23:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
