<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for BlackBerry -- QNX Software Development Platform (QNX SDP)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/blackberry/qnx%20software%20development%20platform%20%28qnx%20sdp%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for BlackBerry -- QNX Software Development Platform (QNX SDP)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:22:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3892|2024-08-05T14:39:41.193Z -- blackberry -- qnx%20software%20development%20platform%20%28qnx%20sdp%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3892</link>
      <description>In BlackBerry QNX Software Development Platform (SDP) 6.6.0, an information disclosure vulnerability in the default configuration of the QNX SDP could allow an attacker to gain information relating to memory layout that could be used in a blended attack by executing commands targeting procfs resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3892|2024-08-05T14:39:41.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-9371|2024-08-05T17:02:44.372Z -- blackberry -- qnx%20software%20development%20platform%20%28qnx%20sdp%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-9371</link>
      <description>In BlackBerry QNX Software Development Platform (SDP) 6.6.0 and 6.5.0 SP1 and earlier, a loss of integrity vulnerability in the default configuration of the QNX SDP could allow an attacker being able to reduce the entropy of the PRNG, making other blended attacks more practical by gaining control over environmental factors that influence seed generation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-9371|2024-08-05T17:02:44.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-9369|2024-08-05T17:02:44.381Z -- blackberry -- qnx%20software%20development%20platform%20%28qnx%20sdp%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-9369</link>
      <description>In BlackBerry QNX Software Development Platform (SDP) 6.6.0 and 6.5.0 SP1 and earlier, an information disclosure vulnerability in the default configuration of the QNX SDP could allow an attacker to gain information relating to memory layout of higher privileged processes by manipulating environment variables that influence the loader.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-9369|2024-08-05T17:02:44.381Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3891|2024-08-05T14:39:41.298Z -- blackberry -- qnx%20software%20development%20platform%20%28qnx%20sdp%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3891</link>
      <description>In BlackBerry QNX Software Development Platform (SDP) 6.6.0, an elevation of privilege vulnerability in the default configuration of the QNX SDP with QNet enabled on networks comprising two or more QNet nodes could allow an attacker to access local and remote files or take ownership of files on other QNX nodes regardless of permissions by executing commands targeting arbitrary nodes from a secondary QNX 6.6.0 QNet node.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3891|2024-08-05T14:39:41.298Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3893|2024-08-05T14:39:41.483Z -- blackberry -- qnx%20software%20development%20platform%20%28qnx%20sdp%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3893</link>
      <description>In BlackBerry QNX Software Development Platform (SDP) 6.6.0, the default configuration of the QNX SDP system did not in all circumstances prevent attackers from modifying the GOT or PLT tables with buffer overflow attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3893|2024-08-05T14:39:41.483Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
