<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for HackerOne -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/hackerone/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for HackerOne -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 08:24:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16074|2024-09-17T01:42:04.209Z -- hackerone -- crossenv%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16074</link>
      <description>crossenv was a malicious module published with the intent to hijack environment variables. It has been unpublished by npm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16074|2024-09-17T01:42:04.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16115|2024-09-17T01:12:20.165Z -- hackerone -- timespan%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16115</link>
      <description>The timespan module is vulnerable to regular expression denial of service. Given 50k characters of untrusted user input it will block the event loop for around 10 seconds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16115|2024-09-17T01:12:20.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10681|2024-09-17T02:20:41.157Z -- hackerone -- roslib-socketio%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10681</link>
      <description>roslib-socketio - The standard ROS Javascript Library fork for add support to socket.io roslib-socketio downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10681|2024-09-17T02:20:41.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16213|2024-09-17T03:03:32.402Z -- hackerone -- mfrserver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16213</link>
      <description>mfrserver is a simple file server. mfrserver is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16213|2024-09-17T03:03:32.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10562|2024-09-17T04:14:46.356Z -- hackerone -- iedriver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10562</link>
      <description>iedriver is an NPM wrapper for Selenium IEDriver. iedriver versions below 3.0.0 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves the module vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10562|2024-09-17T04:14:46.356Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16109|2024-09-17T02:20:42.989Z -- hackerone -- easyquick%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16109</link>
      <description>easyquick is a simple web server. easyquick is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url. Access is constrained, however, to supported file types. Requesting a file such as /etc/passwd returns a "not supported" error.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16109|2024-09-17T02:20:42.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16130|2024-09-17T03:43:42.412Z -- hackerone -- exxxxxxxxxxx%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16130</link>
      <description>exxxxxxxxxxx is an Http eX Frame Google Style JavaScript Guide. exxxxxxxxxxx is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url. Accessible files are restricted to those with a file extension. Files with no extension such as /etc/passwd throw an error.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16130|2024-09-17T03:43:42.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-9242|2024-09-17T03:12:59.354Z -- hackerone -- ecstatic%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-9242</link>
      <description>Certain input strings when passed to new Date() or Date.parse() in ecstatic node module before 1.4.0 will cause v8 to raise an exception. This leads to a crash and denial of service in ecstatic when this input is passed into the server via the If-Modified-Since header.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-9242|2024-09-17T03:12:59.354Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10684|2024-09-17T00:16:26.720Z -- hackerone -- healthcenter%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10684</link>
      <description>healthcenter - IBM Monitoring and Diagnostic Tools health Center agent healthcenter downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10684|2024-09-17T00:16:26.720Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10543|2024-09-17T00:22:05.189Z -- hackerone -- call%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10543</link>
      <description>call is an HTTP router that is primarily used by the hapi framework. There exists a bug in call versions 2.0.1-3.0.1 that does not validate empty parameters, which could result in invalid input bypassing the route validation rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10543|2024-09-17T00:22:05.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10564|2024-09-17T01:26:03.354Z -- hackerone -- apk-parser%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10564</link>
      <description>apk-parser is a tool to extract Android Manifest info from an APK file. apk-parser versions below 0.1.6 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10564|2024-09-17T01:26:03.354Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10662|2024-09-17T02:11:25.036Z -- hackerone -- tomita%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10662</link>
      <description>tomita is a node wrapper for Yandex Tomita Parser tomita downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10662|2024-09-17T02:11:25.036Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16055|2024-09-17T01:10:56.654Z -- hackerone -- sqlserver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16055</link>
      <description>`sqlserver` was a malicious module published with the intent to hijack environment variables. It has been unpublished by npm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16055|2024-09-17T01:10:56.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16110|2024-09-17T02:27:30.487Z -- hackerone -- weather.swlyons%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16110</link>
      <description>weather.swlyons is a simple web server for weather updates. weather.swlyons is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16110|2024-09-17T02:27:30.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16211|2024-09-17T02:11:33.978Z -- hackerone -- lessindex%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16211</link>
      <description>lessindex is a static file server. lessindex is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16211|2024-09-17T02:11:33.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10536|2024-09-17T01:46:42.911Z -- hackerone -- engine.io-client%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10536</link>
      <description>engine.io-client is the client for engine.io, the implementation of a transport-based cross-browser/cross-device bi-directional communication layer for Socket.IO. The vulnerability is related to the way that node.js handles the `rejectUnauthorized` setting. If the value is something that evaluates to false, certificate verification will be disabled. This is problematic as engine.io-client 1.6.8 and earlier passes in an object for settings that includes the rejectUnauthorized property, whether it has been set or not. If the value has not been explicitly changed, it will be passed in as `null`, resulting in certificate verification being turned off.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10536|2024-09-17T01:46:42.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16030|2024-09-17T00:41:28.696Z -- hackerone -- useragent%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16030</link>
      <description>Useragent is used to parse useragent headers. It uses several regular expressions to accomplish this. An attacker could edit their own headers, creating an arbitrarily long useragent string, causing the event loop and server to block. This affects Useragent 2.1.12 and earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16030|2024-09-17T00:41:28.696Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3734|2024-09-17T02:26:33.956Z -- hackerone -- stattic%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3734</link>
      <description>stattic node module suffers from a Path Traversal vulnerability due to lack of validation of path, which allows a malicious user to read content of any file with known path.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3734|2024-09-17T02:26:33.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16057|2024-09-17T00:15:50.693Z -- hackerone -- nodemssql%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16057</link>
      <description>nodemssql was a malicious module published with the intent to hijack environment variables. It has been unpublished by npm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16057|2024-09-17T00:15:50.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10686|2024-09-17T03:38:24.495Z -- hackerone -- fis-sass-all%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10686</link>
      <description>fis-sass-all is another libsass wrapper for node. fis-sass-all downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10686|2024-09-17T03:38:24.495Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16166|2024-09-17T02:42:10.339Z -- hackerone -- byucslabsix%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16166</link>
      <description>byucslabsix is an http server. byucslabsix is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16166|2024-09-17T02:42:10.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16176|2024-09-17T02:27:42.811Z -- hackerone -- jansenstuffpleasework%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16176</link>
      <description>jansenstuffpleasework is a file server. jansenstuffpleasework is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16176|2024-09-17T02:27:42.811Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10602|2024-09-17T03:17:58.934Z -- hackerone -- haxe%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10602</link>
      <description>haxe is a cross-platform toolkit haxe downloads zipped resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested zip file with an attacker controlled zip file if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10602|2024-09-17T03:17:58.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16044|2024-09-17T00:21:50.833Z -- hackerone -- d3.js%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16044</link>
      <description>`d3.js` was a malicious module published with the intent to hijack environment variables. It has been unpublished by npm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16044|2024-09-17T00:21:50.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16175|2024-09-17T01:21:42.413Z -- hackerone -- ewgaddis.lab6%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16175</link>
      <description>ewgaddis.lab6 is a file server. ewgaddis.lab6 is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16175|2024-09-17T01:21:42.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16023|2024-09-17T01:01:40.957Z -- hackerone -- decamelize%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16023</link>
      <description>Decamelize is used to convert a dash/dot/underscore/space separated string to camelCase. Decamelize 1.1.0 through 1.1.1 uses regular expressions to evaluate a string and takes unescaped separator values, which can be used to create a denial of service attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16023|2024-09-17T01:01:40.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10603|2024-09-17T03:23:52.030Z -- hackerone -- air-sdk%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10603</link>
      <description>air-sdk is a NPM wrapper for the Adobe AIR SDK. air-sdk downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10603|2024-09-17T03:23:52.030Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10631|2024-09-17T00:17:09.947Z -- hackerone -- jvminstall%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10631</link>
      <description>jvminstall is a module for downloading and unpacking jvm to local system. jvminstall downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10631|2024-09-17T00:17:09.947Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16006|2024-09-17T03:01:59.476Z -- hackerone -- remarkable%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16006</link>
      <description>Remarkable is a markdown parser. In versions 1.6.2 and lower, remarkable allows the use of `data:` URIs in links and can therefore execute javascript.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16006|2024-09-17T03:01:59.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-9243|2024-09-17T02:27:19.677Z -- hackerone -- hapi%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-9243</link>
      <description>When server level, connection level or route level CORS configurations in hapi node module before 11.1.4 are combined and when a higher level config included security restrictions (like origin), a higher level config that included security restrictions (like origin) would have those restrictions overridden by less restrictive defaults (e.g. origin defaults to all origins `*`).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-9243|2024-09-17T02:27:19.677Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16121|2024-09-17T02:15:46.516Z -- hackerone -- datachannel-client%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16121</link>
      <description>datachannel-client is a signaling implementation for DataChannel.js. datachannel-client is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16121|2024-09-17T02:15:46.516Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16071|2024-09-17T01:25:34.845Z -- hackerone -- nodemailer-js%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16071</link>
      <description>nodemailer-js was a malicious module published with the intent to hijack environment variables. It has been unpublished by npm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16071|2024-09-17T01:25:34.845Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10628|2024-09-17T03:42:50.199Z -- hackerone -- selenium-wrapper%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10628</link>
      <description>selenium-wrapper is a selenium server wrapper, including installation and chrome webdriver. selenium-wrapper downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10628|2024-09-17T03:42:50.199Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10528|2024-09-17T01:30:39.884Z -- hackerone -- restafary%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10528</link>
      <description>restafary is a REpresentful State Transfer API for Creating, Reading, Using, Deleting files on a server from the web. Restafary before 1.6.1 is able to set up a root path, which should only allow it to run inside of that root path it specified.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10528|2024-09-17T01:30:39.884Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16181|2024-09-17T03:48:01.989Z -- hackerone -- wintiwebdev%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16181</link>
      <description>wintiwebdev is a static file server. wintiwebdev is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16181|2024-09-17T03:48:01.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16051|2024-09-17T01:36:13.920Z -- hackerone -- sqliter%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16051</link>
      <description>`sqliter` was a malicious module published with the intent to hijack environment variables. It has been unpublished by npm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16051|2024-09-17T01:36:13.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16120|2024-09-17T01:31:37.503Z -- hackerone -- liyujing%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16120</link>
      <description>liyujing is a static file server. liyujing is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16120|2024-09-17T01:31:37.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16103|2024-09-17T01:11:53.088Z -- hackerone -- serveryztyzt%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16103</link>
      <description>serveryztyzt is a simple http server. serveryztyzt is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the URL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16103|2024-09-17T01:11:53.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10672|2024-09-17T03:34:00.636Z -- hackerone -- cloudpub-redis%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10672</link>
      <description>cloudpub-redis is a module for CloudPub: Redis Backend cloudpub-redis downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10672|2024-09-17T03:34:00.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10666|2024-09-17T03:39:02.884Z -- hackerone -- tomita-parser%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10666</link>
      <description>tomita-parser is a Node wrapper for Yandex Tomita Parser tomita-parser downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10666|2024-09-17T03:39:02.884Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10690|2024-09-17T03:43:57.111Z -- hackerone -- openframe-ascii-image%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10690</link>
      <description>openframe-ascii-image module is an openframe plugin which adds support for ascii images via fim. openframe-ascii-image downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10690|2024-09-17T03:43:57.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16097|2024-09-17T00:30:39.731Z -- hackerone -- tiny-http%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16097</link>
      <description>tiny-http is a simple http server. tiny-http is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16097|2024-09-17T00:30:39.731Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16017|2024-09-17T01:40:49.487Z -- hackerone -- sanitize-html%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16017</link>
      <description>sanitize-html is a library for scrubbing html input for malicious values Versions 1.2.2 and below have a cross site scripting vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16017|2024-09-17T01:40:49.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16086|2024-09-17T00:31:35.528Z -- hackerone -- ua-parser%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16086</link>
      <description>ua-parser is a port of Browserscope's user agent parser. ua-parser is vulnerable to a ReDoS (Regular Expression Denial of Service) attack when given a specially crafted UserAgent header.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16086|2024-09-17T00:31:35.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16152|2024-09-17T02:37:05.290Z -- hackerone -- static-html-server%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16152</link>
      <description>static-html-server is a static file server. static-html-server is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16152|2024-09-17T02:37:05.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16197|2024-09-17T02:53:09.329Z -- hackerone -- qinserve%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16197</link>
      <description>qinserve is a static file server. qinserve is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16197|2024-09-17T02:53:09.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10682|2024-09-17T01:21:46.325Z -- hackerone -- massif%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10682</link>
      <description>massif is a Phantomjs fork massif downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10682|2024-09-17T01:21:46.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10641|2024-09-17T02:26:43.954Z -- hackerone -- node-bsdiff-android%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10641</link>
      <description>node-bsdiff-android downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10641|2024-09-17T02:26:43.954Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3739|2024-09-17T04:25:44.584Z -- hackerone -- https-proxy-agent%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3739</link>
      <description>https-proxy-agent before 2.1.1 passes auth option to the Buffer constructor without proper sanitization, resulting in DoS and uninitialized memory leak in setups where an attacker could submit typed input to the 'auth' parameter (e.g. JSON).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3739|2024-09-17T04:25:44.584Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10683|2024-09-17T01:11:32.095Z -- hackerone -- arcanist%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10683</link>
      <description>arcanist downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10683|2024-09-17T01:11:32.095Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10544|2024-09-17T02:56:54.139Z -- hackerone -- uws%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10544</link>
      <description>uws is a WebSocket server library. By sending a 256mb websocket message to a uws server instance with permessage-deflate enabled, there is a possibility used compression will shrink said 256mb down to less than 16mb of websocket payload which passes the length check of 16mb payload. This data will then inflate up to 256mb and crash the node process by exceeding V8's maximum string size. This affects uws &gt;=0.10.0 &lt;=0.10.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10544|2024-09-17T02:56:54.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10556|2024-09-17T03:47:51.757Z -- hackerone -- sequelize%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10556</link>
      <description>sequelize is an Object-relational mapping, or a middleman to convert things from Postgres, MySQL, MariaDB, SQLite and Microsoft SQL Server into usable data for NodeJS In Postgres, SQLite, and Microsoft SQL Server there is an issue where arrays are treated as strings and improperly escaped. This causes potential SQL injection in sequelize 3.19.3 and earlier, where a malicious user could put `["test", "'); DELETE TestTable WHERE Id = 1 --')"]` inside of ``` database.query('SELECT * FROM TestTable WHERE Name IN (:names)', { replacements: { names: directCopyOfUserInput } }); ``` and cause the SQL statement to become `SELECT Id FROM Table WHERE Name IN ('test', '\'); DELETE TestTable WHERE Id = 1 --')`. In Postgres, MSSQL, and SQLite, the backslash has no special meaning. This causes the the statement to delete whichever Id has a value of 1 in the TestTable table.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10556|2024-09-17T03:47:51.757Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0899|2024-09-17T02:20:54.846Z -- hackerone -- rubygems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0899</link>
      <description>RubyGems version 2.6.12 and earlier is vulnerable to maliciously crafted gem specifications that include terminal escape characters. Printing the gem specification would execute terminal escape sequences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0899|2024-09-17T02:20:54.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10630|2024-09-17T01:21:00.795Z -- hackerone -- install-g-test%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10630</link>
      <description>install-g-test downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10630|2024-09-17T01:21:00.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16207|2024-09-17T01:21:18.986Z -- hackerone -- discordi.js%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16207</link>
      <description>discordi.js is a malicious module based on the discord.js library that exfiltrates login tokens to pastebin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16207|2024-09-17T01:21:18.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16104|2024-09-17T02:32:16.994Z -- hackerone -- citypredict.whauwiller%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16104</link>
      <description>citypredict.whauwiller is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16104|2024-09-17T02:32:16.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16095|2024-09-17T01:21:46.761Z -- hackerone -- serverliujiayi1%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16095</link>
      <description>serverliujiayi1 is a simple http server. serverliujiayi1 is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the URL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16095|2024-09-17T01:21:46.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16150|2024-09-17T03:59:54.740Z -- hackerone -- wangguojing123%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16150</link>
      <description>wanggoujing123 is a simple webserver. wanggoujing123 is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16150|2024-09-17T03:59:54.740Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10689|2024-09-17T03:54:53.079Z -- hackerone -- windows-iedriver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10689</link>
      <description>The windows-iedriver module downloads fixed version of iedriverserver.exe windows-iedriver downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10689|2024-09-17T03:54:53.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16068|2024-09-17T01:12:02.148Z -- hackerone -- ffmepg%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16068</link>
      <description>ffmepg was a malicious module published with the intent to hijack environment variables. It has been unpublished by npm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16068|2024-09-17T01:12:02.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10674|2024-09-17T02:46:58.844Z -- hackerone -- limbus-buildgen%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10674</link>
      <description>limbus-buildgen is a "build anywhere" build system. limbus-buildgen versions below 0.1.1 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10674|2024-09-17T02:46:58.844Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16016|2024-09-17T01:46:48.797Z -- hackerone -- sanitize-html%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16016</link>
      <description>Sanitize-html is a library for scrubbing html input of malicious values. Versions 1.11.1 and below are vulnerable to cross site scripting (XSS) in certain scenarios: If allowed at least one nonTextTags, the result is a potential XSS vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16016|2024-09-17T01:46:48.797Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16196|2024-09-17T00:42:07.189Z -- hackerone -- quickserver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16196</link>
      <description>quickserver is a simple static file server. quickserver is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16196|2024-09-17T00:42:07.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10622|2024-09-17T03:37:43.283Z -- hackerone -- nodeschnaps%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10622</link>
      <description>nodeschnaps is a NodeJS compatibility layer for Java (Rhino). nodeschnaps downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10622|2024-09-17T03:37:43.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10610|2024-09-17T04:29:20.044Z -- hackerone -- unicode-json%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10610</link>
      <description>unicode-json is a unicode lookup table. unicode-json before 2.0.0 downloads data resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10610|2024-09-17T04:29:20.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10606|2024-09-17T00:55:44.362Z -- hackerone -- grunt-webdriver-qunit%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10606</link>
      <description>grunt-webdriver-qunit is a grunt plugin to run qunit with webdriver in grunt grunt-webdriver-qunit downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10606|2024-09-17T00:55:44.362Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10660|2024-09-17T02:27:59.515Z -- hackerone -- fis-parser-sass-bin%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10660</link>
      <description>fis-parser-sass-bin a plugin for fis to compile sass using node-sass-binaries. fis-parser-sass-bin downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10660|2024-09-17T02:27:59.515Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16096|2024-09-17T03:19:00.448Z -- hackerone -- serveryaozeyan%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16096</link>
      <description>serveryaozeyan is a simple HTTP server. serveryaozeyan is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the URL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16096|2024-09-17T03:19:00.448Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-10067|2024-09-17T00:11:12.478Z -- hackerone -- paypal-ipn%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-10067</link>
      <description>paypal-ipn before 3.0.0 uses the `test_ipn` parameter (which is set by the PayPal IPN simulator) to determine if it should use the production PayPal site or the sandbox. With a bit of time, an attacker could craft a request using the simulator that would fool any application which does not explicitly check for test_ipn in production.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-10067|2024-09-17T00:11:12.478Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3737|2024-09-17T03:42:53.453Z -- hackerone -- sshpk%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3737</link>
      <description>sshpk is vulnerable to ReDoS when parsing crafted invalid public keys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3737|2024-09-17T03:42:53.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16139|2024-09-17T03:07:05.460Z -- hackerone -- jikes%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16139</link>
      <description>jikes is a file server. jikes is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url. Accessible files are restricted to files with .htm and .js extensions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16139|2024-09-17T03:07:05.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16049|2024-09-17T01:46:17.496Z -- hackerone -- nodesqlite%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16049</link>
      <description>`nodesqlite` was a malicious module published with the intent to hijack environment variables. It has been unpublished by npm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16049|2024-09-17T01:46:17.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0898|2024-09-17T01:36:46.258Z -- hackerone -- ruby
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0898</link>
      <description>Ruby before 2.4.2, 2.3.5, and 2.2.8 is vulnerable to a malicious format string which contains a precious specifier (*) with a huge minus value. Such situation can lead to a buffer overrun, resulting in a heap memory corruption or an information disclosure from the heap.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0898|2024-09-17T01:36:46.258Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16003|2024-09-17T03:13:33.305Z -- hackerone -- windows-build-tools%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16003</link>
      <description>windows-build-tools is a module for installing C++ Build Tools for Windows using npm. windows-build-tools versions below 1.0.0 download resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16003|2024-09-17T03:13:33.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10553|2024-09-17T00:16:46.372Z -- hackerone -- sequelize%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10553</link>
      <description>sequelize is an Object-relational mapping, or a middleman to convert things from Postgres, MySQL, MariaDB, SQLite and Microsoft SQL Server into usable data for NodeJS. A fix was pushed out that fixed potential SQL injection in sequelize 2.1.3 and earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10553|2024-09-17T00:16:46.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10592|2024-09-17T03:59:08.695Z -- hackerone -- jser-stat%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10592</link>
      <description>jser-stat is a JSer.info stat library. jser-stat downloads data resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10592|2024-09-17T03:59:08.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16185|2024-09-17T04:14:34.319Z -- hackerone -- uekw1511server%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16185</link>
      <description>uekw1511server is a static file server. uekw1511server is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16185|2024-09-17T04:14:34.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10554|2024-09-17T01:55:55.539Z -- hackerone -- sequelize%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10554</link>
      <description>sequelize is an Object-relational mapping, or a middleman to convert things from Postgres, MySQL, MariaDB, SQLite and Microsoft SQL Server into usable data for NodeJS. Before version 1.7.0-alpha3, sequelize defaulted SQLite to use MySQL backslash escaping, even though SQLite uses Postgres escaping.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10554|2024-09-17T01:55:55.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16177|2024-09-17T02:27:54.306Z -- hackerone -- chatbyvista%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16177</link>
      <description>chatbyvista is a file server. chatbyvista is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16177|2024-09-17T02:27:54.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10576|2024-09-17T01:21:20.514Z -- hackerone -- fuseki%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10576</link>
      <description>Fuseki server wrapper and management API in fuseki before 1.0.1 downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10576|2024-09-17T01:21:20.514Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16021|2024-09-17T01:46:00.192Z -- hackerone -- uri-js%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16021</link>
      <description>uri-js is a module that tries to fully implement RFC 3986. One of these features is validating whether or not a supplied URL is valid or not. To do this, uri-js uses a regular expression, This regular expression is vulnerable to redos. This causes the program to hang and the CPU to idle at 100% usage while uri-js is trying to validate if the supplied URL is valid or not. To check if you're vulnerable, look for a call to `require("uri-js").parse()` where a user is able to send their own input. This affects uri-js 2.1.1 and earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16021|2024-09-17T01:46:00.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16064|2024-09-17T03:19:02.079Z -- hackerone -- node-openssl%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16064</link>
      <description>node-openssl was a malicious module published with the intent to hijack environment variables. It has been unpublished by npm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16064|2024-09-17T03:19:02.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16118|2024-09-17T01:06:51.232Z -- hackerone -- forwarded%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16118</link>
      <description>The forwarded module is used by the Express.js framework to handle the X-Forwarded-For header. It is vulnerable to a regular expression denial of service when it's passed specially crafted input to parse. This causes the event loop to be blocked causing a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16118|2024-09-17T01:06:51.232Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10643|2024-09-17T00:21:27.841Z -- hackerone -- jstestdriver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10643</link>
      <description>jstestdriver is a wrapper for Google's jstestdriver. jstestdriver downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10643|2024-09-17T00:21:27.841Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16009|2024-09-17T02:41:23.964Z -- hackerone -- ag-grid%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16009</link>
      <description>ag-grid is an advanced data grid that is library agnostic. ag-grid is vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via Angular Expressions, if AngularJS is used in combination with ag-grid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16009|2024-09-17T02:41:23.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10646|2024-09-17T02:47:15.435Z -- hackerone -- resourcehacker%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10646</link>
      <description>resourcehacker is a Node wrapper of Resource Hacker (windows executable resource editor). resourcehacker downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10646|2024-09-17T02:47:15.435Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16217|2024-09-17T02:27:24.116Z -- hackerone -- fbr-client%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16217</link>
      <description>fbr-client sends files through sockets via socket.io and webRTC. fbr-client is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16217|2024-09-17T02:27:24.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16070|2024-09-17T04:29:04.270Z -- hackerone -- nodecaffe%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16070</link>
      <description>nodecaffe was a malicious module published with the intent to hijack environment variables. It has been unpublished by npm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16070|2024-09-17T04:29:04.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0903|2024-09-17T03:54:57.184Z -- hackerone -- rubygems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0903</link>
      <description>RubyGems versions between 2.0.0 and 2.6.13 are vulnerable to a possible remote code execution vulnerability. YAML deserialization of gem specifications can bypass class white lists. Specially crafted serialized objects can possibly be used to escalate to remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0903|2024-09-17T03:54:57.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10639|2024-09-17T00:56:14.613Z -- hackerone -- redis-srvr%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10639</link>
      <description>redis-srvr is a npm wrapper for redis-server. redis-srvr downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10639|2024-09-17T00:56:14.613Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16039|2024-09-17T02:47:23.736Z -- hackerone -- hftp%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16039</link>
      <description>`hftp` is a static http or ftp server `hftp` is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16039|2024-09-17T02:47:23.736Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16099|2024-09-17T00:56:56.438Z -- hackerone -- no-case%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16099</link>
      <description>The no-case module is vulnerable to regular expression denial of service. When malicious untrusted user input is passed into no-case it can block the event loop causing a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16099|2024-09-17T00:56:56.438Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16082|2024-09-17T03:49:23.543Z -- hackerone -- pg%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16082</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability was found within the pg module when the remote database or query specifies a specially crafted column name. There are 2 likely scenarios in which one would likely be vulnerable. 1) Executing unsafe, user-supplied sql which contains a malicious column name. 2) Connecting to an untrusted database and executing a query which returns results where any of the column names are malicious.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16082|2024-09-17T03:49:23.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10642|2024-09-17T00:26:32.715Z -- hackerone -- cmake%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10642</link>
      <description>cmake installs the cmake x86 linux binaries. cmake downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10642|2024-09-17T00:26:32.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10675|2024-09-17T02:36:56.109Z -- hackerone -- libsbmlsim%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10675</link>
      <description>libsbmlsim is a module that installs linux binaries for libsbmlsim libsbmlsim downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10675|2024-09-17T02:36:56.109Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16170|2024-09-17T01:55:38.101Z -- hackerone -- liuyaserver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16170</link>
      <description>liuyaserver is a static file server. liuyaserver is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16170|2024-09-17T01:55:38.101Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16035|2024-09-17T01:26:31.843Z -- hackerone -- hubl-server%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16035</link>
      <description>The hubl-server module is a wrapper for the HubL Development Server. During installation hubl-server downloads a set of dependencies from api.hubapi.com. It appears in the code that these files are downloaded over HTTPS however the api.hubapi.com endpoint redirects to a HTTP url. Because of this behavior an attacker with the ability to man-in-the-middle a developer or system performing a package installation could compromise the integrity of the installation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16035|2024-09-17T01:26:31.843Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3716|2024-09-17T02:53:14.084Z -- hackerone -- simplehttpserver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3716</link>
      <description>simplehttpserver node module suffers from a Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability to a lack of validation of file names.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3716|2024-09-17T02:53:14.084Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10626|2024-09-17T00:17:29.653Z -- hackerone -- mystem3%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10626</link>
      <description>mystem3 is a NodeJS wrapper for the Yandex MyStem 3. mystem3 downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10626|2024-09-17T00:17:29.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16155|2024-09-17T00:35:58.830Z -- hackerone -- fast-http-cli%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16155</link>
      <description>fast-http-cli is the command line interface for fast-http, a simple web server. fast-http-cli is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16155|2024-09-17T00:35:58.830Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10539|2024-09-17T02:11:28.261Z -- hackerone -- negotiator%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10539</link>
      <description>negotiator is an HTTP content negotiator for Node.js and is used by many modules and frameworks including Express and Koa. The header for "Accept-Language", when parsed by negotiator 0.6.0 and earlier is vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service via a specially crafted string.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10539|2024-09-17T02:11:28.261Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16202|2024-09-17T01:46:24.524Z -- hackerone -- coffeescript%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16202</link>
      <description>The cofeescript module exfiltrates sensitive data such as a user's private SSH key and bash history to a third party server during installation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16202|2024-09-17T01:46:24.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16076|2024-09-17T00:06:15.829Z -- hackerone -- proxy.js%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16076</link>
      <description>proxy.js was a malicious module published with the intent to hijack environment variables. It has been unpublished by npm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16076|2024-09-17T00:06:15.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16191|2024-09-17T01:56:05.224Z -- hackerone -- cypserver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16191</link>
      <description>cypserver is a static file server. cypserver is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16191|2024-09-17T01:56:05.224Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16148|2024-09-17T00:31:50.337Z -- hackerone -- serve46%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16148</link>
      <description>serve46 is a static file server. serve46 is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16148|2024-09-17T00:31:50.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10560|2024-09-17T00:40:36.154Z -- hackerone -- galenframework-cli%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10560</link>
      <description>galenframework-cli is the node wrapper for the Galen Framework. galenframework-cli below 2.3.1 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10560|2024-09-17T00:40:36.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3719|2024-09-17T04:19:14.237Z -- hackerone -- mixin-deep%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3719</link>
      <description>mixin-deep node module before 1.3.1 suffers from a Modification of Assumed-Immutable Data (MAID) vulnerability, which allows a malicious user to modify the prototype of "Object" via __proto__, causing the addition or modification of an existing property that will exist on all objects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3719|2024-09-17T04:19:14.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16060|2024-09-17T03:48:25.761Z -- hackerone -- babelcli%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16060</link>
      <description>babelcli was a malicious module published with the intent to hijack environment variables. It has been unpublished by npm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16060|2024-09-17T03:48:25.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16065|2024-09-17T00:37:05.170Z -- hackerone -- openssl.js%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16065</link>
      <description>openssl.js was a malicious module published with the intent to hijack environment variables. It has been unpublished by npm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16065|2024-09-17T00:37:05.170Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16178|2024-09-17T00:40:55.913Z -- hackerone -- intsol-package%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16178</link>
      <description>intsol-package is a file server. intsol-package is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16178|2024-09-17T00:40:55.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10676|2024-09-17T01:31:56.336Z -- hackerone -- rs-brightcove%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10676</link>
      <description>rs-brightcove is a wrapper around brightcove's web api rs-brightcove downloads source file resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10676|2024-09-17T01:31:56.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16101|2024-09-17T01:41:09.946Z -- hackerone -- serverwg%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16101</link>
      <description>serverwg is a simple http server. serverwg is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the URL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16101|2024-09-17T01:41:09.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16013|2024-09-17T04:09:41.605Z -- hackerone -- hapi%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16013</link>
      <description>hapi is a web and services application framework. When hapi &gt;= 15.0.0 &lt;= 16.1.0 encounters a malformed `accept-encoding` header an uncaught exception is thrown. This may cause hapi to crash or to hang the client connection until the timeout period is reached.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16013|2024-09-17T04:09:41.605Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0928|2024-09-17T04:04:20.635Z -- hackerone -- html-janitor%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0928</link>
      <description>html-janitor node module suffers from an External Control of Critical State Data vulnerability via user-control of the '_sanitized' variable causing sanitization to be bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0928|2024-09-17T04:04:20.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16212|2024-09-17T01:26:41.368Z -- hackerone -- ltt%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16212</link>
      <description>ltt is a static file server. ltt is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16212|2024-09-17T01:26:41.368Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0931|2024-09-17T03:59:01.542Z -- hackerone -- html-janitor%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0931</link>
      <description>html-janitor node module suffers from a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via clean() accepting user-controlled values.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0931|2024-09-17T03:59:01.542Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10549|2024-09-17T01:46:02.640Z -- hackerone -- sails%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10549</link>
      <description>Sails is an MVC style framework for building realtime web applications. Version 0.12.7 and lower have an issue with the CORS configuration where the value of the origin header is reflected as the value for the Access-Control-Allow-Origin header. This would allow an attacker to make AJAX requests to vulnerable hosts through cross site scripting or a malicious HTML Document, effectively bypassing the Same Origin Policy. Note that this is only an issue when `allRoutes` is set to `true` and `origin` is set to `*` or left commented out in the sails CORS config file. The problem can be compounded when the cors `credentials` setting is not provided. At that point authenticated cross domain requests are possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10549|2024-09-17T01:46:02.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16029|2024-09-17T00:11:57.294Z -- hackerone -- hostr%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16029</link>
      <description>hostr is a simple web server that serves up the contents of the current directory. There is a directory traversal vulnerability in hostr 2.3.5 and earlier that allows an attacker to read files outside the current directory by sending `../` in the url path for GET requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16029|2024-09-17T00:11:57.294Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10619|2024-09-17T00:56:48.996Z -- hackerone -- pennyworth%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10619</link>
      <description>pennyworth is a natural language templating engine. pennyworth downloads data resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10619|2024-09-17T00:56:48.996Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10698|2024-09-17T03:02:38.654Z -- hackerone -- mystem-fix%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10698</link>
      <description>mystem-fix is a node.js wrapper for MyStem morphology text analyzer by Yandex.ru mystem-fix downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10698|2024-09-17T03:02:38.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10523|2024-09-17T02:15:35.059Z -- hackerone -- mqtt-packet%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10523</link>
      <description>MQTT before 3.4.6 and 4.0.x before 4.0.5 allows specifically crafted MQTT packets to crash the application, making a DoS attack feasible with very little bandwidth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10523|2024-09-17T02:15:35.059Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3733|2024-09-17T01:06:57.354Z -- hackerone -- crud-file-server%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3733</link>
      <description>crud-file-server node module before 0.9.0 suffers from a Path Traversal vulnerability due to incorrect validation of url, which allows a malicious user to read content of any file with known path.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3733|2024-09-17T01:06:57.354Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10580|2024-09-17T01:21:50.851Z -- hackerone -- nodewebkit%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10580</link>
      <description>nodewebkit is an installer for node-webkit. nodewebkit downloads zipped resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested zip file with an attacker controlled zip file if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10580|2024-09-17T01:21:50.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10656|2024-09-17T02:32:45.932Z -- hackerone -- qbs%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10656</link>
      <description>qbs is a build tool that helps simplify the build process for developing projects across multiple platforms. qbs downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10656|2024-09-17T02:32:45.932Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16162|2024-09-17T03:43:29.798Z -- hackerone -- 22lixian%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16162</link>
      <description>22lixian is a simple file server. 22lixian is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16162|2024-09-17T03:43:29.798Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16093|2024-09-17T03:18:53.585Z -- hackerone -- cyber-js%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16093</link>
      <description>cyber-js is a simple http server. A cyberjs server is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16093|2024-09-17T03:18:53.585Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3713|2024-09-17T03:53:09.024Z -- hackerone -- angular-http-server%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3713</link>
      <description>angular-http-server node module suffers from a Path Traversal vulnerability due to lack of validation of possibleFilename, which allows a malicious user to read content of any file with known path.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3713|2024-09-17T03:53:09.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16221|2024-09-17T01:36:50.872Z -- hackerone -- yzt%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16221</link>
      <description>yzt is a simple file server. yzt is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16221|2024-09-17T01:36:50.872Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16066|2024-09-17T04:14:23.387Z -- hackerone -- opencv.js%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16066</link>
      <description>opencv.js was a malicious module published with the intent to hijack environment variables. It has been unpublished by npm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16066|2024-09-17T04:14:23.387Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16192|2024-09-17T02:11:46.475Z -- hackerone -- getcityapi.yoehoehne%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16192</link>
      <description>getcityapi.yoehoehne is a web server. getcityapi.yoehoehne is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16192|2024-09-17T02:11:46.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3722|2024-09-17T04:14:35.263Z -- hackerone -- merge-deep%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3722</link>
      <description>merge-deep node module before 3.0.1 suffers from a Modification of Assumed-Immutable Data (MAID) vulnerability, which allows a malicious user to modify the prototype of "Object" via __proto__, causing the addition or modification of an existing property that will exist on all objects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3722|2024-09-17T04:14:35.263Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10645|2024-09-17T02:57:06.637Z -- hackerone -- grunt-images%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10645</link>
      <description>grunt-images is a grunt plugin for processing images. grunt-images downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10645|2024-09-17T02:57:06.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3715|2024-09-17T04:08:49.420Z -- hackerone -- glance%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3715</link>
      <description>glance node module before 3.0.4 suffers from a Path Traversal vulnerability due to lack of validation of path passed to it, which allows a malicious user to read content of any file with known path.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3715|2024-09-17T04:08:49.420Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16119|2024-09-17T01:52:08.005Z -- hackerone -- fresh%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16119</link>
      <description>Fresh is a module used by the Express.js framework for HTTP response freshness testing. It is vulnerable to a regular expression denial of service when it is passed specially crafted input to parse. This causes the event loop to be blocked causing a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16119|2024-09-17T01:52:08.005Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16222|2024-09-17T03:44:17.687Z -- hackerone -- elding%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16222</link>
      <description>elding is a simple web server. elding is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, allowing an attacker to access the filesystem by placing "../" in the url. The files accessible, however, are limited to files with a file extension. Sending a GET request to /../../../etc/passwd, for example, will return a 404 on etc/passwd/index.js.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16222|2024-09-17T03:44:17.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3726|2024-09-17T00:05:37.055Z -- hackerone -- crud-file-server%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3726</link>
      <description>crud-file-server node module before 0.8.0 suffers from a Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability to a lack of validation of file names.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3726|2024-09-17T00:05:37.055Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10542|2024-09-17T04:03:37.757Z -- hackerone -- ws%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10542</link>
      <description>ws is a "simple to use, blazing fast and thoroughly tested websocket client, server and console for node.js, up-to-date against RFC-6455". By sending an overly long websocket payload to a `ws` server, it is possible to crash the node process. This affects ws 1.1.0 and earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10542|2024-09-17T04:03:37.757Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16117|2024-09-17T01:16:46.857Z -- hackerone -- slug%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16117</link>
      <description>slug is a module to slugify strings, even if they contain unicode. slug is vulnerable to regular expression denial of service is specially crafted untrusted input is passed as input. About 50k characters can block the event loop for 2 seconds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16117|2024-09-17T01:16:46.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10625|2024-09-17T03:43:06.522Z -- hackerone -- headless-browser-lite%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10625</link>
      <description>headless-browser-lite is a minimal npm installer for phantomjs and slimerjs with no external dependencies. headless-browser-lite downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10625|2024-09-17T03:43:06.522Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10608|2024-09-17T00:10:34.045Z -- hackerone -- robot-js%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10608</link>
      <description>robot-js is a module for native system automation for node.js. robot-js downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10608|2024-09-17T00:10:34.045Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3730|2024-09-17T00:56:12.788Z -- hackerone -- mcstatic%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3730</link>
      <description>mcstatic node module suffers from a Path Traversal vulnerability due to lack of validation of filePath, which allows a malicious user to read content of any file with known path.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3730|2024-09-17T00:56:12.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16052|2024-09-17T01:05:54.584Z -- hackerone -- node-fabric%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16052</link>
      <description>`node-fabric` was a malicious module published with the intent to hijack environment variables. It has been unpublished by npm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16052|2024-09-17T01:05:54.584Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10534|2024-09-17T02:37:40.090Z -- hackerone -- electron-packager%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10534</link>
      <description>electron-packager is a command line tool that packages Electron source code into `.app` and `.exe` packages. along with Electron. The `--strict-ssl` command line option in electron-packager &gt;= 5.2.1 &lt;= 6.0.0 || &gt;=6.0.0 &lt;= 6.0.2 defaults to false if not explicitly set to true. This could allow an attacker to perform a man in the middle attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10534|2024-09-17T02:37:40.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10648|2024-09-17T04:14:10.920Z -- hackerone -- marionette-socket-host%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10648</link>
      <description>marionette-socket-host is a marionette-js-runner host for sending actions over a socket. marionette-socket-host downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10648|2024-09-17T04:14:10.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-10068|2024-09-17T03:12:54.633Z -- hackerone -- inert%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-10068</link>
      <description>The inert directory handler in inert node module before 1.1.1 always allows files in hidden directories to be served, even when `showHidden` is false.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-10068|2024-09-17T03:12:54.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10604|2024-09-17T02:47:41.094Z -- hackerone -- dalek-browser-chrome%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10604</link>
      <description>dalek-browser-chrome is Google Chrome bindings for DalekJS. dalek-browser-chrome downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10604|2024-09-17T02:47:41.094Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10527|2024-09-17T01:16:35.976Z -- hackerone -- riot-compiler%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10527</link>
      <description>The riot-compiler version version 2.3.21 has an issue in a regex (Catastrophic Backtracking) thats make it unusable under certain conditions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10527|2024-09-17T01:16:35.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10614|2024-09-17T02:26:59.820Z -- hackerone -- httpsync%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10614</link>
      <description>httpsync is a port of libcurl to node.js. httpsync downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10614|2024-09-17T02:26:59.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-10064|2024-09-17T00:36:04.821Z -- hackerone -- qs%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-10064</link>
      <description>The qs module before 1.0.0 does not have an option or default for specifying object depth and when parsing a string representing a deeply nested object will block the event loop for long periods of time. An attacker could leverage this to cause a temporary denial-of-service condition, for example, in a web application, other requests would not be processed while this blocking is occurring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-10064|2024-09-17T00:36:04.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16077|2024-09-17T03:53:10.528Z -- hackerone -- mongose%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16077</link>
      <description>mongose was a malicious module published with the intent to hijack environment variables. It has been unpublished by npm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16077|2024-09-17T03:53:10.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10595|2024-09-17T02:06:34.048Z -- hackerone -- jdf-sass%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10595</link>
      <description>jdf-sass is a fork from node-sass, jdf use only. jdf-sass downloads executable resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested file with an attacker controlled file if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10595|2024-09-17T02:06:34.048Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16041|2024-09-17T01:55:33.643Z -- hackerone -- ikst%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16041</link>
      <description>ikst versions before 1.1.2 download resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16041|2024-09-17T01:55:33.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10533|2024-09-17T00:35:52.804Z -- hackerone -- express-restify-mongoose%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10533</link>
      <description>express-restify-mongoose is a module to easily create a flexible REST interface for mongoose models. express-restify-mongoose 2.4.2 and earlier and 3.0.X through 3.0.1 allows a malicious user to send a request for `GET /User?distinct=password` and get all the passwords for all the users in the database, despite the field being set to private. This can be used for other private data if the malicious user knew what was set as private for specific routes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10533|2024-09-17T00:35:52.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16125|2024-09-17T03:12:53.281Z -- hackerone -- rtcmulticonnection-client%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16125</link>
      <description>rtcmulticonnection-client is a signaling implementation for RTCMultiConnection.js, a multi-session manager. rtcmulticonnection-client is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16125|2024-09-17T03:12:53.281Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10575|2024-09-17T02:36:12.983Z -- hackerone -- kindlegen%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10575</link>
      <description>Kindlegen is a simple Node.js wrapper of the official kindlegen program. Kindlegen versions before 1.1.0 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10575|2024-09-17T02:36:12.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10520|2024-09-17T01:41:52.603Z -- hackerone -- jadedown%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10520</link>
      <description>jadedown is vulnerable to regular expression denial of service (ReDoS) when certain types of user input is passed in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10520|2024-09-17T01:41:52.603Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10519|2024-09-17T03:02:17.484Z -- hackerone -- bittorrent-dht%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10519</link>
      <description>A security issue was found in bittorrent-dht before 5.1.3 that allows someone to send a specific series of messages to a listening peer and get it to reveal internal memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10519|2024-09-17T03:02:17.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16223|2024-09-17T02:20:48.902Z -- hackerone -- nodeaaaaa%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16223</link>
      <description>nodeaaaaa is a static file server. nodeaaaaa is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16223|2024-09-17T02:20:48.902Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3745|2024-09-17T03:59:23.153Z -- hackerone -- atob%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3745</link>
      <description>atob 2.0.3 and earlier allocates uninitialized Buffers when number is passed in input on Node.js 4.x and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3745|2024-09-17T03:59:23.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10538|2024-09-17T01:36:47.221Z -- hackerone -- cli%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10538</link>
      <description>The package `node-cli` before 1.0.0 insecurely uses the lock_file and log_file. Both of these are temporary, but it allows the starting user to overwrite any file they have access to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10538|2024-09-17T01:36:47.221Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10537|2024-09-17T04:14:50.404Z -- hackerone -- backbone%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10537</link>
      <description>backbone is a module that adds in structure to a JavaScript heavy application through key-value pairs and custom events connecting to your RESTful API through JSON There exists a potential Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in the `Model#Escape` function of backbone 0.3.3 and earlier, if a user is able to supply input. This is due to the regex that's replacing things to miss the conversion of things such as `&lt;` to `&lt;`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10537|2024-09-17T04:14:50.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16100|2024-09-17T02:16:17.609Z -- hackerone -- dns-sync%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16100</link>
      <description>dns-sync is a sync/blocking dns resolver. If untrusted user input is allowed into the resolve() method then command injection is possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16100|2024-09-17T02:16:17.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10541|2024-09-17T03:18:50.154Z -- hackerone -- shell-quote%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10541</link>
      <description>The npm module "shell-quote" 1.6.0 and earlier cannot correctly escape "&gt;" and "&lt;" operator used for redirection in shell. Applications that depend on shell-quote may also be vulnerable. A malicious user could perform code injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10541|2024-09-17T03:18:50.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0902|2024-09-17T00:42:39.081Z -- hackerone -- rubygems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0902</link>
      <description>RubyGems version 2.6.12 and earlier is vulnerable to a DNS hijacking vulnerability that allows a MITM attacker to force the RubyGems client to download and install gems from a server that the attacker controls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0902|2024-09-17T00:42:39.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16025|2024-09-17T01:12:03.298Z -- hackerone -- nes%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16025</link>
      <description>Nes is a websocket extension library for hapi. Hapi is a webserver framework. Versions below and including 6.4.0 have a denial of service vulnerability via an invalid Cookie header. This is only present when websocket authentication is set to `cookie`. Submitting an invalid cookie on the websocket upgrade request will cause the node process to error out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16025|2024-09-17T01:12:03.298Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10566|2024-09-17T02:52:25.988Z -- hackerone -- install-nw%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10566</link>
      <description>install-nw is a module which quickly and robustly installs and caches NW.js. install-nw versions below 1.1.5 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10566|2024-09-17T02:52:25.988Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16136|2024-09-17T03:18:13.960Z -- hackerone -- method-override%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16136</link>
      <description>method-override is a module used by the Express.js framework to let you use HTTP verbs such as PUT or DELETE in places where the client doesn't support it. method-override is vulnerable to a regular expression denial of service vulnerability when specially crafted input is passed in to be parsed via the X-HTTP-Method-Override header.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16136|2024-09-17T03:18:13.960Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10561|2024-09-17T04:24:57.968Z -- hackerone -- bitty%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10561</link>
      <description>Bitty is a development web server tool that functions similar to `python -m SimpleHTTPServer`. Version 0.2.10 has a directory traversal vulnerability that is exploitable via the URL path in GET requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10561|2024-09-17T04:24:57.968Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10657|2024-09-17T03:34:22.989Z -- hackerone -- co-cli-installer%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10657</link>
      <description>co-cli-installer downloads the co-cli module as part of the install process, but does so over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10657|2024-09-17T03:34:22.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10578|2024-09-17T01:11:45.242Z -- hackerone -- unicode%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10578</link>
      <description>unicode loads unicode data downloaded from unicode.org into nodejs. Unicode before 9.0.0 downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10578|2024-09-17T01:11:45.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10612|2024-09-17T02:37:40.561Z -- hackerone -- dalek-browser-ie-canary%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10612</link>
      <description>dalek-browser-ie-canary is Internet Explorer bindings for DalekJS. dalek-browser-ie-canary downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10612|2024-09-17T02:37:40.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10596|2024-09-17T00:40:50.717Z -- hackerone -- imageoptim%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10596</link>
      <description>imageoptim is a Node.js wrapper for some images compression algorithms. imageoptim downloads zipped resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested tarball with an attacker controlled tarball if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10596|2024-09-17T00:40:50.717Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10673|2024-09-17T01:16:06.952Z -- hackerone -- ipip-coffee%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10673</link>
      <description>ipip-coffee queries geolocation information from IP ipip-coffee downloads geolocation resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. This could impact the integrity and availability of the data being used to make geolocation decisions by an application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10673|2024-09-17T01:16:06.952Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16200|2024-09-17T02:11:08.457Z -- hackerone -- uv-tj-demo%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16200</link>
      <description>uv-tj-demo is a static file server. uv-tj-demo is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16200|2024-09-17T02:11:08.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10558|2024-09-17T02:36:42.182Z -- hackerone -- aerospike%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10558</link>
      <description>aerospike is an Aerospike add-on module for Node.js. aerospike versions below 2.4.2 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves the module vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10558|2024-09-17T02:36:42.182Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3714|2024-09-17T00:51:50.998Z -- hackerone -- node-srv%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3714</link>
      <description>node-srv node module suffers from a Path Traversal vulnerability due to lack of validation of url, which allows a malicious user to read content of any file with known path.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3714|2024-09-17T00:51:50.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16028|2024-09-17T02:06:18.622Z -- hackerone -- react-native-meteor-oauth%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16028</link>
      <description>react-native-meteor-oauth is a library for Oauth2 login to a Meteor server in React Native. The oauth Random Token is generated using a non-cryptographically strong RNG (Math.random()).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16028|2024-09-17T02:06:18.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10688|2024-09-17T01:51:52.519Z -- hackerone -- haxe3%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10688</link>
      <description>Haxe 3 : The Cross-Platform Toolkit (a fork from David Mouton's damoebius/haxe-npm) haxe3 downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10688|2024-09-17T01:51:52.519Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-9236|2024-09-17T04:15:13.448Z -- hackerone -- hapi%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-9236</link>
      <description>Hapi versions less than 11.0.0 implement CORS incorrectly and allowed for configurations that at best returned inconsistent headers and at worst allowed cross-origin activities that were expected to be forbidden. If the connection has CORS enabled but one route has it off, and the route is not GET, the OPTIONS prefetch request will return the default CORS headers and then the actual request will go through and return no CORS headers. This defeats the purpose of turning CORS on the route.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-9236|2024-09-17T04:15:13.448Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10525|2024-09-17T01:01:50.306Z -- hackerone -- hapi-auth-jwt2%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10525</link>
      <description>When attempting to allow authentication mode `try` in hapi, hapi-auth-jwt2 version 5.1.1 introduced an issue whereby people could bypass authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10525|2024-09-17T01:01:50.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3712|2024-09-17T00:05:56.311Z -- hackerone -- serve%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3712</link>
      <description>serve node module before 6.4.9 suffers from a Path Traversal vulnerability due to not handling %2e (.) and %2f (/) and allowing them in paths, which allows a malicious user to view the contents of any directory with known path.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3712|2024-09-17T00:05:56.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10637|2024-09-17T01:36:38.265Z -- hackerone -- haxe-dev%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10637</link>
      <description>haxe-dev is a cross-platform toolkit. haxe-dev downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10637|2024-09-17T01:36:38.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10605|2024-09-17T04:24:06.306Z -- hackerone -- dalek-browser-ie%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10605</link>
      <description>dalek-browser-ie is Internet Explorer bindings for DalekJS. dalek-browser-ie downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10605|2024-09-17T04:24:06.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16036|2024-09-17T02:47:21.539Z -- hackerone -- badjs-sourcemap-server%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16036</link>
      <description>`badjs-sourcemap-server` receives files sent by `badjs-sourcemap`. `badjs-sourcemap-server` is vulnerable to a directory traversal issue, giving an attacker access to the filesystem by placing "../" in the url.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16036|2024-09-17T02:47:21.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3758|2024-09-17T02:11:59.627Z -- hackerone -- express-cart
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3758</link>
      <description>Unrestricted file upload (RCE) in express-cart module before 1.1.7 allows a privileged user to gain access in the hosting machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3758|2024-09-17T02:11:59.627Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16114|2024-09-17T03:44:01.567Z -- hackerone -- marked%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16114</link>
      <description>The marked module is vulnerable to a regular expression denial of service. Based on the information published in the public issue, 1k characters can block for around 6 seconds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16114|2024-09-17T03:44:01.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10640|2024-09-17T03:02:53.433Z -- hackerone -- node-thulac%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10640</link>
      <description>node-thulac is a node binding for thulac. node-thulac downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10640|2024-09-17T03:02:53.433Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10531|2024-09-17T04:28:55.235Z -- hackerone -- marked%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10531</link>
      <description>marked is an application that is meant to parse and compile markdown. Due to the way that marked 0.3.5 and earlier parses input, specifically HTML entities, it's possible to bypass marked's content injection protection (`sanitize: true`) to inject a `javascript:` URL. This flaw exists because `&amp;#xNNanything;` gets parsed to what it could and leaves the rest behind, resulting in just `anything;` being left.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10531|2024-09-17T04:28:55.235Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10557|2024-09-17T02:16:19.032Z -- hackerone -- appium-chromedriver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10557</link>
      <description>appium-chromedriver is a Node.js wrapper around Chromedriver. Versions below 2.9.4 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves the module vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10557|2024-09-17T02:16:19.032Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10535|2024-09-17T01:30:58.704Z -- hackerone -- csrf-lite%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10535</link>
      <description>csrf-lite is a cross-site request forgery protection library for framework-less node sites. csrf-lite uses `===`, a fail first string comparison, instead of a time constant string comparison This enables an attacker to guess the secret in no more than (16*18)288 guesses, instead of the 16^18 guesses required were the timing attack not present.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10535|2024-09-17T01:30:58.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10601|2024-09-17T04:18:48.609Z -- hackerone -- webdrvr%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10601</link>
      <description>webdrvr is a npm wrapper for Selenium Webdriver including Chromedriver / IEDriver / IOSDriver / Ghostdriver. webdrvr downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10601|2024-09-17T04:18:48.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10518|2024-09-17T02:57:19.095Z -- hackerone -- ws%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10518</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in the ping functionality of the ws module before 1.0.0 which allowed clients to allocate memory by sending a ping frame. The ping functionality by default responds with a pong frame and the previously given payload of the ping frame. This is exactly what you expect, but internally ws always transforms all data that we need to send to a Buffer instance and that is where the vulnerability existed. ws didn't do any checks for the type of data it was sending. With buffers in node when you allocate it when a number instead of a string it will allocate the amount of bytes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10518|2024-09-17T02:57:19.095Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10597|2024-09-17T01:01:45.608Z -- hackerone -- cobalt-cli%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10597</link>
      <description>cobalt-cli downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10597|2024-09-17T01:01:45.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
