<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for HackerOne -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/hackerone/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for HackerOne -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:21:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10628|2024-08-06T03:30:19.663Z -- hackerone -- selenium-wrapper%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10628</link>
      <description>selenium-wrapper is a selenium server wrapper, including installation and chrome webdriver. selenium-wrapper downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10628|2024-08-06T03:30:19.663Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10634|2024-08-06T03:30:19.970Z -- hackerone -- scalajs-standalone-bin%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10634</link>
      <description>scala-standalone-bin is a Binary wrapper for ScalaJS. scala-standalone-bin downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10634|2024-08-06T03:30:19.970Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10658|2024-08-06T03:30:20.149Z -- hackerone -- native-opencv%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10658</link>
      <description>native-opencv is the OpenCV library installed via npm native-opencv downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10658|2024-08-06T03:30:20.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10651|2024-08-06T03:30:19.949Z -- hackerone -- webdriver-launcher%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10651</link>
      <description>webdriver-launcher is a Node.js Selenium Webdriver Launcher. webdriver-launcher downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10651|2024-08-06T03:30:19.949Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10532|2024-08-06T03:21:52.157Z -- hackerone -- console-io%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10532</link>
      <description>console-io is a module that allows users to implement a web console in their application. A malicious user could bypass the authentication and execute any command that the user who is running the console-io application 2.2.13 and earlier is able to run. This means that if console-io was running from root, the attacker would have full access to the system. This vulnerability exists because the console-io application does not configure socket.io to require authentication, which allows a malicious user to connect via a websocket to send commands and receive the response.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10532|2024-08-06T03:21:52.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10650|2024-08-06T03:30:19.976Z -- hackerone -- ntfserver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10650</link>
      <description>ntfserver is a Network Testing Framework Server. ntfserver downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10650|2024-08-06T03:30:19.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10561|2024-08-06T03:30:19.095Z -- hackerone -- bitty%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10561</link>
      <description>Bitty is a development web server tool that functions similar to `python -m SimpleHTTPServer`. Version 0.2.10 has a directory traversal vulnerability that is exploitable via the URL path in GET requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10561|2024-08-06T03:30:19.095Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10644|2024-08-06T03:30:19.526Z -- hackerone -- slimerjs-edge%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10644</link>
      <description>slimerjs-edge is a npm wrapper for installing the bleeding edge version of slimerjs. slimerjs-edge downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10644|2024-08-06T03:30:19.526Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10560|2024-08-06T03:30:18.322Z -- hackerone -- galenframework-cli%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10560</link>
      <description>galenframework-cli is the node wrapper for the Galen Framework. galenframework-cli below 2.3.1 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10560|2024-08-06T03:30:18.322Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10593|2024-08-06T03:30:19.451Z -- hackerone -- ibapi%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10593</link>
      <description>ibapi is an Interactive Brokers API addon for NodeJS. ibapi downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. Before 2.5.6, it may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10593|2024-08-06T03:30:19.451Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10683|2024-08-06T03:30:20.130Z -- hackerone -- arcanist%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10683</link>
      <description>arcanist downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10683|2024-08-06T03:30:20.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10565|2024-08-06T03:30:18.479Z -- hackerone -- operadriver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10565</link>
      <description>operadriver is a Opera Driver for Selenium. operadriver versions below 0.2.3 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10565|2024-08-06T03:30:18.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10681|2024-08-06T03:30:20.129Z -- hackerone -- roslib-socketio%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10681</link>
      <description>roslib-socketio - The standard ROS Javascript Library fork for add support to socket.io roslib-socketio downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10681|2024-08-06T03:30:20.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10574|2024-08-06T03:30:18.405Z -- hackerone -- apk-parser3%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10574</link>
      <description>apk-parser3 is a module to extract Android Manifest info from an APK file. apk-parser3 versions before 0.1.3 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10574|2024-08-06T03:30:18.405Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10567|2024-08-06T03:30:18.483Z -- hackerone -- product-monitor%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10567</link>
      <description>product-monitor is a HTML/JavaScript template for monitoring a product by encouraging product developers to gather all the information about the status of a product, including live monitoring, statistics, endpoints, and test results into one place. product-monitor versions below 2.2.5 download JavaScript resources over HTTP, which leaves the module vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested JavaScript file with an attacker controlled JavaScript file if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10567|2024-08-06T03:30:18.483Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10695|2024-08-06T03:30:20.143Z -- hackerone -- npm-test-sqlite3-trunk%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10695</link>
      <description>The npm-test-sqlite3-trunk module provides asynchronous, non-blocking SQLite3 bindings. npm-test-sqlite3-trunk downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10695|2024-08-06T03:30:20.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10552|2024-08-06T03:21:52.225Z -- hackerone -- igniteui%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10552</link>
      <description>igniteui 0.0.5 and earlier downloads JavaScript and CSS resources over insecure protocol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10552|2024-08-06T03:21:52.225Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10519|2024-08-06T03:21:52.243Z -- hackerone -- bittorrent-dht%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10519</link>
      <description>A security issue was found in bittorrent-dht before 5.1.3 that allows someone to send a specific series of messages to a listening peer and get it to reveal internal memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10519|2024-08-06T03:21:52.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-9239|2024-08-06T08:43:42.619Z -- hackerone -- ansi2html%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-9239</link>
      <description>ansi2html is vulnerable to regular expression denial of service (ReDoS) when certain types of user input is passed in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-9239|2024-08-06T08:43:42.619Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10537|2024-08-06T03:21:52.242Z -- hackerone -- backbone%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10537</link>
      <description>backbone is a module that adds in structure to a JavaScript heavy application through key-value pairs and custom events connecting to your RESTful API through JSON There exists a potential Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in the `Model#Escape` function of backbone 0.3.3 and earlier, if a user is able to supply input. This is due to the regex that's replacing things to miss the conversion of things such as `&lt;` to `&lt;`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10537|2024-08-06T03:21:52.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10640|2024-08-06T03:30:19.036Z -- hackerone -- node-thulac%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10640</link>
      <description>node-thulac is a node binding for thulac. node-thulac downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10640|2024-08-06T03:30:19.036Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10544|2024-08-06T03:21:52.282Z -- hackerone -- uws%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10544</link>
      <description>uws is a WebSocket server library. By sending a 256mb websocket message to a uws server instance with permessage-deflate enabled, there is a possibility used compression will shrink said 256mb down to less than 16mb of websocket payload which passes the length check of 16mb payload. This data will then inflate up to 256mb and crash the node process by exceeding V8's maximum string size. This affects uws &gt;=0.10.0 &lt;=0.10.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10544|2024-08-06T03:21:52.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10612|2024-08-06T03:30:19.316Z -- hackerone -- dalek-browser-ie-canary%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10612</link>
      <description>dalek-browser-ie-canary is Internet Explorer bindings for DalekJS. dalek-browser-ie-canary downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10612|2024-08-06T03:30:19.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10597|2024-08-06T03:30:19.195Z -- hackerone -- cobalt-cli%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10597</link>
      <description>cobalt-cli downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10597|2024-08-06T03:30:19.195Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10665|2024-08-06T03:30:20.135Z -- hackerone -- herbivore%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10665</link>
      <description>herbivore is a packet sniffing and crafting library. Built on libtins herbivore 0.0.3 and below download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10665|2024-08-06T03:30:20.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10668|2024-08-06T03:30:20.149Z -- hackerone -- libsbml%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10668</link>
      <description>libsbml is a module that installs Linux binaries for libSBML libsbml downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10668|2024-08-06T03:30:20.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10568|2024-08-06T03:30:18.392Z -- hackerone -- geoip-lite-country%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10568</link>
      <description>geoip-lite-country is a stripped down version of geoip-lite, supporting only country lookup. geoip-lite-country before 1.1.4 downloads data resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10568|2024-08-06T03:30:18.392Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10541|2024-08-06T03:21:52.153Z -- hackerone -- shell-quote%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10541</link>
      <description>The npm module "shell-quote" 1.6.0 and earlier cannot correctly escape "&gt;" and "&lt;" operator used for redirection in shell. Applications that depend on shell-quote may also be vulnerable. A malicious user could perform code injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10541|2024-08-06T03:21:52.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10520|2024-08-06T03:21:52.133Z -- hackerone -- jadedown%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10520</link>
      <description>jadedown is vulnerable to regular expression denial of service (ReDoS) when certain types of user input is passed in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10520|2024-08-06T03:21:52.133Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10660|2024-08-06T03:30:20.139Z -- hackerone -- fis-parser-sass-bin%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10660</link>
      <description>fis-parser-sass-bin a plugin for fis to compile sass using node-sass-binaries. fis-parser-sass-bin downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10660|2024-08-06T03:30:20.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10608|2024-08-06T03:30:19.169Z -- hackerone -- robot-js%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10608</link>
      <description>robot-js is a module for native system automation for node.js. robot-js downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10608|2024-08-06T03:30:19.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10694|2024-08-06T03:30:20.168Z -- hackerone -- alto-saxophone%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10694</link>
      <description>alto-saxophone is a module to install and launch Chromedriver for Mac, Linux or Windows. alto-saxophone versions below 2.25.1 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10694|2024-08-06T03:30:20.168Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-10066|2024-08-06T14:02:38.275Z -- hackerone -- fancy-server%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-10066</link>
      <description>Versions less than 0.1.4 of the static file server module fancy-server are vulnerable to directory traversal. An attacker can provide input such as `../` to read files outside of the served directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-10066|2024-08-06T14:02:38.275Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10592|2024-08-06T03:30:18.889Z -- hackerone -- jser-stat%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10592</link>
      <description>jser-stat is a JSer.info stat library. jser-stat downloads data resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10592|2024-08-06T03:30:18.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10610|2024-08-06T03:30:19.651Z -- hackerone -- unicode-json%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10610</link>
      <description>unicode-json is a unicode lookup table. unicode-json before 2.0.0 downloads data resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10610|2024-08-06T03:30:19.651Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10669|2024-08-06T03:30:20.131Z -- hackerone -- soci%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10669</link>
      <description>soci downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10669|2024-08-06T03:30:20.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10691|2024-08-06T03:30:20.139Z -- hackerone -- windows-seleniumjar%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10691</link>
      <description>windows-seleniumjar is a module that downloads the Selenium Jar file windows-seleniumjar downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10691|2024-08-06T03:30:20.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10643|2024-08-06T03:30:19.621Z -- hackerone -- jstestdriver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10643</link>
      <description>jstestdriver is a wrapper for Google's jstestdriver. jstestdriver downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10643|2024-08-06T03:30:19.621Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-9241|2024-08-06T08:43:41.875Z -- hackerone -- hapi%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-9241</link>
      <description>Certain input passed into the If-Modified-Since or Last-Modified headers will cause an 'illegal access' exception to be raised. Instead of sending a HTTP 500 error back to the sender, hapi node module before 11.1.3 will continue to hold the socket open until timed out (default node timeout is 2 minutes).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-9241|2024-08-06T08:43:41.875Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10527|2024-08-06T03:21:52.168Z -- hackerone -- riot-compiler%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10527</link>
      <description>The riot-compiler version version 2.3.21 has an issue in a regex (Catastrophic Backtracking) thats make it unusable under certain conditions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10527|2024-08-06T03:21:52.168Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10591|2024-08-06T03:30:18.471Z -- hackerone -- prince%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10591</link>
      <description>Prince is a Node API for executing XML/HTML to PDF renderer PrinceXML via prince(1) CLI. prince downloads zipped resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested tarball with an attacker controlled tarball if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10591|2024-08-06T03:30:18.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10635|2024-08-06T03:30:19.199Z -- hackerone -- broccoli-closure%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10635</link>
      <description>broccoli-closure is a Closure compiler plugin for Broccoli. broccoli-closure before 1.3.1 downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10635|2024-08-06T03:30:19.199Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10661|2024-08-06T03:30:20.152Z -- hackerone -- phantomjs-cheniu%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10661</link>
      <description>phantomjs-cheniu is a Headless WebKit with JS API phantomjs-cheniu downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10661|2024-08-06T03:30:20.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10638|2024-08-06T03:30:19.060Z -- hackerone -- js-given%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10638</link>
      <description>js-given is a JavaScript frontend to jgiven. js-given downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10638|2024-08-06T03:30:19.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10632|2024-08-06T03:30:19.123Z -- hackerone -- apk-parser2%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10632</link>
      <description>apk-parser2 is a module which extracts Android Manifest info from an APK file. apk-parser2 downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10632|2024-08-06T03:30:19.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10528|2024-08-06T03:21:52.156Z -- hackerone -- restafary%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10528</link>
      <description>restafary is a REpresentful State Transfer API for Creating, Reading, Using, Deleting files on a server from the web. Restafary before 1.6.1 is able to set up a root path, which should only allow it to run inside of that root path it specified.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10528|2024-08-06T03:21:52.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10548|2024-08-06T03:21:52.165Z -- hackerone -- reduce-css-calc%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10548</link>
      <description>Arbitrary code execution is possible in reduce-css-calc node module &lt;=1.2.4 through crafted css. This makes cross sites scripting (XSS) possible on the client and arbitrary code injection possible on the server and user input is passed to the `calc` function.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10548|2024-08-06T03:21:52.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10682|2024-08-06T03:30:20.144Z -- hackerone -- massif%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10682</link>
      <description>massif is a Phantomjs fork massif downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10682|2024-08-06T03:30:20.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10562|2024-08-06T03:30:18.327Z -- hackerone -- iedriver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10562</link>
      <description>iedriver is an NPM wrapper for Selenium IEDriver. iedriver versions below 3.0.0 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves the module vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10562|2024-08-06T03:30:18.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10684|2024-08-06T03:30:20.245Z -- hackerone -- healthcenter%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10684</link>
      <description>healthcenter - IBM Monitoring and Diagnostic Tools health Center agent healthcenter downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10684|2024-08-06T03:30:20.245Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10584|2024-08-06T03:30:19.142Z -- hackerone -- dalek-browser-chrome-canary%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10584</link>
      <description>dalek-browser-chrome-canary provides Google Chrome bindings for DalekJS. dalek-browser-chrome-canary downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10584|2024-08-06T03:30:19.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10667|2024-08-06T03:30:20.113Z -- hackerone -- selenium-portal%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10667</link>
      <description>selenium-portal is a Selenium Testing Framework selenium-portal downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10667|2024-08-06T03:30:20.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10572|2024-08-06T03:30:19.041Z -- hackerone -- mongodb-instance%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10572</link>
      <description>mongodb-instance before 0.0.3 installs mongodb locally. mongodb-instance downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10572|2024-08-06T03:30:19.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10598|2024-08-06T03:30:20.129Z -- hackerone -- arrayfire-js%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10598</link>
      <description>arrayfire-js is a module for ArrayFire for the Node.js platform. arrayfire-js downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10598|2024-08-06T03:30:20.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10581|2024-08-06T03:30:19.075Z -- hackerone -- steroids%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10581</link>
      <description>Steroids is PhoneGap on Steroids, providing native UI elements, multiple WebViews and enhancements for better developer productivity. steroids downloads zipped resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested tarball with an attacker controlled tarball if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10581|2024-08-06T03:30:19.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10656|2024-08-06T03:30:19.990Z -- hackerone -- qbs%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10656</link>
      <description>qbs is a build tool that helps simplify the build process for developing projects across multiple platforms. qbs downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10656|2024-08-06T03:30:19.990Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10529|2024-08-06T03:21:52.221Z -- hackerone -- droppy%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10529</link>
      <description>Droppy versions &lt;3.5.0 does not perform any verification for cross-domain websocket requests. An attacker is able to make a specially crafted page that can send requests as the context of the currently logged in user. For example this means the malicious user could add a new admin account under his control and delete others.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10529|2024-08-06T03:21:52.221Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10672|2024-08-06T03:30:20.141Z -- hackerone -- cloudpub-redis%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10672</link>
      <description>cloudpub-redis is a module for CloudPub: Redis Backend cloudpub-redis downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10672|2024-08-06T03:30:20.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10538|2024-08-06T03:21:52.221Z -- hackerone -- cli%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10538</link>
      <description>The package `node-cli` before 1.0.0 insecurely uses the lock_file and log_file. Both of these are temporary, but it allows the starting user to overwrite any file they have access to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10538|2024-08-06T03:21:52.221Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10689|2024-08-06T03:30:20.163Z -- hackerone -- windows-iedriver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10689</link>
      <description>The windows-iedriver module downloads fixed version of iedriverserver.exe windows-iedriver downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10689|2024-08-06T03:30:20.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10647|2024-08-06T03:30:19.688Z -- hackerone -- node-air-sdk%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10647</link>
      <description>node-air-sdk is an AIR SDK for nodejs. node-air-sdk downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10647|2024-08-06T03:30:19.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10549|2024-08-06T03:21:52.248Z -- hackerone -- sails%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10549</link>
      <description>Sails is an MVC style framework for building realtime web applications. Version 0.12.7 and lower have an issue with the CORS configuration where the value of the origin header is reflected as the value for the Access-Control-Allow-Origin header. This would allow an attacker to make AJAX requests to vulnerable hosts through cross site scripting or a malicious HTML Document, effectively bypassing the Same Origin Policy. Note that this is only an issue when `allRoutes` is set to `true` and `origin` is set to `*` or left commented out in the sails CORS config file. The problem can be compounded when the cors `credentials` setting is not provided. At that point authenticated cross domain requests are possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10549|2024-08-06T03:21:52.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10675|2024-08-06T03:30:20.155Z -- hackerone -- libsbmlsim%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10675</link>
      <description>libsbmlsim is a module that installs linux binaries for libsbmlsim libsbmlsim downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10675|2024-08-06T03:30:20.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10558|2024-08-06T03:30:18.495Z -- hackerone -- aerospike%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10558</link>
      <description>aerospike is an Aerospike add-on module for Node.js. aerospike versions below 2.4.2 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves the module vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10558|2024-08-06T03:30:18.495Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-9243|2024-08-06T08:43:42.327Z -- hackerone -- hapi%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-9243</link>
      <description>When server level, connection level or route level CORS configurations in hapi node module before 11.1.4 are combined and when a higher level config included security restrictions (like origin), a higher level config that included security restrictions (like origin) would have those restrictions overridden by less restrictive defaults (e.g. origin defaults to all origins `*`).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-9243|2024-08-06T08:43:42.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10607|2024-08-06T03:30:19.896Z -- hackerone -- openframe-glslviewer%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10607</link>
      <description>openframe-glsviewer is a Openframe extension which adds support for shaders via glslViewer. openframe-glsviewer downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10607|2024-08-06T03:30:19.896Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10619|2024-08-06T03:30:19.938Z -- hackerone -- pennyworth%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10619</link>
      <description>pennyworth is a natural language templating engine. pennyworth downloads data resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10619|2024-08-06T03:30:19.938Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10664|2024-08-06T03:30:20.143Z -- hackerone -- mystem%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10664</link>
      <description>mystem is a Node.js wrapper for MyStem morphology text analyzer by Yandex.ru mystem downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10664|2024-08-06T03:30:20.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10637|2024-08-06T03:30:19.861Z -- hackerone -- haxe-dev%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10637</link>
      <description>haxe-dev is a cross-platform toolkit. haxe-dev downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10637|2024-08-06T03:30:19.861Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10636|2024-08-06T03:30:19.897Z -- hackerone -- grunt-ccompiler%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10636</link>
      <description>grunt-ccompiler is a Closure Compiler Grunt Plugin. grunt-ccompiler downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10636|2024-08-06T03:30:19.897Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10555|2024-08-06T03:21:52.250Z -- hackerone -- jwt-simple%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10555</link>
      <description>Since "algorithm" isn't enforced in jwt.decode()in jwt-simple 0.3.0 and earlier, a malicious user could choose what algorithm is sent sent to the server. If the server is expecting RSA but is sent HMAC-SHA with RSA's public key, the server will think the public key is actually an HMAC private key. This could be used to forge any data an attacker wants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10555|2024-08-06T03:21:52.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10617|2024-08-06T03:30:20.145Z -- hackerone -- box2d-native%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10617</link>
      <description>box2d-native downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10617|2024-08-06T03:30:20.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10670|2024-08-06T03:30:20.174Z -- hackerone -- windows-seleniumjar-mirror%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10670</link>
      <description>windows-seleniumjar-mirror downloads the Selenium Jar file windows-seleniumjar-mirror downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10670|2024-08-06T03:30:20.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10671|2024-08-06T03:30:20.119Z -- hackerone -- mystem-wrapper%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10671</link>
      <description>mystem-wrapper is a Yandex mystem app wrapper module. mystem-wrapper downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10671|2024-08-06T03:30:20.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10518|2024-08-06T03:21:52.139Z -- hackerone -- ws%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10518</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in the ping functionality of the ws module before 1.0.0 which allowed clients to allocate memory by sending a ping frame. The ping functionality by default responds with a pong frame and the previously given payload of the ping frame. This is exactly what you expect, but internally ws always transforms all data that we need to send to a Buffer instance and that is where the vulnerability existed. ws didn't do any checks for the type of data it was sending. With buffers in node when you allocate it when a number instead of a string it will allocate the amount of bytes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10518|2024-08-06T03:21:52.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10606|2024-08-06T03:30:19.600Z -- hackerone -- grunt-webdriver-qunit%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10606</link>
      <description>grunt-webdriver-qunit is a grunt plugin to run qunit with webdriver in grunt grunt-webdriver-qunit downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10606|2024-08-06T03:30:19.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-10067|2024-08-06T14:02:38.126Z -- hackerone -- paypal-ipn%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-10067</link>
      <description>paypal-ipn before 3.0.0 uses the `test_ipn` parameter (which is set by the PayPal IPN simulator) to determine if it should use the production PayPal site or the sandbox. With a bit of time, an attacker could craft a request using the simulator that would fool any application which does not explicitly check for test_ipn in production.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-10067|2024-08-06T14:02:38.126Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10575|2024-08-06T03:30:20.040Z -- hackerone -- kindlegen%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10575</link>
      <description>Kindlegen is a simple Node.js wrapper of the official kindlegen program. Kindlegen versions before 1.1.0 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10575|2024-08-06T03:30:20.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10601|2024-08-06T03:30:19.257Z -- hackerone -- webdrvr%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10601</link>
      <description>webdrvr is a npm wrapper for Selenium Webdriver including Chromedriver / IEDriver / IOSDriver / Ghostdriver. webdrvr downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10601|2024-08-06T03:30:19.257Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10655|2024-08-06T03:30:20.164Z -- hackerone -- clang-extra%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10655</link>
      <description>The clang-extra module installs LLVM's clang-extra tools. clang-extra downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10655|2024-08-06T03:30:20.164Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10535|2024-08-06T03:21:52.227Z -- hackerone -- csrf-lite%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10535</link>
      <description>csrf-lite is a cross-site request forgery protection library for framework-less node sites. csrf-lite uses `===`, a fail first string comparison, instead of a time constant string comparison This enables an attacker to guess the secret in no more than (16*18)288 guesses, instead of the 16^18 guesses required were the timing attack not present.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10535|2024-08-06T03:21:52.227Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10554|2024-08-06T03:21:52.158Z -- hackerone -- sequelize%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10554</link>
      <description>sequelize is an Object-relational mapping, or a middleman to convert things from Postgres, MySQL, MariaDB, SQLite and Microsoft SQL Server into usable data for NodeJS. Before version 1.7.0-alpha3, sequelize defaulted SQLite to use MySQL backslash escaping, even though SQLite uses Postgres escaping.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10554|2024-08-06T03:21:52.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10596|2024-08-06T03:30:19.035Z -- hackerone -- imageoptim%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10596</link>
      <description>imageoptim is a Node.js wrapper for some images compression algorithms. imageoptim downloads zipped resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested tarball with an attacker controlled tarball if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10596|2024-08-06T03:30:19.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10623|2024-08-06T03:30:19.490Z -- hackerone -- macaca-chromedriver-zxa%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10623</link>
      <description>macaca-chromedriver-zxa is a Node.js wrapper for the selenium chromedriver. macaca-chromedriver-zxa downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10623|2024-08-06T03:30:19.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10688|2024-08-06T03:30:20.151Z -- hackerone -- haxe3%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10688</link>
      <description>Haxe 3 : The Cross-Platform Toolkit (a fork from David Mouton's damoebius/haxe-npm) haxe3 downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10688|2024-08-06T03:30:20.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10652|2024-08-06T03:30:19.995Z -- hackerone -- prebuild-lwip%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10652</link>
      <description>prebuild-lwip is a module for comprehensive, fast, and simple image processing and manipulation. prebuild-lwip downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10652|2024-08-06T03:30:19.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10627|2024-08-06T03:30:19.094Z -- hackerone -- scala-bin%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10627</link>
      <description>scala-bin is a binary wrapper for Scala. scala-bin downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10627|2024-08-06T03:30:19.094Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10566|2024-08-06T03:30:18.486Z -- hackerone -- install-nw%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10566</link>
      <description>install-nw is a module which quickly and robustly installs and caches NW.js. install-nw versions below 1.1.5 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10566|2024-08-06T03:30:18.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10578|2024-08-06T03:30:18.494Z -- hackerone -- unicode%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10578</link>
      <description>unicode loads unicode data downloaded from unicode.org into nodejs. Unicode before 9.0.0 downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10578|2024-08-06T03:30:18.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10540|2024-08-06T03:21:52.228Z -- hackerone -- minimatch%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10540</link>
      <description>Minimatch is a minimal matching utility that works by converting glob expressions into JavaScript `RegExp` objects. The primary function, `minimatch(path, pattern)` in Minimatch 3.0.1 and earlier is vulnerable to ReDoS in the `pattern` parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10540|2024-08-06T03:21:52.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10571|2024-08-06T03:30:18.983Z -- hackerone -- bkjs-wand%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10571</link>
      <description>bkjs-wand is imagemagick wand support for node.js and backendjs bkjs-wand versions lower than 0.3.2 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10571|2024-08-06T03:30:18.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10693|2024-08-06T03:30:20.180Z -- hackerone -- pm2-kafka%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10693</link>
      <description>pm2-kafka is a PM2 module that installs and runs a kafka server pm2-kafka downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10693|2024-08-06T03:30:20.180Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10590|2024-08-06T03:30:18.406Z -- hackerone -- cue-sdk-node%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10590</link>
      <description>cue-sdk-node is a Corsair Cue SDK wrapper for node.js. cue-sdk-node downloads zipped resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested zip file with an attacker controlled zip file if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10590|2024-08-06T03:30:18.406Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10576|2024-08-06T03:30:18.459Z -- hackerone -- fuseki%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10576</link>
      <description>Fuseki server wrapper and management API in fuseki before 1.0.1 downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10576|2024-08-06T03:30:18.459Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10523|2024-08-06T03:21:52.173Z -- hackerone -- mqtt-packet%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10523</link>
      <description>MQTT before 3.4.6 and 4.0.x before 4.0.5 allows specifically crafted MQTT packets to crash the application, making a DoS attack feasible with very little bandwidth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10523|2024-08-06T03:21:52.173Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-10064|2024-08-06T14:02:38.236Z -- hackerone -- qs%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-10064</link>
      <description>The qs module before 1.0.0 does not have an option or default for specifying object depth and when parsing a string representing a deeply nested object will block the event loop for long periods of time. An attacker could leverage this to cause a temporary denial-of-service condition, for example, in a web application, other requests would not be processed while this blocking is occurring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-10064|2024-08-06T14:02:38.236Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10589|2024-08-06T03:30:18.486Z -- hackerone -- selenium-binaries%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10589</link>
      <description>selenium-binaries downloads Selenium related binaries for your OS. selenium-binaries downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10589|2024-08-06T03:30:18.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10676|2024-08-06T03:30:20.156Z -- hackerone -- rs-brightcove%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10676</link>
      <description>rs-brightcove is a wrapper around brightcove's web api rs-brightcove downloads source file resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10676|2024-08-06T03:30:20.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10639|2024-08-06T03:30:19.667Z -- hackerone -- redis-srvr%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10639</link>
      <description>redis-srvr is a npm wrapper for redis-server. redis-srvr downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10639|2024-08-06T03:30:19.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-9244|2024-08-06T08:43:42.290Z -- hackerone -- mysql%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-9244</link>
      <description>Keys of objects in mysql node module v2.0.0-alpha7 and earlier are not escaped with `mysql.escape()` which could lead to SQL Injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-9244|2024-08-06T08:43:42.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10588|2024-08-06T03:30:19.141Z -- hackerone -- nw%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10588</link>
      <description>nw is an installer for nw.js. nw downloads zipped resources over HTTP, It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested zip file with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10588|2024-08-06T03:30:19.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10611|2024-08-06T03:30:19.675Z -- hackerone -- strider-sauce%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10611</link>
      <description>strider-sauce is Sauce Labs / Selenium support for Strider. strider-sauce downloads zipped resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested zip file with an attacker controlled zip file if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10611|2024-08-06T03:30:19.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10525|2024-08-06T03:21:52.166Z -- hackerone -- hapi-auth-jwt2%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10525</link>
      <description>When attempting to allow authentication mode `try` in hapi, hapi-auth-jwt2 version 5.1.1 introduced an issue whereby people could bypass authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10525|2024-08-06T03:21:52.166Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10679|2024-08-06T03:30:20.141Z -- hackerone -- selenium-standalone-painful%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10679</link>
      <description>selenium-standalone-painful installs a start-selenium command line to start a standalone selenium server with chrome-driver. selenium-standalone-painful downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10679|2024-08-06T03:30:20.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10594|2024-08-06T03:30:19.465Z -- hackerone -- ipip%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10594</link>
      <description>ipip is a Node.js module to query geolocation information for an IP or domain, based on database by ipip.net. ipip downloads data resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10594|2024-08-06T03:30:19.465Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10534|2024-08-06T03:21:52.177Z -- hackerone -- electron-packager%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10534</link>
      <description>electron-packager is a command line tool that packages Electron source code into `.app` and `.exe` packages. along with Electron. The `--strict-ssl` command line option in electron-packager &gt;= 5.2.1 &lt;= 6.0.0 || &gt;=6.0.0 &lt;= 6.0.2 defaults to false if not explicitly set to true. This could allow an attacker to perform a man in the middle attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10534|2024-08-06T03:21:52.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10614|2024-08-06T03:30:19.484Z -- hackerone -- httpsync%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10614</link>
      <description>httpsync is a port of libcurl to node.js. httpsync downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10614|2024-08-06T03:30:19.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-9235|2024-08-06T08:43:41.633Z -- hackerone -- jsonwebtoken%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-9235</link>
      <description>In jsonwebtoken node module before 4.2.2 it is possible for an attacker to bypass verification when a token digitally signed with an asymmetric key (RS/ES family) of algorithms but instead the attacker send a token digitally signed with a symmetric algorithm (HS* family).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-9235|2024-08-06T08:43:41.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10654|2024-08-06T03:30:20.135Z -- hackerone -- sfml%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10654</link>
      <description>sfml downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10654|2024-08-06T03:30:20.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10659|2024-08-06T03:30:20.132Z -- hackerone -- poco%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10659</link>
      <description>poco - The POCO libraries, downloads source file resources used for compilation over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10659|2024-08-06T03:30:20.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10559|2024-08-06T03:30:18.442Z -- hackerone -- selenium-download%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10559</link>
      <description>selenium-download downloads the latest versions of the selenium standalone server and the chromedriver. selenium-download before 2.0.7 downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10559|2024-08-06T03:30:18.442Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10603|2024-08-06T03:30:19.290Z -- hackerone -- air-sdk%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10603</link>
      <description>air-sdk is a NPM wrapper for the Adobe AIR SDK. air-sdk downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10603|2024-08-06T03:30:19.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10536|2024-08-06T03:21:52.275Z -- hackerone -- engine.io-client%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10536</link>
      <description>engine.io-client is the client for engine.io, the implementation of a transport-based cross-browser/cross-device bi-directional communication layer for Socket.IO. The vulnerability is related to the way that node.js handles the `rejectUnauthorized` setting. If the value is something that evaluates to false, certificate verification will be disabled. This is problematic as engine.io-client 1.6.8 and earlier passes in an object for settings that includes the rejectUnauthorized property, whether it has been set or not. If the value has not been explicitly changed, it will be passed in as `null`, resulting in certificate verification being turned off.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10536|2024-08-06T03:21:52.275Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10673|2024-08-06T03:30:20.117Z -- hackerone -- ipip-coffee%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10673</link>
      <description>ipip-coffee queries geolocation information from IP ipip-coffee downloads geolocation resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. This could impact the integrity and availability of the data being used to make geolocation decisions by an application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10673|2024-08-06T03:30:20.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-9238|2024-08-06T08:43:42.637Z -- hackerone -- secure-compare%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-9238</link>
      <description>secure-compare 3.0.0 and below do not actually compare two strings properly. compare was actually comparing the first argument with itself, meaning the check passed for any two strings of the same length.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-9238|2024-08-06T08:43:42.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10649|2024-08-06T03:30:20.111Z -- hackerone -- frames-compiler%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10649</link>
      <description>frames-compiler downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10649|2024-08-06T03:30:20.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10696|2024-08-06T03:30:20.137Z -- hackerone -- windows-latestchromedriver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10696</link>
      <description>windows-latestchromedriver downloads the latest version of chromedriver.exe. windows-latestchromedriver downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10696|2024-08-06T03:30:20.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10570|2024-08-06T03:30:19.533Z -- hackerone -- pngcrush-installer%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10570</link>
      <description>pngcrush-installer is an installer for Pngcrush. pngcrush-installer versions below 1.8.10 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10570|2024-08-06T03:30:19.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10557|2024-08-06T03:30:18.469Z -- hackerone -- appium-chromedriver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10557</link>
      <description>appium-chromedriver is a Node.js wrapper around Chromedriver. Versions below 2.9.4 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves the module vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10557|2024-08-06T03:30:18.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-9242|2024-08-06T08:43:42.598Z -- hackerone -- ecstatic%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-9242</link>
      <description>Certain input strings when passed to new Date() or Date.parse() in ecstatic node module before 1.4.0 will cause v8 to raise an exception. This leads to a crash and denial of service in ecstatic when this input is passed into the server via the If-Modified-Since header.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-9242|2024-08-06T08:43:42.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10620|2024-08-06T03:30:19.546Z -- hackerone -- atom-node-module-installer%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10620</link>
      <description>atom-node-module-installer installs node modules for atom-shell applications. atom-node-module-installer binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10620|2024-08-06T03:30:19.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10550|2024-08-06T03:21:52.228Z -- hackerone -- sequelize%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10550</link>
      <description>sequelize is an Object-relational mapping, or a middleman to convert things from Postgres, MySQL, MariaDB, SQLite and Microsoft SQL Server into usable data for NodeJS If user input goes into the `limit` or `order` parameters, a malicious user can put in their own SQL statements. This affects sequelize 3.16.0 and earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10550|2024-08-06T03:21:52.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10687|2024-08-06T03:30:20.130Z -- hackerone -- windows-selenium-chromedriver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10687</link>
      <description>windows-selenium-chromedriver is a module that downloads the Selenium Jar file. windows-selenium-chromedriver downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10687|2024-08-06T03:30:20.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10580|2024-08-06T03:30:18.406Z -- hackerone -- nodewebkit%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10580</link>
      <description>nodewebkit is an installer for node-webkit. nodewebkit downloads zipped resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested zip file with an attacker controlled zip file if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10580|2024-08-06T03:30:18.406Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10556|2024-08-06T03:30:18.167Z -- hackerone -- sequelize%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10556</link>
      <description>sequelize is an Object-relational mapping, or a middleman to convert things from Postgres, MySQL, MariaDB, SQLite and Microsoft SQL Server into usable data for NodeJS In Postgres, SQLite, and Microsoft SQL Server there is an issue where arrays are treated as strings and improperly escaped. This causes potential SQL injection in sequelize 3.19.3 and earlier, where a malicious user could put `["test", "'); DELETE TestTable WHERE Id = 1 --')"]` inside of ``` database.query('SELECT * FROM TestTable WHERE Name IN (:names)', { replacements: { names: directCopyOfUserInput } }); ``` and cause the SQL statement to become `SELECT Id FROM Table WHERE Name IN ('test', '\'); DELETE TestTable WHERE Id = 1 --')`. In Postgres, MSSQL, and SQLite, the backslash has no special meaning. This causes the the statement to delete whichever Id has a value of 1 in the TestTable table.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10556|2024-08-06T03:30:18.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10547|2024-08-06T03:21:52.154Z -- hackerone -- nunjucks%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10547</link>
      <description>Nunjucks is a full featured templating engine for JavaScript. Versions 2.4.2 and lower have a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in autoescape mode. In autoescape mode, all template vars should automatically be escaped. By using an array for the keys, such as `name[]=&lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt;`, it is possible to bypass autoescaping and inject content into the DOM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10547|2024-08-06T03:21:52.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10678|2024-08-06T03:30:20.146Z -- hackerone -- serc.js%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10678</link>
      <description>serc.js is a Selenium RC process wrapper serc.js downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10678|2024-08-06T03:30:20.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10616|2024-08-06T03:30:19.887Z -- hackerone -- openframe-image%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10616</link>
      <description>openframe-image is an Openframe extension which adds support for images via fbi. openframe-image downloads data resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10616|2024-08-06T03:30:19.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10633|2024-08-06T03:30:20.159Z -- hackerone -- dwebp-bin%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10633</link>
      <description>dwebp-bin is a dwebp node.js wrapper that convert WebP into PNG. dwebp-bin downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10633|2024-08-06T03:30:20.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10546|2024-08-06T03:21:52.157Z -- hackerone -- pouchdb%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10546</link>
      <description>An arbitrary code injection vector was found in PouchDB 6.0.4 and lesser via the map/reduce functions used in PouchDB temporary views and design documents. The code execution engine for this branch is not properly sandboxed and may be used to run arbitrary JavaScript as well as system commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10546|2024-08-06T03:21:52.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10539|2024-08-06T03:21:52.246Z -- hackerone -- negotiator%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10539</link>
      <description>negotiator is an HTTP content negotiator for Node.js and is used by many modules and frameworks including Express and Koa. The header for "Accept-Language", when parsed by negotiator 0.6.0 and earlier is vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service via a specially crafted string.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10539|2024-08-06T03:21:52.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10641|2024-08-06T03:30:19.624Z -- hackerone -- node-bsdiff-android%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10641</link>
      <description>node-bsdiff-android downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10641|2024-08-06T03:30:19.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10602|2024-08-06T03:30:19.090Z -- hackerone -- haxe%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10602</link>
      <description>haxe is a cross-platform toolkit haxe downloads zipped resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested zip file with an attacker controlled zip file if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10602|2024-08-06T03:30:19.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10666|2024-08-06T03:30:20.126Z -- hackerone -- tomita-parser%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10666</link>
      <description>tomita-parser is a Node wrapper for Yandex Tomita Parser tomita-parser downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10666|2024-08-06T03:30:20.126Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10674|2024-08-06T03:30:20.133Z -- hackerone -- limbus-buildgen%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10674</link>
      <description>limbus-buildgen is a "build anywhere" build system. limbus-buildgen versions below 0.1.1 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10674|2024-08-06T03:30:20.133Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10642|2024-08-06T03:30:19.651Z -- hackerone -- cmake%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10642</link>
      <description>cmake installs the cmake x86 linux binaries. cmake downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10642|2024-08-06T03:30:19.651Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10587|2024-08-06T03:30:19.011Z -- hackerone -- wasdk%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10587</link>
      <description>wasdk is a toolkit for creating WebAssembly modules. wasdk downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10587|2024-08-06T03:30:19.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10551|2024-08-06T03:21:52.163Z -- hackerone -- waterline-sequel%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10551</link>
      <description>waterline-sequel is a module that helps generate SQL statements for Waterline apps Any user input that goes into Waterline's `like`, `contains`, `startsWith`, or `endsWith` will end up in waterline-sequel with the potential for malicious code. A malicious user can input their own SQL statements in waterline-sequel 0.50 that will get executed and have full access to the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10551|2024-08-06T03:21:52.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10646|2024-08-06T03:30:19.996Z -- hackerone -- resourcehacker%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10646</link>
      <description>resourcehacker is a Node wrapper of Resource Hacker (windows executable resource editor). resourcehacker downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10646|2024-08-06T03:30:19.996Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10577|2024-08-06T03:30:18.418Z -- hackerone -- ibm_db%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10577</link>
      <description>ibm_db is an asynchronous/synchronous interface for node.js to IBM DB2 and IBM Informix. ibm_db before 1.0.2 downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10577|2024-08-06T03:30:18.418Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10630|2024-08-06T03:30:19.188Z -- hackerone -- install-g-test%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10630</link>
      <description>install-g-test downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10630|2024-08-06T03:30:19.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10648|2024-08-06T03:30:19.961Z -- hackerone -- marionette-socket-host%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10648</link>
      <description>marionette-socket-host is a marionette-js-runner host for sending actions over a socket. marionette-socket-host downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10648|2024-08-06T03:30:19.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10686|2024-08-06T03:30:20.141Z -- hackerone -- fis-sass-all%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10686</link>
      <description>fis-sass-all is another libsass wrapper for node. fis-sass-all downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10686|2024-08-06T03:30:20.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10564|2024-08-06T03:30:18.471Z -- hackerone -- apk-parser%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10564</link>
      <description>apk-parser is a tool to extract Android Manifest info from an APK file. apk-parser versions below 0.1.6 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10564|2024-08-06T03:30:18.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10657|2024-08-06T03:30:20.117Z -- hackerone -- co-cli-installer%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10657</link>
      <description>co-cli-installer downloads the co-cli module as part of the install process, but does so over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10657|2024-08-06T03:30:20.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10521|2024-08-06T03:21:52.155Z -- hackerone -- jshamcrest%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10521</link>
      <description>jshamcrest is vulnerable to regular expression denial of service (ReDoS) when certain types of user input is passed in to the emailAddress validator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10521|2024-08-06T03:21:52.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10625|2024-08-06T03:30:19.793Z -- hackerone -- headless-browser-lite%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10625</link>
      <description>headless-browser-lite is a minimal npm installer for phantomjs and slimerjs with no external dependencies. headless-browser-lite downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10625|2024-08-06T03:30:19.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10573|2024-08-06T03:30:19.952Z -- hackerone -- baryton-saxophone%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10573</link>
      <description>baryton-saxophone is a module to install and launch Selenium Server for Mac, Linux and Windows. baryton-saxophone versions below 3.0.1 download binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10573|2024-08-06T03:30:19.952Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10569|2024-08-06T03:30:18.412Z -- hackerone -- embedza%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10569</link>
      <description>embedza is a module to create HTML snippets/embeds from URLs using info from oEmbed, Open Graph, meta tags. embedza versions below 1.2.4 download JavaScript resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested JavaScript file with an attacker controlled JavaScript file if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10569|2024-08-06T03:30:18.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10582|2024-08-06T03:30:19.099Z -- hackerone -- closurecompiler%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10582</link>
      <description>closurecompiler is a Closure Compiler for node.js. closurecompiler downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10582|2024-08-06T03:30:19.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10629|2024-08-06T03:30:19.855Z -- hackerone -- nw-with-arm%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10629</link>
      <description>nw-with-arm is a NW Installer including ARM-Build. nw-with-arm downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10629|2024-08-06T03:30:19.855Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10579|2024-08-06T03:30:19.145Z -- hackerone -- chromedriver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10579</link>
      <description>Chromedriver is an NPM wrapper for selenium ChromeDriver. Chromedriver before 2.26.1 downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10579|2024-08-06T03:30:19.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-9240|2024-08-06T08:43:41.887Z -- hackerone -- keystone%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-9240</link>
      <description>Due to a bug in the the default sign in functionality in the keystone node module before 0.3.16, incomplete email addresses could be matched. A correct password is still required to complete sign in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-9240|2024-08-06T08:43:41.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10645|2024-08-06T03:30:19.852Z -- hackerone -- grunt-images%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10645</link>
      <description>grunt-images is a grunt plugin for processing images. grunt-images downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10645|2024-08-06T03:30:19.852Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10613|2024-08-06T03:30:19.097Z -- hackerone -- bionode-sra%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10613</link>
      <description>bionode-sra is a Node.js wrapper for SRA Toolkit. bionode-sra downloads data resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10613|2024-08-06T03:30:19.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10585|2024-08-06T03:30:18.492Z -- hackerone -- libxl%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10585</link>
      <description>libxl provides Node bindings for the libxl library for reading and writing excel (XLS and XLSX) spreadsheets. libxl downloads zipped resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested zip file with an attacker controlled zip file if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10585|2024-08-06T03:30:18.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10524|2024-08-06T03:21:52.155Z -- hackerone -- i18n-node-angular%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10524</link>
      <description>i18n-node-angular is a module used to interact between i18n and angular without using additional resources. A REST API endpoint that is used for development in i18n-node-angular before 1.4.0 was not disabled in production environments a malicious user could fill up the server causing a Denial of Service or content injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10524|2024-08-06T03:21:52.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10621|2024-08-06T03:30:20.111Z -- hackerone -- fibjs%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10621</link>
      <description>fibjs is a runtime for javascript applictions built on google v8 JS. fibjs downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10621|2024-08-06T03:30:20.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10626|2024-08-06T03:30:19.784Z -- hackerone -- mystem3%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10626</link>
      <description>mystem3 is a NodeJS wrapper for the Yandex MyStem 3. mystem3 downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10626|2024-08-06T03:30:19.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10600|2024-08-06T03:30:20.050Z -- hackerone -- webrtc-native%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10600</link>
      <description>webrtc-native uses WebRTC from chromium project. webrtc-native downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10600|2024-08-06T03:30:20.050Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10698|2024-08-06T03:30:20.129Z -- hackerone -- mystem-fix%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10698</link>
      <description>mystem-fix is a node.js wrapper for MyStem morphology text analyzer by Yandex.ru mystem-fix downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10698|2024-08-06T03:30:20.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-9236|2024-08-06T08:43:42.636Z -- hackerone -- hapi%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-9236</link>
      <description>Hapi versions less than 11.0.0 implement CORS incorrectly and allowed for configurations that at best returned inconsistent headers and at worst allowed cross-origin activities that were expected to be forbidden. If the connection has CORS enabled but one route has it off, and the route is not GET, the OPTIONS prefetch request will return the default CORS headers and then the actual request will go through and return no CORS headers. This defeats the purpose of turning CORS on the route.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-9236|2024-08-06T08:43:42.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10663|2024-08-06T03:30:20.150Z -- hackerone -- wixtoolset%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10663</link>
      <description>wixtoolset is a Node module wrapper around the wixtoolset binaries wixtoolset downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10663|2024-08-06T03:30:20.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10680|2024-08-06T03:30:20.293Z -- hackerone -- adamvr-geoip-lite%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10680</link>
      <description>adamvr-geoip-lite is a light weight native JavaScript implementation of GeoIP API from MaxMind adamvr-geoip-lite downloads geoip resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. This impacts the integrity and availability of this geoip data that may alter the decisions made by an application using this data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10680|2024-08-06T03:30:20.293Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10533|2024-08-06T03:21:52.171Z -- hackerone -- express-restify-mongoose%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10533</link>
      <description>express-restify-mongoose is a module to easily create a flexible REST interface for mongoose models. express-restify-mongoose 2.4.2 and earlier and 3.0.X through 3.0.1 allows a malicious user to send a request for `GET /User?distinct=password` and get all the passwords for all the users in the database, despite the field being set to private. This can be used for other private data if the malicious user knew what was set as private for specific routes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10533|2024-08-06T03:21:52.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10685|2024-08-06T03:30:20.159Z -- hackerone -- pk-app-wonderbox%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10685</link>
      <description>pk-app-wonderbox is an integration with wonderbox pk-app-wonderbox downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10685|2024-08-06T03:30:20.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10618|2024-08-06T03:30:19.648Z -- hackerone -- node-browser%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10618</link>
      <description>node-browser is a wrapper webdriver by nodejs. node-browser downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10618|2024-08-06T03:30:19.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10690|2024-08-06T03:30:20.153Z -- hackerone -- openframe-ascii-image%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10690</link>
      <description>openframe-ascii-image module is an openframe plugin which adds support for ascii images via fim. openframe-ascii-image downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10690|2024-08-06T03:30:20.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10599|2024-08-06T03:30:19.800Z -- hackerone -- sauce-connect%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10599</link>
      <description>sauce-connect is a Node.js wrapper over the SauceLabs SauceConnect.jar program for establishing a secure tunnel for intranet testing. sauce-connect downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10599|2024-08-06T03:30:19.800Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10586|2024-08-06T03:30:18.415Z -- hackerone -- macaca-chromedriver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10586</link>
      <description>macaca-chromedriver is a Node.js wrapper for the selenium chromedriver. macaca-chromedriver before 1.0.29 downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10586|2024-08-06T03:30:18.415Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10609|2024-08-06T03:30:19.189Z -- hackerone -- chromedriver126%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10609</link>
      <description>chromedriver126 is chromedriver version 1.26 for linux OS. chromedriver126 downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10609|2024-08-06T03:30:19.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10697|2024-08-06T03:30:20.152Z -- hackerone -- react-native-baidu-voice-synthesizer%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10697</link>
      <description>react-native-baidu-voice-synthesizer is a baidu voice speech synthesizer for react native. react-native-baidu-voice-synthesizer downloads resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10697|2024-08-06T03:30:20.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10677|2024-08-06T03:30:20.159Z -- hackerone -- google-closure-tools-latest%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10677</link>
      <description>google-closure-tools-latest is a Node.js module wrapper for downloading the latest version of the Google Closure tools google-closure-tools-latest downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10677|2024-08-06T03:30:20.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10543|2024-08-06T03:21:52.140Z -- hackerone -- call%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10543</link>
      <description>call is an HTTP router that is primarily used by the hapi framework. There exists a bug in call versions 2.0.1-3.0.1 that does not validate empty parameters, which could result in invalid input bypassing the route validation rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10543|2024-08-06T03:21:52.140Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10662|2024-08-06T03:30:20.136Z -- hackerone -- tomita%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10662</link>
      <description>tomita is a node wrapper for Yandex Tomita Parser tomita downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested resources with an attacker controlled copy if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10662|2024-08-06T03:30:20.136Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10531|2024-08-06T03:21:52.151Z -- hackerone -- marked%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10531</link>
      <description>marked is an application that is meant to parse and compile markdown. Due to the way that marked 0.3.5 and earlier parses input, specifically HTML entities, it's possible to bypass marked's content injection protection (`sanitize: true`) to inject a `javascript:` URL. This flaw exists because `&amp;#xNNanything;` gets parsed to what it could and leaves the rest behind, resulting in just `anything;` being left.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10531|2024-08-06T03:21:52.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10604|2024-08-06T03:30:19.340Z -- hackerone -- dalek-browser-chrome%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10604</link>
      <description>dalek-browser-chrome is Google Chrome bindings for DalekJS. dalek-browser-chrome downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10604|2024-08-06T03:30:19.340Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10542|2024-08-06T03:21:52.152Z -- hackerone -- ws%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10542</link>
      <description>ws is a "simple to use, blazing fast and thoroughly tested websocket client, server and console for node.js, up-to-date against RFC-6455". By sending an overly long websocket payload to a `ws` server, it is possible to crash the node process. This affects ws 1.1.0 and earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10542|2024-08-06T03:21:52.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10622|2024-08-06T03:30:19.080Z -- hackerone -- nodeschnaps%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10622</link>
      <description>nodeschnaps is a NodeJS compatibility layer for Java (Rhino). nodeschnaps downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10622|2024-08-06T03:30:19.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-10065|2024-08-06T14:02:38.297Z -- hackerone -- remarkable%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-10065</link>
      <description>Certain input when passed into remarkable before 1.4.1 will bypass the bad protocol check that disallows the javascript: scheme allowing for javascript: url's to be injected into the rendered content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-10065|2024-08-06T14:02:38.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10653|2024-08-06T03:30:19.930Z -- hackerone -- xd-testing%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10653</link>
      <description>xd-testing is a testing library for cross-device (XD) web applications. xd-testing downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10653|2024-08-06T03:30:19.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10615|2024-08-06T03:30:20.125Z -- hackerone -- curses%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10615</link>
      <description>curses is bindings for the native curses library, a full featured console IO library. curses downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10615|2024-08-06T03:30:20.125Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10631|2024-08-06T03:30:19.740Z -- hackerone -- jvminstall%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10631</link>
      <description>jvminstall is a module for downloading and unpacking jvm to local system. jvminstall downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10631|2024-08-06T03:30:19.740Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10526|2024-08-06T03:21:52.150Z -- hackerone -- grunt-gh-pages%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10526</link>
      <description>A common setup to deploy to gh-pages on every commit via a CI system is to expose a github token to ENV and to use it directly in the auth part of the url. In module versions &lt; 0.9.1 the auth portion of the url is outputted as part of the grunt tasks logging function. If this output is publicly available then the credentials should be considered compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10526|2024-08-06T03:21:52.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10553|2024-08-06T03:21:52.242Z -- hackerone -- sequelize%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10553</link>
      <description>sequelize is an Object-relational mapping, or a middleman to convert things from Postgres, MySQL, MariaDB, SQLite and Microsoft SQL Server into usable data for NodeJS. A fix was pushed out that fixed potential SQL injection in sequelize 2.1.3 and earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10553|2024-08-06T03:21:52.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10605|2024-08-06T03:30:19.186Z -- hackerone -- dalek-browser-ie%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10605</link>
      <description>dalek-browser-ie is Internet Explorer bindings for DalekJS. dalek-browser-ie downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10605|2024-08-06T03:30:19.186Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10530|2024-08-06T03:21:52.188Z -- hackerone -- airbrake%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10530</link>
      <description>The airbrake module 0.3.8 and earlier defaults to sending environment variables over HTTP. Environment variables can often times contain secret keys and other sensitive values. A malicious user could be on the same network as a regular user and intercept all the secret keys the user is sending. This goes against common best practice, which is to use HTTPS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10530|2024-08-06T03:21:52.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10595|2024-08-06T03:30:19.038Z -- hackerone -- jdf-sass%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10595</link>
      <description>jdf-sass is a fork from node-sass, jdf use only. jdf-sass downloads executable resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested file with an attacker controlled file if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10595|2024-08-06T03:30:19.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10624|2024-08-06T03:30:19.966Z -- hackerone -- selenium-chromedriver%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10624</link>
      <description>selenium-chromedriver is a simple utility for downloading the Selenium Webdriver for Google Chrome selenium-chromedriver downloads binary resources over HTTP, which leaves it vulnerable to MITM attacks. It may be possible to cause remote code execution (RCE) by swapping out the requested binary with an attacker controlled binary if the attacker is on the network or positioned in between the user and the remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10624|2024-08-06T03:30:19.966Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10563|2024-08-06T03:30:18.477Z -- hackerone -- go-ipfs-dep%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10563</link>
      <description>During the installation process, the go-ipfs-deps module before 0.4.4 insecurely downloads resources over HTTP. This allows for a MITM attack to compromise the integrity of the resources used by this module and could allow for further compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10563|2024-08-06T03:30:18.477Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-10068|2024-08-06T14:02:38.190Z -- hackerone -- inert%20node%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-10068</link>
      <description>The inert directory handler in inert node module before 1.1.1 always allows files in hidden directories to be served, even when `showHidden` is false.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-10068|2024-08-06T14:02:38.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
