<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for stripe -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/stripe/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for stripe -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 08:23:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29188|2024-08-03T06:17:54.114Z -- stripe -- smokescreen
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29188</link>
      <description>Smokescreen is an HTTP proxy. The primary use case for Smokescreen is to prevent server-side request forgery (SSRF) attacks in which external attackers leverage the behavior of applications to connect to or scan internal infrastructure. Smokescreen also offers an option to deny access to additional (e.g., external) URLs by way of a deny list. There was an issue in Smokescreen that made it possible to bypass the deny list feature by surrounding the hostname with square brackets (e.g. `[example.com]`). This only impacted the HTTP proxy functionality of Smokescreen. HTTPS requests were not impacted. Smokescreen version 0.0.4 contains a patch for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29188|2024-08-03T06:17:54.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 23:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24825|2024-08-03T04:20:50.515Z -- stripe -- smokescreen
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24825</link>
      <description>Smokescreen is a simple HTTP proxy that fogs over naughty URLs. The primary use case for Smokescreen is to prevent server-side request forgery (SSRF) attacks in which external attackers leverage the behavior of applications to connect to or scan internal infrastructure. Smokescreen also offers an option to deny access to additional (e.g., external) URLs by way of a deny list. There was an issue in Smokescreen that made it possible to bypass the deny list feature by appending a dot to the end of user-supplied URLs, or by providing input in a different letter case. Recommended to upgrade Smokescreen to version 0.0.3 or later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24825|2024-08-03T04:20:50.515Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 19:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24753|2024-08-03T04:20:50.100Z -- stripe -- stripe-cli
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24753</link>
      <description>Stripe CLI is a command-line tool for the Stripe eCommerce platform. A vulnerability in Stripe CLI exists on Windows when certain commands are run in a directory where an attacker has planted files. The commands are `stripe login`, `stripe config -e`, `stripe community`, and `stripe open`. MacOS and Linux are unaffected. An attacker who successfully exploits the vulnerability can run arbitrary code in the context of the current user. The update addresses the vulnerability by throwing an error in these situations before the code can run.Users are advised to upgrade to version 1.7.13. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24753|2024-08-03T04:20:50.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 22:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
