<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for keerti1924 -- PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/keerti1924/php-mysql-user-login-system.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for keerti1924 -- PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1700|2024-02-21T15:31:04.565Z -- keerti1924 -- PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1700</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /signup.php. The manipulation of the argument username with the input &lt;script&gt;alert("xss")&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254388. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /signup.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments username mit der Eingabe &lt;script&gt;alert("xss")&lt;/script&gt; mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1700|2024-02-21T15:31:04.565Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1701|2024-02-21T15:31:06.175Z -- keerti1924 -- PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1701</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /edit.php. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254389 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /edit.php. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper access controls-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1701|2024-02-21T15:31:06.175Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1702|2024-02-21T16:31:04.593Z -- keerti1924 -- PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1702</link><description>A vulnerability was found in keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /edit.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-254390 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /edit.php. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1702|2024-02-21T16:31:04.593Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 16:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2264|2024-03-07T21:00:06.751Z -- keerti1924 -- PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2264</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256034 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System 1.0 entdeckt. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei /login.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments email mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2264|2024-03-07T21:00:06.751Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 21:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2265|2024-03-07T21:31:05.029Z -- keerti1924 -- PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2265</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file login.sql. The manipulation leads to inclusion of sensitive information in source code. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256035. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in keerti1924 PHP-MYSQL-User-Login-System 1.0 gefunden. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei login.sql. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine inclusion of sensitive information in source code-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2265|2024-03-07T21:31:05.029Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 21:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>