<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Foscam -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/foscam/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Foscam -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 19:20:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2854|2024-09-17T04:20:34.508Z -- foscam -- foscam%20indoor%20ip%20camera%20c1%20series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2854</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the DDNS client used by the Foscam C1 Indoor HD Camera running application firmware 2.52.2.43. On devices with DDNS enabled, an attacker who is able to intercept HTTP connections will be able to fully compromise the device by creating a rogue HTTP server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2854|2024-09-17T04:20:34.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2874|2024-09-17T03:43:57.607Z -- foscam -- foscam%20indoor%20ip%20camera%20c1%20series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2874</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in the Multi-Camera interface used by the Foscam C1 Indoor HD Camera running application firmware 2.52.2.43. A specially crafted request on port 10001 can allow for a user to retrieve sensitive information without authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2874|2024-09-17T03:43:57.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2833|2024-09-17T02:21:27.300Z -- foscam -- indoor%20ip%20camera
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2833</link>
      <description>An exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the web management interface used by the Foscam C1 Indoor HD Camera running application firmware 2.52.2.37. A specially crafted HTTP request can allow for a user to inject arbitrary shell characters resulting in command injection during the boot process. To trigger this vulnerability, an attacker needs to send an HTTP request and reboot the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2833|2024-09-17T02:21:27.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2878|2024-09-17T03:18:34.203Z -- foscam -- foscam%20c1%20indoor%20hd%20camera
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2878</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the web management interface used by the Foscam C1 Indoor HD Camera running application firmware 2.52.2.43. A specially crafted HTTP request can cause a buffer overflow resulting in overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can simply send an HTTP request to the device to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2878|2024-09-17T03:18:34.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2879|2024-09-17T03:38:09.053Z -- foscam -- foscam%20c1%20indoor%20hd%20camera
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2879</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the UPnP implementation used by the Foscam C1 Indoor HD Camera running application firmware 2.52.2.43. A specially crafted UPnP discovery response can cause a buffer overflow resulting in overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker needs to be in the same subnetwork and reply to a discovery message to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2879|2024-09-17T03:38:09.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2832|2024-09-17T04:08:52.705Z -- foscam -- indoor%20ip%20camera
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2832</link>
      <description>An exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the web management interface used by the Foscam C1 Indoor HD Camera running application firmware 2.52.2.37. A specially crafted HTTP request can allow for a user to inject arbitrary shell characters during a password change resulting in command injection. An attacker can simply send an HTTP request to the device to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2832|2024-09-17T04:08:52.705Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2877|2024-09-17T02:26:47.991Z -- foscam -- foscam%20c1%20indoor%20hd%20camera
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2877</link>
      <description>A missing error check exists in the Multi-Camera interface used by the Foscam C1 Indoor HD Camera running application firmware 2.52.2.43. A specially crafted request on port 10001 could allow an attacker to reset the user accounts to factory defaults, without authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2877|2024-09-17T02:26:47.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
