<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Ruijie -- RG-EG350</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ruijie/rg-eg350.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Ruijie -- RG-EG350</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 23:21:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2909|2024-03-26T21:00:06.849Z -- ruijie -- rg-eg350</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2909</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Ruijie RG-EG350 up to 20240318. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setAction of the file /itbox_pi/networksafe.php?a=set of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument bandwidth leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257977 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Ruijie RG-EG350 bis 20240318 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Betroffen ist die Funktion setAction der Datei /itbox_pi/networksafe.php?a=set der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments bandwidth mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2909|2024-03-26T21:00:06.849Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 21:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2910|2024-06-05T19:50:05.546Z -- ruijie -- rg-eg350</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2910</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Ruijie RG-EG350 up to 20240318. Affected by this issue is the function vpnAction of the file /itbox_pi/vpn_quickset_service.php?a=set_vpn of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument ip/port/user/pass/dns/startIp leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257978 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Ruijie RG-EG350 bis 20240318 entdeckt. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion vpnAction der Datei /itbox_pi/vpn_quickset_service.php?a=set_vpn der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments ip/port/user/pass/dns/startIp mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2910|2024-06-05T19:50:05.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 21:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
