<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for LinkedIn -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/linkedin/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for LinkedIn -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 18:24:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4264|2024-08-03T17:23:10.011Z -- linkedin -- dustjs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4264</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in LinkedIn dustjs up to 2.x and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to improperly controlled modification of object prototype attributes ('prototype pollution'). The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.0.0 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is ddb6523832465d38c9d80189e9de60519ac307c3. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-216464.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in LinkedIn dustjs bis 2.x gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improperly controlled modification of object prototype attributes ('prototype pollution')-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 3.0.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als ddb6523832465d38c9d80189e9de60519ac307c3 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4264|2024-08-03T17:23:10.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
