<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for OmniSharp -- csharp-language-server-protocol</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/omnisharp/csharp-language-server-protocol.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for OmniSharp -- csharp-language-server-protocol</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 05:22:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4952|2024-08-03T01:55:46.088Z -- omnisharp -- csharp-language-server-protocol
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4952</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in OmniSharp csharp-language-server-protocol up to 0.19.6 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function CreateSerializerSettings of the file src/JsonRpc/Serialization/SerializerBase.cs of the component JSON Serializer. The manipulation leads to resource consumption. Upgrading to version 0.19.7 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 7fd2219f194a9ef2a8901bb131c5fa12272305ce. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-234238 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In OmniSharp csharp-language-server-protocol bis 0.19.6 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Dabei geht es um die Funktion CreateSerializerSettings der Datei src/JsonRpc/Serialization/SerializerBase.cs der Komponente JSON Serializer. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine resource consumption-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 0.19.7 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 7fd2219f194a9ef2a8901bb131c5fa12272305ce bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4952|2024-08-03T01:55:46.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 02:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
