<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TOTOLINK -- A3600R</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/totolink/a3600r.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TOTOLINK -- A3600R</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 07:21:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7186|2024-07-29T06:00:09.895Z -- totolink -- a3600r
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7186</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function setWiFiAclAddConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument comment leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272607. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um die Funktion setWiFiAclAddConfig der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments comment mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7186|2024-07-29T06:00:09.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7187|2024-07-29T06:31:04.399Z -- totolink -- a3600r
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7187</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument File leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272608. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um die Funktion UploadCustomModule der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments File mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7187|2024-07-29T06:31:04.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7183|2024-07-29T04:31:04.254Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7183</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected is the function setUploadSetting of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272604. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion setUploadSetting der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments FileName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7183|2024-07-29T04:31:04.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 04:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7178|2024-07-29T02:00:08.334Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7178</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setMacQos of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument priority/macAddress leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272599. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion setMacQos der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments priority/macAddress mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7178|2024-07-29T02:00:08.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 02:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7179|2024-07-29T02:31:03.995Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7179</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument startTime/endTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272600. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 ausgemacht. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion setParentalRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments startTime/endTime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7179|2024-07-29T02:31:03.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 02:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7176|2024-07-29T01:01:19.532Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7176</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function setIpQosRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument comment leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272597 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 gefunden. Dies betrifft die Funktion setIpQosRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments comment mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7176|2024-07-29T01:01:19.532Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 01:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7175|2024-07-29T00:31:04.158Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7175</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ipDoamin leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272596. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Das betrifft die Funktion setDiagnosisCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments ipDoamin mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7175|2024-07-29T00:31:04.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7159|2024-07-28T14:31:06.336Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7159</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini of the component Telnet Service. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272573 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini der Komponente Telnet Service. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded password-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7159|2024-07-28T14:31:06.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 14:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7172|2024-07-28T23:00:08.214Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7172</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getSaveConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272593 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Dabei geht es um die Funktion getSaveConfig der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7172|2024-07-28T23:00:08.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 23:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7171|2024-07-28T22:31:03.790Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7171</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected is the function NTPSyncWithHost of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostTime leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272592. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 entdeckt. Es geht dabei um die Funktion NTPSyncWithHost der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank Manipulation des Arguments hostTime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7171|2024-07-28T22:31:03.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 22:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7177|2024-07-29T01:31:03.907Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7177</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function setLanguageCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument langType leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272598 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 ausgemacht. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion setLanguageCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments langType mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7177|2024-07-29T01:31:03.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 01:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7180|2024-07-29T03:00:09.470Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7180</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. This affects the function setPortForwardRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument comment leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272601 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion setPortForwardRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments comment mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7180|2024-07-29T03:00:09.470Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 03:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7182|2024-07-29T04:00:06.814Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7182</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. This issue affects the function setUpgradeFW of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272603. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion setUpgradeFW der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank Manipulation des Arguments FileName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7182|2024-07-29T04:00:06.814Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 04:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7181|2024-07-29T03:31:04.422Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7181</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. This vulnerability affects the function setTelnetCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument telnet_enabled leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272602 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist die Funktion setTelnetCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments telnet_enabled mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7181|2024-07-29T03:31:04.422Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 03:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7184|2024-07-29T05:00:07.143Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7184</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setUrlFilterRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272605 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um die Funktion setUrlFilterRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7184|2024-07-29T05:00:07.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 05:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7185|2024-07-29T05:31:03.591Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7185</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setWebWlanIdx of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument webWlanIdx leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272606 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion setWebWlanIdx der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulation des Arguments webWlanIdx mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7185|2024-07-29T05:31:03.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 05:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
