<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Totolink -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/totolink/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Totolink -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 23:21:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7170|2024-07-28T22:00:06.652Z -- totolink -- a3000ru
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7170</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3000RU 5.9c.5185. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272591. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3000RU 5.9c.5185 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded password-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7170|2024-07-28T22:00:06.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 22:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7171|2024-07-28T22:31:03.790Z -- totolink -- a3600r
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7171</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected is the function NTPSyncWithHost of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostTime leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272592. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 entdeckt. Es geht dabei um die Funktion NTPSyncWithHost der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank Manipulation des Arguments hostTime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7171|2024-07-28T22:31:03.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 22:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7172|2024-07-28T23:00:08.214Z -- totolink -- a3600r
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7172</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getSaveConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;setting. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272593 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Dabei geht es um die Funktion getSaveConfig der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;setting. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7172|2024-07-28T23:00:08.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 23:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7159|2024-07-28T14:31:06.336Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7159</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini of the component Telnet Service. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272573 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini der Komponente Telnet Service. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded password-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7159|2024-07-28T14:31:06.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 14:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7157|2024-07-28T11:00:06.342Z -- totolink -- a3100r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7157</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3100R 4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function getSaveConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272571. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3100R 4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion getSaveConfig der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7157|2024-07-28T11:00:06.342Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 11:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7156|2024-07-28T11:05:27.616Z -- totolink -- a3700r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7156</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /cgi-bin/ExportSettings.sh of the component apmib Configuration Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272570 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /cgi-bin/ExportSettings.sh der Komponente apmib Configuration Handler. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7156|2024-07-28T11:05:27.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 10:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7154|2024-07-28T09:31:04.048Z -- totolink -- a3700r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7154</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513. Affected is an unknown function of the file /wizard.html of the component Password Reset Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272568. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /wizard.html der Komponente Password Reset Handler. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper access controls-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7154|2024-07-28T09:31:04.048Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 09:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7155|2024-07-28T10:00:06.076Z -- totolink -- a3300r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7155</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /etc/shadow.sample. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272569 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /etc/shadow.sample. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded password-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal angegangen werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie gilt als schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7155|2024-07-28T10:00:06.076Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 10:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1783|2024-02-23T00:00:10.799Z -- totolink -- lr1200gb</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1783</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130/9.3.5u.6698_B20230810. Affected is the function loginAuth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-254574 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130/9.3.5u.6698_B20230810 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion loginAuth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente Web Interface. Dank Manipulation des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1783|2024-02-23T00:00:10.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1661|2024-02-21T11:51:10.953Z -- totolink -- x6000r</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1661</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_B20230719. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /etc/shadow. The manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254179. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /etc/shadow. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine hard-coded credentials-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal angegangen werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie gilt als schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1661|2024-02-21T11:51:10.953Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 12:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1781|2024-02-23T00:00:08.886Z -- totolink -- x6000r%20ax3000</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1781</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink X6000R AX3000 9.4.0cu.852_20230719. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function setWizardCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component shttpd. The manipulation leads to command injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254573 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink X6000R AX3000 9.4.0cu.852_20230719 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion setWizardCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente shttpd. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1781|2024-02-23T00:00:08.886Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2353|2024-03-10T07:31:04.225Z -- totolink -- x6000r</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2353</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_20230719. This issue affects the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component shttpd. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256313 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_20230719 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion setDiagnosisCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente shttpd. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments ip mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2353|2024-03-10T07:31:04.225Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 07:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1781|2024-07-25T18:10:22.627Z -- totolink -- x6000r%20ax3000</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1781</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink X6000R AX3000 9.4.0cu.852_20230719. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function setWizardCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component shttpd. The manipulation leads to command injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254573 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink X6000R AX3000 9.4.0cu.852_20230719 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion setWizardCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente shttpd. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1781|2024-07-25T18:10:22.627Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7156|2024-07-28T10:31:04.509Z -- totolink -- a3700r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7156</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /cgi-bin/ExportSettings.sh of the component apmib Configuration Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272570 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /cgi-bin/ExportSettings.sh der Komponente apmib Configuration Handler. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7156|2024-07-28T10:31:04.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 10:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7158|2024-07-28T13:31:03.637Z -- totolink -- a3100r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7158</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3100R 4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setTelnetCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument telnet_enabled leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272572. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3100R 4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist die Funktion setTelnetCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments telnet_enabled mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7158|2024-07-28T13:31:03.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 13:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7160|2024-07-28T15:00:07.203Z -- totolink -- a3700r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7160</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513. Affected is the function setWanCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostName leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272574 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion setWanCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments hostName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7160|2024-07-28T15:00:07.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
