<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Totolink -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/totolink/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Totolink -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 18:23:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7908|2024-08-18T17:00:05.376Z -- totolink -- ex1200l
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7908</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023. Affected is the function setDefResponse of the file /www/cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument IpAddress leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion setDefResponse der Datei /www/cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank Manipulation des Arguments IpAddress mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7908|2024-08-18T17:00:05.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1783|2024-08-12T15:59:03.697Z -- totolink -- lr1200gb</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1783</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130/9.3.5u.6698_B20230810. Affected is the function loginAuth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-254574 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130/9.3.5u.6698_B20230810 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion loginAuth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente Web Interface. Dank Manipulation des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1783|2024-08-12T15:59:03.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7338|2024-08-06T20:41:31.965Z -- totolink -- ex1200l</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7338</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023. This affects the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument week/sTime/eTime leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273261 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023 gefunden. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion setParentalRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments week/sTime/eTime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7338|2024-08-06T20:41:31.965Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 03:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7333|2024-08-06T20:42:41.669Z -- totolink -- n350rt</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7333</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument week/sTime/eTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273256. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft die Funktion setParentalRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments week/sTime/eTime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7333|2024-08-06T20:42:41.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7464|2024-08-05T15:41:34.346Z -- totolink -- cp900</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7464</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK CP900 6.3c.566. This issue affects the function setTelnetCfg of the component Telnet Service. The manipulation of the argument telnet_enabled leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273557 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK CP900 6.3c.566 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion setTelnetCfg der Komponente Telnet Service. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments telnet_enabled mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7464|2024-08-05T15:41:34.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7465|2024-08-05T10:20:55.103Z -- totolink -- cp450</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7465</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK CP450 4.1.0cu.747_B20191224. Affected is the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273558 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK CP450 4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion loginauth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7465|2024-08-05T10:20:55.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7462|2024-08-05T10:19:25.079Z -- totolink -- n350rt</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7462</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. This affects the function setWizardCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ssid leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273555. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft die Funktion setWizardCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments ssid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7462|2024-08-05T10:19:25.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7463|2024-08-05T00:31:04.075Z -- totolink -- cp900</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7463</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK CP900 6.3c.566. This vulnerability affects the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument File leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273556. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK CP900 6.3c.566 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft die Funktion UploadCustomModule der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments File mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7463|2024-08-05T00:31:04.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7464|2024-08-05T01:00:06.527Z -- totolink -- cp900</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7464</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK CP900 6.3c.566. This issue affects the function setTelnetCfg of the component Telnet Service. The manipulation of the argument telnet_enabled leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273557 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK CP900 6.3c.566 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion setTelnetCfg der Komponente Telnet Service. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments telnet_enabled mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7464|2024-08-05T01:00:06.527Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7334|2024-08-02T15:41:49.498Z -- totolink -- ex1200l</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7334</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273257 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion UploadCustomModule der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7334|2024-08-02T15:41:49.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7337|2024-08-01T20:39:06.187Z -- totolink -- ex1200l</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7337</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023. Affected by this issue is the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273260. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023 entdeckt. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion loginauth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7337|2024-08-01T20:39:06.187Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 03:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1781|2024-08-01T18:48:22.142Z -- totolink -- x6000r%20ax3000</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1781</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink X6000R AX3000 9.4.0cu.852_20230719. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function setWizardCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component shttpd. The manipulation leads to command injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254573 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink X6000R AX3000 9.4.0cu.852_20230719 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion setWizardCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente shttpd. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1781|2024-08-01T18:48:22.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1783|2024-08-01T18:48:22.003Z -- totolink -- lr1200gb</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1783</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130/9.3.5u.6698_B20230810. Affected is the function loginAuth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-254574 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130/9.3.5u.6698_B20230810 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion loginAuth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente Web Interface. Dank Manipulation des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1783|2024-08-01T18:48:22.003Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7336|2024-08-01T13:30:01.939Z -- totolink -- ex200</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7336</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK EX200 4.0.3c.7646_B20201211. Affected by this vulnerability is the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273259. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK EX200 4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion loginauth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7336|2024-08-01T13:30:01.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 02:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7331|2024-08-01T13:26:04.393Z -- totolink -- a3300r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7331</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument File leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273254 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um die Funktion UploadCustomModule der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments File mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7331|2024-08-01T13:26:04.393Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7336|2024-08-01T02:31:04.790Z -- totolink -- ex200</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7336</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK EX200 4.0.3c.7646_B20201211. Affected by this vulnerability is the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273259. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK EX200 4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion loginauth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7336|2024-08-01T02:31:04.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 02:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7332|2024-08-01T00:31:04.452Z -- totolink -- cp450</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7332</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK CP450 4.1.0cu.747_B20191224. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini of the component Telnet Service. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273255. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK CP450 4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini der Komponente Telnet Service. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded password-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7332|2024-08-01T00:31:04.452Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7215|2024-07-30T18:49:27.559Z -- totolink -- lr1200</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7215</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK LR1200 9.3.1cu.2832 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function NTPSyncWithHost of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument host_time leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272786 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK LR1200 9.3.1cu.2832 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion NTPSyncWithHost der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments host_time mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7215|2024-07-30T18:49:27.559Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 03:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7216|2024-07-30T14:48:20.468Z -- totolink -- lr1200</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7216</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK LR1200 9.3.1cu.2832. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /etc/shadow.sample. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272787. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK LR1200 9.3.1cu.2832 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /etc/shadow.sample. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded password-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie ist schwierig auszunutzen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7216|2024-07-30T14:48:20.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 04:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7187|2024-07-30T14:04:11.331Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7187</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument File leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272608. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um die Funktion UploadCustomModule der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments File mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7187|2024-07-30T14:04:11.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7214|2024-07-30T14:38:29.525Z -- totolink -- lr350</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7214</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK LR350 9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setWanCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostName leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272785 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK LR350 9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um die Funktion setWanCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments hostName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7214|2024-07-30T14:38:29.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 03:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7213|2024-07-30T14:06:43.578Z -- totolink -- a7000r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7213</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK A7000R 9.1.0u.6268_B20220504. Affected is the function setWizardCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ssid leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272784. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A7000R 9.1.0u.6268_B20220504 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion setWizardCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments ssid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7213|2024-07-30T14:06:43.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 02:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7216|2024-07-30T04:00:05.592Z -- totolink -- lr1200</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7216</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK LR1200 9.3.1cu.2832. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /etc/shadow.sample. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272787. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK LR1200 9.3.1cu.2832 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /etc/shadow.sample. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded password-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie ist schwierig auszunutzen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7216|2024-07-30T04:00:05.592Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 04:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7217|2024-07-30T04:31:04.864Z -- totolink -- ca300-poe</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7217</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK CA300-PoE 6.2c.884. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument password leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272788. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK CA300-PoE 6.2c.884 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um die Funktion loginauth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7217|2024-07-30T04:31:04.864Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 04:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7213|2024-07-30T02:31:04.063Z -- totolink -- a7000r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7213</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK A7000R 9.1.0u.6268_B20220504. Affected is the function setWizardCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ssid leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272784. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A7000R 9.1.0u.6268_B20220504 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion setWizardCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments ssid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7213|2024-07-30T02:31:04.063Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 02:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7170|2024-07-29T18:13:41.104Z -- totolink -- a3000ru</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7170</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3000RU 5.9c.5185. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272591. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3000RU 5.9c.5185 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded password-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7170|2024-07-29T18:13:41.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 22:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7184|2024-07-29T18:33:30.906Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7184</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setUrlFilterRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272605 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um die Funktion setUrlFilterRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7184|2024-07-29T18:33:30.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 05:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7185|2024-07-29T16:18:55.945Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7185</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setWebWlanIdx of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument webWlanIdx leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272606 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion setWebWlanIdx der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulation des Arguments webWlanIdx mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7185|2024-07-29T16:18:55.945Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 05:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7182|2024-07-29T16:09:09.865Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7182</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. This issue affects the function setUpgradeFW of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272603. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion setUpgradeFW der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank Manipulation des Arguments FileName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7182|2024-07-29T16:09:09.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 04:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7176|2024-07-29T13:29:18.484Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7176</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function setIpQosRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument comment leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272597 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 gefunden. Dies betrifft die Funktion setIpQosRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments comment mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7176|2024-07-29T13:29:18.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 01:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7186|2024-07-29T14:00:19.552Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7186</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function setWiFiAclAddConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument comment leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272607. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um die Funktion setWiFiAclAddConfig der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments comment mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7186|2024-07-29T14:00:19.552Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7181|2024-07-29T13:27:22.498Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7181</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. This vulnerability affects the function setTelnetCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument telnet_enabled leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272602 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist die Funktion setTelnetCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments telnet_enabled mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7181|2024-07-29T13:27:22.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 03:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7157|2024-07-29T13:56:54.838Z -- totolink -- a3100r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7157</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3100R 4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function getSaveConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272571. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3100R 4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion getSaveConfig der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7157|2024-07-29T13:56:54.838Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 11:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7179|2024-07-29T13:50:07.105Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7179</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument startTime/endTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272600. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 ausgemacht. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion setParentalRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments startTime/endTime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7179|2024-07-29T13:50:07.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 02:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7160|2024-07-29T13:30:39.583Z -- totolink -- a3700r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7160</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513. Affected is the function setWanCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostName leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272574 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion setWanCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments hostName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7160|2024-07-29T13:30:39.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7173|2024-07-29T13:52:51.208Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7173</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected by this issue is the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument password/http_host leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. VDB-272594 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 entdeckt. Hierbei geht es um die Funktion loginauth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments password/http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7173|2024-07-29T13:52:51.208Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 23:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7155|2024-07-29T14:01:56.724Z -- totolink -- a3300r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7155</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /etc/shadow.sample. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272569 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /etc/shadow.sample. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded password-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal angegangen werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie gilt als schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7155|2024-07-29T14:01:56.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 10:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7172|2024-07-29T13:56:54.929Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7172</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getSaveConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272593 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Dabei geht es um die Funktion getSaveConfig der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7172|2024-07-29T13:56:54.929Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 23:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7184|2024-07-29T13:42:51.363Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7184</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setUrlFilterRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272605 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um die Funktion setUrlFilterRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7184|2024-07-29T13:42:51.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 05:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7185|2024-07-29T05:31:03.591Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7185</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setWebWlanIdx of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument webWlanIdx leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272606 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion setWebWlanIdx der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulation des Arguments webWlanIdx mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7185|2024-07-29T05:31:03.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 05:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7184|2024-07-29T05:00:07.143Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7184</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setUrlFilterRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272605 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um die Funktion setUrlFilterRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7184|2024-07-29T05:00:07.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 05:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7181|2024-07-29T03:31:04.422Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7181</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. This vulnerability affects the function setTelnetCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument telnet_enabled leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272602 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist die Funktion setTelnetCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments telnet_enabled mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7181|2024-07-29T03:31:04.422Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 03:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7182|2024-07-29T04:00:06.814Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7182</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. This issue affects the function setUpgradeFW of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272603. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion setUpgradeFW der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank Manipulation des Arguments FileName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7182|2024-07-29T04:00:06.814Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 04:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7180|2024-07-29T03:00:09.470Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7180</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. This affects the function setPortForwardRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument comment leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272601 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion setPortForwardRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments comment mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7180|2024-07-29T03:00:09.470Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 03:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7177|2024-07-29T01:31:03.907Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7177</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function setLanguageCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument langType leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272598 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 ausgemacht. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion setLanguageCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments langType mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7177|2024-07-29T01:31:03.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 01:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7170|2024-07-28T22:00:06.652Z -- totolink -- a3000ru</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7170</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3000RU 5.9c.5185. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272591. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3000RU 5.9c.5185 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded password-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7170|2024-07-28T22:00:06.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 22:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7171|2024-07-28T22:31:03.790Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7171</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected is the function NTPSyncWithHost of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostTime leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272592. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 entdeckt. Es geht dabei um die Funktion NTPSyncWithHost der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank Manipulation des Arguments hostTime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7171|2024-07-28T22:31:03.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 22:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7172|2024-07-28T23:00:08.214Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7172</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getSaveConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272593 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Dabei geht es um die Funktion getSaveConfig der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7172|2024-07-28T23:00:08.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 23:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7159|2024-07-28T14:31:06.336Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7159</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini of the component Telnet Service. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272573 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini der Komponente Telnet Service. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded password-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7159|2024-07-28T14:31:06.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 14:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7157|2024-07-28T11:00:06.342Z -- totolink -- a3100r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7157</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3100R 4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function getSaveConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272571. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3100R 4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion getSaveConfig der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7157|2024-07-28T11:00:06.342Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 11:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7156|2024-07-28T11:05:27.616Z -- totolink -- a3700r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7156</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /cgi-bin/ExportSettings.sh of the component apmib Configuration Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272570 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /cgi-bin/ExportSettings.sh der Komponente apmib Configuration Handler. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7156|2024-07-28T11:05:27.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 10:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7154|2024-07-28T09:31:04.048Z -- totolink -- a3700r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7154</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513. Affected is an unknown function of the file /wizard.html of the component Password Reset Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272568. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /wizard.html der Komponente Password Reset Handler. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper access controls-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7154|2024-07-28T09:31:04.048Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 09:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7155|2024-07-28T10:00:06.076Z -- totolink -- a3300r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7155</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /etc/shadow.sample. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272569 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /etc/shadow.sample. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded password-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal angegangen werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie gilt als schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7155|2024-07-28T10:00:06.076Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 10:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1783|2024-02-23T00:00:10.799Z -- totolink -- lr1200gb</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1783</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130/9.3.5u.6698_B20230810. Affected is the function loginAuth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-254574 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130/9.3.5u.6698_B20230810 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion loginAuth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente Web Interface. Dank Manipulation des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1783|2024-02-23T00:00:10.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1781|2024-02-23T00:00:08.886Z -- totolink -- x6000r%20ax3000</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1781</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink X6000R AX3000 9.4.0cu.852_20230719. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function setWizardCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component shttpd. The manipulation leads to command injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254573 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink X6000R AX3000 9.4.0cu.852_20230719 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion setWizardCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente shttpd. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1781|2024-02-23T00:00:08.886Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2353|2024-03-10T07:31:04.225Z -- totolink -- x6000r</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2353</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_20230719. This issue affects the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component shttpd. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256313 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_20230719 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion setDiagnosisCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente shttpd. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments ip mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2353|2024-03-10T07:31:04.225Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 07:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1781|2024-07-25T18:10:22.627Z -- totolink -- x6000r%20ax3000</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1781</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink X6000R AX3000 9.4.0cu.852_20230719. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function setWizardCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component shttpd. The manipulation leads to command injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254573 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink X6000R AX3000 9.4.0cu.852_20230719 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion setWizardCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente shttpd. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1781|2024-07-25T18:10:22.627Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7156|2024-07-28T10:31:04.509Z -- totolink -- a3700r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7156</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /cgi-bin/ExportSettings.sh of the component apmib Configuration Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272570 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /cgi-bin/ExportSettings.sh der Komponente apmib Configuration Handler. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7156|2024-07-28T10:31:04.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 10:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7158|2024-07-28T13:31:03.637Z -- totolink -- a3100r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7158</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3100R 4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setTelnetCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument telnet_enabled leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272572. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3100R 4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist die Funktion setTelnetCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments telnet_enabled mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7158|2024-07-28T13:31:03.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 13:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7160|2024-07-28T15:00:07.203Z -- totolink -- a3700r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7160</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513. Affected is the function setWanCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostName leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272574 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion setWanCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments hostName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7160|2024-07-28T15:00:07.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7175|2024-07-29T00:31:04.158Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7175</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ipDoamin leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272596. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Das betrifft die Funktion setDiagnosisCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments ipDoamin mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7175|2024-07-29T00:31:04.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7176|2024-07-29T01:01:19.532Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7176</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function setIpQosRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument comment leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272597 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 gefunden. Dies betrifft die Funktion setIpQosRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments comment mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7176|2024-07-29T01:01:19.532Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 01:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7179|2024-07-29T02:31:03.995Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7179</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument startTime/endTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272600. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 ausgemacht. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion setParentalRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments startTime/endTime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7179|2024-07-29T02:31:03.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 02:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7178|2024-07-29T02:00:08.334Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7178</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setMacQos of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument priority/macAddress leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272599. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion setMacQos der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments priority/macAddress mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7178|2024-07-29T02:00:08.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 02:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7183|2024-07-29T04:31:04.254Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7183</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected is the function setUploadSetting of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272604. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion setUploadSetting der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments FileName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7183|2024-07-29T04:31:04.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 04:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7187|2024-07-29T06:31:04.399Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7187</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument File leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272608. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um die Funktion UploadCustomModule der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments File mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7187|2024-07-29T06:31:04.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7186|2024-07-29T06:00:09.895Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7186</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function setWiFiAclAddConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument comment leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272607. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um die Funktion setWiFiAclAddConfig der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments comment mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7186|2024-07-29T06:00:09.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7183|2024-07-29T14:04:48.555Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7183</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected is the function setUploadSetting of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272604. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion setUploadSetting der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments FileName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7183|2024-07-29T14:04:48.555Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 04:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7177|2024-07-29T14:07:34.983Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7177</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function setLanguageCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument langType leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272598 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 ausgemacht. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion setLanguageCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments langType mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7177|2024-07-29T14:07:34.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 01:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7171|2024-07-29T17:13:30.842Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7171</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected is the function NTPSyncWithHost of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostTime leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272592. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 entdeckt. Es geht dabei um die Funktion NTPSyncWithHost der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank Manipulation des Arguments hostTime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7171|2024-07-29T17:13:30.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 22:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7154|2024-07-29T17:02:59.182Z -- totolink -- a3700r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7154</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513. Affected is an unknown function of the file /wizard.html of the component Password Reset Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272568. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /wizard.html der Komponente Password Reset Handler. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper access controls-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7154|2024-07-29T17:02:59.182Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 09:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7158|2024-07-29T17:27:15.923Z -- totolink -- a3100r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7158</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3100R 4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setTelnetCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument telnet_enabled leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272572. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3100R 4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist die Funktion setTelnetCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments telnet_enabled mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7158|2024-07-29T17:27:15.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 13:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7178|2024-07-29T17:03:38.011Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7178</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setMacQos of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument priority/macAddress leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272599. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion setMacQos der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments priority/macAddress mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7178|2024-07-29T17:03:38.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 02:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7174|2024-07-29T17:00:51.628Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7174</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. This affects the function setdeviceName of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument deviceMac/deviceName leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272595. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 gefunden. Es betrifft die Funktion setdeviceName der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulation des Arguments deviceMac/deviceName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7174|2024-07-29T17:00:51.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7159|2024-07-29T17:06:47.984Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7159</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini of the component Telnet Service. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272573 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini der Komponente Telnet Service. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded password-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7159|2024-07-29T17:06:47.984Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 14:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7180|2024-07-29T20:56:03.641Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7180</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. This affects the function setPortForwardRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument comment leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272601 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion setPortForwardRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments comment mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7180|2024-07-29T20:56:03.641Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 03:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7175|2024-07-29T20:56:35.684Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7175</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ipDoamin leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272596. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Das betrifft die Funktion setDiagnosisCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments ipDoamin mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7175|2024-07-29T20:56:35.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7212|2024-07-30T01:31:04.510Z -- totolink -- a7000r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7212</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A7000R 9.1.0u.6268_B20220504. This issue affects the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument password leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272783. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A7000R 9.1.0u.6268_B20220504 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion loginauth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7212|2024-07-30T01:31:04.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 01:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7214|2024-07-30T03:00:08.298Z -- totolink -- lr350</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7214</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK LR350 9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setWanCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostName leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272785 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK LR350 9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um die Funktion setWanCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments hostName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7214|2024-07-30T03:00:08.298Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 03:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7215|2024-07-30T03:31:03.942Z -- totolink -- lr1200</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7215</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK LR1200 9.3.1cu.2832 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function NTPSyncWithHost of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument host_time leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272786 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK LR1200 9.3.1cu.2832 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion NTPSyncWithHost der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments host_time mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7215|2024-07-30T03:31:03.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 03:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7217|2024-07-30T13:13:01.840Z -- totolink -- ca300-poe</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7217</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK CA300-PoE 6.2c.884. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument password leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272788. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK CA300-PoE 6.2c.884 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um die Funktion loginauth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7217|2024-07-30T13:13:01.840Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 04:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7212|2024-07-30T17:21:16.329Z -- totolink -- a7000r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7212</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A7000R 9.1.0u.6268_B20220504. This issue affects the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument password leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272783. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A7000R 9.1.0u.6268_B20220504 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion loginauth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7212|2024-07-30T17:21:16.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 01:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7214|2024-07-31T17:35:01.503Z -- totolink -- lr350</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7214</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK LR350 9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setWanCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostName leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272785 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK LR350 9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um die Funktion setWanCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments hostName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7214|2024-07-31T17:35:01.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 03:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7335|2024-08-01T02:00:06.560Z -- totolink -- ex200</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7335</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK EX200 4.0.3c.7646_B20201211. Affected is the function getSaveConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273258 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK EX200 4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 entdeckt. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion getSaveConfig der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7335|2024-08-01T02:00:06.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 02:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7334|2024-08-01T01:31:04.816Z -- totolink -- ex1200l</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7334</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273257 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion UploadCustomModule der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7334|2024-08-01T01:31:04.816Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7333|2024-08-01T01:00:07.454Z -- totolink -- n350rt</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7333</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument week/sTime/eTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273256. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft die Funktion setParentalRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments week/sTime/eTime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7333|2024-08-01T01:00:07.454Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7337|2024-08-01T03:00:06.098Z -- totolink -- ex1200l</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7337</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023. Affected by this issue is the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273260. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023 entdeckt. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion loginauth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7337|2024-08-01T03:00:06.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 03:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7338|2024-08-01T03:31:04.032Z -- totolink -- ex1200l</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7338</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023. This affects the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument week/sTime/eTime leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273261 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023 gefunden. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion setParentalRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments week/sTime/eTime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7338|2024-08-01T03:31:04.032Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 03:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7331|2024-08-01T14:18:14.922Z -- totolink -- a3300r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7331</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument File leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273254 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um die Funktion UploadCustomModule der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments File mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7331|2024-08-01T14:18:14.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7337|2024-08-01T19:17:42.177Z -- totolink -- ex1200l</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7337</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023. Affected by this issue is the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273260. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023 entdeckt. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion loginauth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7337|2024-08-01T19:17:42.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 03:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2353|2024-08-01T19:11:53.347Z -- totolink -- x6000r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2353</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_20230719. This issue affects the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component shttpd. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256313 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_20230719 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion setDiagnosisCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente shttpd. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments ip mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2353|2024-08-01T19:11:53.347Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 07:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7217|2024-08-01T21:52:31.497Z -- totolink -- ca300-poe</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7217</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK CA300-PoE 6.2c.884. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument password leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272788. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK CA300-PoE 6.2c.884 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um die Funktion loginauth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7217|2024-08-01T21:52:31.497Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 04:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7180|2024-08-01T21:52:30.827Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7180</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. This affects the function setPortForwardRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument comment leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272601 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion setPortForwardRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments comment mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7180|2024-08-01T21:52:30.827Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 03:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7184|2024-08-01T21:52:30.703Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7184</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setUrlFilterRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272605 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um die Funktion setUrlFilterRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7184|2024-08-01T21:52:30.703Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 05:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7172|2024-08-01T21:52:31.007Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7172</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getSaveConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272593 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Dabei geht es um die Funktion getSaveConfig der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7172|2024-08-01T21:52:31.007Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 23:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7213|2024-08-01T21:52:31.549Z -- totolink -- a7000r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7213</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK A7000R 9.1.0u.6268_B20220504. Affected is the function setWizardCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ssid leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272784. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A7000R 9.1.0u.6268_B20220504 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion setWizardCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments ssid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7213|2024-08-01T21:52:31.549Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 02:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7155|2024-08-01T21:52:30.711Z -- totolink -- a3300r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7155</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /etc/shadow.sample. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272569 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /etc/shadow.sample. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded password-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal angegangen werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie gilt als schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7155|2024-08-01T21:52:30.711Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 10:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7173|2024-08-01T21:52:31.013Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7173</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected by this issue is the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument password/http_host leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. VDB-272594 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 entdeckt. Hierbei geht es um die Funktion loginauth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments password/http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7173|2024-08-01T21:52:31.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 23:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7182|2024-08-01T21:52:30.845Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7182</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. This issue affects the function setUpgradeFW of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272603. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion setUpgradeFW der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank Manipulation des Arguments FileName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7182|2024-08-01T21:52:30.845Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 04:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7185|2024-08-01T21:52:30.652Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7185</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setWebWlanIdx of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument webWlanIdx leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272606 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion setWebWlanIdx der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulation des Arguments webWlanIdx mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7185|2024-08-01T21:52:30.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 05:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7212|2024-08-01T21:52:31.058Z -- totolink -- a7000r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7212</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A7000R 9.1.0u.6268_B20220504. This issue affects the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument password leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272783. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A7000R 9.1.0u.6268_B20220504 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion loginauth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7212|2024-08-01T21:52:31.058Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 01:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7183|2024-08-01T21:52:30.859Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7183</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected is the function setUploadSetting of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272604. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion setUploadSetting der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments FileName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7183|2024-08-01T21:52:30.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 04:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7156|2024-08-01T21:52:30.916Z -- totolink -- a3700r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7156</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /cgi-bin/ExportSettings.sh of the component apmib Configuration Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272570 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /cgi-bin/ExportSettings.sh der Komponente apmib Configuration Handler. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7156|2024-08-01T21:52:30.916Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 10:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7171|2024-08-01T21:52:31.099Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7171</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. Affected is the function NTPSyncWithHost of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostTime leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272592. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 entdeckt. Es geht dabei um die Funktion NTPSyncWithHost der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank Manipulation des Arguments hostTime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7171|2024-08-01T21:52:31.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 22:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7214|2024-08-01T21:52:31.506Z -- totolink -- lr350</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7214</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK LR350 9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setWanCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostName leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272785 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK LR350 9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um die Funktion setWanCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments hostName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7214|2024-08-01T21:52:31.506Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 03:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7215|2024-08-01T21:52:31.460Z -- totolink -- lr1200</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7215</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK LR1200 9.3.1cu.2832 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function NTPSyncWithHost of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument host_time leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272786 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK LR1200 9.3.1cu.2832 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion NTPSyncWithHost der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments host_time mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7215|2024-08-01T21:52:31.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 03:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7154|2024-08-01T21:52:30.686Z -- totolink -- a3700r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7154</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513. Affected is an unknown function of the file /wizard.html of the component Password Reset Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272568. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /wizard.html der Komponente Password Reset Handler. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper access controls-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7154|2024-08-01T21:52:30.686Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 09:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7158|2024-08-01T21:52:30.601Z -- totolink -- a3100r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7158</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3100R 4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setTelnetCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument telnet_enabled leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272572. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3100R 4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist die Funktion setTelnetCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments telnet_enabled mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7158|2024-08-01T21:52:30.601Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 13:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7160|2024-08-01T21:52:30.737Z -- totolink -- a3700r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7160</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513. Affected is the function setWanCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostName leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272574 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3700R 9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion setWanCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments hostName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7160|2024-08-01T21:52:30.737Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7179|2024-08-01T21:52:30.671Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7179</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument startTime/endTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272600. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 ausgemacht. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion setParentalRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments startTime/endTime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7179|2024-08-01T21:52:30.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 02:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7157|2024-08-01T21:52:30.570Z -- totolink -- a3100r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7157</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3100R 4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function getSaveConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272571. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3100R 4.1.2cu.5050_B20200504 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion getSaveConfig der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7157|2024-08-01T21:52:30.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 11:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7181|2024-08-01T21:52:30.842Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7181</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. This vulnerability affects the function setTelnetCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument telnet_enabled leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272602 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist die Funktion setTelnetCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments telnet_enabled mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7181|2024-08-01T21:52:30.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 03:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7187|2024-08-01T21:52:30.831Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7187</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument File leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272608. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um die Funktion UploadCustomModule der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments File mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7187|2024-08-01T21:52:30.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7178|2024-08-01T21:52:30.721Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7178</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setMacQos of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument priority/macAddress leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272599. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion setMacQos der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments priority/macAddress mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7178|2024-08-01T21:52:30.721Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 02:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7170|2024-08-01T21:52:30.503Z -- totolink -- a3000ru</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7170</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3000RU 5.9c.5185. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272591. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3000RU 5.9c.5185 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded password-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7170|2024-08-01T21:52:30.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 22:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7174|2024-08-01T21:52:30.807Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7174</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. This affects the function setdeviceName of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument deviceMac/deviceName leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272595. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 gefunden. Es betrifft die Funktion setdeviceName der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulation des Arguments deviceMac/deviceName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7174|2024-08-01T21:52:30.807Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7175|2024-08-01T21:52:30.999Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7175</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ipDoamin leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272596. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Das betrifft die Funktion setDiagnosisCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments ipDoamin mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7175|2024-08-01T21:52:30.999Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7159|2024-08-01T21:52:30.682Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7159</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini of the component Telnet Service. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272573 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini der Komponente Telnet Service. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded password-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7159|2024-08-01T21:52:30.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 14:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7216|2024-08-01T21:52:31.490Z -- totolink -- lr1200</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7216</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK LR1200 9.3.1cu.2832. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /etc/shadow.sample. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272787. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK LR1200 9.3.1cu.2832 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /etc/shadow.sample. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded password-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie ist schwierig auszunutzen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7216|2024-08-01T21:52:31.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 04:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7186|2024-08-01T21:52:30.969Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7186</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function setWiFiAclAddConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument comment leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272607. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um die Funktion setWiFiAclAddConfig der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments comment mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7186|2024-08-01T21:52:30.969Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7176|2024-08-01T21:52:30.812Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7176</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function setIpQosRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument comment leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272597 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 gefunden. Dies betrifft die Funktion setIpQosRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments comment mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7176|2024-08-01T21:52:30.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 01:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7177|2024-08-01T21:52:31.116Z -- totolink -- a3600r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7177</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function setLanguageCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument langType leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272598 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK A3600R 4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102 ausgemacht. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion setLanguageCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments langType mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7177|2024-08-01T21:52:31.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 01:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7465|2024-08-05T01:31:04.318Z -- totolink -- cp450</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7465</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK CP450 4.1.0cu.747_B20191224. Affected is the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273558 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK CP450 4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion loginauth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7465|2024-08-05T01:31:04.318Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7463|2024-08-05T13:55:20.896Z -- totolink -- cp900</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7463</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK CP900 6.3c.566. This vulnerability affects the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument File leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273556. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK CP900 6.3c.566 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft die Funktion UploadCustomModule der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments File mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7463|2024-08-05T13:55:20.896Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7332|2024-08-06T19:35:53.846Z -- totolink -- cp450</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7332</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK CP450 4.1.0cu.747_B20191224. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini of the component Telnet Service. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273255. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK CP450 4.1.0cu.747_B20191224 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini der Komponente Telnet Service. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded password-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7332|2024-08-06T19:35:53.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7335|2024-08-06T19:39:28.167Z -- totolink -- ex200</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7335</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK EX200 4.0.3c.7646_B20201211. Affected is the function getSaveConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273258 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in TOTOLINK EX200 4.0.3c.7646_B20201211 entdeckt. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion getSaveConfig der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7335|2024-08-06T19:39:28.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 02:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2353|2024-08-12T13:49:53.588Z -- totolink -- x6000r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2353</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_20230719. This issue affects the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component shttpd. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256313 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_20230719 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion setDiagnosisCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente shttpd. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments ip mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2353|2024-08-12T13:49:53.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 07:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7907|2024-08-18T16:00:05.668Z -- totolink -- x6000r</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7907</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_20230719. This issue affects the function setSyslogCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument rtLogServer leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in TOTOLINK X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_20230719 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion setSyslogCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments rtLogServer mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7907|2024-08-18T16:00:05.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
