<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Totolink -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/totolink/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Totolink -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1002|2024-01-29T14:00:06.271Z -- Totolink -- N200RE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1002</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setIpPortFilterRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ePort leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252271. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Das betrifft die Funktion setIpPortFilterRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments ePort mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1002|2024-01-29T14:00:06.271Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1003|2024-01-29T14:31:03.812Z -- Totolink -- N200RE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1003</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. Affected by this issue is the function setLanguageCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument lang leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252272. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 entdeckt. Dies betrifft die Funktion setLanguageCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments lang mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1003|2024-01-29T14:31:03.812Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1783|2024-02-23T00:00:10.799Z -- Totolink -- LR1200GB
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1783</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130/9.3.5u.6698_B20230810. Affected is the function loginAuth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-254574 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130/9.3.5u.6698_B20230810 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion loginAuth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente Web Interface. Dank Manipulation des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1783|2024-02-23T00:00:10.799Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1004|2024-01-29T15:00:07.267Z -- Totolink -- N200RE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1004</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. This affects the function loginAuth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252273 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 gefunden. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion loginAuth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1004|2024-01-29T15:00:07.267Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1661|2024-02-21T11:51:10.953Z -- Totolink -- X6000R
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1661</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_B20230719. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /etc/shadow. The manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254179. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /etc/shadow. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine hard-coded credentials-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal angegangen werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie gilt als schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1661|2024-02-21T11:51:10.953Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 12:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1000|2024-01-29T13:31:03.916Z -- Totolink -- N200RE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1000</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function setTracerouteCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument command leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252269 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um die Funktion setTracerouteCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments command mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1000|2024-01-29T13:31:03.916Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1781|2024-02-23T00:00:08.886Z -- Totolink -- X6000R AX3000
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1781</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink X6000R AX3000 9.4.0cu.852_20230719. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function setWizardCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component shttpd. The manipulation leads to command injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254573 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink X6000R AX3000 9.4.0cu.852_20230719 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion setWizardCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente shttpd. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1781|2024-02-23T00:00:08.886Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1001|2024-01-29T13:31:04.977Z -- Totolink -- N200RE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1001</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. Affected is the function main of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252270 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 entdeckt. Es betrifft die Funktion main der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1001|2024-01-29T13:31:04.977Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0296|2024-02-09T19:05:55.645Z -- Totolink -- N200RE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0296</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function NTPSyncWithHost of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument host_time leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249862 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Betroffen ist die Funktion NTPSyncWithHost der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments host_time mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0296|2024-02-09T19:05:55.645Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 04:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0577|2024-02-09T19:12:02.462Z -- Totolink -- LR1200GB
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0577</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function setLanguageCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument lang leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250793 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion setLanguageCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulation des Arguments lang mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0577|2024-02-09T19:12:02.462Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0998|2024-01-29T13:00:07.339Z -- Totolink -- N200RE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0998</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252267. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um die Funktion setDiagnosisCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulation des Arguments ip mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0998|2024-01-29T13:00:07.339Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0999|2024-01-29T13:00:08.732Z -- Totolink -- N200RE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0999</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument eTime leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252268. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um die Funktion setParentalRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments eTime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0999|2024-01-29T13:00:08.732Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0576|2024-02-09T19:12:01.212Z -- Totolink -- LR1200GB
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0576</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setIpPortFilterRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument sPort leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250792. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist die Funktion setIpPortFilterRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments sPort mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0576|2024-02-09T19:12:01.212Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 15:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0297|2024-02-09T19:05:56.821Z -- Totolink -- N200RE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0297</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function UploadFirmwareFile of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249863. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 gefunden. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion UploadFirmwareFile der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments FileName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0297|2024-02-09T19:05:56.821Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 04:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0571|2024-02-09T19:11:51.057Z -- Totolink -- LR1200GB
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0571</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. This issue affects the function setSmsCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument text leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250787. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion setSmsCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments text mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0571|2024-02-09T19:11:51.057Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 13:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0291|2024-02-09T19:05:15.916Z -- Totolink -- LR1200GB
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0291</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function UploadFirmwareFile of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249857 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion UploadFirmwareFile der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments FileName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0291|2024-02-09T19:05:15.916Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 01:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0570|2024-04-01T06:44:19.939Z -- Totolink -- N350RT
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0570</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6265. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-250786 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6265 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente Setting Handler. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper access controls-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0570|2024-04-01T06:44:19.939Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 13:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0573|2024-02-09T19:11:49.784Z -- Totolink -- LR1200GB
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0573</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250789 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion setDiagnosisCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments ip mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0573|2024-02-09T19:11:49.784Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 14:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0569|2024-04-01T06:43:53.841Z -- Totolink -- T8
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0569</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Totolink T8 4.1.5cu.833_20220905. This affects the function getSysStatusCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation of the argument ssid/key leads to information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.1.5cu.862_B20230228 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-250785 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Totolink T8 4.1.5cu.833_20220905 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es betrifft die Funktion getSysStatusCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente Setting Handler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments ssid/key mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 4.1.5cu.862_B20230228 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0569|2024-04-01T06:43:53.841Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 12:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0292|2024-02-09T19:05:14.701Z -- Totolink -- LR1200GB
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0292</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. Affected is the function setOpModeCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostName leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249858 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 entdeckt. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion setOpModeCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Manipulation des Arguments hostName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0292|2024-02-09T19:05:14.701Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0944|2024-04-01T06:45:04.575Z -- Totolink -- T8
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0944</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink T8 4.1.5cu.833_20220905. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation leads to session expiration. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252188. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink T8 4.1.5cu.833_20220905 ausgemacht. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine session expiration-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie ist schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0944|2024-04-01T06:45:04.575Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0293|2024-02-09T19:05:18.383Z -- Totolink -- LR1200GB
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0293</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setUploadSetting of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249859. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion setUploadSetting der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments FileName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0293|2024-02-09T19:05:18.383Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 02:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0572|2024-02-09T19:11:53.478Z -- Totolink -- LR1200GB
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0572</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. Affected is the function setOpModeCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument pppoeUser leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250788. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion setOpModeCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments pppoeUser mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0572|2024-02-09T19:11:53.478Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 14:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0579|2024-02-09T19:12:03.729Z -- Totolink -- X2000R
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0579</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Totolink X2000R 1.0.0-B20221212.1452. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formMapDelDevice of the file /boafrm/formMapDelDevice. The manipulation of the argument macstr leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250795. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Totolink X2000R 1.0.0-B20221212.1452 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Es geht um die Funktion formMapDelDevice der Datei /boafrm/formMapDelDevice. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments macstr mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0579|2024-02-09T19:12:03.729Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 16:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0294|2024-02-09T19:05:17.127Z -- Totolink -- LR1200GB
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0294</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. Affected by this issue is the function setUssd of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ussd leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249860. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 entdeckt. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion setUssd der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments ussd mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0294|2024-02-09T19:05:17.127Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0943|2024-04-01T06:44:49.986Z -- Totolink -- N350RT
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0943</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6255. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation leads to session expiration. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252187. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6255 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine session expiration-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie gilt als schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0943|2024-04-01T06:44:49.986Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0575|2024-02-09T19:11:59.986Z -- Totolink -- LR1200GB
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0575</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function setTracerouteCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument command leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250791. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion setTracerouteCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments command mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0575|2024-02-09T19:11:59.986Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0298|2024-02-09T19:05:58.020Z -- Totolink -- N200RE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0298</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249864. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 ausgemacht. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion setDiagnosisCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments ip mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0298|2024-02-09T19:05:58.020Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 05:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0299|2024-02-09T19:05:59.213Z -- Totolink -- N200RE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0299</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setTracerouteCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument command leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249865 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Es geht um die Funktion setTracerouteCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments command mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0299|2024-02-09T19:05:59.213Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 05:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0574|2024-02-09T19:11:54.703Z -- Totolink -- LR1200GB
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0574</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument sTime leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250790 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion setParentalRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank Manipulation des Arguments sTime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0574|2024-02-09T19:11:54.703Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 15:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0942|2024-04-01T06:44:33.095Z -- Totolink -- N200RE V5
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0942</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE V5 9.3.5u.6255_B20211224. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation leads to session expiration. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252186 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Totolink N200RE V5 9.3.5u.6255_B20211224 ausgemacht. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine session expiration-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie gilt als schwierig auszunutzen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0942|2024-04-01T06:44:33.095Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 19:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0295|2024-02-09T19:05:54.464Z -- Totolink -- LR1200GB
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0295</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. This affects the function setWanCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostName leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249861 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 gefunden. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion setWanCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments hostName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0295|2024-02-09T19:05:54.464Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 03:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0578|2024-02-09T19:12:18.126Z -- Totolink -- LR1200GB
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0578</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. Affected is the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument File leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250794 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion UploadCustomModule der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments File mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0578|2024-02-09T19:12:18.126Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 16:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0997|2024-01-29T12:31:03.782Z -- Totolink -- N200RE
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0997</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setOpModeCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument pppoeUser leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252266 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion setOpModeCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments pppoeUser mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0997|2024-01-29T12:31:03.782Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 12:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2353|2024-03-10T07:31:04.225Z -- Totolink -- X6000R
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2353</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_20230719. This issue affects the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component shttpd. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256313 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_20230719 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion setDiagnosisCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente shttpd. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments ip mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2353|2024-03-10T07:31:04.225Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 07:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>