<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Totolink -- N350RT</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/totolink/n350rt.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Totolink -- N350RT</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:24:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7214|2024-08-02T08:57:35.818Z -- totolink -- n350rt
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7214</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. Affected by this issue is the function main of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=login of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument v8 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249770 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 entdeckt. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion main der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=login der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch Manipulation des Arguments v8 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7214|2024-08-02T08:57:35.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7213|2024-08-02T08:57:35.625Z -- totolink -- n350rt
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7213</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. Affected by this vulnerability is the function main of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=login&amp;flag=1 of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument v33 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249769 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion main der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=login&amp;flag=1 der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments v33 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7213|2024-08-02T08:57:35.625Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 19:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7219|2024-08-02T08:57:35.094Z -- totolink -- n350rt
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7219</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B202012 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function loginAuth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249853 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B202012 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um die Funktion loginAuth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments http_host mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7219|2024-08-02T08:57:35.094Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 06:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7187|2024-08-02T08:57:34.113Z -- totolink -- n350rt
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7187</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=login&amp;flag=ie8 of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249389 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=login&amp;flag=ie8 der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7187|2024-08-02T08:57:34.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7218|2024-08-02T08:57:34.973Z -- totolink -- n350rt
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7218</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B202012. Affected is the function loginAuth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument password leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249852. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B202012 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um die Funktion loginAuth der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7218|2024-08-02T08:57:34.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 21:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7333|2024-08-01T01:00:07.454Z -- totolink -- n350rt</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7333</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument week/sTime/eTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273256. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In TOTOLINK N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft die Funktion setParentalRules der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments week/sTime/eTime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7333|2024-08-01T01:00:07.454Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
