<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Totolink -- T6</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/totolink/t6.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Totolink -- T6</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:23:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7223|2024-08-02T08:57:35.016Z -- totolink -- t6
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7223</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Totolink T6 4.1.9cu.5241_B20210923. This affects an unknown part of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument topicurl with the input showSyslog leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249867. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Totolink T6 4.1.9cu.5241_B20210923 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments topicurl mit der Eingabe showSyslog mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper access controls-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7223|2024-08-02T08:57:35.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7221|2024-08-02T08:57:35.031Z -- totolink -- t6
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7221</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink T6 4.1.9cu.5241_B20210923. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function main of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=login of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument v41 leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249855. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Totolink T6 4.1.9cu.5241_B20210923 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft die Funktion main der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=login der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Dank Manipulation des Arguments v41 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7221|2024-08-02T08:57:35.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 14:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
