<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Totolink -- X6000R</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/totolink/x6000r.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Totolink -- X6000R</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1661|2024-02-21T11:51:10.953Z -- Totolink -- X6000R
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1661</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_B20230719. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /etc/shadow. The manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254179. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /etc/shadow. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine hard-coded credentials-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal angegangen werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie gilt als schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1661|2024-02-21T11:51:10.953Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 12:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2353|2024-03-10T07:31:04.225Z -- Totolink -- X6000R
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2353</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_20230719. This issue affects the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi of the component shttpd. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256313 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Totolink X6000R 9.4.0cu.852_20230719 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion setDiagnosisCfg der Datei /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi der Komponente shttpd. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments ip mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2353|2024-03-10T07:31:04.225Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 07:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>