<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Fidelis Cybersecurity -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/fidelis%20cybersecurity/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Fidelis Cybersecurity -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:22:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-0997|2024-09-17T01:51:19.514Z -- fidelis%20cybersecurity -- fidelis%20network
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-0997</link>
      <description>Improper file permissions in the CommandPost, Collector, and Sensor components of Fidelis Network and Deception enables an attacker with local, administrative access to the CLI to modify affected script files, which could result in arbitrary commands being run as root upon subsequent logon by a root user. The vulnerability is present in Fidelis Network and Deception versions prior to 9.4.5. Patches and updates are available to address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-0997|2024-09-17T01:51:19.514Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 19:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35048|2024-09-17T02:46:55.900Z -- fidelis%20cybersecurity -- fidelis%20network
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35048</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in Fidelis Network and Deception CommandPost enables unauthenticated SQL injection through the web interface. The vulnerability could lead to exposure of authentication tokens in some versions of Fidelis software. The vulnerability is present in Fidelis Network and Deception versions prior to 9.3.7 and in version 9.4. Patches and updates are available to address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35048|2024-09-17T02:46:55.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 11:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24394|2024-09-17T03:59:09.816Z -- fidelis%20cybersecurity -- fidelis%20network
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24394</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in Fidelis Network and Deception CommandPost enables authenticated command injection through the web interface using the “update_checkfile” value for the “filename” parameter. The vulnerability could allow a specially crafted HTTP request to execute system commands on the CommandPost and return results in an HTTP response via an authenticated session. The vulnerability is present in Fidelis Network and Deception versions prior to 9.4.5. Patches and updates are available to address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24394|2024-09-17T03:59:09.816Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 19:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
