<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Fidelis Cybersecurity -- Fidelis Network</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/fidelis%20cybersecurity/fidelis%20network.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Fidelis Cybersecurity -- Fidelis Network</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 16:24:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35047|2024-08-04T00:33:50.508Z -- fidelis%20cybersecurity -- fidelis%20network
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35047</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the CommandPost, Collector, and Sensor components of Fidelis Network and Deception enables an attacker with user level access to the CLI to inject root level commands into the component and neighboring Fidelis components. The vulnerability is present in Fidelis Network and Deception versions prior to 9.3.7 and in version 9.4. Patches and updates are available to address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35047|2024-08-04T00:33:50.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35048|2024-08-04T00:33:50.936Z -- fidelis%20cybersecurity -- fidelis%20network
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35048</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in Fidelis Network and Deception CommandPost enables unauthenticated SQL injection through the web interface. The vulnerability could lead to exposure of authentication tokens in some versions of Fidelis software. The vulnerability is present in Fidelis Network and Deception versions prior to 9.3.7 and in version 9.4. Patches and updates are available to address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35048|2024-08-04T00:33:50.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35050|2024-08-04T00:33:50.675Z -- fidelis%20cybersecurity -- fidelis%20network
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35050</link>
      <description>User credentials stored in a recoverable format within Fidelis Network and Deception CommandPost. In the event that an attacker gains access to the CommandPost, these values could be decoded and used to login to the application. The vulnerability is present in Fidelis Network and Deception versions prior to 9.3.3. This vulnerability has been addressed in version 9.3.3 and subsequent versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35050|2024-08-04T00:33:50.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35049|2024-08-04T00:33:50.630Z -- fidelis%20cybersecurity -- fidelis%20network
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35049</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in Fidelis Network and Deception CommandPost enables authenticated command injection through the web interface. The vulnerability could allow a specially crafted HTTP request to execute system commands on the CommandPost and return results in an HTTP response in an authenticated session. The vulnerability is present in Fidelis Network and Deception versions prior to 9.3.7 and in version 9.4. Patches and updates are available to address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35049|2024-08-04T00:33:50.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
