<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Fidelis Cybersecurity -- Fidelis Network</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/fidelis%20cybersecurity/fidelis%20network.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Fidelis Cybersecurity -- Fidelis Network</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24391|2024-08-03T04:07:02.528Z -- fidelis%20cybersecurity -- fidelis%20network
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24391</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in Fidelis Network and Deception CommandPost enables SQL injection through the web interface by an attacker with user level access. The vulnerability is present in Fidelis Network and Deception versions prior to 9.4.5. Patches and updates are available to address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24391|2024-08-03T04:07:02.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24393|2024-08-03T04:07:02.426Z -- fidelis%20cybersecurity -- fidelis%20network
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24393</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in Fidelis Network and Deception CommandPost enables authenticated command injection through the web interface using the “check_vertica_upgrade” value for the “cpIp” parameter. The vulnerability could allow a specially crafted HTTP request to execute system commands on the CommandPost and return results in an HTTP response via an authenticated session. The vulnerability is present in Fidelis Network and Deception versions prior to 9.4.5. Patches and updates are available to address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24393|2024-08-03T04:07:02.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24394|2024-08-03T04:07:02.537Z -- fidelis%20cybersecurity -- fidelis%20network
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24394</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in Fidelis Network and Deception CommandPost enables authenticated command injection through the web interface using the “update_checkfile” value for the “filename” parameter. The vulnerability could allow a specially crafted HTTP request to execute system commands on the CommandPost and return results in an HTTP response via an authenticated session. The vulnerability is present in Fidelis Network and Deception versions prior to 9.4.5. Patches and updates are available to address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24394|2024-08-03T04:07:02.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24390|2024-08-03T04:07:02.633Z -- fidelis%20cybersecurity -- fidelis%20network
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24390</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in rconfig “remote_text_file” enables an attacker with user level access to the CLI to inject user level commands into Fidelis Network and Deception CommandPost, Collector, Sensor, and Sandbox components as well as neighboring Fidelis components. The vulnerability is present in Fidelis Network and Deception versions prior to 9.4.5. Patches and updates are available to address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24390|2024-08-03T04:07:02.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24392|2024-08-03T04:07:02.600Z -- fidelis%20cybersecurity -- fidelis%20network
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24392</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in Fidelis Network and Deception CommandPost enables authenticated command injection through the web interface using the “feed_comm_test” value for the “feed” parameter. The vulnerability could allow a specially crafted HTTP request to execute system commands on the CommandPost and return results in an HTTP response via an authenticated session. The vulnerability is present in Fidelis Network and Deception versions prior to 9.4.5. Patches and updates are available to address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24392|2024-08-03T04:07:02.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24388|2024-08-03T04:07:02.557Z -- fidelis%20cybersecurity -- fidelis%20network
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24388</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in rconfig “date” enables an attacker with user level access to the CLI to inject root level commands into Fidelis Network and Deception CommandPost, Collector, Sensor, and Sandbox components as well as neighboring Fidelis components. The vulnerability is present in Fidelis Network and Deception versions prior to 9.4.5. Patches and updates are available to address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24388|2024-08-03T04:07:02.557Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24389|2024-08-03T04:07:02.463Z -- fidelis%20cybersecurity -- fidelis%20network
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24389</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in rconfig “cert_utils” enables an attacker with user level access to the CLI to inject root level commands into Fidelis Network and Deception CommandPost, Collector, Sensor, and Sandbox components as well as neighboring Fidelis components. The vulnerability is present in Fidelis Network and Deception versions prior to 9.4.5. Patches and updates are available to address this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24389|2024-08-03T04:07:02.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
