<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT5583, MT5586, MT5691, MT5695, MT5696, MT9010, MT9011, MT9012, MT9015, MT9016, MT9020, MT9021, MT9022, MT9025, MT9026, MT9216, MT9218, MT9220, MT9221, MT9222, MT9255, MT9256, MT9266, MT9269, MT9286, MT9288, MT9602, MT9603, MT9610, MT9611, MT9612, MT9613, MT9615, MT9617, MT9618, MT9629, MT9630, MT9631, MT9632, MT9633, MT9636, MT9638, MT9639, MT9649, MT9650, MT9652, MT9653, MT9660, MT9666, MT9667, MT9669, MT9671, MT9675, MT9679, MT9685, MT9686, MT9688, MT9689</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mediatek%2C%20inc./mt5583%2C%20mt5586%2C%20mt5691%2C%20mt5695%2C%20mt5696%2C%20mt9010%2C%20mt9011%2C%20mt9012%2C%20mt9015%2C%20mt9016%2C%20mt9020%2C%20mt9021%2C%20mt9022%2C%20mt9025%2C%20mt9026%2C%20mt9216%2C%20mt9218%2C%20mt9220%2C%20mt9221%2C%20mt9222%2C%20mt9255%2C%20mt9256%2C%20mt9266%2C%20mt9269%2C%20mt9286%2C%20mt9288%2C%20mt9602%2C%20mt9603%2C%20mt9610%2C%20mt9611%2C%20mt9612%2C%20mt9613%2C%20mt9615%2C%20mt9617%2C%20mt9618%2C%20mt9629%2C%20mt9630%2C%20mt9631%2C%20mt9632%2C%20mt9633%2C%20mt9636%2C%20mt9638%2C%20mt9639%2C%20mt9649%2C%20mt9650%2C%20mt9652%2C%20mt9653%2C%20mt9660%2C%20mt9666%2C%20mt9667%2C%20mt9669%2C%20mt9671%2C%20mt9675%2C%20mt9679%2C%20mt9685%2C%20mt9686%2C%20mt9688%2C%20mt9689.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT5583, MT5586, MT5691, MT5695, MT5696, MT9010, MT9011, MT9012, MT9015, MT9016, MT9020, MT9021, MT9022, MT9025, MT9026, MT9216, MT9218, MT9220, MT9221, MT9222, MT9255, MT9256, MT9266, MT9269, MT9286, MT9288, MT9602, MT9603, MT9610, MT9611, MT9612, MT9613, MT9615, MT9617, MT9618, MT9629, MT9630, MT9631, MT9632, MT9633, MT9636, MT9638, MT9639, MT9649, MT9650, MT9652, MT9653, MT9660, MT9666, MT9667, MT9669, MT9671, MT9675, MT9679, MT9685, MT9686, MT9688, MT9689</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-20002|2024-02-05T05:59:42.613Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT5583, MT5586, MT5691, MT5695, MT5696, MT9010, MT9011, MT9012, MT9015, MT9016, MT9020, MT9021, MT9022, MT9025, MT9026, MT9216, MT9218, MT9220, MT9221, MT9222, MT9255, MT9256, MT9266, MT9269, MT9286, MT9288, MT9602, MT9603, MT9610, MT9611, MT9612, MT9613, MT9615, MT9617, MT9618, MT9629, MT9630, MT9631, MT9632, MT9633, MT9636, MT9638, MT9639, MT9649, MT9650, MT9652, MT9653, MT9660, MT9666, MT9667, MT9669, MT9671, MT9675, MT9679, MT9685, MT9686, MT9688, MT9689
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20002</link><description>In TVAPI, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: DTV03961715; Issue ID: DTV03961715.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20002|2024-02-05T05:59:42.613Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20001|2024-02-05T05:59:41.091Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT5583, MT5586, MT5691, MT5695, MT5696, MT9010, MT9011, MT9012, MT9015, MT9016, MT9020, MT9021, MT9022, MT9025, MT9026, MT9216, MT9218, MT9220, MT9221, MT9222, MT9255, MT9256, MT9266, MT9269, MT9286, MT9288, MT9602, MT9603, MT9610, MT9611, MT9612, MT9613, MT9615, MT9617, MT9618, MT9629, MT9630, MT9631, MT9632, MT9633, MT9636, MT9638, MT9639, MT9649, MT9650, MT9652, MT9653, MT9660, MT9666, MT9667, MT9669, MT9671, MT9675, MT9679, MT9685, MT9686, MT9688, MT9689
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20001</link><description>In TVAPI, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: DTV03961601; Issue ID: DTV03961601.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20001|2024-02-05T05:59:41.091Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>