<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Centreon -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/centreon/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Centreon -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-42424|2024-08-03T13:10:40.889Z -- centreon -- centreon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42424</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to modify poller broker configuration. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to the level of an administrator. Was ZDI-CAN-18556.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-42424|2024-08-03T13:10:40.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-42426|2024-08-03T13:10:40.430Z -- centreon -- centreon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42426</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to modify poller broker configuration. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to the level of an administrator. Was ZDI-CAN-18554.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-42426|2024-08-03T13:10:40.430Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34871|2024-08-03T09:22:10.706Z -- centreon -- centreon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34871</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the configuration of poller resources. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to the level of an administrator. Was ZDI-CAN-16335.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34871|2024-08-03T09:22:10.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 15:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-42427|2024-08-03T13:10:40.922Z -- centreon -- centreon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42427</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the contact groups configuration page. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to the level of an administrator. Was ZDI-CAN-18541.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-42427|2024-08-03T13:10:40.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41142|2024-08-03T12:35:49.560Z -- centreon -- centreon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41142</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to configure poller resources. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to the level of an administrator. Was ZDI-CAN-18304.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41142|2024-08-03T12:35:49.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-42428|2024-08-03T13:10:40.468Z -- centreon -- centreon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42428</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to modify poller broker configuration. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to the level of an administrator. Was ZDI-CAN-18410.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-42428|2024-08-03T13:10:40.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-42425|2024-08-03T13:10:40.413Z -- centreon -- centreon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42425</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to modify poller broker configuration. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to the level of an administrator. Was ZDI-CAN-18555.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-42425|2024-08-03T13:10:40.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-42429|2024-08-03T13:10:40.890Z -- centreon -- centreon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42429</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to modify poller broker configuration. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to the level of an administrator. Was ZDI-CAN-18557.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-42429|2024-08-03T13:10:40.890Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34872|2024-08-03T09:22:10.611Z -- centreon -- centreon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34872</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the processing of Virtual Metrics. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-16336.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34872|2024-08-03T09:22:10.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 15:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23117|2024-08-01T22:51:11.292Z -- centreon -- centreon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23117</link>
      <description>Centreon updateContactServiceCommands SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateContactServiceCommands function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22297.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23117|2024-08-01T22:51:11.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23118|2024-08-01T22:51:11.213Z -- centreon -- centreon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23118</link>
      <description>Centreon updateContactHostCommands SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateContactHostCommands function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22298.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23118|2024-08-01T22:51:11.213Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23116|2024-08-01T22:51:11.262Z -- centreon -- centreon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23116</link>
      <description>Centreon updateLCARelation SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateLCARelation function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22296.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23116|2024-08-01T22:51:11.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23119|2024-08-01T22:51:11.351Z -- centreon -- centreon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23119</link>
      <description>Centreon insertGraphTemplate SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the insertGraphTemplate function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22339.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23119|2024-08-01T22:51:11.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23115|2024-08-01T22:51:11.311Z -- centreon -- centreon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23115</link>
      <description>Centreon updateGroups SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateGroups function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22295.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23115|2024-08-01T22:51:11.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23115|2024-07-16T15:24:19.128Z -- centreon -- centreon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23115</link>
      <description>Centreon updateGroups SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateGroups function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22295.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23115|2024-07-16T15:24:19.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0637|2024-06-19T19:27:24.875Z -- centreon -- centreon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0637</link>
      <description>Centreon updateDirectory SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateDirectory function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22294.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0637|2024-06-19T19:27:24.875Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23118|2024-04-01T21:48:11.076Z -- centreon -- centreon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23118</link>
      <description>Centreon updateContactHostCommands SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateContactHostCommands function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22298.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23118|2024-04-01T21:48:11.076Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23119|2024-04-01T21:48:27.225Z -- centreon -- centreon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23119</link>
      <description>Centreon insertGraphTemplate SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the insertGraphTemplate function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22339.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23119|2024-04-01T21:48:27.225Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23115|2024-04-01T21:47:10.063Z -- centreon -- centreon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23115</link>
      <description>Centreon updateGroups SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateGroups function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22295.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23115|2024-04-01T21:47:10.063Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23116|2024-04-01T21:47:27.377Z -- centreon -- centreon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23116</link>
      <description>Centreon updateLCARelation SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateLCARelation function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22296.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23116|2024-04-01T21:47:27.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23117|2024-04-01T21:47:42.390Z -- centreon -- centreon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23117</link>
      <description>Centreon updateContactServiceCommands SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateContactServiceCommands function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22297.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23117|2024-04-01T21:47:42.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0637|2024-04-01T21:45:52.634Z -- centreon -- centreon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0637</link>
      <description>Centreon updateDirectory SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateDirectory function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22294.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0637|2024-04-01T21:45:52.634Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51633|2024-06-04T17:20:38.427Z -- centreon -- centreon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51633</link>
      <description>Centreon sysName Cross-Site Scripting Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of the sysName OID in SNMP. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can lead to the injection of an arbitrary script. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-20731.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51633|2024-06-04T17:20:38.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23119|2024-07-10T13:15:05.991Z -- centreon -- centreon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23119</link>
      <description>Centreon insertGraphTemplate SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the insertGraphTemplate function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22339.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23119|2024-07-10T13:15:05.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0637|2024-08-01T18:11:35.640Z -- centreon -- centreon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0637</link>
      <description>Centreon updateDirectory SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateDirectory function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22294.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0637|2024-08-01T18:11:35.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51633|2024-08-02T22:40:34.140Z -- centreon -- centreon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51633</link>
      <description>Centreon sysName Cross-Site Scripting Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of the sysName OID in SNMP. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can lead to the injection of an arbitrary script. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-20731.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51633|2024-08-02T22:40:34.140Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
