<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for cyberlord92 -- Active Directory Integration / LDAP Integration</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cyberlord92/active%20directory%20integration%20%2F%20ldap%20integration.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for cyberlord92 -- Active Directory Integration / LDAP Integration</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:23:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2484|2024-08-02T06:26:09.348Z -- cyberlord92 -- active%20directory%20integration%20%2F%20ldap%20integration
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2484</link>
      <description>The Active Directory Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the orderby and order parameters in versions up to, and including, 4.1.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with administrator privileges to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2484|2024-08-02T06:26:09.348Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4506|2024-08-02T07:31:05.501Z -- cyberlord92 -- active%20directory%20integration%20%2F%20ldap%20integration
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4506</link>
      <description>The Active Directory Integration / LDAP Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to LDAP Passback in versions up to, and including, 4.1.10. This is due to insufficient validation when changing the LDAP server. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrative access and above, to change the LDAP server and retrieve the credentials for the original LDAP server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4506|2024-08-02T07:31:05.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 01:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2599|2024-08-02T06:26:09.903Z -- cyberlord92 -- active%20directory%20integration%20%2F%20ldap%20integration
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2599</link>
      <description>The Active Directory Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery leading to time-based SQL Injection via the orderby and order parameters in versions up to, and including, 4.1.4 due to missing nonce verification on the get_users function and insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to cause resource exhaustion via a forged request granted they can trick an administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2599|2024-08-02T06:26:09.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3447|2024-08-02T06:55:03.573Z -- cyberlord92 -- active%20directory%20integration%20%2F%20ldap%20integration
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3447</link>
      <description>The Active Directory Integration / LDAP Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to LDAP Injection in versions up to, and including, 4.1.5. This is due to insufficient escaping on the supplied username value. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract potentially sensitive information from the LDAP directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3447|2024-08-02T06:55:03.573Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 04:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
