<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Mozilla -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mozilla/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Mozilla -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 09:23:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12404|2024-08-05T08:38:05.124Z -- mozilla -- network%20security%20services%20%28nss%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12404</link>
      <description>A cached side channel attack during handshakes using RSA encryption could allow for the decryption of encrypted content. This is a variant of the Adaptive Chosen Ciphertext attack (AKA Bleichenbacher attack) and affects all NSS versions prior to NSS 3.41.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12404|2024-08-05T08:38:05.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 16:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12374|2024-08-05T08:30:59.927Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12374</link>
      <description>Plaintext of decrypted emails can leak through by user submitting an embedded form by pressing enter key within a text input field. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12374|2024-08-05T08:30:59.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5096|2024-08-05T05:26:46.688Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5096</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur while editing events in form elements on a page, resulting in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 52.6 and Thunderbird &lt; 52.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5096|2024-08-05T05:26:46.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17003|2024-08-05T01:24:48.597Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20for%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17003</link>
      <description>Scanning a QR code that contained a javascript: URL would have resulted in the Javascript being executed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17003|2024-08-05T01:24:48.597Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17023|2024-08-05T01:24:48.748Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17023</link>
      <description>After a HelloRetryRequest has been sent, the client may negotiate a lower protocol that TLS 1.3, resulting in an invalid state transition in the TLS State Machine. If the client gets into this state, incoming Application Data records will be ignored. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 72.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17023|2024-08-05T01:24:48.748Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12385|2024-08-05T08:30:59.811Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12385</link>
      <description>A potentially exploitable crash in TransportSecurityInfo used for SSL can be triggered by data stored in the local cache in the user profile directory. This issue is only exploitable in combination with another vulnerability allowing an attacker to write data into the local cache or from locally installed malware. This issue also triggers a non-exploitable startup crash for users switching between the Nightly and Release versions of Firefox if the same profile is used. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 60.2.1, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.2.1, and Firefox &lt; 62.0.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12385|2024-08-05T08:30:59.811Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17006|2024-08-05T01:24:48.804Z -- mozilla -- nss
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17006</link>
      <description>In Network Security Services (NSS) before 3.46, several cryptographic primitives had missing length checks. In cases where the application calling the library did not perform a sanity check on the inputs it could result in a crash due to a buffer overflow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17006|2024-08-05T01:24:48.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 20:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5159|2024-08-05T05:26:46.960Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5159</link>
      <description>An integer overflow can occur in the Skia library due to 32-bit integer use in an array without integer overflow checks, resulting in possible out-of-bounds writes. This could lead to a potentially exploitable crash triggerable by web content. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.8, Thunderbird ESR &lt; 52.8, Firefox &lt; 60, and Firefox ESR &lt; 52.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5159|2024-08-05T05:26:46.960Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17009|2024-08-05T01:24:48.744Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17009</link>
      <description>When running, the updater service wrote status and log files to an unrestricted location; potentially allowing an unprivileged process to locate and exploit a vulnerability in file handling in the updater service. *Note: This attack requires local system access and only affects Windows. Other operating systems are not affected.*. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.3, Firefox ESR &lt; 68.3, and Firefox &lt; 71.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17009|2024-08-05T01:24:48.744Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5091|2024-08-05T05:26:46.599Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5091</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur during WebRTC connections when interacting with the DTMF timers. This results in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 52.6 and Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5091|2024-08-05T05:26:46.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12399|2024-08-05T08:38:04.826Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12399</link>
      <description>When a new protocol handler is registered, the API accepts a title argument which can be used to mislead users about which domain is registering the new protocol. This may result in the user approving a protocol handler that they otherwise would not have. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 63.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12399|2024-08-05T08:38:04.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5145|2024-08-05T05:26:46.970Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5145</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs were reported in Firefox ESR 52.6. These bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort that some of these could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 52.7 and Thunderbird &lt; 52.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5145|2024-08-05T05:26:46.970Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12388|2024-08-05T08:30:59.828Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12388</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers and community members reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 62. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort that some of these could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 63.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12388|2024-08-05T08:30:59.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5122|2024-08-05T05:26:46.973Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5122</link>
      <description>A potential integer overflow in the "DoCrypt" function of WebCrypto was identified. If a means was found of exploiting it, it could result in an out-of-bounds write. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5122|2024-08-05T05:26:46.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12390|2024-08-05T08:30:59.986Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12390</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers and community members reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 62 and Firefox ESR 60.2. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort that some of these could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 63, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.3, and Thunderbird &lt; 60.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12390|2024-08-05T08:30:59.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5113|2024-08-05T05:26:46.766Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5113</link>
      <description>The "browser.identity.launchWebAuthFlow" function of WebExtensions is only allowed to load content over "https:" but this requirement was not properly enforced. This can potentially allow privileged pages to be loaded by the extension. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5113|2024-08-05T05:26:46.766Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12397|2024-08-05T08:30:59.851Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12397</link>
      <description>A WebExtension can request access to local files without the warning prompt stating that the extension will "Access your data for all websites" being displayed to the user. This allows extensions to run content scripts in local pages without permission warnings when a local file is opened. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 60.3 and Firefox &lt; 63.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12397|2024-08-05T08:30:59.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12365|2024-08-05T08:30:59.980Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12365</link>
      <description>A compromised IPC child process can escape the content sandbox and list the names of arbitrary files on the file system without user consent or interaction. This could result in exposure of private local files. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 60, Thunderbird &lt; 52.9, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.1, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.9, and Firefox &lt; 61.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12365|2024-08-05T08:30:59.980Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5160|2024-08-05T05:26:46.989Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5160</link>
      <description>WebRTC can use a "WrappedI420Buffer" pixel buffer but the owning image object can be freed while it is still in use. This can result in the WebRTC encoder using uninitialized memory, leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5160|2024-08-05T05:26:46.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5098|2024-08-05T05:26:46.825Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5098</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur when form input elements, focus, and selections are manipulated by script content. This results in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.6, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.6, and Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5098|2024-08-05T05:26:46.825Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5184|2024-08-05T05:26:47.204Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5184</link>
      <description>Using remote content in encrypted messages can lead to the disclosure of plaintext. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird ESR &lt; 52.8 and Thunderbird &lt; 52.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5184|2024-08-05T05:26:47.204Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5172|2024-08-05T05:26:46.957Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5172</link>
      <description>The Live Bookmarks page and the PDF viewer can run injected script content if a user pastes script from the clipboard into them while viewing RSS feeds or PDF files. This could allow a malicious site to socially engineer a user to copy and paste malicious script content that could then run with the context of either page but does not allow for privilege escalation. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5172|2024-08-05T05:26:46.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5123|2024-08-05T05:26:46.948Z -- mozilla -- bugzilla
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5123</link>
      <description>A third party website can access information available to a user with access to a restricted bug entry using the image generation in report.cgi in all Bugzilla versions prior to 4.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5123|2024-08-05T05:26:46.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 15:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17019|2024-08-05T01:24:48.672Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17019</link>
      <description>When Python was installed on Windows, a python file being served with the MIME type of text/plain could be executed by Python instead of being opened as a text file when the Open option was selected upon download. *Note: this issue only occurs on Windows. Other operating systems are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 72.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17019|2024-08-05T01:24:48.672Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:28:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5127|2024-08-05T05:26:46.976Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5127</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow can occur when manipulating the SVG "animatedPathSegList" through script. This results in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.7, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.7, and Firefox &lt; 59.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5127|2024-08-05T05:26:46.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12401|2024-08-05T08:38:05.048Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12401</link>
      <description>Some special resource URIs will cause a non-exploitable crash if loaded with optional parameters following a '?' in the parsed string. This could lead to denial of service (DOS) attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 63.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12401|2024-08-05T08:38:05.048Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12375|2024-08-05T08:30:59.920Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12375</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 61. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort that some of these could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 62.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12375|2024-08-05T08:30:59.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12359|2024-08-05T08:30:59.942Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12359</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow can occur when rendering canvas content while adjusting the height and width of the canvas element dynamically, causing data to be written outside of the currently computed boundaries. This results in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 60, Thunderbird &lt; 52.9, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.1, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.9, and Firefox &lt; 61.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12359|2024-08-05T08:30:59.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5157|2024-08-05T05:26:46.995Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5157</link>
      <description>Same-origin protections for the PDF viewer can be bypassed, allowing a malicious site to intercept messages meant for the viewer. This could allow the site to retrieve PDF files restricted to viewing by an authenticated user on a third-party website. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 52.8 and Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5157|2024-08-05T05:26:46.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17007|2024-08-05T01:24:48.580Z -- mozilla -- nss
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17007</link>
      <description>In Network Security Services before 3.44, a malformed Netscape Certificate Sequence can cause NSS to crash, resulting in a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17007|2024-08-05T01:24:48.580Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 20:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5165|2024-08-05T05:26:47.013Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5165</link>
      <description>In 32-bit versions of Firefox, the Adobe Flash plugin setting for "Enable Adobe Flash protected mode" is unchecked by default even though the Adobe Flash sandbox is actually enabled. The displayed state is the reverse of the true setting, resulting in user confusion. This could cause users to select this setting intending to activate it and inadvertently turn protections off. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5165|2024-08-05T05:26:47.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5134|2024-08-05T05:26:46.963Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5134</link>
      <description>WebExtensions may use "view-source:" URLs to view local "file:" URL content, as well as content stored in "about:cache", bypassing restrictions that only allow WebExtensions to view specific content. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 59.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5134|2024-08-05T05:26:46.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5156|2024-08-05T05:26:46.986Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5156</link>
      <description>A vulnerability can occur when capturing a media stream when the media source type is changed as the capture is occurring. This can result in stream data being cast to the wrong type causing a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 60, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.1, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.9, and Firefox &lt; 61.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5156|2024-08-05T05:26:46.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5180|2024-08-05T05:26:47.098Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5180</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur during WebGL operations. While this results in a potentially exploitable crash, the vulnerability is limited because the memory is freed and reused in a brief window of time during the freeing of the same callstack. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5180|2024-08-05T05:26:47.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17001|2024-08-05T01:24:48.679Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17001</link>
      <description>A Content-Security-Policy that blocks in-line scripts could be bypassed using an object tag to execute JavaScript in the protected document (cross-site scripting). This is a separate bypass from CVE-2019-17000.*Note: This flaw only affected Firefox 69 and was not present in earlier versions.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 70.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17001|2024-08-05T01:24:48.679Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12369|2024-08-05T08:31:00.394Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12369</link>
      <description>WebExtensions bundled with embedded experiments were not correctly checked for proper authorization. This allowed a malicious WebExtension to gain full browser permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 60.1 and Firefox &lt; 61.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12369|2024-08-05T08:31:00.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5132|2024-08-05T05:26:46.978Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5132</link>
      <description>The Find API for WebExtensions can search some privileged pages, such as "about:debugging", if these pages are open in a tab. This could allow a malicious WebExtension to search for otherwise protected data if a user has it open. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 59.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5132|2024-08-05T05:26:46.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17010|2024-08-05T01:24:48.864Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17010</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, when checking the Resist Fingerprinting preference during device orientation checks, a race condition could have caused a use-after-free and a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.3, Firefox ESR &lt; 68.3, and Firefox &lt; 71.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17010|2024-08-05T01:24:48.864Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5090|2024-08-05T05:26:46.716Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5090</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs were reported in Firefox 57. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort that some of these could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5090|2024-08-05T05:26:46.716Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5155|2024-08-05T05:26:47.016Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5155</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur while adjusting layout during SVG animations with text paths. This results in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.8, Thunderbird ESR &lt; 52.8, Firefox &lt; 60, and Firefox ESR &lt; 52.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5155|2024-08-05T05:26:47.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17015|2024-08-05T01:24:48.689Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17015</link>
      <description>During the initialization of a new content process, a pointer offset can be manipulated leading to memory corruption and a potentially exploitable crash in the parent process. *Note: this issue only occurs on Windows. Other operating systems are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 68.4 and Firefox &lt; 72.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17015|2024-08-05T01:24:48.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5128|2024-08-05T05:26:46.869Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5128</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur when manipulating elements, events, and selection ranges during editor operations. This results in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 59.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5128|2024-08-05T05:26:46.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5141|2024-08-05T05:26:46.981Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5141</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the notifications Push API where notifications can be sent through service workers by web content without direct user interaction. This could be used to open new tabs in a denial of service (DOS) attack or to display unwanted content from arbitrary URLs to users. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 59.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5141|2024-08-05T05:26:46.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5107|2024-08-05T05:26:46.745Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5107</link>
      <description>The printing process can bypass local access protections to read files available through symlinks, bypassing local file restrictions. The printing process requires files in a specific format so arbitrary data cannot be read but it is possible that some local file information could be exposed. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5107|2024-08-05T05:26:46.745Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12383|2024-08-05T08:30:59.923Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12383</link>
      <description>If a user saved passwords before Firefox 58 and then later set a master password, an unencrypted copy of these passwords is still accessible. This is because the older stored password file was not deleted when the data was copied to a new format starting in Firefox 58. The new master password is added only on the new file. This could allow the exposure of stored password data outside of user expectations. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 62, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.2.1, and Thunderbird &lt; 60.2.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12383|2024-08-05T08:30:59.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12386|2024-08-05T08:30:59.824Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12386</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in register allocation in JavaScript can lead to type confusion, allowing for an arbitrary read and write. This leads to remote code execution inside the sandboxed content process when triggered. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 60.2.2 and Firefox &lt; 62.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12386|2024-08-05T08:30:59.824Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5162|2024-08-05T05:26:46.974Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5162</link>
      <description>Plaintext of decrypted emails can leak through the src attribute of remote images, or links. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird ESR &lt; 52.8 and Thunderbird &lt; 52.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5162|2024-08-05T05:26:46.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5181|2024-08-05T05:26:47.013Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5181</link>
      <description>If a URL using the "file:" protocol is dragged and dropped onto an open tab that is running in a different child process the tab will open a local file corresponding to the dropped URL, contrary to policy. One way to make the target tab open more reliably in a separate process is to open it with the "noopener" keyword. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5181|2024-08-05T05:26:47.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12371|2024-08-05T08:31:00.284Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12371</link>
      <description>An integer overflow vulnerability in the Skia library when allocating memory for edge builders on some systems with at least 16 GB of RAM. This results in the use of uninitialized memory, resulting in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 60.1, Thunderbird &lt; 60, and Firefox &lt; 61.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12371|2024-08-05T08:31:00.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 13:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5097|2024-08-05T05:26:46.623Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5097</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur during XSL transformations when the source document for the transformation is manipulated by script content during the transformation. This results in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.6, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.6, and Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5097|2024-08-05T05:26:46.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17000|2024-08-05T01:24:48.682Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17000</link>
      <description>An object tag with a data URI did not correctly inherit the document's Content Security Policy. This allowed a CSP bypass in a cross-origin frame if the document's policy explicitly allowed data: URIs. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 70.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17000|2024-08-05T01:24:48.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 20:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12403|2024-08-05T08:38:04.796Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12403</link>
      <description>If a site is loaded over a HTTPS connection but loads a favicon resource over HTTP, the mixed content warning is not displayed to users. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 63.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12403|2024-08-05T08:38:04.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17016|2024-08-05T01:24:48.588Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17016</link>
      <description>When pasting a &amp;lt;style&amp;gt; tag from the clipboard into a rich text editor, the CSS sanitizer incorrectly rewrites a @namespace rule. This could allow for injection into certain types of websites resulting in data exfiltration. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 68.4 and Firefox &lt; 72.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17016|2024-08-05T01:24:48.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17024|2024-08-05T01:24:48.822Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17024</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 71 and Firefox ESR 68.3. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 68.4 and Firefox &lt; 72.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17024|2024-08-05T01:24:48.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5114|2024-08-05T05:26:46.784Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5114</link>
      <description>If an existing cookie is changed to be "HttpOnly" while a document is open, the original value remains accessible through script until that document is closed. Network requests correctly use the changed HttpOnly cookie. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5114|2024-08-05T05:26:46.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5146|2024-08-05T05:26:46.948Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5146</link>
      <description>An out of bounds memory write while processing Vorbis audio data was reported through the Pwn2Own contest. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 59.0.1, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.7.2, and Thunderbird &lt; 52.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5146|2024-08-05T05:26:46.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12407|2024-08-05T08:38:05.119Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12407</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow occurs when drawing and validating elements with the ANGLE graphics library, used for WebGL content, when working with the VertexBuffer11 module. This results in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 64.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12407|2024-08-05T08:38:05.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5151|2024-08-05T05:26:46.992Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5151</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs were reported in Firefox 59. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort that some of these could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5151|2024-08-05T05:26:46.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12368|2024-08-05T08:30:59.772Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12368</link>
      <description>Windows 10 does not warn users before opening executable files with the SettingContent-ms extension even when they have been downloaded from the internet and have the "Mark of the Web." Without the warning, unsuspecting users unfamiliar with this new file type might run an unwanted executable. This also allows a WebExtension with the limited downloads.open permission to execute arbitrary code without user interaction on Windows 10 systems. *Note: this issue only affects Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 60, Thunderbird &lt; 52.9, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.1, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.9, and Firefox &lt; 61.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12368|2024-08-05T08:30:59.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17008|2024-08-05T01:24:48.697Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17008</link>
      <description>When using nested workers, a use-after-free could occur during worker destruction. This resulted in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.3, Firefox ESR &lt; 68.3, and Firefox &lt; 71.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17008|2024-08-05T01:24:48.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5175|2024-08-05T05:26:47.000Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5175</link>
      <description>A mechanism to bypass Content Security Policy (CSP) protections on sites that have a "script-src" policy of "'strict-dynamic'". If a target website contains an HTML injection flaw an attacker could inject a reference to a copy of the "require.js" library that is part of Firefox's Developer Tools, and then use a known technique using that library to bypass the CSP restrictions on executing injected scripts. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5175|2024-08-05T05:26:47.000Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5186|2024-08-05T05:26:47.205Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5186</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 60. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort that some of these could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 61.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5186|2024-08-05T05:26:47.205Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5176|2024-08-05T05:26:46.989Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5176</link>
      <description>The JSON Viewer displays clickable hyperlinks for strings that are parseable as URLs, including "javascript:" links. If a JSON file contains malicious JavaScript script embedded as "javascript:" links, users may be tricked into clicking and running this code in the context of the JSON Viewer. This can allow for the theft of cookies and authorization tokens which are accessible to that context. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5176|2024-08-05T05:26:46.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5182|2024-08-05T05:26:47.148Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5182</link>
      <description>If a text string that happens to be a filename in the operating system's native format is dragged and dropped onto the addressbar the specified local file will be opened. This is contrary to policy and is what would happen if the string were the equivalent "file:" URL. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5182|2024-08-05T05:26:47.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5103|2024-08-05T05:26:46.737Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5103</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur during mouse event handling due to issues with multiprocess support. This results in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.6, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.6, and Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5103|2024-08-05T05:26:46.737Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12405|2024-08-05T08:38:04.965Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12405</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers and community members reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 63 and Firefox ESR 60.3. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort that some of these could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 60.4, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.4, and Firefox &lt; 64.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12405|2024-08-05T08:38:04.965Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12392|2024-08-05T08:30:59.822Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12392</link>
      <description>When manipulating user events in nested loops while opening a document through script, it is possible to trigger a potentially exploitable crash due to poor event handling. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 63, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.3, and Thunderbird &lt; 60.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12392|2024-08-05T08:30:59.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5178|2024-08-05T05:26:46.980Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5178</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow was found during UTF8 to Unicode string conversion within JavaScript with extremely large amounts of data. This vulnerability requires the use of a malicious or vulnerable legacy extension in order to occur. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird ESR &lt; 52.8, Thunderbird &lt; 52.8, and Firefox ESR &lt; 52.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5178|2024-08-05T05:26:46.980Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17022|2024-08-05T01:24:48.712Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17022</link>
      <description>When pasting a &amp;lt;style&amp;gt; tag from the clipboard into a rich text editor, the CSS sanitizer does not escape &amp;lt; and &amp;gt; characters. Because the resulting string is pasted directly into the text node of the element this does not result in a direct injection into the webpage; however, if a webpage subsequently copies the node's innerHTML, assigning it to another innerHTML, this would result in an XSS vulnerability. Two WYSIWYG editors were identified with this behavior, more may exist. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 68.4 and Firefox &lt; 72.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17022|2024-08-05T01:24:48.712Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12393|2024-08-05T08:31:00.111Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12393</link>
      <description>A potential vulnerability was found in 32-bit builds where an integer overflow during the conversion of scripts to an internal UTF-16 representation could result in allocating a buffer too small for the conversion. This leads to a possible out-of-bounds write. *Note: 64-bit builds are not vulnerable to this issue.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 63, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.3, and Thunderbird &lt; 60.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12393|2024-08-05T08:31:00.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5110|2024-08-05T05:26:46.714Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5110</link>
      <description>If cursor visibility is toggled by script using from 'none' to an image and back through script, the cursor will be rendered temporarily invisible within Firefox. Note: This vulnerability only affects OS X. Other operating systems are not affected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5110|2024-08-05T05:26:46.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5137|2024-08-05T05:26:46.945Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5137</link>
      <description>A legacy extension's non-contentaccessible, defined resources can be loaded by an arbitrary web page through script. This script does this by using a maliciously crafted path string to reference the resources. Note: this vulnerability does not affect WebExtensions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 59.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5137|2024-08-05T05:26:46.945Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5154|2024-08-05T05:26:46.975Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5154</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur while enumerating attributes during SVG animations with clip paths. This results in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.8, Thunderbird ESR &lt; 52.8, Firefox &lt; 60, and Firefox ESR &lt; 52.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5154|2024-08-05T05:26:46.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5138|2024-08-05T05:26:46.981Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5138</link>
      <description>A spoofing vulnerability can occur when a malicious site with an extremely long domain name is opened in an Android Custom Tab (a browser panel inside another app) and the default browser is Firefox for Android. This could allow an attacker to spoof which page is actually loaded and in use. Note: this issue only affects Firefox for Android. Other versions and operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 59.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5138|2024-08-05T05:26:46.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5183|2024-08-05T05:26:47.203Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5183</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers backported selected changes in the Skia library. These changes correct memory corruption issues including invalid buffer reads and writes during graphic operations. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird ESR &lt; 52.8, Thunderbird &lt; 52.8, and Firefox ESR &lt; 52.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5183|2024-08-05T05:26:47.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12389|2024-08-05T08:31:00.289Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12389</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers and community members reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox ESR 60.2. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort that some of these could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 60.3 and Thunderbird &lt; 60.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12389|2024-08-05T08:31:00.289Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5153|2024-08-05T05:26:46.992Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5153</link>
      <description>If websocket data is sent with mixed text and binary in a single message, the binary data can be corrupted. This can result in an out-of-bounds read with the read memory sent to the originating server in response. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5153|2024-08-05T05:26:46.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5163|2024-08-05T05:26:47.037Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5163</link>
      <description>If a malicious attacker has used another vulnerability to gain full control over a content process, they may be able to replace the alternate data resources stored in the JavaScript Start-up Bytecode Cache (JSBC) for other JavaScript code. If the parent process then runs this replaced code, the executed script would be run with the parent process' privileges, escaping the sandbox on content processes. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5163|2024-08-05T05:26:47.037Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5106|2024-08-05T05:26:46.796Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5106</link>
      <description>Style editor traffic in the Developer Tools can be routed through a service worker hosted on a third party website if a user selects error links when these tools are open. This can allow style editor information used within Developer Tools to leak cross-origin. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5106|2024-08-05T05:26:46.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17021|2024-08-05T01:24:48.727Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17021</link>
      <description>During the initialization of a new content process, a race condition occurs that can allow a content process to disclose heap addresses from the parent process. *Note: this issue only occurs on Windows. Other operating systems are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 68.4 and Firefox &lt; 72.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17021|2024-08-05T01:24:48.727Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5169|2024-08-05T05:26:46.981Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5169</link>
      <description>If manipulated hyperlinked text with "chrome:" URL contained in it is dragged and dropped on the "home" icon, the home page can be reset to include a normally-unlinkable chrome page as one of the home page tabs. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5169|2024-08-05T05:26:46.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12402|2024-08-05T08:38:04.838Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12402</link>
      <description>The internal WebBrowserPersist code does not use correct origin context for a resource being saved. This manifests when sub-resources are loaded as part of "Save Page As..." functionality. For example, a malicious page could recover a visitor's Windows username and NTLM hash by including resources otherwise unreachable to the malicious page, if they can convince the visitor to save the complete web page. Similarly, SameSite cookies are sent on cross-origin requests when the "Save Page As..." menu item is selected to save a page, which can result in saving the wrong version of resources based on those cookies. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 63.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12402|2024-08-05T08:38:04.838Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17017|2024-08-05T01:24:48.752Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17017</link>
      <description>Due to a missing case handling object types, a type confusion vulnerability could occur, resulting in a crash. We presume that with enough effort that it could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 68.4 and Firefox &lt; 72.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17017|2024-08-05T01:24:48.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12372|2024-08-05T08:30:59.862Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12372</link>
      <description>Decrypted S/MIME parts, when included in HTML crafted for an attack, can leak plaintext when included in a a HTML reply/forward. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12372|2024-08-05T08:30:59.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12364|2024-08-05T08:31:00.279Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12364</link>
      <description>NPAPI plugins, such as Adobe Flash, can send non-simple cross-origin requests, bypassing CORS by making a same-origin POST that does a 307 redirect to the target site. This allows for a malicious site to engage in cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 60, Thunderbird &lt; 52.9, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.1, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.9, and Firefox &lt; 61.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12364|2024-08-05T08:31:00.279Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5185|2024-08-05T05:26:46.969Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5185</link>
      <description>Plaintext of decrypted emails can leak through by user submitting an embedded form. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird ESR &lt; 52.8 and Thunderbird &lt; 52.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5185|2024-08-05T05:26:46.969Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17020|2024-08-05T01:24:48.668Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17020</link>
      <description>If an XML file is served with a Content Security Policy and the XML file includes an XSL stylesheet, the Content Security Policy will not be applied to the contents of the XSL stylesheet. If the XSL sheet e.g. includes JavaScript, it would bypass any of the restrictions of the Content Security Policy applied to the XML document. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 72.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17020|2024-08-05T01:24:48.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5104|2024-08-05T05:26:46.991Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5104</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur during font face manipulation when a font face is freed while still in use, resulting in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.6, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.6, and Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5104|2024-08-05T05:26:46.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5188|2024-08-05T05:26:46.950Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5188</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 60, Firefox ESR 60, and Firefox ESR 52.8. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort that some of these could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 60, Thunderbird &lt; 52.9, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.1, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.9, and Firefox &lt; 61.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5188|2024-08-05T05:26:46.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12395|2024-08-05T08:30:59.771Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12395</link>
      <description>By rewriting the Host: request headers using the webRequest API, a WebExtension can bypass domain restrictions through domain fronting. This would allow access to domains that share a host that are otherwise restricted. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 60.3 and Firefox &lt; 63.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12395|2024-08-05T08:30:59.771Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5173|2024-08-05T05:26:46.982Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5173</link>
      <description>The filename appearing in the "Downloads" panel improperly renders some Unicode characters, allowing for the file name to be spoofed. This can be used to obscure the file extension of potentially executable files from user view in the panel. Note: the dialog to open the file will show the full, correct filename and whether it is executable or not. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5173|2024-08-05T05:26:46.982Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5089|2024-08-05T05:26:47.041Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5089</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs were reported in Firefox 57 and Firefox ESR 52.5. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort that some of these could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.6, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.6, and Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5089|2024-08-05T05:26:47.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5121|2024-08-05T05:26:46.931Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5121</link>
      <description>Low descenders on some Tibetan characters in several fonts on OS X are clipped when rendered in the addressbar. When used as part of an Internationalized Domain Name (IDN) this can be used for domain name spoofing attacks. Note: This attack only affects OS X operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5121|2024-08-05T05:26:46.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12396|2024-08-05T08:30:59.819Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12396</link>
      <description>A vulnerability where a WebExtension can run content scripts in disallowed contexts following navigation or other events. This allows for potential privilege escalation by the WebExtension on sites where content scripts should not be run. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 60.3 and Firefox &lt; 63.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12396|2024-08-05T08:30:59.819Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5126|2024-08-05T05:26:46.859Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5126</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs were reported in Firefox 58. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort that some of these could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 59.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5126|2024-08-05T05:26:46.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12379|2024-08-05T08:30:59.942Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12379</link>
      <description>When the Mozilla Updater opens a MAR format file which contains a very long item filename, an out-of-bounds write can be triggered, leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This requires running the Mozilla Updater manually on the local system with the malicious MAR file in order to occur. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 62, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.2, and Thunderbird &lt; 60.2.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12379|2024-08-05T08:30:59.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5094|2024-08-05T05:26:46.806Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5094</link>
      <description>A heap buffer overflow vulnerability may occur in WebAssembly when "shrinkElements" is called followed by garbage collection on memory that is now uninitialized. This results in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5094|2024-08-05T05:26:46.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5101|2024-08-05T05:26:46.785Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5101</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur when manipulating floating "first-letter" style elements, resulting in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5101|2024-08-05T05:26:46.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5142|2024-08-05T05:26:46.871Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5142</link>
      <description>If Media Capture and Streams API permission is requested from documents with "data:" or "blob:" URLs, the permission notifications do not properly display the originating domain. The notification states "Unknown protocol" as the requestee, leading to user confusion about which site is asking for this permission. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 59.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5142|2024-08-05T05:26:46.871Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17013|2024-08-05T01:24:48.751Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17013</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 70. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 71.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17013|2024-08-05T01:24:48.751Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5143|2024-08-05T05:26:46.997Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5143</link>
      <description>URLs using "javascript:" have the protocol removed when pasted into the addressbar to protect users from cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks, but if a tab character is embedded in the "javascript:" URL the protocol is not removed and the script will execute. This could allow users to be socially engineered to run an XSS attack against themselves. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 59.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5143|2024-08-05T05:26:46.997Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5109|2024-08-05T05:26:46.892Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5109</link>
      <description>An audio capture session can started under an incorrect origin from the site making the capture request. Users are still prompted to allow the request but the prompt can display the wrong origin, leading to user confusion about which site is making the request to capture an audio stream. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5109|2024-08-05T05:26:46.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5140|2024-08-05T05:26:46.945Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5140</link>
      <description>Image for moz-icons can be accessed through the "moz-icon:" protocol through script in web content even when otherwise prohibited. This could allow for information leakage of which applications are associated with specific MIME types by a malicious page. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 59.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5140|2024-08-05T05:26:46.945Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5187|2024-08-05T05:26:47.047Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5187</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 60 and Firefox ESR 60. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort that some of these could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 60, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.1, and Firefox &lt; 61.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5187|2024-08-05T05:26:47.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12367|2024-08-05T08:30:59.761Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12367</link>
      <description>In the previous mitigations for Spectre, the resolution or precision of various methods was reduced to counteract the ability to measure precise time intervals. In that work PerformanceNavigationTiming was not adjusted but it was found that it could be used as a precision timer. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 60, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.1, and Firefox &lt; 61.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12367|2024-08-05T08:30:59.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12387|2024-08-05T08:30:59.795Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12387</link>
      <description>A vulnerability where the JavaScript JIT compiler inlines Array.prototype.push with multiple arguments that results in the stack pointer being off by 8 bytes after a bailout. This leaks a memory address to the calling function which can be used as part of an exploit inside the sandboxed content process. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 60.2.2 and Firefox &lt; 62.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12387|2024-08-05T08:30:59.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17011|2024-08-05T01:24:48.683Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17011</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, when retrieving a document from a DocShell in the antitracking code, a race condition could cause a use-after-free condition and a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.3, Firefox ESR &lt; 68.3, and Firefox &lt; 71.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17011|2024-08-05T01:24:48.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:23:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17014|2024-08-05T01:24:48.675Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17014</link>
      <description>If an image had not loaded correctly (such as when it is not actually an image), it could be dragged and dropped cross-domain, resulting in a cross-origin information leak. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 71.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17014|2024-08-05T01:24:48.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5152|2024-08-05T05:26:46.963Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5152</link>
      <description>WebExtensions with the appropriate permissions can attach content scripts to Mozilla sites such as accounts.firefox.com and listen to network traffic to the site through the "webRequest" API. For example, this allows for the interception of username and an encrypted password during login to Firefox Accounts. This issue does not expose synchronization traffic directly and is limited to the process of user login to the website and the data displayed to the user once logged in. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5152|2024-08-05T05:26:46.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5174|2024-08-05T05:26:47.099Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5174</link>
      <description>In the Windows 10 April 2018 Update, Windows Defender SmartScreen honors the "SEE_MASK_FLAG_NO_UI" flag associated with downloaded files and will not show any UI. Files that are unknown and potentially dangerous will be allowed to run because SmartScreen will not prompt the user for a decision, and if the user is offline all files will be allowed to be opened because Windows won't prompt the user to ask what to do. Firefox incorrectly sets this flag when downloading files, leading to less secure behavior from SmartScreen. Note: this issue only affects Windows 10 users running the April 2018 update or later. It does not affect other Windows users or other operating systems. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.8, Thunderbird ESR &lt; 52.8, Firefox &lt; 60, and Firefox ESR &lt; 52.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5174|2024-08-05T05:26:47.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12391|2024-08-05T08:31:00.102Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12391</link>
      <description>During HTTP Live Stream playback on Firefox for Android, audio data can be accessed across origins in violation of security policies. Because the problem is in the underlying Android service, this issue is addressed by treating all HLS streams as cross-origin and opaque to access. *Note: this issue only affects Firefox for Android. Desktop versions of Firefox are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 63, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.3, and Thunderbird &lt; 60.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12391|2024-08-05T08:31:00.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-25136|2024-08-05T03:00:19.229Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25136</link>
      <description>A compromised child process could have injected XBL Bindings into privileged CSS rules, resulting in arbitrary code execution and a sandbox escape. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 70.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-25136|2024-08-05T03:00:19.229Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 10:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17026|2024-08-05T01:24:48.586Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17026</link>
      <description>Incorrect alias information in IonMonkey JIT compiler for setting array elements could lead to a type confusion. We are aware of targeted attacks in the wild abusing this flaw. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 68.4.1, Thunderbird &lt; 68.4.1, and Firefox &lt; 72.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17026|2024-08-05T01:24:48.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 04:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5147|2024-08-05T05:26:46.978Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5147</link>
      <description>The libtremor library has the same flaw as CVE-2018-5146. This library is used by Firefox in place of libvorbis on Android and ARM platforms. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 52.7.2 and Firefox &lt; 59.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5147|2024-08-05T05:26:46.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5164|2024-08-05T05:26:46.998Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5164</link>
      <description>Content Security Policy (CSP) is not applied correctly to all parts of multipart content sent with the "multipart/x-mixed-replace" MIME type. This could allow for script to run where CSP should block it, allowing for cross-site scripting (XSS) and other attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5164|2024-08-05T05:26:46.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5112|2024-08-05T05:26:46.832Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5112</link>
      <description>Development Tools panels of an extension are required to load URLs for the panels as relative URLs from the extension manifest file but this requirement was not enforced in all instances. This could allow the development tools panel for the extension to load a URL that it should not be able to access, including potentially privileged pages. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5112|2024-08-05T05:26:46.832Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5166|2024-08-05T05:26:46.980Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5166</link>
      <description>WebExtensions can use request redirection and a "filterReponseData" filter to bypass host permission settings to redirect network traffic and access content from a host for which they do not have explicit user permission. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5166|2024-08-05T05:26:46.980Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17002|2024-08-05T01:24:48.808Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17002</link>
      <description>If upgrade-insecure-requests was specified in the Content Security Policy, and a link was dragged and dropped from that page, the link was not upgraded to https. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 70.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17002|2024-08-05T01:24:48.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12398|2024-08-05T08:38:04.776Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12398</link>
      <description>By using the reflected URL in some special resource URIs, such as chrome:, it is possible to inject stylesheets and bypass Content Security Policy (CSP). This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 63.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12398|2024-08-05T08:38:04.776Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12363|2024-08-05T08:30:59.771Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12363</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur when script uses mutation events to move DOM nodes between documents, resulting in the old document that held the node being freed but the node still having a pointer referencing it. This results in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 60, Thunderbird &lt; 52.9, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.1, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.9, and Firefox &lt; 61.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12363|2024-08-05T08:30:59.771Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12361|2024-08-05T08:31:00.338Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12361</link>
      <description>An integer overflow can occur in the SwizzleData code while calculating buffer sizes. The overflowed value is used for subsequent graphics computations when their inputs are not sanitized which results in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 60, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.1, and Firefox &lt; 61.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12361|2024-08-05T08:31:00.338Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5136|2024-08-05T05:26:46.971Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5136</link>
      <description>A shared worker created from a "data:" URL in one tab can be shared by another tab with a different origin, bypassing the same-origin policy. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 59.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5136|2024-08-05T05:26:46.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5167|2024-08-05T05:26:46.993Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5167</link>
      <description>The web console and JavaScript debugger do not sanitize all output that can be hyperlinked. Both will display "chrome:" links as active, clickable hyperlinks in their output. Web sites should not be able to directly link to internal chrome pages. Additionally, the JavaScript debugger will display "javascript:" links, which users could be tricked into clicking by malicious sites. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5167|2024-08-05T05:26:46.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5161|2024-08-05T05:26:46.999Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5161</link>
      <description>Crafted message headers can cause a Thunderbird process to hang on receiving the message. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird ESR &lt; 52.8 and Thunderbird &lt; 52.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5161|2024-08-05T05:26:46.999Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5131|2024-08-05T05:26:46.949Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5131</link>
      <description>Under certain circumstances the "fetch()" API can return transient local copies of resources that were sent with a "no-store" or "no-cache" cache header instead of downloading a copy from the network as it should. This can result in previously stored, locally cached data of a website being accessible to users if they share a common profile while browsing. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 52.7 and Firefox &lt; 59.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5131|2024-08-05T05:26:46.949Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17025|2024-08-05T01:24:48.686Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17025</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 71. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 72.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17025|2024-08-05T01:24:48.686Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5116|2024-08-05T05:26:46.975Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5116</link>
      <description>WebExtensions with the "ActiveTab" permission are able to access frames hosted within the active tab even if the frames are cross-origin. Malicious extensions can inject frames from arbitrary origins into the loaded page and then interact with them, bypassing same-origin user expectations with this permission. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5116|2024-08-05T05:26:46.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5092|2024-08-05T05:26:46.545Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5092</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur when the thread for a Web Worker is freed from memory prematurely instead of from memory in the main thread while cancelling fetch operations. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5092|2024-08-05T05:26:46.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12382|2024-08-05T08:30:59.749Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12382</link>
      <description>The displayed addressbar URL can be spoofed on Firefox for Android using a javascript: URI in concert with JavaScript to insert text before the loaded domain name, scrolling the loaded domain out of view to the right. This can lead to user confusion. *This vulnerability only affects Firefox for Android &lt; 62.*</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12382|2024-08-05T08:30:59.749Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5150|2024-08-05T05:26:46.983Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5150</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs were reported in Firefox 59, Firefox ESR 52.7, and Thunderbird 52.7. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort that some of these could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.8, Thunderbird ESR &lt; 52.8, Firefox &lt; 60, and Firefox ESR &lt; 52.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5150|2024-08-05T05:26:46.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5093|2024-08-05T05:26:46.835Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5093</link>
      <description>A heap buffer overflow vulnerability may occur in WebAssembly during Memory/Table resizing, resulting in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5093|2024-08-05T05:26:46.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5119|2024-08-05T05:26:46.978Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5119</link>
      <description>The reader view will display cross-origin content when CORS headers are set to prohibit the loading of cross-origin content by a site. This could allow access to content that should be restricted in reader view. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5119|2024-08-05T05:26:46.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12376|2024-08-05T08:30:59.941Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12376</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 61 and Firefox ESR 60.1. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort that some of these could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 62, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.2, and Thunderbird &lt; 60.2.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12376|2024-08-05T08:30:59.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5108|2024-08-05T05:26:46.804Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5108</link>
      <description>A Blob URL can violate origin attribute segregation, allowing it to be accessed from a private browsing tab and for data to be passed between the private browsing tab and a normal tab. This could allow for the leaking of private information specific to the private browsing context. This issue is mitigated by the requirement that the user enter the Blob URL manually in order for the access violation to occur. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5108|2024-08-05T05:26:46.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5144|2024-08-05T05:26:46.979Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5144</link>
      <description>An integer overflow can occur during conversion of text to some Unicode character sets due to an unchecked length parameter. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 52.7 and Thunderbird &lt; 52.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5144|2024-08-05T05:26:46.979Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5102|2024-08-05T05:26:46.667Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5102</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur when manipulating HTML media elements with media streams, resulting in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.6, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.6, and Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5102|2024-08-05T05:26:46.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12400|2024-08-05T08:38:04.959Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12400</link>
      <description>In private browsing mode on Firefox for Android, favicons are cached in the cache/icons folder as they are in non-private mode. This allows information leakage of sites visited during private browsing sessions. *Note: this issue only affects Firefox for Android. Desktop versions of Firefox are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 63.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12400|2024-08-05T08:38:04.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5118|2024-08-05T05:26:46.969Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5118</link>
      <description>The screenshot images displayed in the Activity Stream page displayed when a new tab is opened is created from the meta tags of websites. An issue was discovered where the page could attempt to create these images through "file:" URLs from the local file system. This loading is blocked by the sandbox but could expose local data if combined with another attack that escapes sandbox protections. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5118|2024-08-05T05:26:46.969Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5115|2024-08-05T05:26:46.685Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5115</link>
      <description>If an HTTP authentication prompt is triggered by a background network request from a page or extension, it is displayed over the currently loaded foreground page. Although the prompt contains the real domain making the request, this can result in user confusion about the originating site of the authentication request and may cause users to mistakenly send private credential information to a third party site. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5115|2024-08-05T05:26:46.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12366|2024-08-05T08:30:59.988Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12366</link>
      <description>An invalid grid size during QCMS (color profile) transformations can result in the out-of-bounds read interpreted as a float value. This could leak private data into the output. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 60, Thunderbird &lt; 52.9, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.1, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.9, and Firefox &lt; 61.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12366|2024-08-05T08:30:59.988Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5130|2024-08-05T05:26:46.968Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5130</link>
      <description>When packets with a mismatched RTP payload type are sent in WebRTC connections, in some circumstances a potentially exploitable crash is triggered. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 52.7 and Firefox &lt; 59.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5130|2024-08-05T05:26:46.968Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12377|2024-08-05T08:30:59.857Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12377</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur when refresh driver timers are refreshed in some circumstances during shutdown when the timer is deleted while still in use. This results in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 62, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.2, and Thunderbird &lt; 60.2.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12377|2024-08-05T08:30:59.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5148|2024-08-05T05:26:46.951Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5148</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur in the compositor during certain graphics operations when a raw pointer is used instead of a reference counted one. This results in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 52.7.3 and Firefox &lt; 59.0.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5148|2024-08-05T05:26:46.951Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5135|2024-08-05T05:26:46.978Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5135</link>
      <description>WebExtensions can bypass normal restrictions in some circumstances and use "browser.tabs.executeScript" to inject scripts into contexts where this should not be allowed, such as pages from other WebExtensions or unprivileged "about:" pages. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 59.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5135|2024-08-05T05:26:46.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5129|2024-08-05T05:26:46.961Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5129</link>
      <description>A lack of parameter validation on IPC messages results in a potential out-of-bounds write through malformed IPC messages. This can potentially allow for sandbox escape through memory corruption in the parent process. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.7, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.7, and Firefox &lt; 59.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5129|2024-08-05T05:26:46.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5117|2024-08-05T05:26:46.943Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5117</link>
      <description>If right-to-left text is used in the addressbar with left-to-right alignment, it is possible in some circumstances to scroll this text to spoof the displayed URL. This issue could result in the wrong URL being displayed as a location, which can mislead users to believe they are on a different site than the one loaded. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.6, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.6, and Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5117|2024-08-05T05:26:46.943Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12362|2024-08-05T08:30:59.696Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12362</link>
      <description>An integer overflow can occur during graphics operations done by the Supplemental Streaming SIMD Extensions 3 (SSSE3) scaler, resulting in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 60, Thunderbird &lt; 52.9, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.1, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.9, and Firefox &lt; 61.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12362|2024-08-05T08:30:59.696Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12358|2024-08-05T08:30:59.989Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12358</link>
      <description>Service workers can use redirection to avoid the tainting of cross-origin resources in some instances, allowing a malicious site to read responses which are supposed to be opaque. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 61.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12358|2024-08-05T08:30:59.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12406|2024-08-05T08:38:05.043Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12406</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers and community members reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 63. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort that some of these could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 64.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12406|2024-08-05T08:38:05.043Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5125|2024-08-05T05:26:46.946Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5125</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs were reported in Firefox 58 and Firefox ESR 52.6. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort that some of these could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.7, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.7, and Firefox &lt; 59.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5125|2024-08-05T05:26:46.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5111|2024-08-05T05:26:46.826Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5111</link>
      <description>When the text of a specially formatted URL is dragged to the addressbar from page content, the displayed URL can be spoofed to show a different site than the one loaded. This allows for phishing attacks where a malicious page can spoof the identify of another site. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5111|2024-08-05T05:26:46.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5168|2024-08-05T05:26:46.983Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5168</link>
      <description>Sites can bypass security checks on permissions to install lightweight themes by manipulating the "baseURI" property of the theme element. This could allow a malicious site to install a theme without user interaction which could contain offensive or embarrassing images. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.8, Thunderbird ESR &lt; 52.8, Firefox &lt; 60, and Firefox ESR &lt; 52.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5168|2024-08-05T05:26:46.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12378|2024-08-05T08:30:59.829Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12378</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur when an IndexedDB index is deleted while still in use by JavaScript code that is providing payload values to be stored. This results in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 62, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.2, and Thunderbird &lt; 60.2.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12378|2024-08-05T08:30:59.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17018|2024-08-05T01:24:48.756Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17018</link>
      <description>When in Private Browsing Mode on Windows 10, the Windows keyboard may retain word suggestions to improve the accuracy of the keyboard. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 72.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17018|2024-08-05T01:24:48.756Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12373|2024-08-05T08:31:00.267Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12373</link>
      <description>dDecrypted S/MIME parts hidden with CSS or the plaintext HTML tag can leak plaintext when included in a HTML reply/forward. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12373|2024-08-05T08:31:00.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5158|2024-08-05T05:26:47.026Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5158</link>
      <description>The PDF viewer does not sufficiently sanitize PostScript calculator functions, allowing malicious JavaScript to be injected through a crafted PDF file. This JavaScript can then be run with the permissions of the PDF viewer by its worker. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 52.8 and Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5158|2024-08-05T05:26:47.026Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12370|2024-08-05T08:30:59.694Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12370</link>
      <description>In Reader View SameSite cookie protections are not checked on exiting. This allows for a payload to be triggered when Reader View is exited if loaded by a malicious site while Reader mode is active, bypassing CSRF protections. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 61.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12370|2024-08-05T08:30:59.694Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17012|2024-08-05T01:24:48.674Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17012</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 70 and Firefox ESR 68.2. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.3, Firefox ESR &lt; 68.3, and Firefox &lt; 71.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17012|2024-08-05T01:24:48.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:24:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17005|2024-08-05T01:24:48.626Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17005</link>
      <description>The plain text serializer used a fixed-size array for the number of &lt;ol&gt; elements it could process; however it was possible to overflow the static-sized array leading to memory corruption and a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.3, Firefox ESR &lt; 68.3, and Firefox &lt; 71.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17005|2024-08-05T01:24:48.626Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5095|2024-08-05T05:26:46.649Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5095</link>
      <description>An integer overflow vulnerability in the Skia library when allocating memory for edge builders on some systems with at least 8 GB of RAM. This results in the use of uninitialized memory, resulting in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.6, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.6, and Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5095|2024-08-05T05:26:46.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5105|2024-08-05T05:26:46.665Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5105</link>
      <description>WebExtensions can bypass user prompts to first save and then open an arbitrarily downloaded file. This can result in an executable file running with local user privileges without explicit user consent. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5105|2024-08-05T05:26:46.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5100|2024-08-05T05:26:46.808Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5100</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur when arguments passed to the "IsPotentiallyScrollable" function are freed while still in use by scripts. This results in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5100|2024-08-05T05:26:46.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5133|2024-08-05T05:26:46.987Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5133</link>
      <description>If the "app.support.baseURL" preference is changed by a malicious local program to contain HTML and script content, this content is not sanitized. It will be executed if a user loads "chrome://browser/content/preferences/in-content/preferences.xul" directly in a tab and executes a search. This stored preference is also executed whenever an EME video player plugin displays a CDM-disabled message as a notification message. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 59.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5133|2024-08-05T05:26:46.987Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5099|2024-08-05T05:26:46.818Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5099</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur when the widget listener is holding strong references to browser objects that have previously been freed, resulting in a potentially exploitable crash when these references are used. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 52.6, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.6, and Firefox &lt; 58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5099|2024-08-05T05:26:46.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5170|2024-08-05T05:26:47.040Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5170</link>
      <description>It is possible to spoof the filename of an attachment and display an arbitrary attachment name. This could lead to a user opening a remote attachment which is a different file type than expected. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird ESR &lt; 52.8 and Thunderbird &lt; 52.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5170|2024-08-05T05:26:47.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12360|2024-08-05T08:30:59.673Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12360</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability can occur when deleting an input element during a mutation event handler triggered by focusing that element. This results in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 60, Thunderbird &lt; 52.9, Firefox ESR &lt; 60.1, Firefox ESR &lt; 52.9, and Firefox &lt; 61.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12360|2024-08-05T08:30:59.673Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5177|2024-08-05T05:26:46.996Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5177</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in XSLT during number formatting where a negative buffer size may be allocated in some instances, leading to a buffer overflow and crash if it occurs. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 60.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5177|2024-08-05T05:26:46.996Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12381|2024-08-05T08:30:59.932Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12381</link>
      <description>Manually dragging and dropping an Outlook email message into the browser will trigger a page navigation when the message's mail columns are incorrectly interpreted as a URL. *Note: this issue only affects Windows operating systems with Outlook installed. Other operating systems are not affected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 60.2 and Firefox &lt; 62.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12381|2024-08-05T08:30:59.932Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2613|2024-08-02T19:44:01.782Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2613</link>
      <description>Data was not properly sanitized when decoding a QUIC ACK frame; this could have led to unrestricted memory consumption and a crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2613|2024-08-02T19:44:01.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5388|2024-08-02T07:59:43.260Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5388</link>
      <description>NSS was susceptible to a timing side-channel attack when performing RSA decryption. This attack could potentially allow an attacker to recover the private data. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5388|2024-08-02T07:59:43.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31392|2024-08-02T01:52:56.841Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31392</link>
      <description>If an insecure element was added to a page after a delay, Firefox would not replace the secure icon with a mixed content security status This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31392|2024-08-02T01:52:56.841Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31393|2024-08-02T01:52:56.878Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31393</link>
      <description>Dragging Javascript URLs to the address bar could cause them to be loaded, bypassing restrictions and security protections This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31393|2024-08-02T01:52:56.878Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26282|2024-08-02T00:07:19.173Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26282</link>
      <description>Using an AMP url with a canonical element, an attacker could have executed JavaScript from an opened bookmarked page. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26282|2024-08-02T00:07:19.173Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26281|2024-08-02T00:07:19.537Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26281</link>
      <description>Upon scanning a JavaScript URI with the QR code scanner, an attacker could have executed unauthorized scripts on the current top origin sites in the URL bar. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26281|2024-08-02T00:07:19.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26283|2024-08-02T00:07:19.281Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26283</link>
      <description>An attacker could have executed unauthorized scripts on top origin sites using a JavaScript URI when opening an external URL with a custom Firefox scheme. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26283|2024-08-02T00:07:19.281Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26284|2024-08-02T00:07:19.131Z -- mozilla -- focus%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26284</link>
      <description>Utilizing a 302 redirect, an attacker could have conducted a Universal Cross-Site Scripting (UXSS) on a victim website, if the victim had a link to the attacker's website. This vulnerability affects Focus for iOS &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26284|2024-08-02T00:07:19.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6604|2024-08-01T21:41:03.940Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6604</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 127, Firefox ESR 115.12, and Thunderbird 115.12. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6604|2024-08-01T21:41:03.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5698|2024-08-01T21:18:06.985Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5698</link>
      <description>By manipulating the fullscreen feature while opening a data-list, an attacker could have overlaid a text box over the address bar. This could have led to user confusion and possible spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5698|2024-08-01T21:18:06.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5702|2024-08-01T21:18:06.890Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5702</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in the networking stack could have led to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5702|2024-08-01T21:18:06.890Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5699|2024-08-01T21:18:06.876Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5699</link>
      <description>In violation of spec, cookie prefixes such as `__Secure` were being ignored if they were not correctly capitalized - by spec they should be checked with a case-insensitive comparison. This could have resulted in the browser not correctly honoring the behaviors specified by the prefix. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5699|2024-08-01T21:18:06.876Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5695|2024-08-01T21:18:06.986Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5695</link>
      <description>If an out-of-memory condition occurs at a specific point using allocations in the probabilistic heap checker, an assertion could have been triggered, and in rarer situations, memory corruption could have occurred. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5695|2024-08-01T21:18:06.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6615|2024-08-01T21:41:04.046Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6615</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 127 and Thunderbird 127. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6615|2024-08-01T21:41:04.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6601|2024-08-01T21:41:03.971Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6601</link>
      <description>A race condition could lead to a cross-origin container obtaining permissions of the top-level origin. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6601|2024-08-01T21:41:03.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5690|2024-08-01T21:18:06.700Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5690</link>
      <description>By monitoring the time certain operations take, an attacker could have guessed which external protocol handlers were functional on a user's system. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5690|2024-08-01T21:18:06.700Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5692|2024-08-01T21:18:06.916Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5692</link>
      <description>On Windows 10, when using the 'Save As' functionality, an attacker could have tricked the browser into saving the file with a disallowed extension such as `.url` by including an invalid character in the extension. *Note:* This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5692|2024-08-01T21:18:06.916Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6613|2024-08-01T21:41:03.948Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6613</link>
      <description>The frame iterator could get stuck in a loop when encountering certain wasm frames leading to incorrect stack traces. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6613|2024-08-01T21:41:03.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5697|2024-08-01T21:18:06.946Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5697</link>
      <description>A website was able to detect when a user took a screenshot of a page using the built-in Screenshot functionality in Firefox. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5697|2024-08-01T21:18:06.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6614|2024-08-01T21:41:03.989Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6614</link>
      <description>The frame iterator could get stuck in a loop when encountering certain wasm frames leading to incorrect stack traces. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6614|2024-08-01T21:41:03.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5691|2024-08-01T21:18:06.913Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5691</link>
      <description>By tricking the browser with a `X-Frame-Options` header, a sandboxed iframe could have presented a button that, if clicked by a user, would bypass restrictions to open a new window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5691|2024-08-01T21:18:06.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5689|2024-08-01T21:18:06.829Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5689</link>
      <description>In addition to detecting when a user was taking a screenshot (XXX), a website was able to overlay the 'My Shots' button that appeared, and direct the user to a replica Firefox Screenshots page that could be used for phishing. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5689|2024-08-01T21:18:06.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5694|2024-08-01T21:18:06.830Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5694</link>
      <description>An attacker could have caused a use-after-free in the JavaScript engine to read memory in the JavaScript string section of the heap. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5694|2024-08-01T21:18:06.830Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6607|2024-08-01T21:41:03.973Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6607</link>
      <description>It was possible to prevent a user from exiting pointerlock when pressing escape and to overlay customValidity notifications from a `&amp;lt;select&amp;gt;` element over certain permission prompts. This could be used to confuse a user into giving a site unintended permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6607|2024-08-01T21:41:03.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5696|2024-08-01T21:18:07.014Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5696</link>
      <description>By manipulating the text in an `&amp;lt;input&amp;gt;` tag, an attacker could have caused corrupt memory leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5696|2024-08-01T21:18:07.014Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6605|2024-08-01T21:41:04.045Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6605</link>
      <description>Firefox Android allowed immediate interaction with permission prompts. This could be used for tapjacking. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6605|2024-08-01T21:41:04.045Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5701|2024-08-01T21:18:06.997Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5701</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 126. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5701|2024-08-01T21:18:06.997Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5693|2024-08-01T21:18:06.938Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5693</link>
      <description>Offscreen Canvas did not properly track cross-origin tainting, which could be used to access image data from another site in violation of same-origin policy. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5693|2024-08-01T21:18:06.938Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6609|2024-08-01T21:41:03.946Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6609</link>
      <description>When almost out-of-memory an elliptic curve key which was never allocated could have been freed again. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6609|2024-08-01T21:41:03.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5687|2024-08-01T21:18:06.882Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5687</link>
      <description>If a specific sequence of actions is performed when opening a new tab, the triggering principal associated with the new tab may have been incorrect. The triggering principal is used to calculate many values, including the `Referer` and `Sec-*` headers, meaning there is the potential for incorrect security checks within the browser in addition to incorrect or misleading information sent to remote websites.
*This bug only affects Firefox for Android. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5687|2024-08-01T21:18:06.882Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6610|2024-08-01T21:41:03.956Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6610</link>
      <description>Form validation popups could capture escape key presses. Therefore, spamming form validation messages could be used to prevent users from exiting full-screen mode. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6610|2024-08-01T21:41:03.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6608|2024-08-01T21:41:04.019Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6608</link>
      <description>It was possible to move the cursor using pointerlock from an iframe. This allowed moving the cursor outside of the viewport and the Firefox window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6608|2024-08-01T21:41:04.019Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5700|2024-08-01T21:18:07.031Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5700</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 126, Firefox ESR 115.11, and Thunderbird 115.11. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5700|2024-08-01T21:18:07.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6612|2024-08-01T21:41:04.060Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6612</link>
      <description>CSP violations generated links in the console tab of the developer tools, pointing to the violating resource. This caused a DNS prefetch which leaked that a CSP violation happened. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6612|2024-08-01T21:41:04.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6602|2024-08-01T21:41:03.998Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6602</link>
      <description>A mismatch between allocator and deallocator could have lead to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6602|2024-08-01T21:41:03.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6606|2024-08-01T21:41:04.043Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6606</link>
      <description>Clipboard code failed to check the index on an array access. This could have lead to an out-of-bounds read. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6606|2024-08-01T21:41:04.043Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6611|2024-08-01T21:41:04.049Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6611</link>
      <description>A nested iframe, triggering a cross-site navigation, could send SameSite=Strict or Lax cookies. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6611|2024-08-01T21:41:04.049Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6600|2024-08-01T21:41:03.960Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6600</link>
      <description>Due to large allocation checks in Angle for GLSL shaders being too lenient an out-of-bounds access could occur when allocating more than 8192 ints in private shader memory on mac OS. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6600|2024-08-01T21:41:03.960Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6603|2024-08-01T21:41:04.040Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6603</link>
      <description>In an out-of-memory scenario an allocation could fail but free would have been called on the pointer afterwards leading to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6603|2024-08-01T21:41:04.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5688|2024-08-01T21:18:07.039Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5688</link>
      <description>If a garbage collection was triggered at the right time, a use-after-free could have occurred during object transplant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5688|2024-08-01T21:18:07.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2609|2024-08-01T19:18:48.164Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2609</link>
      <description>The permission prompt input delay could expire while the window is not in focus. This makes it vulnerable to clickjacking by malicious websites. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2609|2024-08-01T19:18:48.164Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2613|2024-08-01T19:18:48.218Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2613</link>
      <description>Data was not properly sanitized when decoding a QUIC ACK frame; this could have led to unrestricted memory consumption and a crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2613|2024-08-01T19:18:48.218Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2612|2024-08-01T19:18:47.923Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2612</link>
      <description>If an attacker could find a way to trigger a particular code path in `SafeRefPtr`, it could have triggered a crash or potentially be leveraged to achieve code execution. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2612|2024-08-01T19:18:47.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2616|2024-08-01T19:18:48.123Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2616</link>
      <description>To harden ICU against exploitation, the behavior for out-of-memory conditions was changed to crash instead of attempt to continue. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9 and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2616|2024-08-01T19:18:48.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2606|2024-08-01T19:18:48.194Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2606</link>
      <description>Passing invalid data could have led to invalid wasm values being created, such as arbitrary integers turning into pointer values. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2606|2024-08-01T19:18:48.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2614|2024-08-01T19:18:48.251Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2614</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 123, Firefox ESR 115.8, and Thunderbird 115.8. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2614|2024-08-01T19:18:48.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2607|2024-08-01T19:18:48.107Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2607</link>
      <description>Return registers were overwritten which could have allowed an attacker to execute arbitrary code. *Note:* This issue only affected Armv7-A systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2607|2024-08-01T19:18:48.107Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2615|2024-08-01T19:18:47.946Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2615</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 123. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2615|2024-08-01T19:18:47.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2608|2024-08-01T19:18:48.282Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2608</link>
      <description>`AppendEncodedAttributeValue(), ExtraSpaceNeededForAttrEncoding()` and `AppendEncodedCharacters()` could have experienced integer overflows, causing underallocation of an output buffer leading to an out of bounds write. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2608|2024-08-01T19:18:48.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2605|2024-08-01T19:18:48.230Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2605</link>
      <description>An attacker could have leveraged the Windows Error Reporter to run arbitrary code on the system escaping the sandbox. *Note:* This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2605|2024-08-01T19:18:48.230Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2611|2024-08-01T19:18:47.977Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2611</link>
      <description>A missing delay on when pointer lock was used could have allowed a malicious page to trick a user into granting permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2611|2024-08-01T19:18:47.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2610|2024-08-01T19:18:47.766Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2610</link>
      <description>Using a markup injection an attacker could have stolen nonce values. This could have been used to bypass strict content security policies. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2610|2024-08-01T19:18:47.766Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3860|2024-07-30T19:53:06.739Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3860</link>
      <description>An out-of-memory condition during object initialization could result in an empty shape list. If the JIT subsequently traced the object it would crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3860|2024-07-30T19:53:06.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3864|2024-07-24T19:40:13.901Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3864</link>
      <description>Memory safety bug present in Firefox 124, Firefox ESR 115.9, and Thunderbird 115.9. This bug showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort this could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3864|2024-07-24T19:40:13.901Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4770|2024-07-23T16:32:22.116Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4770</link>
      <description>When saving a page to PDF, certain font styles could have led to a potential use-after-free crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4770|2024-07-23T16:32:22.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4773|2024-07-23T16:35:01.918Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4773</link>
      <description>When a network error occurred during page load, the prior content could have remained in view with a blank URL bar. This could have been used to obfuscate a spoofed web site. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4773|2024-07-23T16:35:01.918Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6607|2024-07-17T20:21:05.514Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6607</link>
      <description>It was possible to prevent a user from exiting pointerlock when pressing escape and to overlay customValidity notifications from a `&amp;lt;select&amp;gt;` element over certain permission prompts. This could be used to confuse a user into giving a site unintended permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6607|2024-07-17T20:21:05.514Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6605|2024-07-17T15:22:59.569Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6605</link>
      <description>Firefox Android allowed immediate interaction with permission prompts. This could be used for tapjacking. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6605|2024-07-17T15:22:59.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5022|2024-07-16T12:58:14.617Z -- mozilla -- focus%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5022</link>
      <description>The file scheme of URLs would be hidden, resulting in potential spoofing of a website's address in the location bar This vulnerability affects Focus for iOS &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5022|2024-07-16T12:58:14.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 18:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6614|2024-07-11T17:22:27.889Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6614</link>
      <description>The frame iterator could get stuck in a loop when encountering certain wasm frames leading to incorrect stack traces. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6614|2024-07-11T17:22:27.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6612|2024-07-10T21:06:25.324Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6612</link>
      <description>CSP violations generated links in the console tab of the developer tools, pointing to the violating resource. This caused a DNS prefetch which leaked that a CSP violation happened. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6612|2024-07-10T21:06:25.324Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29943|2024-07-10T19:34:41.151Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29943</link>
      <description>An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript object by fooling range-based bounds check elimination. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29943|2024-07-10T19:34:41.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6606|2024-07-10T14:18:43.636Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6606</link>
      <description>Clipboard code failed to check the index on an array access. This could have lead to an out-of-bounds read. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6606|2024-07-10T14:18:43.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6612|2024-07-09T14:26:00.305Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6612</link>
      <description>CSP violations generated links in the console tab of the developer tools, pointing to the violating resource. This caused a DNS prefetch which leaked that a CSP violation happened. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6612|2024-07-09T14:26:00.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6606|2024-07-09T14:25:58.357Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6606</link>
      <description>Clipboard code failed to check the index on an array access. This could have lead to an out-of-bounds read. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6606|2024-07-09T14:25:58.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6600|2024-07-09T14:25:56.437Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6600</link>
      <description>Due to large allocation checks in Angle for GLSL shaders being too lenient an out-of-bounds access could occur when allocating more than 8192 ints in private shader memory on mac OS. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6600|2024-07-09T14:25:56.437Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6613|2024-07-09T14:26:00.593Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6613</link>
      <description>The frame iterator could get stuck in a loop when encountering certain wasm frames leading to incorrect stack traces. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6613|2024-07-09T14:26:00.593Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6605|2024-07-09T14:25:57.930Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6605</link>
      <description>Firefox Android allowed immediate interaction with permission prompts. This could be used for tapjacking. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6605|2024-07-09T14:25:57.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6611|2024-07-09T14:25:59.748Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6611</link>
      <description>A nested iframe, triggering a cross-site navigation, could send SameSite=Strict or Lax cookies. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6611|2024-07-09T14:25:59.748Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6610|2024-07-09T14:25:59.460Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6610</link>
      <description>Form validation popups could capture escape key presses. Therefore, spamming form validation messages could be used to prevent users from exiting full-screen mode. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6610|2024-07-09T14:25:59.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6603|2024-07-09T14:25:57.402Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6603</link>
      <description>In an out-of-memory scenario an allocation could fail but free would have been called on the pointer afterwards leading to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6603|2024-07-09T14:25:57.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6609|2024-07-09T14:25:59.075Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6609</link>
      <description>When almost out-of-memory an elliptic curve key which was never allocated could have been freed again. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6609|2024-07-09T14:25:59.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6604|2024-07-09T14:25:57.691Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6604</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 127, Firefox ESR 115.12, and Thunderbird 115.12. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6604|2024-07-09T14:25:57.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6615|2024-07-09T14:26:01.065Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6615</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 127. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6615|2024-07-09T14:26:01.065Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6602|2024-07-09T14:25:57.026Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6602</link>
      <description>A mismatch between allocator and deallocator could have lead to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6602|2024-07-09T14:25:57.026Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6608|2024-07-09T14:25:58.862Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6608</link>
      <description>It was possible to move the cursor using pointerlock from an iframe. This allowed moving the cursor outside of the viewport and the Firefox window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6608|2024-07-09T14:25:58.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6601|2024-07-09T14:25:56.733Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6601</link>
      <description>A race condition could lead to a cross-origin container obtaining permissions of the top-level origin. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6601|2024-07-09T14:25:56.733Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6607|2024-07-09T14:25:58.566Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6607</link>
      <description>It was possible to prevent a user from exiting pointerlock when pressing escape and to overlay customValidity notifications from a `&amp;lt;select&amp;gt;` element over certain permission prompts. This could be used to confuse a user into giving a site unintended permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6607|2024-07-09T14:25:58.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6614|2024-07-09T14:26:00.836Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6614</link>
      <description>The frame iterator could get stuck in a loop when encountering certain wasm frames leading to incorrect stack traces. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6614|2024-07-09T14:26:00.836Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29943|2024-07-03T03:55:12.405Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29943</link>
      <description>An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript object by fooling range-based bounds check elimination. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29943|2024-07-03T03:55:12.405Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-21T16:52:03.765Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5688</link>
      <description>If a garbage collection was triggered at the right time, a use-after-free could have occurred during object transplant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-21T16:52:03.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-14T03:55:35.603Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5690</link>
      <description>By monitoring the time certain operations take, an attacker could have guessed which external protocol handlers were functional on a user's system. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-14T03:55:35.603Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5689|2024-06-14T03:55:34.783Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5689</link>
      <description>In addition to detecting when a user was taking a screenshot (XXX), a website was able to overlay the 'My Shots' button that appeared, and direct the user to a replica Firefox Screenshots page that could be used for phishing. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5689|2024-06-14T03:55:34.783Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-14T03:55:33.281Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5688</link>
      <description>If a garbage collection was triggered at the right time, a use-after-free could have occurred during object transplant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-14T03:55:33.281Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5699|2024-06-14T03:55:41.870Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5699</link>
      <description>In violation of spec, cookie prefixes such as `__Secure` were being ignored if they were not correctly capitalized - by spec they should be checked with a case-insensitive comparison. This could have resulted in the browser not correctly honoring the behaviors specified by the prefix. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5699|2024-06-14T03:55:41.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5697|2024-06-14T03:55:41.098Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5697</link>
      <description>A website was able to detect when a user took a screenshot of a page using the built-in Screenshot functionality in Firefox. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5697|2024-06-14T03:55:41.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-14T03:55:38.688Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5693</link>
      <description>Offscreen Canvas did not properly track cross-origin tainting, which could be used to access image data from another site in violation of same-origin policy. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-14T03:55:38.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5694|2024-06-14T03:55:34.030Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5694</link>
      <description>An attacker could have caused a use-after-free in the JavaScript engine to read memory in the JavaScript string section of the heap. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5694|2024-06-14T03:55:34.030Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5692|2024-06-14T03:55:37.156Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5692</link>
      <description>On Windows 10, when using the 'Save As' functionality, an attacker could have tricked the browser into saving the file with a disallowed extension such as `.url` by including an invalid character in the extension. *Note:* This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5692|2024-06-14T03:55:37.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5696|2024-06-14T03:55:40.349Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5696</link>
      <description>By manipulating the text in an `&amp;lt;input&amp;gt;` tag, an attacker could have caused corrupt memory leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5696|2024-06-14T03:55:40.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5701|2024-06-14T03:55:43.507Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5701</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 126. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5701|2024-06-14T03:55:43.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5702|2024-06-14T03:55:44.267Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5702</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in the networking stack could have led to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5702|2024-06-14T03:55:44.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-14T03:55:36.444Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5691</link>
      <description>By tricking the browser with a `X-Frame-Options` header, a sandboxed iframe could have presented a button that, if clicked by a user, would bypass restrictions to open a new window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-14T03:55:36.444Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-14T03:55:42.740Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5700</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 126, Firefox ESR 115.11, and Thunderbird 115.11. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-14T03:55:42.740Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5695|2024-06-14T03:55:39.501Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5695</link>
      <description>If an out-of-memory condition occurs at a specific point using allocations in the probabilistic heap checker, an assertion could have been triggered, and in rarer situations, memory corruption could have occurred. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5695|2024-06-14T03:55:39.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38312|2024-06-13T20:01:13.543Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38312</link>
      <description>When browsing private tabs, some data related to location history or webpage thumbnails could be persisted incorrectly within the sandboxed app bundle after app termination This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38312|2024-06-13T20:01:13.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 20:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38313|2024-06-13T20:01:13.281Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38313</link>
      <description>In certain scenarios a malicious website could attempt to display a fake location URL bar which could mislead users as to the actual website address This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38313|2024-06-13T20:01:13.281Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 20:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5698|2024-06-12T19:40:15.526Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5698</link>
      <description>By manipulating the fullscreen feature while opening a data-list, an attacker could have overlaid a text box over the address bar. This could have led to user confusion and possible spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5698|2024-06-12T19:40:15.526Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-12T19:45:38.636Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5688</link>
      <description>If a garbage collection was triggered at the right time, a use-after-free could have occurred during object transplant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-12T19:45:38.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-12T15:52:36.652Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5693</link>
      <description>Offscreen Canvas did not properly track cross-origin tainting, which could be used to access image data from another site in violation of same-origin policy. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-12T15:52:36.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4772|2024-06-12T15:37:16.323Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4772</link>
      <description>An HTTP digest authentication nonce value was generated using `rand()` which could lead to predictable values. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4772|2024-06-12T15:37:16.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4768|2024-06-12T15:38:50.583Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4768</link>
      <description>A bug in popup notifications' interaction with WebAuthn made it easier for an attacker to trick a user into granting permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4768|2024-06-12T15:38:50.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2616|2024-03-19T12:02:58.997Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2616</link>
      <description>To harden ICU against exploitation, the behavior for out-of-memory conditions was changed to crash instead of attempt to continue. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9 and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2616|2024-03-19T12:02:58.997Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2611|2024-03-19T12:02:55.649Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2611</link>
      <description>A missing delay on when pointer lock was used could have allowed a malicious page to trick a user into granting permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2611|2024-03-19T12:02:55.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2607|2024-03-19T12:02:52.932Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2607</link>
      <description>Return registers were overwritten which could have allowed an attacker to execute arbitrary code. *Note:* This issue only affected Armv7-A systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2607|2024-03-19T12:02:52.932Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2606|2024-06-04T17:29:45.735Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2606</link>
      <description>Passing invalid data could have led to invalid wasm values being created, such as arbitrary integers turning into pointer values. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2606|2024-06-04T17:29:45.735Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2610|2024-03-19T12:02:55.079Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2610</link>
      <description>Using a markup injection an attacker could have stolen nonce values. This could have been used to bypass strict content security policies. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2610|2024-03-19T12:02:55.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2609|2024-04-19T16:50:48.947Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2609</link>
      <description>The permission prompt input delay could expire while the window is not in focus. This makes it vulnerable to clickjacking by malicious websites. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2609|2024-04-19T16:50:48.947Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2605|2024-03-19T12:02:51.825Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2605</link>
      <description>An attacker could have leveraged the Windows Error Reporter to run arbitrary code on the system escaping the sandbox. *Note:* This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2605|2024-03-19T12:02:51.825Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2613|2024-03-19T12:02:56.741Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2613</link>
      <description>Data was not properly sanitized when decoding a QUIC ACK frame; this could have led to unrestricted memory consumption and a crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2613|2024-03-19T12:02:56.741Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2612|2024-03-19T12:02:56.196Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2612</link>
      <description>If an attacker could find a way to trigger a particular code path in `SafeRefPtr`, it could have triggered a crash or potentially be leveraged to achieve code execution. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2612|2024-03-19T12:02:56.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2608|2024-03-19T12:02:53.467Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2608</link>
      <description>`AppendEncodedAttributeValue(), ExtraSpaceNeededForAttrEncoding()` and `AppendEncodedCharacters()` could have experienced integer overflows, causing underallocation of an output buffer leading to an out of bounds write. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2608|2024-03-19T12:02:53.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2615|2024-03-19T19:07:24.248Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2615</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 123. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2615|2024-03-19T19:07:24.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2614|2024-03-19T12:02:57.272Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2614</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 123, Firefox ESR 115.8, and Thunderbird 115.8. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2614|2024-03-19T12:02:57.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3856|2024-04-16T15:14:06.623Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3856</link>
      <description>A use-after-free could occur during WASM execution if garbage collection ran during the creation of an array. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3856|2024-04-16T15:14:06.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3860|2024-04-16T15:14:07.848Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3860</link>
      <description>An out-of-memory condition during object initialization could result in an empty shape list. If the JIT subsequently traced the object it would crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3860|2024-04-16T15:14:07.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3861|2024-06-11T12:40:15.856Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3861</link>
      <description>If an AlignedBuffer were assigned to itself, the subsequent self-move could result in an incorrect reference count and later use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3861|2024-06-11T12:40:15.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3857|2024-06-11T12:40:15.302Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3857</link>
      <description>The JIT created incorrect code for arguments in certain cases. This led to potential use-after-free crashes during garbage collection. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3857|2024-06-11T12:40:15.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3302|2024-06-11T12:40:16.505Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3302</link>
      <description>There was no limit to the number of HTTP/2 CONTINUATION frames that would be processed. A server could abuse this to create an Out of Memory condition in the browser. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3302|2024-06-11T12:40:16.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3864|2024-04-24T09:21:23.741Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3864</link>
      <description>Memory safety bug present in Firefox 124, Firefox ESR 115.9, and Thunderbird 115.9. This bug showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort this could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3864|2024-04-24T09:21:23.741Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3852|2024-06-11T12:40:14.586Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3852</link>
      <description>GetBoundName could return the wrong version of an object when JIT optimizations were applied. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3852|2024-06-11T12:40:14.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3853|2024-06-11T12:40:18.950Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3853</link>
      <description>A use-after-free could result if a JavaScript realm was in the process of being initialized when a garbage collection started. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3853|2024-06-11T12:40:18.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3865|2024-04-16T15:14:09.894Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3865</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 124. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3865|2024-04-16T15:14:09.894Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3854|2024-06-11T12:40:14.871Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3854</link>
      <description>In some code patterns the JIT incorrectly optimized switch statements and generated code with out-of-bounds-reads. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3854|2024-06-11T12:40:14.871Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3858|2024-04-16T15:14:07.244Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3858</link>
      <description>It was possible to mutate a JavaScript object so that the JIT could crash while tracing it. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3858|2024-04-16T15:14:07.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3862|2024-04-16T15:14:08.672Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3862</link>
      <description>The MarkStack assignment operator, part of the JavaScript engine, could access uninitialized memory if it were used in a self-assignment. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3862|2024-04-16T15:14:08.672Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3863|2024-06-11T12:40:16.167Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3863</link>
      <description>The executable file warning was not presented when downloading .xrm-ms files.  
*Note: This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3863|2024-06-11T12:40:16.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3859|2024-06-11T12:40:15.584Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3859</link>
      <description>On 32-bit versions there were integer-overflows that led to an out-of-bounds-read that potentially could be triggered by a malformed OpenType font. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3859|2024-06-11T12:40:15.584Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3855|2024-04-16T15:14:06.282Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3855</link>
      <description>In certain cases the JIT incorrectly optimized MSubstr operations, which led to out-of-bounds reads. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3855|2024-04-16T15:14:06.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31392|2024-06-04T17:36:41.520Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31392</link>
      <description>If an insecure element was added to a page after a delay, Firefox would not replace the secure icon with a mixed content security status This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31392|2024-06-04T17:36:41.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31393|2024-06-04T17:37:00.516Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31393</link>
      <description>Dragging Javascript URLs to the address bar could cause them to be loaded, bypassing restrictions and security protections This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31393|2024-06-04T17:37:00.516Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26281|2024-02-22T14:56:45.803Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-26281</link>
      <description>Upon scanning a JavaScript URI with the QR code scanner, an attacker could have executed unauthorized scripts on the current top origin sites in the URL bar. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26281|2024-02-22T14:56:45.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26284|2024-06-10T20:06:36.338Z -- mozilla -- focus%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-26284</link>
      <description>Utilizing a 302 redirect, an attacker could have conducted a Universal Cross-Site Scripting (UXSS) on a victim website, if the victim had a link to the attacker's website. This vulnerability affects Focus for iOS &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26284|2024-06-10T20:06:36.338Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26282|2024-02-22T14:56:44.758Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-26282</link>
      <description>Using an AMP url with a canonical element, an attacker could have executed JavaScript from an opened bookmarked page. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26282|2024-02-22T14:56:44.758Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26283|2024-02-22T14:56:43.860Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-26283</link>
      <description>An attacker could have executed unauthorized scripts on top origin sites using a JavaScript URI when opening an external URL with a custom Firefox scheme. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26283|2024-02-22T14:56:43.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4777|2024-05-14T17:21:24.864Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4777</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 125, Firefox ESR 115.10, and Thunderbird 115.10. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4777|2024-05-14T17:21:24.864Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4367|2024-05-14T17:21:23.486Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4367</link>
      <description>A type check was missing when handling fonts in PDF.js, which would allow arbitrary JavaScript execution in the PDF.js context. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4367|2024-05-14T17:21:23.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4776|2024-06-04T17:53:32.797Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4776</link>
      <description>A file dialog shown while in full-screen mode could have resulted in the window remaining disabled. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4776|2024-06-04T17:53:32.797Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4771|2024-06-06T19:52:20.334Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4771</link>
      <description>A memory allocation check was missing which would lead to a use-after-free if the allocation failed. This could have triggered a crash or potentially be leveraged to achieve code execution. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4771|2024-06-06T19:52:20.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4767|2024-05-14T17:21:23.746Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4767</link>
      <description>If the `browser.privatebrowsing.autostart` preference is enabled, IndexedDB files were not properly deleted when the window was closed. This preference is disabled by default in Firefox. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4767|2024-05-14T17:21:23.746Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4766|2024-06-04T17:54:37.373Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4766</link>
      <description>Different techniques existed to obscure the fullscreen notification in Firefox for Android.  These could have lead to potential user confusion and spoofing attacks.
*This bug only affects Firefox for Android. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4766|2024-06-04T17:54:37.373Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4770|2024-05-14T17:21:24.594Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4770</link>
      <description>When saving a page to PDF, certain font styles could have led to a potential use-after-free crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4770|2024-05-14T17:21:24.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4765|2024-05-14T17:21:25.339Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4765</link>
      <description>Web application manifests were stored by using an insecure MD5 hash which allowed for a hash collision to overwrite another application's manifest. This could have been exploited to run arbitrary code in another application's context. 
*This issue only affects Firefox for Android. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4765|2024-05-14T17:21:25.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4773|2024-05-14T17:21:26.363Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4773</link>
      <description>When a network error occurred during page load, the prior content could have remained in view with a blank URL bar. This could have been used to obfuscate a spoofed web site. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4773|2024-05-14T17:21:26.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4769|2024-05-14T17:21:24.318Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4769</link>
      <description>When importing resources using Web Workers, error messages would distinguish the difference between `application/javascript` responses and non-script responses.  This could have been abused to learn information cross-origin. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4769|2024-05-14T17:21:24.318Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4768|2024-05-14T17:21:24.047Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4768</link>
      <description>A bug in popup notifications' interaction with WebAuthn made it easier for an attacker to trick a user into granting permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4768|2024-05-14T17:21:24.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4772|2024-05-14T17:21:26.111Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4772</link>
      <description>An HTTP digest authentication nonce value was generated using `rand()` which could lead to predictable values. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4772|2024-05-14T17:21:26.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4764|2024-06-04T17:55:43.516Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4764</link>
      <description>Multiple WebRTC threads could have claimed a newly connected audio input leading to use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4764|2024-06-04T17:55:43.516Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4775|2024-06-04T17:56:05.266Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4775</link>
      <description>An iterator stop condition was missing when handling WASM code in the built-in profiler, potentially leading to invalid memory access and undefined behavior. *Note:* This issue only affects the application when the profiler is running. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4775|2024-06-04T17:56:05.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4774|2024-05-14T17:21:26.609Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4774</link>
      <description>The `ShmemCharMapHashEntry()` code was susceptible to potentially undefined behavior by bypassing the move semantics for one of its data members. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4774|2024-05-14T17:21:26.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4778|2024-06-04T17:56:34.311Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4778</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 125. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4778|2024-06-04T17:56:34.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29944|2024-03-22T16:18:28.977Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29944</link>
      <description>An attacker was able to inject an event handler into a privileged object that would allow arbitrary JavaScript execution in the parent process. Note: This vulnerability affects Desktop Firefox only, it does not affect mobile versions of Firefox. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.0.1 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29944|2024-03-22T16:18:28.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29943|2024-03-22T12:55:39.866Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29943</link>
      <description>An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript object by fooling range-based bounds check elimination. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29943|2024-03-22T12:55:39.866Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1555|2024-06-04T17:59:28.932Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1555</link>
      <description>When opening a website using the `firefox://` protocol handler, SameSite cookies were not properly respected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1555|2024-06-04T17:59:28.932Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1563|2024-02-22T14:56:42.888Z -- mozilla -- focus%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1563</link>
      <description>An attacker could have executed unauthorized scripts on top origin sites using a JavaScript URI when opening an external URL with a custom Firefox scheme and a timeout race condition. This vulnerability affects Focus for iOS &lt; 122.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1563|2024-02-22T14:56:42.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1554|2024-02-20T13:21:37.414Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1554</link>
      <description>The `fetch()` API and navigation incorrectly shared the same cache, as the cache key did not include the optional headers `fetch()` may contain.  Under the correct circumstances, an attacker may have been able to poison the local browser cache by priming it with a `fetch()` response controlled by the additional headers. Upon navigation to the same URL, the user would see the cached response instead of the expected response. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1554|2024-02-20T13:21:37.414Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1549|2024-02-20T19:23:35.141Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1549</link>
      <description>If a website set a large custom cursor, portions of the cursor could have overlapped with the permission dialog, potentially resulting in user confusion and unexpected granted permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1549|2024-02-20T19:23:35.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1553|2024-02-20T19:23:41.022Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1553</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 122, Firefox ESR 115.7, and Thunderbird 115.7. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1553|2024-02-20T19:23:41.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1552|2024-02-20T19:23:39.596Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1552</link>
      <description>Incorrect code generation could have led to unexpected numeric conversions and potential undefined behavior.*Note:* This issue only affects 32-bit ARM devices. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1552|2024-02-20T19:23:39.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1548|2024-02-20T19:23:33.739Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1548</link>
      <description>A website could have obscured the fullscreen notification by using a dropdown select input element. This could have led to user confusion and possible spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1548|2024-02-20T19:23:33.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1551|2024-02-20T19:23:38.186Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1551</link>
      <description>Set-Cookie response headers were being incorrectly honored in multipart HTTP responses. If an attacker could control the Content-Type response header, as well as control part of the response body, they could inject Set-Cookie response headers that would have been honored by the browser. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1551|2024-02-20T19:23:38.186Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1547|2024-06-04T18:00:44.564Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1547</link>
      <description>Through a series of API calls and redirects, an attacker-controlled alert dialog could have been displayed on another website (with the victim website's URL shown). This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1547|2024-06-04T18:00:44.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1546|2024-02-20T19:23:30.714Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1546</link>
      <description>When storing and re-accessing data on a networking channel, the length of buffers may have been confused, resulting in an out-of-bounds memory read. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1546|2024-02-20T19:23:30.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1550|2024-02-20T19:23:36.552Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1550</link>
      <description>A malicious website could have used a combination of exiting fullscreen mode and `requestPointerLock` to cause the user's mouse to be re-positioned unexpectedly, which could have led to user confusion and inadvertently granting permissions they did not intend to grant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1550|2024-02-20T19:23:36.552Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1557|2024-02-20T13:21:38.413Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1557</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 122. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1557|2024-02-20T13:21:38.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1936|2024-03-04T21:31:54.044Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1936</link>
      <description>The encrypted subject of an email message could be incorrectly and permanently assigned to an arbitrary other email message in Thunderbird's local cache. Consequently, when replying to the contaminated email message, the user might accidentally leak the confidential subject to a third party. While this update fixes the bug and avoids future message contamination, it does not automatically repair existing contaminations. Users are advised to use the repair folder functionality, which is available from the context menu of email folders, which will erase incorrect subject assignments. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1936|2024-03-04T21:31:54.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 21:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1556|2024-06-04T18:01:33.835Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1556</link>
      <description>The incorrect object was checked for NULL in the built-in profiler, potentially leading to invalid memory access and undefined behavior. *Note:* This issue only affects the application when the profiler is running. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1556|2024-06-04T18:01:33.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-11T12:40:13.093Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5691</link>
      <description>By tricking the browser with a `X-Frame-Options` header, a sandboxed iframe could have presented a button that, if clicked by a user, would bypass restrictions to open a new window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-11T12:40:13.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5687|2024-06-11T16:16:51.765Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5687</link>
      <description>If a specific sequence of actions is performed when opening a new tab, the triggering principal associated with the new tab may have been incorrect. The triggering principal is used to calculate many values, including the `Referer` and `Sec-*` headers, meaning there is the potential for incorrect security checks within the browser in addition to incorrect or misleading information sent to remote websites.
*This bug only affects Firefox for Android. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5687|2024-06-11T16:16:51.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5701|2024-06-11T12:40:18.692Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5701</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 126. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5701|2024-06-11T12:40:18.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5022|2024-05-17T18:42:24.791Z -- mozilla -- focus%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5022</link>
      <description>The file scheme of URLs would be hidden, resulting in potential spoofing of a website's address in the location bar This vulnerability affects Focus for iOS &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5022|2024-05-17T18:42:24.791Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 18:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-11T16:16:40.610Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5700</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 126, Firefox ESR 115.11, and Thunderbird 115.11. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-11T16:16:40.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-11T14:02:15.786Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5690</link>
      <description>By monitoring the time certain operations take, an attacker could have guessed which external protocol handlers were functional on a user's system. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-11T14:02:15.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5697|2024-06-11T14:03:17.234Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5697</link>
      <description>A website was able to detect when a user took a screenshot of a page using the built-in Screenshot functionality in Firefox. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5697|2024-06-11T14:03:17.234Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5696|2024-06-11T12:40:13.963Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5696</link>
      <description>By manipulating the text in an `&amp;lt;input&amp;gt;` tag, an attacker could have caused corrupt memory leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5696|2024-06-11T12:40:13.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5699|2024-06-11T12:40:18.427Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5699</link>
      <description>In violation of spec, cookie prefixes such as `__Secure` were being ignored if they were not correctly capitalized - by spec they should be checked with a case-insensitive comparison. This could have resulted in the browser not correctly honoring the behaviors specified by the prefix. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5699|2024-06-11T12:40:18.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5695|2024-06-11T14:03:31.199Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5695</link>
      <description>If an out-of-memory condition occurs at a specific point using allocations in the probabilistic heap checker, an assertion could have been triggered, and in rarer situations, memory corruption could have occurred. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5695|2024-06-11T14:03:31.199Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5694|2024-06-11T12:40:17.378Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5694</link>
      <description>An attacker could have caused a use-after-free in the JavaScript engine to read memory in the JavaScript string section of the heap. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5694|2024-06-11T12:40:17.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5698|2024-06-11T12:40:18.183Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5698</link>
      <description>By manipulating the fullscreen feature while opening a data-list, an attacker could have overlaid a text box over the address bar. This could have led to user confusion and possible spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5698|2024-06-11T12:40:18.183Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-11T12:40:13.675Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5693</link>
      <description>Offscreen Canvas did not properly track cross-origin tainting, which could be used to access image data from another site in violation of same-origin policy. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-11T12:40:13.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5689|2024-06-11T14:49:43.183Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5689</link>
      <description>In addition to detecting when a user was taking a screenshot (XXX), a website was able to overlay the 'My Shots' button that appeared, and direct the user to a replica Firefox Screenshots page that could be used for phishing. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5689|2024-06-11T14:49:43.183Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-11T12:40:12.457Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5688</link>
      <description>If a garbage collection was triggered at the right time, a use-after-free could have occurred during object transplant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-11T12:40:12.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5692|2024-06-11T12:40:13.370Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5692</link>
      <description>On Windows, when using the 'Save As' functionality, an attacker could have tricked the browser into saving the file with a disallowed extension such as `.url` by including an invalid character in the extension. *Note:* This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5692|2024-06-11T12:40:13.370Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5702|2024-06-11T12:40:12.176Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5702</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in the networking stack could have led to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5702|2024-06-11T12:40:12.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5388|2024-03-19T12:02:54.004Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5388</link>
      <description>NSS was susceptible to a timing side-channel attack when performing RSA decryption. This attack could potentially allow an attacker to recover the private data. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5388|2024-03-19T12:02:54.004Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-12T18:33:20.746Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5691</link>
      <description>By tricking the browser with a `X-Frame-Options` header, a sandboxed iframe could have presented a button that, if clicked by a user, would bypass restrictions to open a new window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-12T18:33:20.746Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5694|2024-06-12T18:17:35.413Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5694</link>
      <description>An attacker could have caused a use-after-free in the JavaScript engine to read memory in the JavaScript string section of the heap. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5694|2024-06-12T18:17:35.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-11T12:40:14.287Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5700</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 126, Firefox ESR 115.11, and Thunderbird 115.11. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-11T12:40:14.287Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-11T12:40:12.752Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5690</link>
      <description>By monitoring the time certain operations take, an attacker could have guessed which external protocol handlers were functional on a user's system. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-11T12:40:12.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-13T22:33:23.767Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5700</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 126, Firefox ESR 115.11, and Thunderbird 115.11. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-13T22:33:23.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-13T22:33:22.889Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5691</link>
      <description>By tricking the browser with a `X-Frame-Options` header, a sandboxed iframe could have presented a button that, if clicked by a user, would bypass restrictions to open a new window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-13T22:33:22.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5702|2024-06-13T22:33:17.141Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5702</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in the networking stack could have led to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5702|2024-06-13T22:33:17.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5696|2024-06-13T22:33:23.568Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5696</link>
      <description>By manipulating the text in an `&amp;lt;input&amp;gt;` tag, an attacker could have caused corrupt memory leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5696|2024-06-13T22:33:23.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5692|2024-06-13T22:33:23.103Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5692</link>
      <description>On Windows 10, when using the 'Save As' functionality, an attacker could have tricked the browser into saving the file with a disallowed extension such as `.url` by including an invalid character in the extension. *Note:* This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5692|2024-06-13T22:33:23.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-13T22:33:23.345Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5693</link>
      <description>Offscreen Canvas did not properly track cross-origin tainting, which could be used to access image data from another site in violation of same-origin policy. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-13T22:33:23.345Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-13T22:33:17.374Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5688</link>
      <description>If a garbage collection was triggered at the right time, a use-after-free could have occurred during object transplant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-13T22:33:17.374Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-13T22:33:22.644Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5690</link>
      <description>By monitoring the time certain operations take, an attacker could have guessed which external protocol handlers were functional on a user's system. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-13T22:33:22.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38313|2024-06-14T16:24:07.846Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38313</link>
      <description>In certain scenarios a malicious website could attempt to display a fake location URL bar which could mislead users as to the actual website address This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38313|2024-06-14T16:24:07.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 20:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-21T18:15:54.759Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5688</link>
      <description>If a garbage collection was triggered at the right time, a use-after-free could have occurred during object transplant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-21T18:15:54.759Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3863|2024-06-21T18:16:01.262Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3863</link>
      <description>The executable file warning was not presented when downloading .xrm-ms files.  
*Note: This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3863|2024-06-21T18:16:01.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3857|2024-06-21T18:15:59.609Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3857</link>
      <description>The JIT created incorrect code for arguments in certain cases. This led to potential use-after-free crashes during garbage collection. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3857|2024-06-21T18:15:59.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5696|2024-06-21T18:15:57.462Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5696</link>
      <description>By manipulating the text in an `&amp;lt;input&amp;gt;` tag, an attacker could have caused corrupt memory leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5696|2024-06-21T18:15:57.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3859|2024-06-21T18:16:00.213Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3859</link>
      <description>On 32-bit versions there were integer-overflows that led to an out-of-bounds-read that potentially could be triggered by a malformed OpenType font. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3859|2024-06-21T18:16:00.213Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-21T18:15:55.850Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5691</link>
      <description>By tricking the browser with a `X-Frame-Options` header, a sandboxed iframe could have presented a button that, if clicked by a user, would bypass restrictions to open a new window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-21T18:15:55.850Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5692|2024-06-21T18:15:56.403Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5692</link>
      <description>On Windows 10, when using the 'Save As' functionality, an attacker could have tricked the browser into saving the file with a disallowed extension such as `.url` by including an invalid character in the extension. *Note:* This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5692|2024-06-21T18:15:56.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-21T18:15:55.293Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5690</link>
      <description>By monitoring the time certain operations take, an attacker could have guessed which external protocol handlers were functional on a user's system. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-21T18:15:55.293Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2608|2024-06-21T18:52:18.600Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2608</link>
      <description>`AppendEncodedAttributeValue(), ExtraSpaceNeededForAttrEncoding()` and `AppendEncodedCharacters()` could have experienced integer overflows, causing underallocation of an output buffer leading to an out of bounds write. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2608|2024-06-21T18:52:18.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3302|2024-06-21T18:16:01.831Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3302</link>
      <description>There was no limit to the number of HTTP/2 CONTINUATION frames that would be processed. A server could abuse this to create an Out of Memory condition in the browser. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3302|2024-06-21T18:16:01.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-21T18:15:58.018Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5700</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 126, Firefox ESR 115.11, and Thunderbird 115.11. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-21T18:15:58.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3852|2024-06-21T18:15:58.554Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3852</link>
      <description>GetBoundName could return the wrong version of an object when JIT optimizations were applied. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3852|2024-06-21T18:15:58.554Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3861|2024-06-21T18:16:00.743Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3861</link>
      <description>If an AlignedBuffer were assigned to itself, the subsequent self-move could result in an incorrect reference count and later use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3861|2024-06-21T18:16:00.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5702|2024-06-21T18:15:54.214Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5702</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in the networking stack could have led to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5702|2024-06-21T18:15:54.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3854|2024-06-21T18:15:59.089Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3854</link>
      <description>In some code patterns the JIT incorrectly optimized switch statements and generated code with out-of-bounds-reads. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3854|2024-06-21T18:15:59.089Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-21T18:15:56.931Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5693</link>
      <description>Offscreen Canvas did not properly track cross-origin tainting, which could be used to access image data from another site in violation of same-origin policy. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-21T18:15:56.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1552|2024-07-05T17:21:47.180Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1552</link>
      <description>Incorrect code generation could have led to unexpected numeric conversions and potential undefined behavior.*Note:* This issue only affects 32-bit ARM devices. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1552|2024-07-05T17:21:47.180Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2611|2024-07-05T17:21:13.176Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2611</link>
      <description>A missing delay on when pointer lock was used could have allowed a malicious page to trick a user into granting permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2611|2024-07-05T17:21:13.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26282|2024-07-05T17:21:01.368Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26282</link>
      <description>Using an AMP url with a canonical element, an attacker could have executed JavaScript from an opened bookmarked page. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26282|2024-07-05T17:21:01.368Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1563|2024-07-05T17:21:57.263Z -- mozilla -- focus%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1563</link>
      <description>An attacker could have executed unauthorized scripts on top origin sites using a JavaScript URI when opening an external URL with a custom Firefox scheme and a timeout race condition. This vulnerability affects Focus for iOS &lt; 122.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1563|2024-07-05T17:21:57.263Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1551|2024-07-05T17:20:59.781Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1551</link>
      <description>Set-Cookie response headers were being incorrectly honored in multipart HTTP responses. If an attacker could control the Content-Type response header, as well as control part of the response body, they could inject Set-Cookie response headers that would have been honored by the browser. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1551|2024-07-05T17:20:59.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2616|2024-07-05T17:21:11.755Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20esr</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2616</link>
      <description>To harden ICU against exploitation, the behavior for out-of-memory conditions was changed to crash instead of attempt to continue. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9 and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2616|2024-07-05T17:21:11.755Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1548|2024-07-05T17:21:47.586Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1548</link>
      <description>A website could have obscured the fullscreen notification by using a dropdown select input element. This could have led to user confusion and possible spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1548|2024-07-05T17:21:47.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1546|2024-07-05T17:21:44.662Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1546</link>
      <description>When storing and re-accessing data on a networking channel, the length of buffers may have been confused, resulting in an out-of-bounds memory read. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1546|2024-07-05T17:21:44.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26281|2024-07-05T17:21:56.799Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26281</link>
      <description>Upon scanning a JavaScript URI with the QR code scanner, an attacker could have executed unauthorized scripts on the current top origin sites in the URL bar. This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26281|2024-07-05T17:21:56.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5388|2024-07-05T17:21:12.662Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5388</link>
      <description>NSS was susceptible to a timing side-channel attack when performing RSA decryption. This attack could potentially allow an attacker to recover the private data. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5388|2024-07-05T17:21:12.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1550|2024-07-05T17:21:44.306Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1550</link>
      <description>A malicious website could have used a combination of exiting fullscreen mode and `requestPointerLock` to cause the user's mouse to be re-positioned unexpectedly, which could have led to user confusion and inadvertently granting permissions they did not intend to grant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1550|2024-07-05T17:21:44.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4774|2024-07-05T17:22:50.439Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4774</link>
      <description>The `ShmemCharMapHashEntry()` code was susceptible to potentially undefined behavior by bypassing the move semantics for one of its data members. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4774|2024-07-05T17:22:50.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6604|2024-07-09T15:06:06.130Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6604</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 127, Firefox ESR 115.12, and Thunderbird 115.12. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6604|2024-07-09T15:06:06.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5693|2024-07-09T15:29:15.068Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5693</link>
      <description>Offscreen Canvas did not properly track cross-origin tainting, which could be used to access image data from another site in violation of same-origin policy. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5693|2024-07-09T15:29:15.068Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6615|2024-07-09T15:05:19.743Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6615</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 127. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6615|2024-07-09T15:05:19.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6608|2024-07-10T16:31:59.234Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6608</link>
      <description>It was possible to move the cursor using pointerlock from an iframe. This allowed moving the cursor outside of the viewport and the Firefox window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6608|2024-07-10T16:31:59.234Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6602|2024-07-10T20:14:24.710Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6602</link>
      <description>A mismatch between allocator and deallocator could have lead to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6602|2024-07-10T20:14:24.710Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6611|2024-07-10T20:28:20.273Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6611</link>
      <description>A nested iframe, triggering a cross-site navigation, could send SameSite=Strict or Lax cookies. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6611|2024-07-10T20:28:20.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6613|2024-07-11T15:08:46.394Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6613</link>
      <description>The frame iterator could get stuck in a loop when encountering certain wasm frames leading to incorrect stack traces. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6613|2024-07-11T15:08:46.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6603|2024-07-11T15:14:25.435Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6603</link>
      <description>In an out-of-memory scenario an allocation could fail but free would have been called on the pointer afterwards leading to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6603|2024-07-11T15:14:25.435Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6607|2024-07-15T21:37:18.753Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6607</link>
      <description>It was possible to prevent a user from exiting pointerlock when pressing escape and to overlay customValidity notifications from a `&amp;lt;select&amp;gt;` element over certain permission prompts. This could be used to confuse a user into giving a site unintended permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6607|2024-07-15T21:37:18.753Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6604|2024-07-16T17:54:52.069Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6604</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 127, Firefox ESR 115.12, and Thunderbird 115.12. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6604|2024-07-16T17:54:52.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6610|2024-07-16T17:54:49.513Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6610</link>
      <description>Form validation popups could capture escape key presses. Therefore, spamming form validation messages could be used to prevent users from exiting full-screen mode. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6610|2024-07-16T17:54:49.513Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6613|2024-07-16T17:54:51.544Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6613</link>
      <description>The frame iterator could get stuck in a loop when encountering certain wasm frames leading to incorrect stack traces. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6613|2024-07-16T17:54:51.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6600|2024-07-16T17:54:49.789Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6600</link>
      <description>Due to large allocation checks in Angle for GLSL shaders being too lenient an out-of-bounds access could occur when allocating more than 8192 ints in private shader memory on mac OS. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6600|2024-07-16T17:54:49.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6609|2024-07-16T17:54:49.177Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6609</link>
      <description>When almost out-of-memory an elliptic curve key which was never allocated could have been freed again. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6609|2024-07-16T17:54:49.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6614|2024-07-16T17:54:51.807Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6614</link>
      <description>The frame iterator could get stuck in a loop when encountering certain wasm frames leading to incorrect stack traces. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6614|2024-07-16T17:54:51.807Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6608|2024-07-16T17:54:48.892Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6608</link>
      <description>It was possible to move the cursor using pointerlock from an iframe. This allowed moving the cursor outside of the viewport and the Firefox window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6608|2024-07-16T17:54:48.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6602|2024-07-16T17:54:50.421Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6602</link>
      <description>A mismatch between allocator and deallocator could have lead to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6602|2024-07-16T17:54:50.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6607|2024-07-16T17:54:48.564Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6607</link>
      <description>It was possible to prevent a user from exiting pointerlock when pressing escape and to overlay customValidity notifications from a `&amp;lt;select&amp;gt;` element over certain permission prompts. This could be used to confuse a user into giving a site unintended permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6607|2024-07-16T17:54:48.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6605|2024-07-16T17:54:52.596Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6605</link>
      <description>Firefox Android allowed immediate interaction with permission prompts. This could be used for tapjacking. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6605|2024-07-16T17:54:52.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6603|2024-07-16T17:54:50.723Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6603</link>
      <description>In an out-of-memory scenario an allocation could fail but free would have been called on the pointer afterwards leading to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6603|2024-07-16T17:54:50.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6611|2024-07-16T17:54:50.992Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6611</link>
      <description>A nested iframe, triggering a cross-site navigation, could send SameSite=Strict or Lax cookies. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6611|2024-07-16T17:54:50.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6612|2024-07-16T17:54:51.273Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6612</link>
      <description>CSP violations generated links in the console tab of the developer tools, pointing to the violating resource. This caused a DNS prefetch which leaked that a CSP violation happened. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6612|2024-07-16T17:54:51.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6606|2024-07-16T17:54:48.190Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6606</link>
      <description>Clipboard code failed to check the index on an array access. This could have lead to an out-of-bounds read. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6606|2024-07-16T17:54:48.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6615|2024-07-16T17:54:52.339Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6615</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 127 and Thunderbird 127. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6615|2024-07-16T17:54:52.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6601|2024-07-16T17:54:50.070Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6601</link>
      <description>A race condition could lead to a cross-origin container obtaining permissions of the top-level origin. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6601|2024-07-16T17:54:50.070Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6612|2024-07-17T16:07:10.562Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6612</link>
      <description>CSP violations generated links in the console tab of the developer tools, pointing to the violating resource. This caused a DNS prefetch which leaked that a CSP violation happened. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6612|2024-07-17T16:07:10.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2610|2024-07-18T14:54:44.372Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2610</link>
      <description>Using a markup injection an attacker could have stolen nonce values. This could have been used to bypass strict content security policies. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2610|2024-07-18T14:54:44.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6610|2024-07-23T19:20:48.750Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6610</link>
      <description>Form validation popups could capture escape key presses. Therefore, spamming form validation messages could be used to prevent users from exiting full-screen mode. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6610|2024-07-23T19:20:48.750Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6601|2024-07-23T19:21:20.978Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6601</link>
      <description>A race condition could lead to a cross-origin container obtaining permissions of the top-level origin. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6601|2024-07-23T19:21:20.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3855|2024-07-30T15:34:34.471Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3855</link>
      <description>In certain cases the JIT incorrectly optimized MSubstr operations, which led to out-of-bounds reads. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3855|2024-07-30T15:34:34.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5696|2024-07-31T19:39:25.437Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5696</link>
      <description>By manipulating the text in an `&amp;lt;input&amp;gt;` tag, an attacker could have caused corrupt memory leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5696|2024-07-31T19:39:25.437Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5692|2024-07-31T19:40:41.013Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5692</link>
      <description>On Windows 10, when using the 'Save As' functionality, an attacker could have tricked the browser into saving the file with a disallowed extension such as `.url` by including an invalid character in the extension. *Note:* This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5692|2024-07-31T19:40:41.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1549|2024-08-01T18:40:21.447Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1549</link>
      <description>If a website set a large custom cursor, portions of the cursor could have overlapped with the permission dialog, potentially resulting in user confusion and unexpected granted permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1549|2024-08-01T18:40:21.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1548|2024-08-01T18:40:21.403Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1548</link>
      <description>A website could have obscured the fullscreen notification by using a dropdown select input element. This could have led to user confusion and possible spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1548|2024-08-01T18:40:21.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1550|2024-08-01T18:40:21.314Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1550</link>
      <description>A malicious website could have used a combination of exiting fullscreen mode and `requestPointerLock` to cause the user's mouse to be re-positioned unexpectedly, which could have led to user confusion and inadvertently granting permissions they did not intend to grant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1550|2024-08-01T18:40:21.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1554|2024-08-01T18:40:21.447Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1554</link>
      <description>The `fetch()` API and navigation incorrectly shared the same cache, as the cache key did not include the optional headers `fetch()` may contain.  Under the correct circumstances, an attacker may have been able to poison the local browser cache by priming it with a `fetch()` response controlled by the additional headers. Upon navigation to the same URL, the user would see the cached response instead of the expected response. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1554|2024-08-01T18:40:21.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1557|2024-08-01T18:40:21.450Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1557</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 122. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1557|2024-08-01T18:40:21.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1936|2024-08-01T18:56:22.343Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1936</link>
      <description>The encrypted subject of an email message could be incorrectly and permanently assigned to an arbitrary other email message in Thunderbird's local cache. Consequently, when replying to the contaminated email message, the user might accidentally leak the confidential subject to a third party. While this update fixes the bug and avoids future message contamination, it does not automatically repair existing contaminations. Users are advised to use the repair folder functionality, which is available from the context menu of email folders, which will erase incorrect subject assignments. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1936|2024-08-01T18:56:22.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 21:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1553|2024-08-01T18:40:21.410Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1553</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 122, Firefox ESR 115.7, and Thunderbird 115.7. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1553|2024-08-01T18:40:21.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1556|2024-08-01T18:40:21.454Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1556</link>
      <description>The incorrect object was checked for NULL in the built-in profiler, potentially leading to invalid memory access and undefined behavior. *Note:* This issue only affects the application when the profiler is running. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1556|2024-08-01T18:40:21.454Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1552|2024-08-01T18:40:21.419Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1552</link>
      <description>Incorrect code generation could have led to unexpected numeric conversions and potential undefined behavior.*Note:* This issue only affects 32-bit ARM devices. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1552|2024-08-01T18:40:21.419Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1551|2024-08-01T18:40:21.333Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1551</link>
      <description>Set-Cookie response headers were being incorrectly honored in multipart HTTP responses. If an attacker could control the Content-Type response header, as well as control part of the response body, they could inject Set-Cookie response headers that would have been honored by the browser. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1551|2024-08-01T18:40:21.333Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1555|2024-08-01T18:40:21.427Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1555</link>
      <description>When opening a website using the `firefox://` protocol handler, SameSite cookies were not properly respected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1555|2024-08-01T18:40:21.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1547|2024-08-01T18:40:21.411Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1547</link>
      <description>Through a series of API calls and redirects, an attacker-controlled alert dialog could have been displayed on another website (with the victim website's URL shown). This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1547|2024-08-01T18:40:21.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1546|2024-08-01T18:40:21.460Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1546</link>
      <description>When storing and re-accessing data on a networking channel, the length of buffers may have been confused, resulting in an out-of-bounds memory read. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1546|2024-08-01T18:40:21.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1563|2024-08-01T18:40:21.368Z -- mozilla -- focus%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1563</link>
      <description>An attacker could have executed unauthorized scripts on top origin sites using a JavaScript URI when opening an external URL with a custom Firefox scheme and a timeout race condition. This vulnerability affects Focus for iOS &lt; 122.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1563|2024-08-01T18:40:21.368Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3865|2024-08-01T20:26:57.032Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3865</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 124. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3865|2024-08-01T20:26:57.032Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3856|2024-08-01T20:26:56.396Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3856</link>
      <description>A use-after-free could occur during WASM execution if garbage collection ran during the creation of an array. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3856|2024-08-01T20:26:56.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3864|2024-08-01T20:26:57.039Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3864</link>
      <description>Memory safety bug present in Firefox 124, Firefox ESR 115.9, and Thunderbird 115.9. This bug showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort this could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3864|2024-08-01T20:26:57.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3858|2024-08-01T20:26:56.914Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3858</link>
      <description>It was possible to mutate a JavaScript object so that the JIT could crash while tracing it. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3858|2024-08-01T20:26:56.914Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5022|2024-08-01T20:55:10.438Z -- mozilla -- focus%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5022</link>
      <description>The file scheme of URLs would be hidden, resulting in potential spoofing of a website's address in the location bar This vulnerability affects Focus for iOS &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5022|2024-08-01T20:55:10.438Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 18:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4769|2024-08-01T20:47:41.943Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4769</link>
      <description>When importing resources using Web Workers, error messages would distinguish the difference between `application/javascript` responses and non-script responses.  This could have been abused to learn information cross-origin. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4769|2024-08-01T20:47:41.943Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4772|2024-08-01T20:47:41.740Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4772</link>
      <description>An HTTP digest authentication nonce value was generated using `rand()` which could lead to predictable values. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4772|2024-08-01T20:47:41.740Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3302|2024-08-01T20:05:08.440Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3302</link>
      <description>There was no limit to the number of HTTP/2 CONTINUATION frames that would be processed. A server could abuse this to create an Out of Memory condition in the browser. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3302|2024-08-01T20:05:08.440Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4777|2024-08-01T20:55:09.343Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4777</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 125, Firefox ESR 115.10, and Thunderbird 115.10. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4777|2024-08-01T20:55:09.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4775|2024-08-01T20:47:41.779Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4775</link>
      <description>An iterator stop condition was missing when handling WASM code in the built-in profiler, potentially leading to invalid memory access and undefined behavior. *Note:* This issue only affects the application when the profiler is running. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4775|2024-08-01T20:47:41.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4778|2024-08-01T20:55:08.737Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4778</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 125. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4778|2024-08-01T20:55:08.737Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3854|2024-08-01T20:26:57.045Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3854</link>
      <description>In some code patterns the JIT incorrectly optimized switch statements and generated code with out-of-bounds-reads. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3854|2024-08-01T20:26:57.045Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4764|2024-08-01T20:47:41.789Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4764</link>
      <description>Multiple WebRTC threads could have claimed a newly connected audio input leading to use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4764|2024-08-01T20:47:41.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3857|2024-08-01T20:26:56.991Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3857</link>
      <description>The JIT created incorrect code for arguments in certain cases. This led to potential use-after-free crashes during garbage collection. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3857|2024-08-01T20:26:56.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4773|2024-08-01T20:47:41.768Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4773</link>
      <description>When a network error occurred during page load, the prior content could have remained in view with a blank URL bar. This could have been used to obfuscate a spoofed web site. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4773|2024-08-01T20:47:41.768Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4767|2024-08-01T20:47:41.701Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4767</link>
      <description>If the `browser.privatebrowsing.autostart` preference is enabled, IndexedDB files were not properly deleted when the window was closed. This preference is disabled by default in Firefox. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4767|2024-08-01T20:47:41.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4776|2024-08-01T20:47:41.780Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4776</link>
      <description>A file dialog shown while in full-screen mode could have resulted in the window remaining disabled. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4776|2024-08-01T20:47:41.780Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3855|2024-08-01T20:26:56.942Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3855</link>
      <description>In certain cases the JIT incorrectly optimized MSubstr operations, which led to out-of-bounds reads. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3855|2024-08-01T20:26:56.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4771|2024-08-01T20:47:41.788Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4771</link>
      <description>A memory allocation check was missing which would lead to a use-after-free if the allocation failed. This could have triggered a crash or potentially be leveraged to achieve code execution. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4771|2024-08-01T20:47:41.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3853|2024-08-01T20:26:57.145Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3853</link>
      <description>A use-after-free could result if a JavaScript realm was in the process of being initialized when a garbage collection started. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3853|2024-08-01T20:26:57.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4770|2024-08-01T20:47:41.760Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4770</link>
      <description>When saving a page to PDF, certain font styles could have led to a potential use-after-free crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4770|2024-08-01T20:47:41.760Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3862|2024-08-01T20:26:56.406Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3862</link>
      <description>The MarkStack assignment operator, part of the JavaScript engine, could access uninitialized memory if it were used in a self-assignment. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3862|2024-08-01T20:26:56.406Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4766|2024-08-01T20:47:41.924Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4766</link>
      <description>Different techniques existed to obscure the fullscreen notification in Firefox for Android.  These could have lead to potential user confusion and spoofing attacks.
*This bug only affects Firefox for Android. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4766|2024-08-01T20:47:41.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3859|2024-08-01T20:26:56.940Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3859</link>
      <description>On 32-bit versions there were integer-overflows that led to an out-of-bounds-read that potentially could be triggered by a malformed OpenType font. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3859|2024-08-01T20:26:56.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3852|2024-08-01T20:26:56.409Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3852</link>
      <description>GetBoundName could return the wrong version of an object when JIT optimizations were applied. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3852|2024-08-01T20:26:56.409Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4367|2024-08-01T20:40:47.051Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4367</link>
      <description>A type check was missing when handling fonts in PDF.js, which would allow arbitrary JavaScript execution in the PDF.js context. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4367|2024-08-01T20:40:47.051Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4774|2024-08-01T20:47:41.780Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4774</link>
      <description>The `ShmemCharMapHashEntry()` code was susceptible to potentially undefined behavior by bypassing the move semantics for one of its data members. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4774|2024-08-01T20:47:41.780Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3860|2024-08-01T20:26:56.961Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3860</link>
      <description>An out-of-memory condition during object initialization could result in an empty shape list. If the JIT subsequently traced the object it would crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3860|2024-08-01T20:26:56.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3863|2024-08-01T20:26:57.123Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3863</link>
      <description>The executable file warning was not presented when downloading .xrm-ms files.  
*Note: This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3863|2024-08-01T20:26:57.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4768|2024-08-01T20:47:41.692Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4768</link>
      <description>A bug in popup notifications' interaction with WebAuthn made it easier for an attacker to trick a user into granting permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4768|2024-08-01T20:47:41.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3861|2024-08-01T20:26:57.101Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3861</link>
      <description>If an AlignedBuffer were assigned to itself, the subsequent self-move could result in an incorrect reference count and later use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3861|2024-08-01T20:26:57.101Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4765|2024-08-01T20:47:41.687Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4765</link>
      <description>Web application manifests were stored by using an insecure MD5 hash which allowed for a hash collision to overwrite another application's manifest. This could have been exploited to run arbitrary code in another application's context. 
*This issue only affects Firefox for Android. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4765|2024-08-01T20:47:41.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29944|2024-08-02T01:17:58.626Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29944</link>
      <description>An attacker was able to inject an event handler into a privileged object that would allow arbitrary JavaScript execution in the parent process. Note: This vulnerability affects Desktop Firefox only, it does not affect mobile versions of Firefox. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.0.1 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29944|2024-08-02T01:17:58.626Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29943|2024-08-02T01:17:58.445Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29943</link>
      <description>An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript object by fooling range-based bounds check elimination. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29943|2024-08-02T01:17:58.445Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38312|2024-08-02T04:04:25.248Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38312</link>
      <description>When browsing private tabs, some data related to location history or webpage thumbnails could be persisted incorrectly within the sandboxed app bundle after app termination This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38312|2024-08-02T04:04:25.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 20:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38313|2024-08-02T04:04:25.077Z -- mozilla -- firefox%20for%20ios</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38313</link>
      <description>In certain scenarios a malicious website could attempt to display a fake location URL bar which could mislead users as to the actual website address This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38313|2024-08-02T04:04:25.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 20:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
