<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Mozilla -- Firefox</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mozilla/firefox.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Mozilla -- Firefox</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:19:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26973|2024-08-04T16:03:23.261Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26973</link>
      <description>Certain input to the CSS Sanitizer confused it, resulting in incorrect components being removed. This could have been used as a sanitizer bypass. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 84, Thunderbird &lt; 78.6, and Firefox ESR &lt; 78.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26973|2024-08-04T16:03:23.261Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 13:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26955|2024-08-04T16:03:23.169Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26955</link>
      <description>When a user downloaded a file in Firefox for Android, if a cookie is set, it would have been re-sent during a subsequent file download operation on the same domain, regardless of whether the original and subsequent request were in private and non-private browsing modes. *Note: This issue only affected Firefox for Android. Other operating systems are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26955|2024-08-04T16:03:23.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38507|2024-08-04T01:44:23.527Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38507</link>
      <description>The Opportunistic Encryption feature of HTTP2 (RFC 8164) allows a connection to be transparently upgraded to TLS while retaining the visual properties of an HTTP connection, including being same-origin with unencrypted connections on port 80. However, if a second encrypted port on the same IP address (e.g. port 8443) did not opt-in to opportunistic encryption; a network attacker could forward a connection from the browser to port 443 to port 8443, causing the browser to treat the content of port 8443 as same-origin with HTTP. This was resolved by disabling the Opportunistic Encryption feature, which had low usage. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 94, Thunderbird &lt; 91.3, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38507|2024-08-04T01:44:23.527Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15665|2024-08-04T13:22:30.678Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15665</link>
      <description>Firefox did not reset the address bar after the beforeunload dialog was shown if the user chose to remain on the page. This could have resulted in an incorrect URL being shown when used in conjunction with other unexpected browser behaviors. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 80.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15665|2024-08-04T13:22:30.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 18:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26967|2024-08-04T16:03:23.194Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26967</link>
      <description>When listening for page changes with a Mutation Observer, a malicious web page could confuse Firefox Screenshots into interacting with elements other than those that it injected into the page. This would lead to internal errors and unexpected behavior in the Screenshots code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26967|2024-08-04T16:03:23.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6799|2024-08-04T09:11:05.093Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6799</link>
      <description>Command line arguments could have been injected during Firefox invocation as a shell handler for certain unsupported file types. This required Firefox to be configured as the default handler for a given file type and for a file downloaded to be opened in a third party application that insufficiently sanitized URL data. In that situation, clicking a link in the third party application could have been used to retrieve and execute files whose location was supplied through command line arguments. Note: This issue only affects Windows operating systems and when Firefox is configured as the default handler for non-default filetypes. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 73 and Firefox &lt; ESR68.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6799|2024-08-04T09:11:05.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 04:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43531|2024-08-04T03:55:29.364Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43531</link>
      <description>When a user loaded a Web Extensions context menu, the Web Extension could access the post-redirect URL of the element clicked. If the Web Extension lacked the WebRequest permission for the hosts involved in the redirect, this would be a same-origin-violation leaking data the Web Extension should have access to. This was fixed to provide the pre-redirect URL. This is related to CVE-2021-43532 but in the context of Web Extensions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 94.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43531|2024-08-04T03:55:29.364Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26956|2024-08-04T16:03:23.066Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26956</link>
      <description>In some cases, removing HTML elements during sanitization would keep existing SVG event handlers and therefore lead to XSS. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83, Firefox ESR &lt; 78.5, and Thunderbird &lt; 78.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26956|2024-08-04T16:03:23.066Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12390|2024-08-04T11:56:51.727Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12390</link>
      <description>Incorrect origin serialization of URLs with IPv6 addresses could lead to incorrect security checks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 76.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12390|2024-08-04T11:56:51.727Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 17:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12413|2024-08-04T11:56:51.691Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12413</link>
      <description>The Raccoon attack is a timing attack on DHE ciphersuites inherit in the TLS specification. To mitigate this vulnerability, Firefox disabled support for DHE ciphersuites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12413|2024-08-04T11:56:51.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12409|2024-08-04T11:56:51.768Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12409</link>
      <description>When using certain blank characters in a URL, they where incorrectly rendered as spaces instead of an encoded URL. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 77.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12409|2024-08-04T11:56:51.768Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43534|2024-08-04T03:55:29.303Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43534</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers and community members reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 93 and Firefox ESR 91.2. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 94, Thunderbird &lt; 91.3, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43534|2024-08-04T03:55:29.303Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38499|2024-08-04T01:44:22.995Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38499</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 92. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 93.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38499|2024-08-04T01:44:22.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26969|2024-08-04T16:03:23.190Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26969</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 82. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26969|2024-08-04T16:03:23.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12411|2024-08-04T11:56:51.878Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12411</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 76. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 77.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12411|2024-08-04T11:56:51.878Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26976|2024-08-04T16:03:23.169Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26976</link>
      <description>When a HTTPS pages was embedded in a HTTP page, and there was a service worker registered for the former, the service worker could have intercepted the request for the secure page despite the iframe not being a secure context due to the (insecure) framing. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 84.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26976|2024-08-04T16:03:23.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 13:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38508|2024-08-04T01:44:23.522Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38508</link>
      <description>By displaying a form validity message in the correct location at the same time as a permission prompt (such as for geolocation), the validity message could have obscured the prompt, resulting in the user potentially being tricked into granting the permission. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 94, Thunderbird &lt; 91.3, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38508|2024-08-04T01:44:23.522Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38509|2024-08-04T01:44:23.355Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38509</link>
      <description>Due to an unusual sequence of attacker-controlled events, a Javascript alert() dialog with arbitrary (although unstyled) contents could be displayed over top an uncontrolled webpage of the attacker's choosing. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 94, Thunderbird &lt; 91.3, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38509|2024-08-04T01:44:23.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26950|2024-08-04T16:03:22.903Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26950</link>
      <description>In certain circumstances, the MCallGetProperty opcode can be emitted with unmet assumptions resulting in an exploitable use-after-free condition. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 82.0.3, Firefox ESR &lt; 78.4.1, and Thunderbird &lt; 78.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26950|2024-08-04T16:03:22.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15667|2024-08-04T13:22:30.674Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15667</link>
      <description>When processing a MAR update file, after the signature has been validated, an invalid name length could result in a heap overflow, leading to memory corruption and potentially arbitrary code execution. Within Firefox as released by Mozilla, this issue is only exploitable with the Mozilla-controlled signing key. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 80.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15667|2024-08-04T13:22:30.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 18:42:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6801|2024-08-04T09:11:05.135Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6801</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 72. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 73.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6801|2024-08-04T09:11:05.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 04:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43540|2024-08-04T04:03:06.919Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43540</link>
      <description>WebExtensions with the correct permissions were able to create and install ServiceWorkers for third-party websites that would not have been uninstalled with the extension. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 95.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43540|2024-08-04T04:03:06.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-35114|2024-08-04T16:55:10.630Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-35114</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 83. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 84.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-35114|2024-08-04T16:55:10.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 13:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26951|2024-08-04T16:03:22.995Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26951</link>
      <description>A parsing and event loading mismatch in Firefox's SVG code could have allowed load events to fire, even after sanitization. An attacker already capable of exploiting an XSS vulnerability in privileged internal pages could have used this attack to bypass our built-in sanitizer. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83, Firefox ESR &lt; 78.5, and Thunderbird &lt; 78.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26951|2024-08-04T16:03:22.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43530|2024-08-04T03:55:29.359Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43530</link>
      <description>A Universal XSS vulnerability was present in Firefox for Android resulting from improper sanitization when processing a URL scanned from a QR code. *This bug only affects Firefox for Android. Other operating systems are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 94.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43530|2024-08-04T03:55:29.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38505|2024-08-04T01:44:23.530Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38505</link>
      <description>Microsoft introduced a new feature in Windows 10 known as Cloud Clipboard which, if enabled, will record data copied to the clipboard to the cloud, and make it available on other computers in certain scenarios. Applications that wish to prevent copied data from being recorded in Cloud History must use specific clipboard formats; and Firefox before versions 94 and ESR 91.3 did not implement them. This could have caused sensitive data to be recorded to a user's Microsoft account. *This bug only affects Firefox for Windows 10+ with Cloud Clipboard enabled. Other operating systems are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 94, Thunderbird &lt; 91.3, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38505|2024-08-04T01:44:23.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6810|2024-08-04T09:11:05.044Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6810</link>
      <description>After a website had entered fullscreen mode, it could have used a previously opened popup to obscure the notification that indicates the browser is in fullscreen mode. Combined with spoofing the browser chrome, this could have led to confusing the user about the current origin of the page and credential theft or other attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 74.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6810|2024-08-04T09:11:05.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 21:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12412|2024-08-04T11:56:52.061Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12412</link>
      <description>By navigating a tab using the history API, an attacker could cause the address bar to display the incorrect domain (with the https:// scheme, a blocked port number such as '1', and without a lock icon) while controlling the page contents. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 70.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12412|2024-08-04T11:56:52.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12416|2024-08-04T11:56:52.058Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12416</link>
      <description>A VideoStreamEncoder may have been freed in a race condition with VideoBroadcaster::AddOrUpdateSink, resulting in a use-after-free, memory corruption, and a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 78.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12416|2024-08-04T11:56:52.058Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15652|2024-08-04T13:22:30.541Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15652</link>
      <description>By observing the stack trace for JavaScript errors in web workers, it was possible to leak the result of a cross-origin redirect. This applied only to content that can be parsed as script. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 79, Firefox ESR &lt; 68.11, Firefox ESR &lt; 78.1, Thunderbird &lt; 68.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 78.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15652|2024-08-04T13:22:30.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 17:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38494|2024-08-04T01:44:23.464Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38494</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 91. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 92.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38494|2024-08-04T01:44:23.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15670|2024-08-04T13:22:30.668Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15670</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox for Android 79. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 80, Firefox ESR &lt; 78.2, Thunderbird &lt; 78.2, and Firefox for Android &lt; 80.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15670|2024-08-04T13:22:30.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 18:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15675|2024-08-04T13:22:30.629Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15675</link>
      <description>When processing surfaces, the lifetime may outlive a persistent buffer leading to memory corruption and a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 81.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15675|2024-08-04T13:22:30.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 18:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12401|2024-08-04T11:56:51.648Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12401</link>
      <description>During ECDSA signature generation, padding applied in the nonce designed to ensure constant-time scalar multiplication was removed, resulting in variable-time execution dependent on secret data. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 80 and Firefox for Android &lt; 80.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12401|2024-08-04T11:56:51.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38498|2024-08-04T01:44:22.834Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38498</link>
      <description>During process shutdown, a document could have caused a use-after-free of a languages service object, leading to memory corruption and a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 93, Thunderbird &lt; 91.2, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38498|2024-08-04T01:44:22.834Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26957|2024-08-04T16:03:22.861Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26957</link>
      <description>OneCRL was non-functional in the new Firefox for Android due to a missing service initialization. This could result in a failure to enforce some certificate revocations. *Note: This issue only affected Firefox for Android. Other operating systems are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26957|2024-08-04T16:03:22.861Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15677|2024-08-04T13:22:30.687Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15677</link>
      <description>By exploiting an Open Redirect vulnerability on a website, an attacker could have spoofed the site displayed in the download file dialog to show the original site (the one suffering from the open redirect) rather than the site the file was actually downloaded from. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 81, Thunderbird &lt; 78.3, and Firefox ESR &lt; 78.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15677|2024-08-04T13:22:30.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 18:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6824|2024-08-04T09:11:05.150Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6824</link>
      <description>Initially, a user opens a Private Browsing Window and generates a password for a site, then closes the Private Browsing Window but leaves Firefox open. Subsequently, if the user had opened a new Private Browsing Window, revisited the same site, and generated a new password - the generated passwords would have been identical, rather than independent. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 75.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6824|2024-08-04T09:11:05.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 15:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26977|2024-08-04T16:03:23.207Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26977</link>
      <description>By attempting to connect a website using an unresponsive port, an attacker could have controlled the content of a tab while the URL bar displayed the original domain. *Note: This issue only affects Firefox for Android. Other operating systems are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 84.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26977|2024-08-04T16:03:23.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 13:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-35111|2024-08-04T16:55:10.596Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-35111</link>
      <description>When an extension with the proxy permission registered to receive &lt;all_urls&gt;, the proxy.onRequest callback was not triggered for view-source URLs. While web content cannot navigate to such URLs, a user opening View Source could have inadvertently leaked their IP address. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 84, Thunderbird &lt; 78.6, and Firefox ESR &lt; 78.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-35111|2024-08-04T16:55:10.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 13:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12415|2024-08-04T11:56:51.740Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12415</link>
      <description>When "%2F" was present in a manifest URL, Firefox's AppCache behavior may have become confused and allowed a manifest to be served from a subdirectory. This could cause the appcache to be used to service requests for the top level directory. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 78.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12415|2024-08-04T11:56:51.740Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15674|2024-08-04T13:22:30.800Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15674</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 80. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 81.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15674|2024-08-04T13:22:30.800Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 18:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15680|2024-08-04T13:22:30.785Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15680</link>
      <description>If a valid external protocol handler was referenced in an image tag, the resulting broken image size could be distinguished from a broken image size of a non-existent protocol handler. This allowed an attacker to successfully probe whether an external protocol handler was registered. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 82.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15680|2024-08-04T13:22:30.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 20:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12407|2024-08-04T11:56:51.839Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12407</link>
      <description>Mozilla Developer Nicolas Silva found that when using WebRender, Firefox would under certain conditions leak arbitrary GPU memory to the visible screen. The leaked memory content was visible to the user, but not observable from web content. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 77.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12407|2024-08-04T11:56:51.839Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6829|2024-08-04T09:11:05.159Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6829</link>
      <description>When performing EC scalar point multiplication, the wNAF point multiplication algorithm was used; which leaked partial information about the nonce used during signature generation. Given an electro-magnetic trace of a few signature generations, the private key could have been computed. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 80 and Firefox for Android &lt; 80.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6829|2024-08-04T09:11:05.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26979|2024-08-04T16:03:23.189Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26979</link>
      <description>When a user typed a URL in the address bar or the search bar and quickly hit the enter key, a website could sometimes capture that event and then redirect the user before navigation occurred to the desired, entered address. To construct a convincing spoof the attacker would have had to guess what the user was typing, perhaps by suggesting it. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 84.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26979|2024-08-04T16:03:23.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 13:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15673|2024-08-04T13:22:30.827Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15673</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 80 and Firefox ESR 78.2. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 81, Thunderbird &lt; 78.3, and Firefox ESR &lt; 78.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15673|2024-08-04T13:22:30.827Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 18:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38501|2024-08-04T01:44:22.811Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38501</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 92 and Firefox ESR 91.1. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 93, Thunderbird &lt; 91.2, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38501|2024-08-04T01:44:22.811Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38506|2024-08-04T01:44:22.919Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38506</link>
      <description>Through a series of navigations, Firefox could have entered fullscreen mode without notification or warning to the user. This could lead to spoofing attacks on the browser UI including phishing. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 94, Thunderbird &lt; 91.3, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38506|2024-08-04T01:44:22.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6796|2024-08-04T09:11:05.019Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6796</link>
      <description>A content process could have modified shared memory relating to crash reporting information, crash itself, and cause an out-of-bound write. This could have caused memory corruption and a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 73 and Firefox &lt; ESR68.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6796|2024-08-04T09:11:05.019Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 04:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38491|2024-08-04T01:44:22.837Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38491</link>
      <description>Mixed-content checks were unable to analyze opaque origins which led to some mixed content being loaded. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 92.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38491|2024-08-04T01:44:22.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12408|2024-08-04T11:56:51.742Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12408</link>
      <description>When browsing a document hosted on an IP address, an attacker could insert certain characters to flip domain and path information in the address bar. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 77.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12408|2024-08-04T11:56:51.742Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26954|2024-08-04T16:03:23.129Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26954</link>
      <description>When accepting a malicious intent from other installed apps, Firefox for Android accepted manifests from arbitrary file paths and allowed declaring webapp manifests for other origins. This could be used to gain fullscreen access for UI spoofing and could also lead to cross-origin attacks on targeted websites. *Note: This issue only affected Firefox for Android. Other operating systems are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26954|2024-08-04T16:03:23.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12394|2024-08-04T11:56:52.053Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12394</link>
      <description>A logic flaw in our location bar implementation could have allowed a local attacker to spoof the current location by selecting a different origin and removing focus from the input element. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 76.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12394|2024-08-04T11:56:52.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 17:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43533|2024-08-04T03:55:29.263Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43533</link>
      <description>When parsing internationalized domain names, high bits of the characters in the URLs were sometimes stripped, resulting in inconsistencies that could lead to user confusion or attacks such as phishing. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 94.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43533|2024-08-04T03:55:29.263Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:20:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26972|2024-08-04T16:03:23.182Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26972</link>
      <description>The lifecycle of IPC Actors allows managed actors to outlive their manager actors; and the former must ensure that they are not attempting to use a dead actor they have a reference to. Such a check was omitted in WebGL, resulting in a use-after-free and a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 84.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26972|2024-08-04T16:03:23.182Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 13:53:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26953|2024-08-04T16:03:23.059Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26953</link>
      <description>It was possible to cause the browser to enter fullscreen mode without displaying the security UI; thus making it possible to attempt a phishing attack or otherwise confuse the user. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83, Firefox ESR &lt; 78.5, and Thunderbird &lt; 78.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26953|2024-08-04T16:03:23.059Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26964|2024-08-04T16:03:23.076Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26964</link>
      <description>If the Remote Debugging via USB feature was enabled in Firefox for Android on an Android version prior to Android 6.0, untrusted apps could have connected to the feature and operated with the privileges of the browser to read and interact with web content. The feature was implemented as a unix domain socket, protected by the Android SELinux policy; however, SELinux was not enforced for versions prior to 6.0. This was fixed by removing the Remote Debugging via USB feature from affected devices. *Note: This issue only affected Firefox for Android. Other operating systems are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26964|2024-08-04T16:03:23.076Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12400|2024-08-04T11:56:52.044Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12400</link>
      <description>When converting coordinates from projective to affine, the modular inversion was not performed in constant time, resulting in a possible timing-based side channel attack. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 80 and Firefox for Android &lt; 80.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12400|2024-08-04T11:56:52.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6808|2024-08-04T09:11:05.026Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6808</link>
      <description>When a JavaScript URL (javascript:) is evaluated and the result is a string, this string is parsed to create an HTML document, which is then presented. Previously, this document's URL (as reported by the document.location property, for example) was the originating javascript: URL which could lead to spoofing attacks; it is now correctly the URL of the originating document. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 74.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6808|2024-08-04T09:11:05.026Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 21:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15682|2024-08-04T13:22:30.695Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15682</link>
      <description>When a link to an external protocol was clicked, a prompt was presented that allowed the user to choose what application to open it in. An attacker could induce that prompt to be associated with an origin they didn't control, resulting in a spoofing attack. This was fixed by changing external protocol prompts to be tab-modal while also ensuring they could not be incorrectly associated with a different origin. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 82.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15682|2024-08-04T13:22:30.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 20:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6813|2024-08-04T09:11:05.154Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6813</link>
      <description>When protecting CSS blocks with the nonce feature of Content Security Policy, the @import statement in the CSS block could allow an attacker to inject arbitrary styles, bypassing the intent of the Content Security Policy. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 74.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6813|2024-08-04T09:11:05.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 21:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12423|2024-08-04T11:56:51.761Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12423</link>
      <description>When the Windows DLL "webauthn.dll" was missing from the Operating System, and a malicious one was placed in a folder in the user's %PATH%, Firefox may have loaded the DLL, leading to arbitrary code execution. *Note: This issue only affects the Windows operating system; other operating systems are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 78.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12423|2024-08-04T11:56:51.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6826|2024-08-04T09:11:05.117Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6826</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers Tyson Smith, Bob Clary, and Alexandru Michis reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 74. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 75.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6826|2024-08-04T09:11:05.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 15:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26971|2024-08-04T16:03:23.196Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26971</link>
      <description>Certain blit values provided by the user were not properly constrained leading to a heap buffer overflow on some video drivers. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 84, Thunderbird &lt; 78.6, and Firefox ESR &lt; 78.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26971|2024-08-04T16:03:23.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 13:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12396|2024-08-04T11:56:52.035Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12396</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers and community members reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 75. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 76.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12396|2024-08-04T11:56:52.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 16:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15659|2024-08-04T13:22:30.692Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15659</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers and community members reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 78 and Firefox ESR 78.0. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 79, Firefox ESR &lt; 68.11, Firefox ESR &lt; 78.1, Thunderbird &lt; 68.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 78.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15659|2024-08-04T13:22:30.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 17:43:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15678|2024-08-04T13:22:30.808Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15678</link>
      <description>When recursing through graphical layers while scrolling, an iterator may have become invalid, resulting in a potential use-after-free. This occurs because the function APZCTreeManager::ComputeClippedCompositionBounds did not follow iterator invalidation rules. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 81, Thunderbird &lt; 78.3, and Firefox ESR &lt; 78.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15678|2024-08-04T13:22:30.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 18:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38504|2024-08-04T01:44:23.396Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38504</link>
      <description>When interacting with an HTML input element's file picker dialog with webkitdirectory set, a use-after-free could have resulted, leading to memory corruption and a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 94, Thunderbird &lt; 91.3, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38504|2024-08-04T01:44:23.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26974|2024-08-04T16:03:23.202Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26974</link>
      <description>When flex-basis was used on a table wrapper, a StyleGenericFlexBasis object could have been incorrectly cast to the wrong type. This resulted in a heap user-after-free, memory corruption, and a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 84, Thunderbird &lt; 78.6, and Firefox ESR &lt; 78.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26974|2024-08-04T16:03:23.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 13:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6823|2024-08-04T09:11:05.127Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6823</link>
      <description>A malicious extension could have called &lt;code&gt;browser.identity.launchWebAuthFlow&lt;/code&gt;, controlling the redirect_uri, and through the Promise returned, obtain the Auth code and gain access to the user's account at the service provider. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 75.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6823|2024-08-04T09:11:05.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 15:53:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26960|2024-08-04T16:03:23.075Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26960</link>
      <description>If the Compact() method was called on an nsTArray, the array could have been reallocated without updating other pointers, leading to a potential use-after-free and exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83, Firefox ESR &lt; 78.5, and Thunderbird &lt; 78.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26960|2024-08-04T16:03:23.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38492|2024-08-04T01:44:22.943Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38492</link>
      <description>When delegating navigations to the operating system, Firefox would accept the `mk` scheme which might allow attackers to launch pages and execute scripts in Internet Explorer in unprivileged mode. *This bug only affects Firefox for Windows. Other operating systems are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 92, Thunderbird &lt; 91.1, Thunderbird &lt; 78.14, Firefox ESR &lt; 78.14, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38492|2024-08-04T01:44:22.943Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26965|2024-08-04T16:03:23.113Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26965</link>
      <description>Some websites have a feature "Show Password" where clicking a button will change a password field into a textbook field, revealing the typed password. If, when using a software keyboard that remembers user input, a user typed their password and used that feature, the type of the password field was changed, resulting in a keyboard layout change and the possibility for the software keyboard to remember the typed password. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83, Firefox ESR &lt; 78.5, and Thunderbird &lt; 78.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26965|2024-08-04T16:03:23.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-35112|2024-08-04T16:55:10.836Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-35112</link>
      <description>If a user downloaded a file lacking an extension on Windows, and then "Open"-ed it from the downloads panel, if there was an executable file in the downloads directory with the same name but with an executable extension (such as .bat or .exe) that executable would have been launched instead. *Note: This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 84, Thunderbird &lt; 78.6, and Firefox ESR &lt; 78.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-35112|2024-08-04T16:55:10.836Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 13:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15666|2024-08-04T13:22:30.634Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15666</link>
      <description>When trying to load a non-video in an audio/video context the exact status code (200, 302, 404, 500, 412, 403, etc.) was disclosed via the MediaError Message. This level of information leakage is inconsistent with the standardized onerror/onsuccess disclosure and can lead to inferring login status to services or device discovery on a local network among other attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 80 and Firefox for Android &lt; 80.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15666|2024-08-04T13:22:30.634Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 18:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26966|2024-08-04T16:03:23.079Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26966</link>
      <description>Searching for a single word from the address bar caused an mDNS request to be sent on the local network searching for a hostname consisting of that string; resulting in an information leak. *Note: This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83, Firefox ESR &lt; 78.5, and Thunderbird &lt; 78.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26966|2024-08-04T16:03:23.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26962|2024-08-04T16:03:23.155Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26962</link>
      <description>Cross-origin iframes that contained a login form could have been recognized by the login autofill service, and populated. This could have been used in clickjacking attacks, as well as be read across partitions in dynamic first party isolation. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26962|2024-08-04T16:03:23.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26975|2024-08-04T16:03:23.168Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26975</link>
      <description>When a malicious application installed on the user's device broadcast an Intent to Firefox for Android, arbitrary headers could have been specified, leading to attacks such as abusing ambient authority or session fixation. This was resolved by only allowing certain safe-listed headers. *Note: This issue only affected Firefox for Android. Other operating systems are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 84.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26975|2024-08-04T16:03:23.168Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 13:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26961|2024-08-04T16:03:23.165Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26961</link>
      <description>When DNS over HTTPS is in use, it intentionally filters RFC1918 and related IP ranges from the responses as these do not make sense coming from a DoH resolver. However when an IPv4 address was mapped through IPv6, these addresses were erroneously let through, leading to a potential DNS Rebinding attack. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83, Firefox ESR &lt; 78.5, and Thunderbird &lt; 78.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26961|2024-08-04T16:03:23.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12425|2024-08-04T11:56:51.782Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12425</link>
      <description>Due to confusion processing a hyphen character in Date.parse(), a one-byte out of bounds read could have occurred, leading to potential information disclosure. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 78.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12425|2024-08-04T11:56:51.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6815|2024-08-04T09:11:05.122Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6815</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety and script safety bugs present in Firefox 73. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption or escalation of privilege and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 74.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6815|2024-08-04T09:11:05.122Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 21:10:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6809|2024-08-04T09:11:05.119Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6809</link>
      <description>When a Web Extension had the all-urls permission and made a fetch request with a mode set to 'same-origin', it was possible for the Web Extension to read local files. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 74.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6809|2024-08-04T09:11:05.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 21:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26978|2024-08-04T16:03:23.179Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26978</link>
      <description>Using techniques that built on the slipstream research, a malicious webpage could have exposed both an internal network's hosts as well as services running on the user's local machine. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 84, Thunderbird &lt; 78.6, and Firefox ESR &lt; 78.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26978|2024-08-04T16:03:23.179Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 13:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15681|2024-08-04T13:22:30.692Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15681</link>
      <description>When multiple WASM threads had a reference to a module, and were looking up exported functions, one WASM thread could have overwritten another's entry in a shared stub table, resulting in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 82.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15681|2024-08-04T13:22:30.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 20:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26968|2024-08-04T16:03:23.130Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26968</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 82 and Firefox ESR 78.4. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83, Firefox ESR &lt; 78.5, and Thunderbird &lt; 78.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26968|2024-08-04T16:03:23.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15664|2024-08-04T13:22:30.600Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15664</link>
      <description>By holding a reference to the eval() function from an about:blank window, a malicious webpage could have gained access to the InstallTrigger object which would allow them to prompt the user to install an extension. Combined with user confusion, this could result in an unintended or malicious extension being installed. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 80, Thunderbird &lt; 78.2, Thunderbird &lt; 68.12, Firefox ESR &lt; 68.12, Firefox ESR &lt; 78.2, and Firefox for Android &lt; 80.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15664|2024-08-04T13:22:30.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 18:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43532|2024-08-04T03:55:29.273Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43532</link>
      <description>The 'Copy Image Link' context menu action would copy the final image URL after redirects. By embedding an image that triggered authentication flows - in conjunction with a Content Security Policy that stopped a redirection chain in the middle - the final image URL could be one that contained an authentication token used to takeover a user account. If a website tricked a user into copy and pasting the image link back to the page, the page would be able to steal the authentication tokens. This was fixed by making the action return the original URL, before any redirects. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 94.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43532|2024-08-04T03:55:29.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12391|2024-08-04T11:56:51.888Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12391</link>
      <description>Documents formed using data: URLs in an OBJECT element failed to inherit the CSP of the creating context. This allowed the execution of scripts that should have been blocked, albeit with a unique opaque origin. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 76.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12391|2024-08-04T11:56:51.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 17:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38497|2024-08-04T01:44:22.835Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38497</link>
      <description>Through use of reportValidity() and window.open(), a plain-text validation message could have been overlaid on another origin, leading to possible user confusion and spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 93, Thunderbird &lt; 91.2, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38497|2024-08-04T01:44:22.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15668|2024-08-04T13:22:30.671Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15668</link>
      <description>A lock was missing when accessing a data structure and importing certificate information into the trust database. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 80 and Firefox for Android &lt; 80.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15668|2024-08-04T13:22:30.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 18:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12424|2024-08-04T11:56:51.800Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12424</link>
      <description>When constructing a permission prompt for WebRTC, a URI was supplied from the content process. This URI was untrusted, and could have been the URI of an origin that was previously granted permission; bypassing the prompt. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 78.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12424|2024-08-04T11:56:51.800Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 13:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12402|2024-08-04T11:56:51.801Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12402</link>
      <description>During RSA key generation, bignum implementations used a variation of the Binary Extended Euclidean Algorithm which entailed significantly input-dependent flow. This allowed an attacker able to perform electromagnetic-based side channel attacks to record traces leading to the recovery of the secret primes. *Note:* An unmodified Firefox browser does not generate RSA keys in normal operation and is not affected, but products built on top of it might. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 78.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12402|2024-08-04T11:56:51.801Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43535|2024-08-04T03:55:29.311Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43535</link>
      <description>A use-after-free could have occured when an HTTP2 session object was released on a different thread, leading to memory corruption and a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 93, Thunderbird &lt; 91.3, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43535|2024-08-04T03:55:29.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26958|2024-08-04T16:03:23.148Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26958</link>
      <description>Firefox did not block execution of scripts with incorrect MIME types when the response was intercepted and cached through a ServiceWorker. This could lead to a cross-site script inclusion vulnerability, or a Content Security Policy bypass. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83, Firefox ESR &lt; 78.5, and Thunderbird &lt; 78.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26958|2024-08-04T16:03:23.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:22:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15684|2024-08-04T13:22:30.668Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15684</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 81. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 82.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15684|2024-08-04T13:22:30.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 20:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12422|2024-08-04T11:56:51.717Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12422</link>
      <description>In non-standard configurations, a JPEG image created by JavaScript could have caused an internal variable to overflow, resulting in an out of bounds write, memory corruption, and a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 78.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12422|2024-08-04T11:56:51.717Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26959|2024-08-04T16:03:23.168Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26959</link>
      <description>During browser shutdown, reference decrementing could have occured on a previously freed object, resulting in a use-after-free, memory corruption, and a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83, Firefox ESR &lt; 78.5, and Thunderbird &lt; 78.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26959|2024-08-04T16:03:23.168Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15676|2024-08-04T13:22:30.645Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15676</link>
      <description>Firefox sometimes ran the onload handler for SVG elements that the DOM sanitizer decided to remove, resulting in JavaScript being executed after pasting attacker-controlled data into a contenteditable element. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 81, Thunderbird &lt; 78.3, and Firefox ESR &lt; 78.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15676|2024-08-04T13:22:30.645Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 18:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26963|2024-08-04T16:03:23.168Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26963</link>
      <description>Repeated calls to the history and location interfaces could have been used to hang the browser. This was addressed by introducing rate-limiting to these API calls. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26963|2024-08-04T16:03:23.168Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15663|2024-08-04T13:22:30.566Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15663</link>
      <description>If Firefox is installed to a user-writable directory, the Mozilla Maintenance Service would execute updater.exe from the install location with system privileges. Although the Mozilla Maintenance Service does ensure that updater.exe is signed by Mozilla, the version could have been rolled back to a previous version which would have allowed exploitation of an older bug and arbitrary code execution with System Privileges. *Note: This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 80, Thunderbird &lt; 78.2, Thunderbird &lt; 68.12, Firefox ESR &lt; 68.12, and Firefox ESR &lt; 78.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15663|2024-08-04T13:22:30.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 18:43:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12426|2024-08-04T11:56:52.069Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12426</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers and community members reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 77. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 78.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12426|2024-08-04T11:56:52.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26952|2024-08-04T16:03:22.990Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26952</link>
      <description>Incorrect bookkeeping of functions inlined during JIT compilation could have led to memory corruption and a potentially exploitable crash when handling out-of-memory errors. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 83.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26952|2024-08-04T16:03:22.990Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-35113|2024-08-04T16:55:10.635Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-35113</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 83 and Firefox ESR 78.5. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 84, Thunderbird &lt; 78.6, and Firefox ESR &lt; 78.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-35113|2024-08-04T16:55:10.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 13:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38510|2024-08-04T01:44:23.495Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38510</link>
      <description>The executable file warning was not presented when downloading .inetloc files, which, due to a flaw in Mac OS, can run commands on a user's computer.*Note: This issue only affected Mac OS operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 94, Thunderbird &lt; 91.3, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38510|2024-08-04T01:44:23.495Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38503|2024-08-04T01:44:23.381Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38503</link>
      <description>The iframe sandbox rules were not correctly applied to XSLT stylesheets, allowing an iframe to bypass restrictions such as executing scripts or navigating the top-level frame. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 94, Thunderbird &lt; 91.3, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38503|2024-08-04T01:44:23.381Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43544|2024-08-04T04:03:07.823Z -- mozilla -- firefox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43544</link>
      <description>When receiving a URL through a SEND intent, Firefox would have searched for the text, but subsequent usages of the address bar might have caused the URL to load unintentionally, which could lead to XSS and spoofing attacks. *This bug only affects Firefox for Android. Other operating systems are unaffected.*. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 95.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43544|2024-08-04T04:03:07.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2613|2024-08-02T19:44:01.782Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2613</link>
      <description>Data was not properly sanitized when decoding a QUIC ACK frame; this could have led to unrestricted memory consumption and a crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2613|2024-08-02T19:44:01.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5388|2024-08-02T07:59:43.260Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5388</link>
      <description>NSS was susceptible to a timing side-channel attack when performing RSA decryption. This attack could potentially allow an attacker to recover the private data. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5388|2024-08-02T07:59:43.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4765|2024-08-01T20:47:41.687Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4765</link>
      <description>Web application manifests were stored by using an insecure MD5 hash which allowed for a hash collision to overwrite another application's manifest. This could have been exploited to run arbitrary code in another application's context. 
*This issue only affects Firefox for Android. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4765|2024-08-01T20:47:41.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3861|2024-08-01T20:26:57.101Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3861</link>
      <description>If an AlignedBuffer were assigned to itself, the subsequent self-move could result in an incorrect reference count and later use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3861|2024-08-01T20:26:57.101Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4768|2024-08-01T20:47:41.692Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4768</link>
      <description>A bug in popup notifications' interaction with WebAuthn made it easier for an attacker to trick a user into granting permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4768|2024-08-01T20:47:41.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3863|2024-08-01T20:26:57.123Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3863</link>
      <description>The executable file warning was not presented when downloading .xrm-ms files.  
*Note: This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3863|2024-08-01T20:26:57.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3860|2024-08-01T20:26:56.961Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3860</link>
      <description>An out-of-memory condition during object initialization could result in an empty shape list. If the JIT subsequently traced the object it would crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3860|2024-08-01T20:26:56.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4774|2024-08-01T20:47:41.780Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4774</link>
      <description>The `ShmemCharMapHashEntry()` code was susceptible to potentially undefined behavior by bypassing the move semantics for one of its data members. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4774|2024-08-01T20:47:41.780Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4367|2024-08-01T20:40:47.051Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4367</link>
      <description>A type check was missing when handling fonts in PDF.js, which would allow arbitrary JavaScript execution in the PDF.js context. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4367|2024-08-01T20:40:47.051Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3852|2024-08-01T20:26:56.409Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3852</link>
      <description>GetBoundName could return the wrong version of an object when JIT optimizations were applied. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3852|2024-08-01T20:26:56.409Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3859|2024-08-01T20:26:56.940Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3859</link>
      <description>On 32-bit versions there were integer-overflows that led to an out-of-bounds-read that potentially could be triggered by a malformed OpenType font. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3859|2024-08-01T20:26:56.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4766|2024-08-01T20:47:41.924Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4766</link>
      <description>Different techniques existed to obscure the fullscreen notification in Firefox for Android.  These could have lead to potential user confusion and spoofing attacks.
*This bug only affects Firefox for Android. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4766|2024-08-01T20:47:41.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3862|2024-08-01T20:26:56.406Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3862</link>
      <description>The MarkStack assignment operator, part of the JavaScript engine, could access uninitialized memory if it were used in a self-assignment. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3862|2024-08-01T20:26:56.406Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4770|2024-08-01T20:47:41.760Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4770</link>
      <description>When saving a page to PDF, certain font styles could have led to a potential use-after-free crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4770|2024-08-01T20:47:41.760Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3853|2024-08-01T20:26:57.145Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3853</link>
      <description>A use-after-free could result if a JavaScript realm was in the process of being initialized when a garbage collection started. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3853|2024-08-01T20:26:57.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4771|2024-08-01T20:47:41.788Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4771</link>
      <description>A memory allocation check was missing which would lead to a use-after-free if the allocation failed. This could have triggered a crash or potentially be leveraged to achieve code execution. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4771|2024-08-01T20:47:41.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3855|2024-08-01T20:26:56.942Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3855</link>
      <description>In certain cases the JIT incorrectly optimized MSubstr operations, which led to out-of-bounds reads. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3855|2024-08-01T20:26:56.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4776|2024-08-01T20:47:41.780Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4776</link>
      <description>A file dialog shown while in full-screen mode could have resulted in the window remaining disabled. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4776|2024-08-01T20:47:41.780Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4767|2024-08-01T20:47:41.701Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4767</link>
      <description>If the `browser.privatebrowsing.autostart` preference is enabled, IndexedDB files were not properly deleted when the window was closed. This preference is disabled by default in Firefox. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4767|2024-08-01T20:47:41.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4773|2024-08-01T20:47:41.768Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4773</link>
      <description>When a network error occurred during page load, the prior content could have remained in view with a blank URL bar. This could have been used to obfuscate a spoofed web site. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4773|2024-08-01T20:47:41.768Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3857|2024-08-01T20:26:56.991Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3857</link>
      <description>The JIT created incorrect code for arguments in certain cases. This led to potential use-after-free crashes during garbage collection. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3857|2024-08-01T20:26:56.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4764|2024-08-01T20:47:41.789Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4764</link>
      <description>Multiple WebRTC threads could have claimed a newly connected audio input leading to use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4764|2024-08-01T20:47:41.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3854|2024-08-01T20:26:57.045Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3854</link>
      <description>In some code patterns the JIT incorrectly optimized switch statements and generated code with out-of-bounds-reads. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3854|2024-08-01T20:26:57.045Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4778|2024-08-01T20:55:08.737Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4778</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 125. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4778|2024-08-01T20:55:08.737Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4775|2024-08-01T20:47:41.779Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4775</link>
      <description>An iterator stop condition was missing when handling WASM code in the built-in profiler, potentially leading to invalid memory access and undefined behavior. *Note:* This issue only affects the application when the profiler is running. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4775|2024-08-01T20:47:41.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4777|2024-08-01T20:55:09.343Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4777</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 125, Firefox ESR 115.10, and Thunderbird 115.10. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4777|2024-08-01T20:55:09.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3302|2024-08-01T20:05:08.440Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3302</link>
      <description>There was no limit to the number of HTTP/2 CONTINUATION frames that would be processed. A server could abuse this to create an Out of Memory condition in the browser. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3302|2024-08-01T20:05:08.440Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4772|2024-08-01T20:47:41.740Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4772</link>
      <description>An HTTP digest authentication nonce value was generated using `rand()` which could lead to predictable values. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4772|2024-08-01T20:47:41.740Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4769|2024-08-01T20:47:41.943Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4769</link>
      <description>When importing resources using Web Workers, error messages would distinguish the difference between `application/javascript` responses and non-script responses.  This could have been abused to learn information cross-origin. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4769|2024-08-01T20:47:41.943Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3858|2024-08-01T20:26:56.914Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3858</link>
      <description>It was possible to mutate a JavaScript object so that the JIT could crash while tracing it. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3858|2024-08-01T20:26:56.914Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3864|2024-08-01T20:26:57.039Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3864</link>
      <description>Memory safety bug present in Firefox 124, Firefox ESR 115.9, and Thunderbird 115.9. This bug showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort this could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3864|2024-08-01T20:26:57.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3856|2024-08-01T20:26:56.396Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3856</link>
      <description>A use-after-free could occur during WASM execution if garbage collection ran during the creation of an array. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3856|2024-08-01T20:26:56.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3865|2024-08-01T20:26:57.032Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3865</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 124. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3865|2024-08-01T20:26:57.032Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1546|2024-08-01T18:40:21.460Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1546</link>
      <description>When storing and re-accessing data on a networking channel, the length of buffers may have been confused, resulting in an out-of-bounds memory read. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1546|2024-08-01T18:40:21.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1547|2024-08-01T18:40:21.411Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1547</link>
      <description>Through a series of API calls and redirects, an attacker-controlled alert dialog could have been displayed on another website (with the victim website's URL shown). This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1547|2024-08-01T18:40:21.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1555|2024-08-01T18:40:21.427Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1555</link>
      <description>When opening a website using the `firefox://` protocol handler, SameSite cookies were not properly respected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1555|2024-08-01T18:40:21.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1551|2024-08-01T18:40:21.333Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1551</link>
      <description>Set-Cookie response headers were being incorrectly honored in multipart HTTP responses. If an attacker could control the Content-Type response header, as well as control part of the response body, they could inject Set-Cookie response headers that would have been honored by the browser. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1551|2024-08-01T18:40:21.333Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1552|2024-08-01T18:40:21.419Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1552</link>
      <description>Incorrect code generation could have led to unexpected numeric conversions and potential undefined behavior.*Note:* This issue only affects 32-bit ARM devices. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1552|2024-08-01T18:40:21.419Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1556|2024-08-01T18:40:21.454Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1556</link>
      <description>The incorrect object was checked for NULL in the built-in profiler, potentially leading to invalid memory access and undefined behavior. *Note:* This issue only affects the application when the profiler is running. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1556|2024-08-01T18:40:21.454Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1553|2024-08-01T18:40:21.410Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1553</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 122, Firefox ESR 115.7, and Thunderbird 115.7. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1553|2024-08-01T18:40:21.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1557|2024-08-01T18:40:21.450Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1557</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 122. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1557|2024-08-01T18:40:21.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1554|2024-08-01T18:40:21.447Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1554</link>
      <description>The `fetch()` API and navigation incorrectly shared the same cache, as the cache key did not include the optional headers `fetch()` may contain.  Under the correct circumstances, an attacker may have been able to poison the local browser cache by priming it with a `fetch()` response controlled by the additional headers. Upon navigation to the same URL, the user would see the cached response instead of the expected response. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1554|2024-08-01T18:40:21.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1550|2024-08-01T18:40:21.314Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1550</link>
      <description>A malicious website could have used a combination of exiting fullscreen mode and `requestPointerLock` to cause the user's mouse to be re-positioned unexpectedly, which could have led to user confusion and inadvertently granting permissions they did not intend to grant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1550|2024-08-01T18:40:21.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1548|2024-08-01T18:40:21.403Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1548</link>
      <description>A website could have obscured the fullscreen notification by using a dropdown select input element. This could have led to user confusion and possible spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1548|2024-08-01T18:40:21.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1549|2024-08-01T18:40:21.447Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1549</link>
      <description>If a website set a large custom cursor, portions of the cursor could have overlapped with the permission dialog, potentially resulting in user confusion and unexpected granted permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1549|2024-08-01T18:40:21.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5692|2024-07-31T19:40:41.013Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5692</link>
      <description>On Windows 10, when using the 'Save As' functionality, an attacker could have tricked the browser into saving the file with a disallowed extension such as `.url` by including an invalid character in the extension. *Note:* This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5692|2024-07-31T19:40:41.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5696|2024-07-31T19:39:25.437Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5696</link>
      <description>By manipulating the text in an `&amp;lt;input&amp;gt;` tag, an attacker could have caused corrupt memory leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5696|2024-07-31T19:39:25.437Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3855|2024-07-30T15:34:34.471Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3855</link>
      <description>In certain cases the JIT incorrectly optimized MSubstr operations, which led to out-of-bounds reads. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3855|2024-07-30T15:34:34.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6601|2024-07-23T19:21:20.978Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6601</link>
      <description>A race condition could lead to a cross-origin container obtaining permissions of the top-level origin. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6601|2024-07-23T19:21:20.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6610|2024-07-23T19:20:48.750Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6610</link>
      <description>Form validation popups could capture escape key presses. Therefore, spamming form validation messages could be used to prevent users from exiting full-screen mode. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6610|2024-07-23T19:20:48.750Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2610|2024-07-18T14:54:44.372Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2610</link>
      <description>Using a markup injection an attacker could have stolen nonce values. This could have been used to bypass strict content security policies. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2610|2024-07-18T14:54:44.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6612|2024-07-17T16:07:10.562Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6612</link>
      <description>CSP violations generated links in the console tab of the developer tools, pointing to the violating resource. This caused a DNS prefetch which leaked that a CSP violation happened. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6612|2024-07-17T16:07:10.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6601|2024-07-16T17:54:50.070Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6601</link>
      <description>A race condition could lead to a cross-origin container obtaining permissions of the top-level origin. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6601|2024-07-16T17:54:50.070Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6615|2024-07-16T17:54:52.339Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6615</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 127 and Thunderbird 127. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6615|2024-07-16T17:54:52.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6606|2024-07-16T17:54:48.190Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6606</link>
      <description>Clipboard code failed to check the index on an array access. This could have lead to an out-of-bounds read. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6606|2024-07-16T17:54:48.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6612|2024-07-16T17:54:51.273Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6612</link>
      <description>CSP violations generated links in the console tab of the developer tools, pointing to the violating resource. This caused a DNS prefetch which leaked that a CSP violation happened. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6612|2024-07-16T17:54:51.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6611|2024-07-16T17:54:50.992Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6611</link>
      <description>A nested iframe, triggering a cross-site navigation, could send SameSite=Strict or Lax cookies. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6611|2024-07-16T17:54:50.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6603|2024-07-16T17:54:50.723Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6603</link>
      <description>In an out-of-memory scenario an allocation could fail but free would have been called on the pointer afterwards leading to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6603|2024-07-16T17:54:50.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6605|2024-07-16T17:54:52.596Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6605</link>
      <description>Firefox Android allowed immediate interaction with permission prompts. This could be used for tapjacking. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6605|2024-07-16T17:54:52.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6607|2024-07-16T17:54:48.564Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6607</link>
      <description>It was possible to prevent a user from exiting pointerlock when pressing escape and to overlay customValidity notifications from a `&amp;lt;select&amp;gt;` element over certain permission prompts. This could be used to confuse a user into giving a site unintended permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6607|2024-07-16T17:54:48.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6602|2024-07-16T17:54:50.421Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6602</link>
      <description>A mismatch between allocator and deallocator could have lead to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6602|2024-07-16T17:54:50.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6608|2024-07-16T17:54:48.892Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6608</link>
      <description>It was possible to move the cursor using pointerlock from an iframe. This allowed moving the cursor outside of the viewport and the Firefox window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6608|2024-07-16T17:54:48.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6614|2024-07-16T17:54:51.807Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6614</link>
      <description>The frame iterator could get stuck in a loop when encountering certain wasm frames leading to incorrect stack traces. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6614|2024-07-16T17:54:51.807Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6609|2024-07-16T17:54:49.177Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6609</link>
      <description>When almost out-of-memory an elliptic curve key which was never allocated could have been freed again. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6609|2024-07-16T17:54:49.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6600|2024-07-16T17:54:49.789Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6600</link>
      <description>Due to large allocation checks in Angle for GLSL shaders being too lenient an out-of-bounds access could occur when allocating more than 8192 ints in private shader memory on mac OS. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6600|2024-07-16T17:54:49.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6613|2024-07-16T17:54:51.544Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6613</link>
      <description>The frame iterator could get stuck in a loop when encountering certain wasm frames leading to incorrect stack traces. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6613|2024-07-16T17:54:51.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6610|2024-07-16T17:54:49.513Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6610</link>
      <description>Form validation popups could capture escape key presses. Therefore, spamming form validation messages could be used to prevent users from exiting full-screen mode. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6610|2024-07-16T17:54:49.513Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6604|2024-07-16T17:54:52.069Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6604</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 127, Firefox ESR 115.12, and Thunderbird 115.12. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6604|2024-07-16T17:54:52.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6614|2024-07-11T17:22:27.889Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6614</link>
      <description>The frame iterator could get stuck in a loop when encountering certain wasm frames leading to incorrect stack traces. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6614|2024-07-11T17:22:27.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6612|2024-07-10T21:06:25.324Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6612</link>
      <description>CSP violations generated links in the console tab of the developer tools, pointing to the violating resource. This caused a DNS prefetch which leaked that a CSP violation happened. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6612|2024-07-10T21:06:25.324Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29943|2024-07-10T19:34:41.151Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29943</link>
      <description>An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript object by fooling range-based bounds check elimination. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29943|2024-07-10T19:34:41.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6606|2024-07-10T14:18:43.636Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6606</link>
      <description>Clipboard code failed to check the index on an array access. This could have lead to an out-of-bounds read. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6606|2024-07-10T14:18:43.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6612|2024-07-09T14:26:00.305Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6612</link>
      <description>CSP violations generated links in the console tab of the developer tools, pointing to the violating resource. This caused a DNS prefetch which leaked that a CSP violation happened. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6612|2024-07-09T14:26:00.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6606|2024-07-09T14:25:58.357Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6606</link>
      <description>Clipboard code failed to check the index on an array access. This could have lead to an out-of-bounds read. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6606|2024-07-09T14:25:58.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6600|2024-07-09T14:25:56.437Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6600</link>
      <description>Due to large allocation checks in Angle for GLSL shaders being too lenient an out-of-bounds access could occur when allocating more than 8192 ints in private shader memory on mac OS. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6600|2024-07-09T14:25:56.437Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6613|2024-07-09T14:26:00.593Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6613</link>
      <description>The frame iterator could get stuck in a loop when encountering certain wasm frames leading to incorrect stack traces. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6613|2024-07-09T14:26:00.593Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6605|2024-07-09T14:25:57.930Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6605</link>
      <description>Firefox Android allowed immediate interaction with permission prompts. This could be used for tapjacking. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6605|2024-07-09T14:25:57.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6611|2024-07-09T14:25:59.748Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6611</link>
      <description>A nested iframe, triggering a cross-site navigation, could send SameSite=Strict or Lax cookies. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6611|2024-07-09T14:25:59.748Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6610|2024-07-09T14:25:59.460Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6610</link>
      <description>Form validation popups could capture escape key presses. Therefore, spamming form validation messages could be used to prevent users from exiting full-screen mode. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6610|2024-07-09T14:25:59.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6603|2024-07-09T14:25:57.402Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6603</link>
      <description>In an out-of-memory scenario an allocation could fail but free would have been called on the pointer afterwards leading to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6603|2024-07-09T14:25:57.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6609|2024-07-09T14:25:59.075Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6609</link>
      <description>When almost out-of-memory an elliptic curve key which was never allocated could have been freed again. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6609|2024-07-09T14:25:59.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6604|2024-07-09T14:25:57.691Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6604</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 127, Firefox ESR 115.12, and Thunderbird 115.12. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6604|2024-07-09T14:25:57.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6615|2024-07-09T14:26:01.065Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6615</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 127. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6615|2024-07-09T14:26:01.065Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6602|2024-07-09T14:25:57.026Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6602</link>
      <description>A mismatch between allocator and deallocator could have lead to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6602|2024-07-09T14:25:57.026Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6608|2024-07-09T14:25:58.862Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6608</link>
      <description>It was possible to move the cursor using pointerlock from an iframe. This allowed moving the cursor outside of the viewport and the Firefox window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6608|2024-07-09T14:25:58.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6601|2024-07-09T14:25:56.733Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6601</link>
      <description>A race condition could lead to a cross-origin container obtaining permissions of the top-level origin. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6601|2024-07-09T14:25:56.733Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6607|2024-07-09T14:25:58.566Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6607</link>
      <description>It was possible to prevent a user from exiting pointerlock when pressing escape and to overlay customValidity notifications from a `&amp;lt;select&amp;gt;` element over certain permission prompts. This could be used to confuse a user into giving a site unintended permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6607|2024-07-09T14:25:58.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6614|2024-07-09T14:26:00.836Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6614</link>
      <description>The frame iterator could get stuck in a loop when encountering certain wasm frames leading to incorrect stack traces. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6614|2024-07-09T14:26:00.836Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29943|2024-07-03T03:55:12.405Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29943</link>
      <description>An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript object by fooling range-based bounds check elimination. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29943|2024-07-03T03:55:12.405Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-21T16:52:03.765Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5688</link>
      <description>If a garbage collection was triggered at the right time, a use-after-free could have occurred during object transplant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-21T16:52:03.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-13T22:33:22.644Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5690</link>
      <description>By monitoring the time certain operations take, an attacker could have guessed which external protocol handlers were functional on a user's system. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-13T22:33:22.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-13T22:33:17.374Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5688</link>
      <description>If a garbage collection was triggered at the right time, a use-after-free could have occurred during object transplant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-13T22:33:17.374Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-13T22:33:23.345Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5693</link>
      <description>Offscreen Canvas did not properly track cross-origin tainting, which could be used to access image data from another site in violation of same-origin policy. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-13T22:33:23.345Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5692|2024-06-13T22:33:23.103Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5692</link>
      <description>On Windows 10, when using the 'Save As' functionality, an attacker could have tricked the browser into saving the file with a disallowed extension such as `.url` by including an invalid character in the extension. *Note:* This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5692|2024-06-13T22:33:23.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5696|2024-06-13T22:33:23.568Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5696</link>
      <description>By manipulating the text in an `&amp;lt;input&amp;gt;` tag, an attacker could have caused corrupt memory leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5696|2024-06-13T22:33:23.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5702|2024-06-13T22:33:17.141Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5702</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in the networking stack could have led to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5702|2024-06-13T22:33:17.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-13T22:33:22.889Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5691</link>
      <description>By tricking the browser with a `X-Frame-Options` header, a sandboxed iframe could have presented a button that, if clicked by a user, would bypass restrictions to open a new window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-13T22:33:22.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-13T22:33:23.767Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5700</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 126, Firefox ESR 115.11, and Thunderbird 115.11. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-13T22:33:23.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5698|2024-06-12T19:40:15.526Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5698</link>
      <description>By manipulating the fullscreen feature while opening a data-list, an attacker could have overlaid a text box over the address bar. This could have led to user confusion and possible spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5698|2024-06-12T19:40:15.526Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-12T19:45:38.636Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5688</link>
      <description>If a garbage collection was triggered at the right time, a use-after-free could have occurred during object transplant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-12T19:45:38.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-12T15:52:36.652Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5693</link>
      <description>Offscreen Canvas did not properly track cross-origin tainting, which could be used to access image data from another site in violation of same-origin policy. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-12T15:52:36.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4772|2024-06-12T15:37:16.323Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4772</link>
      <description>An HTTP digest authentication nonce value was generated using `rand()` which could lead to predictable values. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4772|2024-06-12T15:37:16.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4768|2024-06-12T15:38:50.583Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4768</link>
      <description>A bug in popup notifications' interaction with WebAuthn made it easier for an attacker to trick a user into granting permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4768|2024-06-12T15:38:50.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2611|2024-03-19T12:02:55.649Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2611</link>
      <description>A missing delay on when pointer lock was used could have allowed a malicious page to trick a user into granting permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2611|2024-03-19T12:02:55.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2607|2024-03-19T12:02:52.932Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2607</link>
      <description>Return registers were overwritten which could have allowed an attacker to execute arbitrary code. *Note:* This issue only affected Armv7-A systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2607|2024-03-19T12:02:52.932Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2606|2024-06-04T17:29:45.735Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2606</link>
      <description>Passing invalid data could have led to invalid wasm values being created, such as arbitrary integers turning into pointer values. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2606|2024-06-04T17:29:45.735Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2610|2024-03-19T12:02:55.079Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2610</link>
      <description>Using a markup injection an attacker could have stolen nonce values. This could have been used to bypass strict content security policies. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2610|2024-03-19T12:02:55.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2609|2024-04-19T16:50:48.947Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2609</link>
      <description>The permission prompt input delay could expire while the window is not in focus. This makes it vulnerable to clickjacking by malicious websites. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2609|2024-04-19T16:50:48.947Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2605|2024-03-19T12:02:51.825Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2605</link>
      <description>An attacker could have leveraged the Windows Error Reporter to run arbitrary code on the system escaping the sandbox. *Note:* This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2605|2024-03-19T12:02:51.825Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2613|2024-03-19T12:02:56.741Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2613</link>
      <description>Data was not properly sanitized when decoding a QUIC ACK frame; this could have led to unrestricted memory consumption and a crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2613|2024-03-19T12:02:56.741Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2612|2024-03-19T12:02:56.196Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2612</link>
      <description>If an attacker could find a way to trigger a particular code path in `SafeRefPtr`, it could have triggered a crash or potentially be leveraged to achieve code execution. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2612|2024-03-19T12:02:56.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2608|2024-03-19T12:02:53.467Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2608</link>
      <description>`AppendEncodedAttributeValue(), ExtraSpaceNeededForAttrEncoding()` and `AppendEncodedCharacters()` could have experienced integer overflows, causing underallocation of an output buffer leading to an out of bounds write. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2608|2024-03-19T12:02:53.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2615|2024-03-19T19:07:24.248Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2615</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 123. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2615|2024-03-19T19:07:24.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2614|2024-03-19T12:02:57.272Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2614</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 123, Firefox ESR 115.8, and Thunderbird 115.8. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2614|2024-03-19T12:02:57.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3856|2024-04-16T15:14:06.623Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3856</link>
      <description>A use-after-free could occur during WASM execution if garbage collection ran during the creation of an array. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3856|2024-04-16T15:14:06.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3860|2024-04-16T15:14:07.848Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3860</link>
      <description>An out-of-memory condition during object initialization could result in an empty shape list. If the JIT subsequently traced the object it would crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3860|2024-04-16T15:14:07.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3861|2024-06-11T12:40:15.856Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3861</link>
      <description>If an AlignedBuffer were assigned to itself, the subsequent self-move could result in an incorrect reference count and later use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3861|2024-06-11T12:40:15.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3857|2024-06-11T12:40:15.302Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3857</link>
      <description>The JIT created incorrect code for arguments in certain cases. This led to potential use-after-free crashes during garbage collection. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3857|2024-06-11T12:40:15.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3302|2024-06-11T12:40:16.505Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3302</link>
      <description>There was no limit to the number of HTTP/2 CONTINUATION frames that would be processed. A server could abuse this to create an Out of Memory condition in the browser. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3302|2024-06-11T12:40:16.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3864|2024-04-24T09:21:23.741Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3864</link>
      <description>Memory safety bug present in Firefox 124, Firefox ESR 115.9, and Thunderbird 115.9. This bug showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort this could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3864|2024-04-24T09:21:23.741Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3852|2024-06-11T12:40:14.586Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3852</link>
      <description>GetBoundName could return the wrong version of an object when JIT optimizations were applied. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3852|2024-06-11T12:40:14.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3853|2024-06-11T12:40:18.950Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3853</link>
      <description>A use-after-free could result if a JavaScript realm was in the process of being initialized when a garbage collection started. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3853|2024-06-11T12:40:18.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3865|2024-04-16T15:14:09.894Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3865</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 124. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3865|2024-04-16T15:14:09.894Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3854|2024-06-11T12:40:14.871Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3854</link>
      <description>In some code patterns the JIT incorrectly optimized switch statements and generated code with out-of-bounds-reads. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3854|2024-06-11T12:40:14.871Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3858|2024-04-16T15:14:07.244Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3858</link>
      <description>It was possible to mutate a JavaScript object so that the JIT could crash while tracing it. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3858|2024-04-16T15:14:07.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3862|2024-04-16T15:14:08.672Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3862</link>
      <description>The MarkStack assignment operator, part of the JavaScript engine, could access uninitialized memory if it were used in a self-assignment. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3862|2024-04-16T15:14:08.672Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3863|2024-06-11T12:40:16.167Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3863</link>
      <description>The executable file warning was not presented when downloading .xrm-ms files.  
*Note: This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3863|2024-06-11T12:40:16.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3859|2024-06-11T12:40:15.584Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3859</link>
      <description>On 32-bit versions there were integer-overflows that led to an out-of-bounds-read that potentially could be triggered by a malformed OpenType font. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3859|2024-06-11T12:40:15.584Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3855|2024-04-16T15:14:06.282Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3855</link>
      <description>In certain cases the JIT incorrectly optimized MSubstr operations, which led to out-of-bounds reads. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3855|2024-04-16T15:14:06.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4777|2024-05-14T17:21:24.864Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4777</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 125, Firefox ESR 115.10, and Thunderbird 115.10. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4777|2024-05-14T17:21:24.864Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4367|2024-05-14T17:21:23.486Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4367</link>
      <description>A type check was missing when handling fonts in PDF.js, which would allow arbitrary JavaScript execution in the PDF.js context. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4367|2024-05-14T17:21:23.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4776|2024-06-04T17:53:32.797Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4776</link>
      <description>A file dialog shown while in full-screen mode could have resulted in the window remaining disabled. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4776|2024-06-04T17:53:32.797Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4771|2024-06-06T19:52:20.334Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4771</link>
      <description>A memory allocation check was missing which would lead to a use-after-free if the allocation failed. This could have triggered a crash or potentially be leveraged to achieve code execution. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4771|2024-06-06T19:52:20.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4767|2024-05-14T17:21:23.746Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4767</link>
      <description>If the `browser.privatebrowsing.autostart` preference is enabled, IndexedDB files were not properly deleted when the window was closed. This preference is disabled by default in Firefox. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4767|2024-05-14T17:21:23.746Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4766|2024-06-04T17:54:37.373Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4766</link>
      <description>Different techniques existed to obscure the fullscreen notification in Firefox for Android.  These could have lead to potential user confusion and spoofing attacks.
*This bug only affects Firefox for Android. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4766|2024-06-04T17:54:37.373Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4770|2024-05-14T17:21:24.594Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4770</link>
      <description>When saving a page to PDF, certain font styles could have led to a potential use-after-free crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4770|2024-05-14T17:21:24.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4765|2024-05-14T17:21:25.339Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4765</link>
      <description>Web application manifests were stored by using an insecure MD5 hash which allowed for a hash collision to overwrite another application's manifest. This could have been exploited to run arbitrary code in another application's context. 
*This issue only affects Firefox for Android. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4765|2024-05-14T17:21:25.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4773|2024-05-14T17:21:26.363Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4773</link>
      <description>When a network error occurred during page load, the prior content could have remained in view with a blank URL bar. This could have been used to obfuscate a spoofed web site. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4773|2024-05-14T17:21:26.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4769|2024-05-14T17:21:24.318Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4769</link>
      <description>When importing resources using Web Workers, error messages would distinguish the difference between `application/javascript` responses and non-script responses.  This could have been abused to learn information cross-origin. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4769|2024-05-14T17:21:24.318Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4768|2024-05-14T17:21:24.047Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4768</link>
      <description>A bug in popup notifications' interaction with WebAuthn made it easier for an attacker to trick a user into granting permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4768|2024-05-14T17:21:24.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4772|2024-05-14T17:21:26.111Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4772</link>
      <description>An HTTP digest authentication nonce value was generated using `rand()` which could lead to predictable values. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4772|2024-05-14T17:21:26.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4764|2024-06-04T17:55:43.516Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4764</link>
      <description>Multiple WebRTC threads could have claimed a newly connected audio input leading to use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4764|2024-06-04T17:55:43.516Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4775|2024-06-04T17:56:05.266Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4775</link>
      <description>An iterator stop condition was missing when handling WASM code in the built-in profiler, potentially leading to invalid memory access and undefined behavior. *Note:* This issue only affects the application when the profiler is running. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4775|2024-06-04T17:56:05.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4774|2024-05-14T17:21:26.609Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4774</link>
      <description>The `ShmemCharMapHashEntry()` code was susceptible to potentially undefined behavior by bypassing the move semantics for one of its data members. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4774|2024-05-14T17:21:26.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4778|2024-06-04T17:56:34.311Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4778</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 125. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4778|2024-06-04T17:56:34.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29944|2024-03-22T16:18:28.977Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29944</link>
      <description>An attacker was able to inject an event handler into a privileged object that would allow arbitrary JavaScript execution in the parent process. Note: This vulnerability affects Desktop Firefox only, it does not affect mobile versions of Firefox. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.0.1 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29944|2024-03-22T16:18:28.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29943|2024-03-22T12:55:39.866Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29943</link>
      <description>An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript object by fooling range-based bounds check elimination. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29943|2024-03-22T12:55:39.866Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1555|2024-06-04T17:59:28.932Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1555</link>
      <description>When opening a website using the `firefox://` protocol handler, SameSite cookies were not properly respected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1555|2024-06-04T17:59:28.932Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1554|2024-02-20T13:21:37.414Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1554</link>
      <description>The `fetch()` API and navigation incorrectly shared the same cache, as the cache key did not include the optional headers `fetch()` may contain.  Under the correct circumstances, an attacker may have been able to poison the local browser cache by priming it with a `fetch()` response controlled by the additional headers. Upon navigation to the same URL, the user would see the cached response instead of the expected response. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1554|2024-02-20T13:21:37.414Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1549|2024-02-20T19:23:35.141Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1549</link>
      <description>If a website set a large custom cursor, portions of the cursor could have overlapped with the permission dialog, potentially resulting in user confusion and unexpected granted permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1549|2024-02-20T19:23:35.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1553|2024-02-20T19:23:41.022Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1553</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 122, Firefox ESR 115.7, and Thunderbird 115.7. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1553|2024-02-20T19:23:41.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1552|2024-02-20T19:23:39.596Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1552</link>
      <description>Incorrect code generation could have led to unexpected numeric conversions and potential undefined behavior.*Note:* This issue only affects 32-bit ARM devices. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1552|2024-02-20T19:23:39.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1548|2024-02-20T19:23:33.739Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1548</link>
      <description>A website could have obscured the fullscreen notification by using a dropdown select input element. This could have led to user confusion and possible spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1548|2024-02-20T19:23:33.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1551|2024-02-20T19:23:38.186Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1551</link>
      <description>Set-Cookie response headers were being incorrectly honored in multipart HTTP responses. If an attacker could control the Content-Type response header, as well as control part of the response body, they could inject Set-Cookie response headers that would have been honored by the browser. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1551|2024-02-20T19:23:38.186Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1547|2024-06-04T18:00:44.564Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1547</link>
      <description>Through a series of API calls and redirects, an attacker-controlled alert dialog could have been displayed on another website (with the victim website's URL shown). This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1547|2024-06-04T18:00:44.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1546|2024-02-20T19:23:30.714Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1546</link>
      <description>When storing and re-accessing data on a networking channel, the length of buffers may have been confused, resulting in an out-of-bounds memory read. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1546|2024-02-20T19:23:30.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1550|2024-02-20T19:23:36.552Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1550</link>
      <description>A malicious website could have used a combination of exiting fullscreen mode and `requestPointerLock` to cause the user's mouse to be re-positioned unexpectedly, which could have led to user confusion and inadvertently granting permissions they did not intend to grant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1550|2024-02-20T19:23:36.552Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1557|2024-02-20T13:21:38.413Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1557</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 122. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1557|2024-02-20T13:21:38.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1556|2024-06-04T18:01:33.835Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1556</link>
      <description>The incorrect object was checked for NULL in the built-in profiler, potentially leading to invalid memory access and undefined behavior. *Note:* This issue only affects the application when the profiler is running. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1556|2024-06-04T18:01:33.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-11T12:40:13.093Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5691</link>
      <description>By tricking the browser with a `X-Frame-Options` header, a sandboxed iframe could have presented a button that, if clicked by a user, would bypass restrictions to open a new window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-11T12:40:13.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5687|2024-06-11T16:16:51.765Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5687</link>
      <description>If a specific sequence of actions is performed when opening a new tab, the triggering principal associated with the new tab may have been incorrect. The triggering principal is used to calculate many values, including the `Referer` and `Sec-*` headers, meaning there is the potential for incorrect security checks within the browser in addition to incorrect or misleading information sent to remote websites.
*This bug only affects Firefox for Android. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5687|2024-06-11T16:16:51.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5701|2024-06-11T12:40:18.692Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5701</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 126. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5701|2024-06-11T12:40:18.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-11T16:16:40.610Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5700</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 126, Firefox ESR 115.11, and Thunderbird 115.11. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-11T16:16:40.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-11T14:02:15.786Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5690</link>
      <description>By monitoring the time certain operations take, an attacker could have guessed which external protocol handlers were functional on a user's system. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-11T14:02:15.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5697|2024-06-11T14:03:17.234Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5697</link>
      <description>A website was able to detect when a user took a screenshot of a page using the built-in Screenshot functionality in Firefox. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5697|2024-06-11T14:03:17.234Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5696|2024-06-11T12:40:13.963Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5696</link>
      <description>By manipulating the text in an `&amp;lt;input&amp;gt;` tag, an attacker could have caused corrupt memory leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5696|2024-06-11T12:40:13.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5699|2024-06-11T12:40:18.427Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5699</link>
      <description>In violation of spec, cookie prefixes such as `__Secure` were being ignored if they were not correctly capitalized - by spec they should be checked with a case-insensitive comparison. This could have resulted in the browser not correctly honoring the behaviors specified by the prefix. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5699|2024-06-11T12:40:18.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5695|2024-06-11T14:03:31.199Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5695</link>
      <description>If an out-of-memory condition occurs at a specific point using allocations in the probabilistic heap checker, an assertion could have been triggered, and in rarer situations, memory corruption could have occurred. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5695|2024-06-11T14:03:31.199Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5694|2024-06-11T12:40:17.378Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5694</link>
      <description>An attacker could have caused a use-after-free in the JavaScript engine to read memory in the JavaScript string section of the heap. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5694|2024-06-11T12:40:17.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5698|2024-06-11T12:40:18.183Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5698</link>
      <description>By manipulating the fullscreen feature while opening a data-list, an attacker could have overlaid a text box over the address bar. This could have led to user confusion and possible spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5698|2024-06-11T12:40:18.183Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-11T12:40:13.675Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5693</link>
      <description>Offscreen Canvas did not properly track cross-origin tainting, which could be used to access image data from another site in violation of same-origin policy. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-11T12:40:13.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5689|2024-06-11T14:49:43.183Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5689</link>
      <description>In addition to detecting when a user was taking a screenshot (XXX), a website was able to overlay the 'My Shots' button that appeared, and direct the user to a replica Firefox Screenshots page that could be used for phishing. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5689|2024-06-11T14:49:43.183Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-11T12:40:12.457Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5688</link>
      <description>If a garbage collection was triggered at the right time, a use-after-free could have occurred during object transplant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-11T12:40:12.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5692|2024-06-11T12:40:13.370Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5692</link>
      <description>On Windows, when using the 'Save As' functionality, an attacker could have tricked the browser into saving the file with a disallowed extension such as `.url` by including an invalid character in the extension. *Note:* This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5692|2024-06-11T12:40:13.370Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5702|2024-06-11T12:40:12.176Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5702</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in the networking stack could have led to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5702|2024-06-11T12:40:12.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5388|2024-03-19T12:02:54.004Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5388</link>
      <description>NSS was susceptible to a timing side-channel attack when performing RSA decryption. This attack could potentially allow an attacker to recover the private data. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5388|2024-03-19T12:02:54.004Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-12T18:33:20.746Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5691</link>
      <description>By tricking the browser with a `X-Frame-Options` header, a sandboxed iframe could have presented a button that, if clicked by a user, would bypass restrictions to open a new window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-12T18:33:20.746Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5694|2024-06-12T18:17:35.413Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5694</link>
      <description>An attacker could have caused a use-after-free in the JavaScript engine to read memory in the JavaScript string section of the heap. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5694|2024-06-12T18:17:35.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-11T12:40:14.287Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5700</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 126, Firefox ESR 115.11, and Thunderbird 115.11. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-11T12:40:14.287Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-11T12:40:12.752Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5690</link>
      <description>By monitoring the time certain operations take, an attacker could have guessed which external protocol handlers were functional on a user's system. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-11T12:40:12.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5695|2024-06-14T03:55:39.501Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5695</link>
      <description>If an out-of-memory condition occurs at a specific point using allocations in the probabilistic heap checker, an assertion could have been triggered, and in rarer situations, memory corruption could have occurred. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5695|2024-06-14T03:55:39.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-14T03:55:42.740Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5700</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 126, Firefox ESR 115.11, and Thunderbird 115.11. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-14T03:55:42.740Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-14T03:55:36.444Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5691</link>
      <description>By tricking the browser with a `X-Frame-Options` header, a sandboxed iframe could have presented a button that, if clicked by a user, would bypass restrictions to open a new window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-14T03:55:36.444Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5702|2024-06-14T03:55:44.267Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5702</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in the networking stack could have led to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5702|2024-06-14T03:55:44.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5701|2024-06-14T03:55:43.507Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5701</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 126. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5701|2024-06-14T03:55:43.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5696|2024-06-14T03:55:40.349Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5696</link>
      <description>By manipulating the text in an `&amp;lt;input&amp;gt;` tag, an attacker could have caused corrupt memory leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5696|2024-06-14T03:55:40.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5692|2024-06-14T03:55:37.156Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5692</link>
      <description>On Windows 10, when using the 'Save As' functionality, an attacker could have tricked the browser into saving the file with a disallowed extension such as `.url` by including an invalid character in the extension. *Note:* This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5692|2024-06-14T03:55:37.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5694|2024-06-14T03:55:34.030Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5694</link>
      <description>An attacker could have caused a use-after-free in the JavaScript engine to read memory in the JavaScript string section of the heap. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5694|2024-06-14T03:55:34.030Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-14T03:55:38.688Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5693</link>
      <description>Offscreen Canvas did not properly track cross-origin tainting, which could be used to access image data from another site in violation of same-origin policy. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-14T03:55:38.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5697|2024-06-14T03:55:41.098Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5697</link>
      <description>A website was able to detect when a user took a screenshot of a page using the built-in Screenshot functionality in Firefox. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5697|2024-06-14T03:55:41.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5699|2024-06-14T03:55:41.870Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5699</link>
      <description>In violation of spec, cookie prefixes such as `__Secure` were being ignored if they were not correctly capitalized - by spec they should be checked with a case-insensitive comparison. This could have resulted in the browser not correctly honoring the behaviors specified by the prefix. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5699|2024-06-14T03:55:41.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-14T03:55:33.281Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5688</link>
      <description>If a garbage collection was triggered at the right time, a use-after-free could have occurred during object transplant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-14T03:55:33.281Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5689|2024-06-14T03:55:34.783Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5689</link>
      <description>In addition to detecting when a user was taking a screenshot (XXX), a website was able to overlay the 'My Shots' button that appeared, and direct the user to a replica Firefox Screenshots page that could be used for phishing. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5689|2024-06-14T03:55:34.783Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-14T03:55:35.603Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5690</link>
      <description>By monitoring the time certain operations take, an attacker could have guessed which external protocol handlers were functional on a user's system. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-14T03:55:35.603Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-21T18:15:54.759Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5688</link>
      <description>If a garbage collection was triggered at the right time, a use-after-free could have occurred during object transplant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5688|2024-06-21T18:15:54.759Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3863|2024-06-21T18:16:01.262Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3863</link>
      <description>The executable file warning was not presented when downloading .xrm-ms files.  
*Note: This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3863|2024-06-21T18:16:01.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3857|2024-06-21T18:15:59.609Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3857</link>
      <description>The JIT created incorrect code for arguments in certain cases. This led to potential use-after-free crashes during garbage collection. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3857|2024-06-21T18:15:59.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5696|2024-06-21T18:15:57.462Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5696</link>
      <description>By manipulating the text in an `&amp;lt;input&amp;gt;` tag, an attacker could have caused corrupt memory leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5696|2024-06-21T18:15:57.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3859|2024-06-21T18:16:00.213Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3859</link>
      <description>On 32-bit versions there were integer-overflows that led to an out-of-bounds-read that potentially could be triggered by a malformed OpenType font. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3859|2024-06-21T18:16:00.213Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-21T18:15:55.850Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5691</link>
      <description>By tricking the browser with a `X-Frame-Options` header, a sandboxed iframe could have presented a button that, if clicked by a user, would bypass restrictions to open a new window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5691|2024-06-21T18:15:55.850Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5692|2024-06-21T18:15:56.403Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5692</link>
      <description>On Windows 10, when using the 'Save As' functionality, an attacker could have tricked the browser into saving the file with a disallowed extension such as `.url` by including an invalid character in the extension. *Note:* This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5692|2024-06-21T18:15:56.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-21T18:15:55.293Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5690</link>
      <description>By monitoring the time certain operations take, an attacker could have guessed which external protocol handlers were functional on a user's system. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5690|2024-06-21T18:15:55.293Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2608|2024-06-21T18:52:18.600Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2608</link>
      <description>`AppendEncodedAttributeValue(), ExtraSpaceNeededForAttrEncoding()` and `AppendEncodedCharacters()` could have experienced integer overflows, causing underallocation of an output buffer leading to an out of bounds write. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2608|2024-06-21T18:52:18.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3302|2024-06-21T18:16:01.831Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3302</link>
      <description>There was no limit to the number of HTTP/2 CONTINUATION frames that would be processed. A server could abuse this to create an Out of Memory condition in the browser. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3302|2024-06-21T18:16:01.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-21T18:15:58.018Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5700</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 126, Firefox ESR 115.11, and Thunderbird 115.11. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5700|2024-06-21T18:15:58.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3852|2024-06-21T18:15:58.554Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3852</link>
      <description>GetBoundName could return the wrong version of an object when JIT optimizations were applied. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3852|2024-06-21T18:15:58.554Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3861|2024-06-21T18:16:00.743Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3861</link>
      <description>If an AlignedBuffer were assigned to itself, the subsequent self-move could result in an incorrect reference count and later use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3861|2024-06-21T18:16:00.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5702|2024-06-21T18:15:54.214Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5702</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in the networking stack could have led to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5702|2024-06-21T18:15:54.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3854|2024-06-21T18:15:59.089Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3854</link>
      <description>In some code patterns the JIT incorrectly optimized switch statements and generated code with out-of-bounds-reads. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3854|2024-06-21T18:15:59.089Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-21T18:15:56.931Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5693</link>
      <description>Offscreen Canvas did not properly track cross-origin tainting, which could be used to access image data from another site in violation of same-origin policy. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5693|2024-06-21T18:15:56.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1552|2024-07-05T17:21:47.180Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1552</link>
      <description>Incorrect code generation could have led to unexpected numeric conversions and potential undefined behavior.*Note:* This issue only affects 32-bit ARM devices. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1552|2024-07-05T17:21:47.180Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2611|2024-07-05T17:21:13.176Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2611</link>
      <description>A missing delay on when pointer lock was used could have allowed a malicious page to trick a user into granting permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2611|2024-07-05T17:21:13.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1551|2024-07-05T17:20:59.781Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1551</link>
      <description>Set-Cookie response headers were being incorrectly honored in multipart HTTP responses. If an attacker could control the Content-Type response header, as well as control part of the response body, they could inject Set-Cookie response headers that would have been honored by the browser. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1551|2024-07-05T17:20:59.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1548|2024-07-05T17:21:47.586Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1548</link>
      <description>A website could have obscured the fullscreen notification by using a dropdown select input element. This could have led to user confusion and possible spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1548|2024-07-05T17:21:47.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1546|2024-07-05T17:21:44.662Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1546</link>
      <description>When storing and re-accessing data on a networking channel, the length of buffers may have been confused, resulting in an out-of-bounds memory read. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1546|2024-07-05T17:21:44.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5388|2024-07-05T17:21:12.662Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5388</link>
      <description>NSS was susceptible to a timing side-channel attack when performing RSA decryption. This attack could potentially allow an attacker to recover the private data. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5388|2024-07-05T17:21:12.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1550|2024-07-05T17:21:44.306Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1550</link>
      <description>A malicious website could have used a combination of exiting fullscreen mode and `requestPointerLock` to cause the user's mouse to be re-positioned unexpectedly, which could have led to user confusion and inadvertently granting permissions they did not intend to grant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 123, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.8, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1550|2024-07-05T17:21:44.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4774|2024-07-05T17:22:50.439Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4774</link>
      <description>The `ShmemCharMapHashEntry()` code was susceptible to potentially undefined behavior by bypassing the move semantics for one of its data members. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4774|2024-07-05T17:22:50.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6604|2024-07-09T15:06:06.130Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6604</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 127, Firefox ESR 115.12, and Thunderbird 115.12. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6604|2024-07-09T15:06:06.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5693|2024-07-09T15:29:15.068Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5693</link>
      <description>Offscreen Canvas did not properly track cross-origin tainting, which could be used to access image data from another site in violation of same-origin policy. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5693|2024-07-09T15:29:15.068Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6615|2024-07-09T15:05:19.743Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6615</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 127. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6615|2024-07-09T15:05:19.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6608|2024-07-10T16:31:59.234Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6608</link>
      <description>It was possible to move the cursor using pointerlock from an iframe. This allowed moving the cursor outside of the viewport and the Firefox window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6608|2024-07-10T16:31:59.234Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6602|2024-07-10T20:14:24.710Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6602</link>
      <description>A mismatch between allocator and deallocator could have lead to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6602|2024-07-10T20:14:24.710Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6611|2024-07-10T20:28:20.273Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6611</link>
      <description>A nested iframe, triggering a cross-site navigation, could send SameSite=Strict or Lax cookies. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6611|2024-07-10T20:28:20.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6613|2024-07-11T15:08:46.394Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6613</link>
      <description>The frame iterator could get stuck in a loop when encountering certain wasm frames leading to incorrect stack traces. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6613|2024-07-11T15:08:46.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6603|2024-07-11T15:14:25.435Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6603</link>
      <description>In an out-of-memory scenario an allocation could fail but free would have been called on the pointer afterwards leading to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6603|2024-07-11T15:14:25.435Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6607|2024-07-15T21:37:18.753Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6607</link>
      <description>It was possible to prevent a user from exiting pointerlock when pressing escape and to overlay customValidity notifications from a `&amp;lt;select&amp;gt;` element over certain permission prompts. This could be used to confuse a user into giving a site unintended permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6607|2024-07-15T21:37:18.753Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6605|2024-07-17T15:22:59.569Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6605</link>
      <description>Firefox Android allowed immediate interaction with permission prompts. This could be used for tapjacking. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6605|2024-07-17T15:22:59.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6607|2024-07-17T20:21:05.514Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6607</link>
      <description>It was possible to prevent a user from exiting pointerlock when pressing escape and to overlay customValidity notifications from a `&amp;lt;select&amp;gt;` element over certain permission prompts. This could be used to confuse a user into giving a site unintended permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6607|2024-07-17T20:21:05.514Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4773|2024-07-23T16:35:01.918Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4773</link>
      <description>When a network error occurred during page load, the prior content could have remained in view with a blank URL bar. This could have been used to obfuscate a spoofed web site. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4773|2024-07-23T16:35:01.918Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4770|2024-07-23T16:32:22.116Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4770</link>
      <description>When saving a page to PDF, certain font styles could have led to a potential use-after-free crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 126, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.11, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4770|2024-07-23T16:32:22.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3864|2024-07-24T19:40:13.901Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3864</link>
      <description>Memory safety bug present in Firefox 124, Firefox ESR 115.9, and Thunderbird 115.9. This bug showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort this could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3864|2024-07-24T19:40:13.901Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3860|2024-07-30T19:53:06.739Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3860</link>
      <description>An out-of-memory condition during object initialization could result in an empty shape list. If the JIT subsequently traced the object it would crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3860|2024-07-30T19:53:06.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2610|2024-08-01T19:18:47.766Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2610</link>
      <description>Using a markup injection an attacker could have stolen nonce values. This could have been used to bypass strict content security policies. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2610|2024-08-01T19:18:47.766Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2611|2024-08-01T19:18:47.977Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2611</link>
      <description>A missing delay on when pointer lock was used could have allowed a malicious page to trick a user into granting permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2611|2024-08-01T19:18:47.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2605|2024-08-01T19:18:48.230Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2605</link>
      <description>An attacker could have leveraged the Windows Error Reporter to run arbitrary code on the system escaping the sandbox. *Note:* This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2605|2024-08-01T19:18:48.230Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2608|2024-08-01T19:18:48.282Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2608</link>
      <description>`AppendEncodedAttributeValue(), ExtraSpaceNeededForAttrEncoding()` and `AppendEncodedCharacters()` could have experienced integer overflows, causing underallocation of an output buffer leading to an out of bounds write. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2608|2024-08-01T19:18:48.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2615|2024-08-01T19:18:47.946Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2615</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 123. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2615|2024-08-01T19:18:47.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2607|2024-08-01T19:18:48.107Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2607</link>
      <description>Return registers were overwritten which could have allowed an attacker to execute arbitrary code. *Note:* This issue only affected Armv7-A systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2607|2024-08-01T19:18:48.107Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2614|2024-08-01T19:18:48.251Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2614</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 123, Firefox ESR 115.8, and Thunderbird 115.8. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2614|2024-08-01T19:18:48.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2606|2024-08-01T19:18:48.194Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2606</link>
      <description>Passing invalid data could have led to invalid wasm values being created, such as arbitrary integers turning into pointer values. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2606|2024-08-01T19:18:48.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2612|2024-08-01T19:18:47.923Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2612</link>
      <description>If an attacker could find a way to trigger a particular code path in `SafeRefPtr`, it could have triggered a crash or potentially be leveraged to achieve code execution. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2612|2024-08-01T19:18:47.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2613|2024-08-01T19:18:48.218Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2613</link>
      <description>Data was not properly sanitized when decoding a QUIC ACK frame; this could have led to unrestricted memory consumption and a crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2613|2024-08-01T19:18:48.218Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2609|2024-08-01T19:18:48.164Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2609</link>
      <description>The permission prompt input delay could expire while the window is not in focus. This makes it vulnerable to clickjacking by malicious websites. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.10, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2609|2024-08-01T19:18:48.164Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 12:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5688|2024-08-01T21:18:07.039Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5688</link>
      <description>If a garbage collection was triggered at the right time, a use-after-free could have occurred during object transplant. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5688|2024-08-01T21:18:07.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6603|2024-08-01T21:41:04.040Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6603</link>
      <description>In an out-of-memory scenario an allocation could fail but free would have been called on the pointer afterwards leading to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6603|2024-08-01T21:41:04.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6600|2024-08-01T21:41:03.960Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6600</link>
      <description>Due to large allocation checks in Angle for GLSL shaders being too lenient an out-of-bounds access could occur when allocating more than 8192 ints in private shader memory on mac OS. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6600|2024-08-01T21:41:03.960Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6611|2024-08-01T21:41:04.049Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6611</link>
      <description>A nested iframe, triggering a cross-site navigation, could send SameSite=Strict or Lax cookies. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6611|2024-08-01T21:41:04.049Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6606|2024-08-01T21:41:04.043Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6606</link>
      <description>Clipboard code failed to check the index on an array access. This could have lead to an out-of-bounds read. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6606|2024-08-01T21:41:04.043Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6602|2024-08-01T21:41:03.998Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6602</link>
      <description>A mismatch between allocator and deallocator could have lead to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6602|2024-08-01T21:41:03.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6612|2024-08-01T21:41:04.060Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6612</link>
      <description>CSP violations generated links in the console tab of the developer tools, pointing to the violating resource. This caused a DNS prefetch which leaked that a CSP violation happened. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6612|2024-08-01T21:41:04.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5700|2024-08-01T21:18:07.031Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5700</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 126, Firefox ESR 115.11, and Thunderbird 115.11. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5700|2024-08-01T21:18:07.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6608|2024-08-01T21:41:04.019Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6608</link>
      <description>It was possible to move the cursor using pointerlock from an iframe. This allowed moving the cursor outside of the viewport and the Firefox window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6608|2024-08-01T21:41:04.019Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6610|2024-08-01T21:41:03.956Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6610</link>
      <description>Form validation popups could capture escape key presses. Therefore, spamming form validation messages could be used to prevent users from exiting full-screen mode. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6610|2024-08-01T21:41:03.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5687|2024-08-01T21:18:06.882Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5687</link>
      <description>If a specific sequence of actions is performed when opening a new tab, the triggering principal associated with the new tab may have been incorrect. The triggering principal is used to calculate many values, including the `Referer` and `Sec-*` headers, meaning there is the potential for incorrect security checks within the browser in addition to incorrect or misleading information sent to remote websites.
*This bug only affects Firefox for Android. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5687|2024-08-01T21:18:06.882Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6609|2024-08-01T21:41:03.946Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6609</link>
      <description>When almost out-of-memory an elliptic curve key which was never allocated could have been freed again. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6609|2024-08-01T21:41:03.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5693|2024-08-01T21:18:06.938Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5693</link>
      <description>Offscreen Canvas did not properly track cross-origin tainting, which could be used to access image data from another site in violation of same-origin policy. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5693|2024-08-01T21:18:06.938Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5701|2024-08-01T21:18:06.997Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5701</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 126. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5701|2024-08-01T21:18:06.997Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6605|2024-08-01T21:41:04.045Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6605</link>
      <description>Firefox Android allowed immediate interaction with permission prompts. This could be used for tapjacking. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6605|2024-08-01T21:41:04.045Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5696|2024-08-01T21:18:07.014Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5696</link>
      <description>By manipulating the text in an `&amp;lt;input&amp;gt;` tag, an attacker could have caused corrupt memory leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5696|2024-08-01T21:18:07.014Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6607|2024-08-01T21:41:03.973Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6607</link>
      <description>It was possible to prevent a user from exiting pointerlock when pressing escape and to overlay customValidity notifications from a `&amp;lt;select&amp;gt;` element over certain permission prompts. This could be used to confuse a user into giving a site unintended permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6607|2024-08-01T21:41:03.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5694|2024-08-01T21:18:06.830Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5694</link>
      <description>An attacker could have caused a use-after-free in the JavaScript engine to read memory in the JavaScript string section of the heap. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5694|2024-08-01T21:18:06.830Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5689|2024-08-01T21:18:06.829Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5689</link>
      <description>In addition to detecting when a user was taking a screenshot (XXX), a website was able to overlay the 'My Shots' button that appeared, and direct the user to a replica Firefox Screenshots page that could be used for phishing. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5689|2024-08-01T21:18:06.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5691|2024-08-01T21:18:06.913Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5691</link>
      <description>By tricking the browser with a `X-Frame-Options` header, a sandboxed iframe could have presented a button that, if clicked by a user, would bypass restrictions to open a new window. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5691|2024-08-01T21:18:06.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6614|2024-08-01T21:41:03.989Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6614</link>
      <description>The frame iterator could get stuck in a loop when encountering certain wasm frames leading to incorrect stack traces. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6614|2024-08-01T21:41:03.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5697|2024-08-01T21:18:06.946Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5697</link>
      <description>A website was able to detect when a user took a screenshot of a page using the built-in Screenshot functionality in Firefox. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5697|2024-08-01T21:18:06.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6613|2024-08-01T21:41:03.948Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6613</link>
      <description>The frame iterator could get stuck in a loop when encountering certain wasm frames leading to incorrect stack traces. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6613|2024-08-01T21:41:03.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5692|2024-08-01T21:18:06.916Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5692</link>
      <description>On Windows 10, when using the 'Save As' functionality, an attacker could have tricked the browser into saving the file with a disallowed extension such as `.url` by including an invalid character in the extension. *Note:* This issue only affected Windows operating systems. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5692|2024-08-01T21:18:06.916Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5690|2024-08-01T21:18:06.700Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5690</link>
      <description>By monitoring the time certain operations take, an attacker could have guessed which external protocol handlers were functional on a user's system. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5690|2024-08-01T21:18:06.700Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6601|2024-08-01T21:41:03.971Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6601</link>
      <description>A race condition could lead to a cross-origin container obtaining permissions of the top-level origin. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6601|2024-08-01T21:41:03.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6615|2024-08-01T21:41:04.046Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6615</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 127 and Thunderbird 127. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6615|2024-08-01T21:41:04.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5695|2024-08-01T21:18:06.986Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5695</link>
      <description>If an out-of-memory condition occurs at a specific point using allocations in the probabilistic heap checker, an assertion could have been triggered, and in rarer situations, memory corruption could have occurred. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5695|2024-08-01T21:18:06.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5699|2024-08-01T21:18:06.876Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5699</link>
      <description>In violation of spec, cookie prefixes such as `__Secure` were being ignored if they were not correctly capitalized - by spec they should be checked with a case-insensitive comparison. This could have resulted in the browser not correctly honoring the behaviors specified by the prefix. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5699|2024-08-01T21:18:06.876Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5702|2024-08-01T21:18:06.890Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5702</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in the networking stack could have led to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 125, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.12, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5702|2024-08-01T21:18:06.890Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5698|2024-08-01T21:18:06.985Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5698</link>
      <description>By manipulating the fullscreen feature while opening a data-list, an attacker could have overlaid a text box over the address bar. This could have led to user confusion and possible spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5698|2024-08-01T21:18:06.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6604|2024-08-01T21:41:03.940Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6604</link>
      <description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 127, Firefox ESR 115.12, and Thunderbird 115.12. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 128, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.13, Thunderbird &lt; 115.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 128.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6604|2024-08-01T21:41:03.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29944|2024-08-02T01:17:58.626Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29944</link>
      <description>An attacker was able to inject an event handler into a privileged object that would allow arbitrary JavaScript execution in the parent process. Note: This vulnerability affects Desktop Firefox only, it does not affect mobile versions of Firefox. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.0.1 and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.9.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29944|2024-08-02T01:17:58.626Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29943|2024-08-02T01:17:58.445Z -- mozilla -- firefox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29943</link>
      <description>An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript object by fooling range-based bounds check elimination. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 124.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29943|2024-08-02T01:17:58.445Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
