<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Mozilla -- Thunderbird</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mozilla/thunderbird.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Mozilla -- Thunderbird</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 12:25:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6819|2024-08-04T09:11:05.160Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6819</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, when running the nsDocShell destructor, a race condition can cause a use-after-free. We are aware of targeted attacks in the wild abusing this flaw. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.7.0, Firefox &lt; 74.0.1, and Firefox ESR &lt; 68.6.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6819|2024-08-04T09:11:05.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 15:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38495|2024-08-04T01:44:22.823Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38495</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Thunderbird 78.13.0. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.1 and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38495|2024-08-04T01:44:22.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6812|2024-08-04T09:11:05.033Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6812</link>
      <description>The first time AirPods are connected to an iPhone, they become named after the user's name by default (e.g. Jane Doe's AirPods.) Websites with camera or microphone permission are able to enumerate device names, disclosing the user's name. To resolve this issue, Firefox added a special case that renames devices containing the substring 'AirPods' to simply 'AirPods'. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.6, Firefox &lt; 74, Firefox &lt; ESR68.6, and Firefox ESR &lt; 68.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6812|2024-08-04T09:11:05.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 21:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12405|2024-08-04T11:56:51.680Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12405</link>
      <description>When browsing a malicious page, a race condition in our SharedWorkerService could occur and lead to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.9.0, Firefox &lt; 77, and Firefox ESR &lt; 68.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12405|2024-08-04T11:56:51.680Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43543|2024-08-04T04:03:06.895Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43543</link>
      <description>Documents loaded with the CSP sandbox directive could have escaped the sandbox's script restriction by embedding additional content. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.4.0, Firefox ESR &lt; 91.4.0, and Firefox &lt; 95.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43543|2024-08-04T04:03:06.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12397|2024-08-04T11:56:52.038Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12397</link>
      <description>By encoding Unicode whitespace characters within the From email header, an attacker can spoof the sender email address that Thunderbird displays. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12397|2024-08-04T11:56:52.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 18:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6811|2024-08-04T09:11:05.163Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6811</link>
      <description>The 'Copy as cURL' feature of Devtools' network tab did not properly escape the HTTP method of a request, which can be controlled by the website. If a user used the 'Copy as Curl' feature and pasted the command into a terminal, it could have resulted in command injection and arbitrary command execution. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.6, Firefox &lt; 74, Firefox &lt; ESR68.6, and Firefox ESR &lt; 68.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6811|2024-08-04T09:11:05.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 21:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6798|2024-08-04T09:11:05.089Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6798</link>
      <description>If a template tag was used in a select tag, the parser could be confused and allow JavaScript parsing and execution when it should not be allowed. A site that relied on the browser behaving correctly could suffer a cross-site scripting vulnerability as a result. In general, this flaw cannot be exploited through email in the Thunderbird product because scripting is disabled when reading mail, but is potentially a risk in browser or browser-like contexts. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.5, Firefox &lt; 73, and Firefox &lt; ESR68.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6798|2024-08-04T09:11:05.089Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 04:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43529|2024-08-04T03:55:29.265Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43529</link>
      <description>Thunderbird versions prior to 91.3.0 are vulnerable to the heap overflow described in CVE-2021-43527 when processing S/MIME messages. Thunderbird versions 91.3.0 and later will not call the vulnerable code when processing S/MIME messages that contain certificates with DER-encoded DSA or RSA-PSS signatures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43529|2024-08-04T03:55:29.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43542|2024-08-04T04:03:08.166Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43542</link>
      <description>Using XMLHttpRequest, an attacker could have identified installed applications by probing error messages for loading external protocols. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.4.0, Firefox ESR &lt; 91.4.0, and Firefox &lt; 95.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43542|2024-08-04T04:03:08.166Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12398|2024-08-04T11:56:52.019Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12398</link>
      <description>If Thunderbird is configured to use STARTTLS for an IMAP server, and the server sends a PREAUTH response, then Thunderbird will continue with an unencrypted connection, causing email data to be sent without protection. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.9.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12398|2024-08-04T11:56:52.019Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38500|2024-08-04T01:44:22.823Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38500</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 92 and Firefox ESR 91.1. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 78.15, Thunderbird &lt; 91.2, Firefox ESR &lt; 91.2, Firefox ESR &lt; 78.15, and Firefox &lt; 93.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38500|2024-08-04T01:44:22.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43541|2024-08-04T04:03:06.909Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43541</link>
      <description>When invoking protocol handlers for external protocols, a supplied parameter URL containing spaces was not properly escaped. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.4.0, Firefox ESR &lt; 91.4.0, and Firefox &lt; 95.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43541|2024-08-04T04:03:06.909Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:20:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6792|2024-08-04T09:11:05.119Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6792</link>
      <description>When deriving an identifier for an email message, uninitialized memory was used in addition to the message contents. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6792|2024-08-04T09:11:05.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 04:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43536|2024-08-04T03:55:29.308Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43536</link>
      <description>Under certain circumstances, asynchronous functions could have caused a navigation to fail but expose the target URL. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.4.0, Firefox ESR &lt; 91.4.0, and Firefox &lt; 95.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43536|2024-08-04T03:55:29.308Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6806|2024-08-04T09:11:05.025Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6806</link>
      <description>By carefully crafting promise resolutions, it was possible to cause an out-of-bounds read off the end of an array resized during script execution. This could have led to memory corruption and a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.6, Firefox &lt; 74, Firefox &lt; ESR68.6, and Firefox ESR &lt; 68.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6806|2024-08-04T09:11:05.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 21:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6820|2024-08-04T09:11:05.035Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6820</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, when handling a ReadableStream, a race condition can cause a use-after-free. We are aware of targeted attacks in the wild abusing this flaw. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.7.0, Firefox &lt; 74.0.1, and Firefox ESR &lt; 68.6.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6820|2024-08-04T09:11:05.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 15:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43538|2024-08-04T04:03:07.658Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43538</link>
      <description>By misusing a race in our notification code, an attacker could have forcefully hidden the notification for pages that had received full screen and pointer lock access, which could have been used for spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.4.0, Firefox ESR &lt; 91.4.0, and Firefox &lt; 95.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43538|2024-08-04T04:03:07.658Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12399|2024-08-04T11:56:51.648Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12399</link>
      <description>NSS has shown timing differences when performing DSA signatures, which was exploitable and could eventually leak private keys. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.9.0, Firefox &lt; 77, and Firefox ESR &lt; 68.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12399|2024-08-04T11:56:51.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:52:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38502|2024-08-04T01:44:22.910Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38502</link>
      <description>Thunderbird ignored the configuration to require STARTTLS security for an SMTP connection. A MITM could perform a downgrade attack to intercept transmitted messages, or could take control of the authenticated session to execute SMTP commands chosen by the MITM. If an unprotected authentication method was configured, the MITM could obtain the authentication credentials, too. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38502|2024-08-04T01:44:22.910Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6793|2024-08-04T09:11:05.026Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6793</link>
      <description>When processing an email message with an ill-formed envelope, Thunderbird could read data from a random memory location. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6793|2024-08-04T09:11:05.026Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 04:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43539|2024-08-04T04:03:06.894Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43539</link>
      <description>Failure to correctly record the location of live pointers across wasm instance calls resulted in a GC occurring within the call not tracing those live pointers. This could have led to a use-after-free causing a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.4.0, Firefox ESR &lt; 91.4.0, and Firefox &lt; 95.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43539|2024-08-04T04:03:06.894Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6825|2024-08-04T09:11:05.021Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6825</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers and community members Tyson Smith and Christian Holler reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 74 and Firefox ESR 68.6. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.7.0, Firefox ESR &lt; 68.7, and Firefox &lt; 75.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6825|2024-08-04T09:11:05.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 15:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43537|2024-08-04T03:55:29.292Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43537</link>
      <description>An incorrect type conversion of sizes from 64bit to 32bit integers allowed an attacker to corrupt memory leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.4.0, Firefox ESR &lt; 91.4.0, and Firefox &lt; 95.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43537|2024-08-04T03:55:29.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6821|2024-08-04T09:11:05.018Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6821</link>
      <description>When reading from areas partially or fully outside the source resource with WebGL's &lt;code&gt;copyTexSubImage&lt;/code&gt; method, the specification requires the returned values be zero. Previously, this memory was uninitialized, leading to potentially sensitive data disclosure. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.7.0, Firefox ESR &lt; 68.7, and Firefox &lt; 75.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6821|2024-08-04T09:11:05.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 15:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43546|2024-08-04T04:03:08.444Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43546</link>
      <description>It was possible to recreate previous cursor spoofing attacks against users with a zoomed native cursor. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.4.0, Firefox ESR &lt; 91.4.0, and Firefox &lt; 95.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43546|2024-08-04T04:03:08.444Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6800|2024-08-04T09:11:05.116Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6800</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers and community members reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 72 and Firefox ESR 68.4. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. In general, these flaws cannot be exploited through email in the Thunderbird product because scripting is disabled when reading mail, but are potentially risks in browser or browser-like contexts. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.5, Firefox &lt; 73, and Firefox &lt; ESR68.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6800|2024-08-04T09:11:05.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 04:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38496|2024-08-04T01:44:23.406Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38496</link>
      <description>During operations on MessageTasks, a task may have been removed while it was still scheduled, resulting in memory corruption and a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 78.15, Thunderbird &lt; 91.2, Firefox ESR &lt; 91.2, Firefox ESR &lt; 78.15, and Firefox &lt; 93.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38496|2024-08-04T01:44:23.406Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43528|2024-08-04T03:55:29.399Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43528</link>
      <description>Thunderbird unexpectedly enabled JavaScript in the composition area. The JavaScript execution context was limited to this area and did not receive chrome-level privileges, but could be used as a stepping stone to further an attack with other vulnerabilities. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.4.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43528|2024-08-04T03:55:29.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:21:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12410|2024-08-04T11:56:51.579Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12410</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 76 and Firefox ESR 68.8. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.9.0, Firefox &lt; 77, and Firefox ESR &lt; 68.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12410|2024-08-04T11:56:51.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6794|2024-08-04T09:11:05.144Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6794</link>
      <description>If a user saved passwords before Thunderbird 60 and then later set a master password, an unencrypted copy of these passwords is still accessible. This is because the older stored password file was not deleted when the data was copied to a new format starting in Thunderbird 60. The new master password is added only on the new file. This could allow the exposure of stored password data outside of user expectations. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6794|2024-08-04T09:11:05.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 04:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6807|2024-08-04T09:11:05.120Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6807</link>
      <description>When a device was changed while a stream was about to be destroyed, the &lt;code&gt;stream-reinit&lt;/code&gt; task may have been executed after the stream was destroyed, causing a use-after-free and a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.6, Firefox &lt; 74, Firefox &lt; ESR68.6, and Firefox ESR &lt; 68.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6807|2024-08-04T09:11:05.120Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 21:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6822|2024-08-04T09:11:05.085Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6822</link>
      <description>On 32-bit builds, an out of bounds write could have occurred when processing an image larger than 4 GB in &lt;code&gt;GMPDecodeData&lt;/code&gt;. It is possible that with enough effort this could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.7.0, Firefox ESR &lt; 68.7, and Firefox &lt; 75.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6822|2024-08-04T09:11:05.085Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 15:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6814|2024-08-04T09:11:05.046Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6814</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox and Thunderbird 68.5. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.6, Firefox &lt; 74, Firefox &lt; ESR68.6, and Firefox ESR &lt; 68.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6814|2024-08-04T09:11:05.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 21:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12406|2024-08-04T11:56:51.745Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12406</link>
      <description>Mozilla Developer Iain Ireland discovered a missing type check during unboxed objects removal, resulting in a crash. We presume that with enough effort that it could be exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.9.0, Firefox &lt; 77, and Firefox ESR &lt; 68.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12406|2024-08-04T11:56:51.745Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:45:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6805|2024-08-04T09:11:05.079Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6805</link>
      <description>When removing data about an origin whose tab was recently closed, a use-after-free could occur in the Quota manager, resulting in a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.6, Firefox &lt; 74, Firefox &lt; ESR68.6, and Firefox ESR &lt; 68.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6805|2024-08-04T09:11:05.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 21:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6795|2024-08-04T09:11:05.139Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6795</link>
      <description>When processing a message that contains multiple S/MIME signatures, a bug in the MIME processing code caused a null pointer dereference, leading to an unexploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6795|2024-08-04T09:11:05.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 04:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6797|2024-08-04T09:11:05.129Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6797</link>
      <description>By downloading a file with the .fileloc extension, a semi-privileged extension could launch an arbitrary application on the user's computer. The attacker is restricted as they are unable to download non-quarantined files or supply command line arguments to the application, limiting the impact. Note: this issue only occurs on Mac OSX. Other operating systems are unaffected. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 68.5, Firefox &lt; 73, and Firefox &lt; ESR68.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6797|2024-08-04T09:11:05.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 04:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43545|2024-08-04T04:03:06.902Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43545</link>
      <description>Using the Location API in a loop could have caused severe application hangs and crashes. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.4.0, Firefox ESR &lt; 91.4.0, and Firefox &lt; 95.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43545|2024-08-04T04:03:06.902Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:19:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1936|2024-03-04T21:31:54.044Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1936</link>
      <description>The encrypted subject of an email message could be incorrectly and permanently assigned to an arbitrary other email message in Thunderbird's local cache. Consequently, when replying to the contaminated email message, the user might accidentally leak the confidential subject to a third party. While this update fixes the bug and avoids future message contamination, it does not automatically repair existing contaminations. Users are advised to use the repair folder functionality, which is available from the context menu of email folders, which will erase incorrect subject assignments. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1936|2024-03-04T21:31:54.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 21:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1936|2024-08-01T18:56:22.343Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1936</link>
      <description>The encrypted subject of an email message could be incorrectly and permanently assigned to an arbitrary other email message in Thunderbird's local cache. Consequently, when replying to the contaminated email message, the user might accidentally leak the confidential subject to a third party. While this update fixes the bug and avoids future message contamination, it does not automatically repair existing contaminations. Users are advised to use the repair folder functionality, which is available from the context menu of email folders, which will erase incorrect subject assignments. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1936|2024-08-01T18:56:22.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 21:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
