<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Mozilla -- Thunderbird</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mozilla/thunderbird.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Mozilla -- Thunderbird</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 07:20:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29909|2024-08-03T06:33:43.165Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29909</link>
      <description>Documents in deeply-nested cross-origin browsing contexts could have obtained permissions granted to the top-level origin, bypassing the existing prompt and wrongfully inheriting the top-level permissions. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.9, Firefox ESR &lt; 91.9, and Firefox &lt; 100.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29909|2024-08-03T06:33:43.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28281|2024-08-03T05:48:37.901Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28281</link>
      <description>If a compromised content process sent an unexpected number of WebAuthN Extensions in a Register command to the parent process, an out of bounds write would have occurred leading to memory corruption and a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.8, Firefox &lt; 99, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28281|2024-08-03T05:48:37.901Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28289|2024-08-03T05:48:37.941Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28289</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers and community members Nika Layzell, Andrew McCreight, Gabriele Svelto, and the Mozilla Fuzzing Team reported memory safety bugs present in Thunderbird 91.7. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.8, Firefox &lt; 99, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28289|2024-08-03T05:48:37.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29913|2024-08-03T06:33:43.161Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29913</link>
      <description>The parent process would not properly check whether the Speech Synthesis feature is enabled, when receiving instructions from a child process. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29913|2024-08-03T06:33:43.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29911|2024-08-03T06:33:43.062Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29911</link>
      <description>An improper implementation of the new iframe sandbox keyword &lt;code&gt;allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation&lt;/code&gt; could lead to script execution without &lt;code&gt;allow-scripts&lt;/code&gt; being present. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.9, Firefox ESR &lt; 91.9, and Firefox &lt; 100.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29911|2024-08-03T06:33:43.062Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3032|2024-08-03T00:53:00.746Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3032</link>
      <description>When receiving an HTML email that contained an &lt;code&gt;iframe&lt;/code&gt; element, which used a &lt;code&gt;srcdoc&lt;/code&gt; attribute to define the inner HTML document, remote objects specified in the nested document, for example images or videos, were not blocked. Rather, the network was accessed, the objects were loaded and displayed. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 102.2.1 and Thunderbird &lt; 91.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3032|2024-08-03T00:53:00.746Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28285|2024-08-03T05:48:37.931Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28285</link>
      <description>When generating the assembly code for &lt;code&gt;MLoadTypedArrayElementHole&lt;/code&gt;, an incorrect AliasSet was used. In conjunction with another vulnerability this could have been used for an out of bounds memory read. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.8, Firefox &lt; 99, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28285|2024-08-03T05:48:37.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28286|2024-08-03T05:48:37.940Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28286</link>
      <description>Due to a layout change, iframe contents could have been rendered outside of its border. This could have led to user confusion or spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.8, Firefox &lt; 99, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28286|2024-08-03T05:48:37.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2226|2024-08-03T00:32:09.375Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2226</link>
      <description>An OpenPGP digital signature includes information about the date when the signature was created. When displaying an email that contains a digital signature, the email's date will be shown. If the dates were different, then Thunderbird didn't report the email as having an invalid signature. If an attacker performed a replay attack, in which an old email with old contents are resent at a later time, it could lead the victim to believe that the statements in the email are current. Fixed versions of Thunderbird will require that the signature's date roughly matches the displayed date of the email. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 102 and Thunderbird &lt; 91.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2226|2024-08-03T00:32:09.375Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1520|2024-08-03T00:10:02.838Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1520</link>
      <description>When viewing an email message A, which contains an attached message B, where B is encrypted or digitally signed or both, Thunderbird may show an incorrect encryption or signature status. After opening and viewing the attached message B, when returning to the display of message A, the message A might be shown with the security status of message B. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1520|2024-08-03T00:10:02.838Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29917|2024-08-03T06:33:43.055Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29917</link>
      <description>Mozilla developers Andrew McCreight, Gabriele Svelto, Tom Ritter and the Mozilla Fuzzing Team reported memory safety bugs present in Firefox 99 and Firefox ESR 91.8. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.9, Firefox ESR &lt; 91.9, and Firefox &lt; 100.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29917|2024-08-03T06:33:43.055Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3034|2024-08-03T01:00:10.217Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3034</link>
      <description>When receiving an HTML email that specified to load an &lt;code&gt;iframe&lt;/code&gt; element from a remote location, a request to the remote document was sent. However, Thunderbird didn't display the document. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 102.2.1 and Thunderbird &lt; 91.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3034|2024-08-03T01:00:10.217Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29916|2024-08-03T06:33:43.182Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29916</link>
      <description>Firefox behaved slightly differently for already known resources when loading CSS resources involving CSS variables. This could have been used to probe the browser history. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.9, Firefox ESR &lt; 91.9, and Firefox &lt; 100.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29916|2024-08-03T06:33:43.182Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3033|2024-08-03T00:53:00.849Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3033</link>
      <description>If a Thunderbird user replied to a crafted HTML email containing a &lt;code&gt;meta&lt;/code&gt; tag, with the &lt;code&gt;meta&lt;/code&gt; tag having the &lt;code&gt;http-equiv="refresh"&lt;/code&gt; attribute, and the content attribute specifying an URL, then Thunderbird started a network request to that URL, regardless of the configuration to block remote content. In combination with certain other HTML elements and attributes in the email, it was possible to execute JavaScript code included in the message in the context of the message compose document. The JavaScript code was able to perform actions including, but probably not limited to, read and modify the contents of the message compose document, including the quoted original message, which could potentially contain the decrypted plaintext of encrypted data in the crafted email. The contents could then be transmitted to the network, either to the URL specified in the META refresh tag, or to a different URL, as the JavaScript code could modify the URL specified in the document. This bug doesn't affect users who have changed the default Message Body display setting to 'simple html' or 'plain text'. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 102.2.1 and Thunderbird &lt; 91.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3033|2024-08-03T00:53:00.849Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29912|2024-08-03T06:33:43.107Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29912</link>
      <description>Requests initiated through reader mode did not properly omit cookies with a SameSite attribute. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.9, Firefox ESR &lt; 91.9, and Firefox &lt; 100.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29912|2024-08-03T06:33:43.107Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1834|2024-08-03T00:17:00.629Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1834</link>
      <description>When displaying the sender of an email, and the sender name contained the Braille Pattern Blank space character multiple times, Thunderbird would have displayed all the spaces. This could have been used by an attacker to send an email message with the attacker's digital signature, that was shown with an arbitrary sender email address chosen by the attacker. If the sender name started with a false email address, followed by many Braille space characters, the attacker's email address was not visible. Because Thunderbird compared the invisible sender address with the signature's email address, if the signing key or certificate was accepted by Thunderbird, the email was shown as having a valid digital signature. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1834|2024-08-03T00:17:00.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29914|2024-08-03T06:33:43.194Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29914</link>
      <description>When reusing existing popups Firefox would have allowed them to cover the fullscreen notification UI, which could have enabled browser spoofing attacks. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.9, Firefox ESR &lt; 91.9, and Firefox &lt; 100.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29914|2024-08-03T06:33:43.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28282|2024-08-03T05:48:37.678Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28282</link>
      <description>By using a link with &lt;code&gt;rel="localization"&lt;/code&gt; a use-after-free could have been triggered by destroying an object during JavaScript execution and then referencing the object through a freed pointer, leading to a potential exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 91.8, Firefox &lt; 99, and Firefox ESR &lt; 91.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28282|2024-08-03T05:48:37.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3155|2024-08-03T01:00:10.866Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3155</link>
      <description>When saving or opening an email attachment on macOS, Thunderbird did not set attribute com.apple.quarantine on the received file. If the received file was an application and the user attempted to open it, then the application was started immediately without asking the user to confirm. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 102.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3155|2024-08-03T01:00:10.866Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1936|2024-08-01T18:56:22.343Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1936</link>
      <description>The encrypted subject of an email message could be incorrectly and permanently assigned to an arbitrary other email message in Thunderbird's local cache. Consequently, when replying to the contaminated email message, the user might accidentally leak the confidential subject to a third party. While this update fixes the bug and avoids future message contamination, it does not automatically repair existing contaminations. Users are advised to use the repair folder functionality, which is available from the context menu of email folders, which will erase incorrect subject assignments. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1936|2024-08-01T18:56:22.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 21:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1936|2024-03-04T21:31:54.044Z -- mozilla -- thunderbird</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1936</link>
      <description>The encrypted subject of an email message could be incorrectly and permanently assigned to an arbitrary other email message in Thunderbird's local cache. Consequently, when replying to the contaminated email message, the user might accidentally leak the confidential subject to a third party. While this update fixes the bug and avoids future message contamination, it does not automatically repair existing contaminations. Users are advised to use the repair folder functionality, which is available from the context menu of email folders, which will erase incorrect subject assignments. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 115.8.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1936|2024-03-04T21:31:54.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 21:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
