<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for octobercms -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/octobercms/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for octobercms -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:19:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23655|2024-08-03T03:51:44.208Z -- octobercms -- october
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23655</link>
      <description>Octobercms is a self-hosted CMS platform based on the Laravel PHP Framework. Affected versions of OctoberCMS did not validate gateway server signatures. As a result non-authoritative gateway servers may be used to exfiltrate user private keys. Users are advised to upgrade their installations to build 474 or v1.1.10. The only known workaround is to manually apply the patch (e3b455ad587282f0fbcb7763c6d9c3d000ca1e6a) which adds server signature validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23655|2024-08-03T03:51:44.208Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 23:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21264|2024-08-03T18:09:14.926Z -- octobercms -- october
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21264</link>
      <description>October is a free, open-source, self-hosted CMS platform based on the Laravel PHP Framework. A bypass of CVE-2020-26231 (fixed in 1.0.470/471 and 1.1.1) was discovered that has the same impact as CVE-2020-26231 &amp; CVE-2020-15247. An authenticated backend user with the `cms.manage_pages`, `cms.manage_layouts`, or `cms.manage_partials` permissions who would **normally** not be permitted to provide PHP code to be executed by the CMS due to `cms.enableSafeMode` being enabled is able to write specific Twig code to escape the Twig sandbox and execute arbitrary PHP. This is not a problem for anyone that trusts their users with those permissions to normally write &amp; manage PHP within the CMS by not having `cms.enableSafeMode` enabled, but would be a problem for anyone relying on `cms.enableSafeMode` to ensure that users with those permissions in production do not have access to write &amp; execute arbitrary PHP. Issue has been patched in Build 472 (v1.0.472) and v1.1.2. As a workaround, apply https://github.com/octobercms/october/commit/f63519ff1e8d375df30deba63156a2fc97aa9ee7 to your installation manually if unable to upgrade to Build 472 or v1.1.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21264|2024-08-03T18:09:14.926Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 16:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35944|2024-08-03T09:51:59.222Z -- octobercms -- october
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35944</link>
      <description>October is a self-hosted Content Management System (CMS) platform based on the Laravel PHP Framework. This vulnerability only affects installations that rely on the safe mode restriction, commonly used when providing public access to the admin panel. Assuming an attacker has access to the admin panel and permission to open the "Editor" section, they can bypass the Safe Mode (`cms.safe_mode`) restriction to introduce new PHP code in a CMS template using a specially crafted request. The issue has been patched in versions 2.2.34 and 3.0.66.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35944|2024-08-03T09:51:59.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24800|2024-08-03T04:20:50.448Z -- octobercms -- october
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24800</link>
      <description>October/System is the system module for October CMS, a self-hosted CMS platform based on the Laravel PHP Framework. Prior to versions 1.0.476, 1.1.12, and 2.2.15, when the developer allows the user to specify their own filename in the `fromData` method, an unauthenticated user can perform remote code execution (RCE) by exploiting a race condition in the temporary storage directory. This vulnerability affects plugins that expose the `October\Rain\Database\Attach\File::fromData` as a public interface and does not affect vanilla installations of October CMS since this method is not exposed or used by the system internally or externally. The issue has been patched in Build 476 (v1.0.476), v1.1.12, and v2.2.15. Those who are unable to upgrade may apply with patch to their installation manually as a workaround.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24800|2024-08-03T04:20:50.448Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 20:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21265|2024-08-03T18:09:15.269Z -- octobercms -- october
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21265</link>
      <description>October is a free, open-source, self-hosted CMS platform based on the Laravel PHP Framework. In October before version 1.1.2, when running on poorly configured servers (i.e. the server routes any request, regardless of the HOST header to an October CMS instance) the potential exists for Host Header Poisoning attacks to succeed. This has been addressed in version 1.1.2 by adding a feature to allow a set of trusted hosts to be specified in the application. As a workaround one may set the configuration setting cms.linkPolicy to force.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21265|2024-08-03T18:09:15.269Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 21:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21705|2024-08-03T02:53:35.373Z -- octobercms -- october
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21705</link>
      <description>Octobercms is a self-hosted CMS platform based on the Laravel PHP Framework. In affected versions user input was not properly sanitized before rendering. An authenticated user with the permissions to create, modify and delete website pages can exploit this vulnerability to bypass `cms.safe_mode` / `cms.enableSafeMode` in order to execute arbitrary code. This issue only affects admin panels that rely on safe mode and restricted permissions. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must first have access to the backend area. The issue has been patched in Build 474 (v1.0.474) and v1.1.10. Users unable to upgrade should apply https://github.com/octobercms/library/commit/c393c5ce9ca2c5acc3ed6c9bb0dab5ffd61965fe to your installation manually.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21705|2024-08-03T02:53:35.373Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 19:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24764|2024-07-02T14:31:21.880Z -- octobercms -- october</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24764</link>
      <description>October is a self-hosted CMS platform based on the Laravel PHP Framework. This issue affects authenticated administrators who may be redirected to an untrusted URL using the PageFinder schema.  The resolver for the page finder link schema (`october://`) allowed external links, therefore allowing an open redirect outside the scope of the active host. This vulnerability has been patched in version 3.5.15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24764|2024-07-02T14:31:21.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25637|2024-06-26T15:55:35.578Z -- octobercms -- october</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25637</link>
      <description>October is a self-hosted CMS platform based on the Laravel PHP Framework. The X-October-Request-Handler Header does not sanitize the AJAX handler name and allows unescaped HTML to be reflected back. There is no impact since this vulnerability cannot be exploited through normal browser interactions. This unescaped value is only detectable when using a proxy interception tool. This issue has been patched in version 3.5.15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25637|2024-06-26T15:55:35.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 15:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25637|2024-06-26T20:53:30.074Z -- octobercms -- october</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25637</link>
      <description>October is a self-hosted CMS platform based on the Laravel PHP Framework. The X-October-Request-Handler Header does not sanitize the AJAX handler name and allows unescaped HTML to be reflected back. There is no impact since this vulnerability cannot be exploited through normal browser interactions. This unescaped value is only detectable when using a proxy interception tool. This issue has been patched in version 3.5.15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25637|2024-06-26T20:53:30.074Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 15:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
