<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for EFS Software -- Easy Address Book Web Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/efs%20software/easy%20address%20book%20web%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for EFS Software -- Easy Address Book Web Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:24:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4493|2024-08-02T07:31:05.381Z -- efs%20software -- easy%20address%20book%20web%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4493</link>
      <description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Easy Address Book Web Server 1.6 version, through the users_admin.ghp file that affects multiple parameters such as (firstname, homephone, lastname, lastname, middlename, workaddress, workcity, workcountry, workphone, workstate, workzip). This vulnerability allows a remote attacker to store a malicious JavaScript payload in the application to be executed when the page is loaded, resulting in an integrity impact.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4493|2024-08-02T07:31:05.381Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 12:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4492|2024-08-02T07:31:06.057Z -- efs%20software -- easy%20address%20book%20web%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4492</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in Easy Address Book Web Server 1.6 version, affecting the parameters (firstname, homephone, lastname, middlename, workaddress, workcity, workcountry, workphone, workstate and workzip) of the /addrbook.ghp file, allowing an attacker to inject a JavaScript payload specially designed to run when the application is loaded</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4492|2024-08-02T07:31:06.057Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 12:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4491|2024-08-02T07:31:06.045Z -- efs%20software -- easy%20address%20book%20web%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4491</link>
      <description>Buffer overflow vulnerability in Easy Address Book Web Server 1.6 version. The exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to send a very long username string to /searchbook.ghp, asking for the name via a POST request, resulting in arbitrary code execution on the remote machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4491|2024-08-02T07:31:06.045Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 12:17:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
