<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Bitdefender -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bitdefender/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Bitdefender -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:23:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49567|2024-10-18T07:59:02.244Z -- bitdefender -- total%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49567</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in the Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality where the product incorrectly checks the site's certificate, which allows an attacker to make MITM SSL connections to an arbitrary site. The product trusts certificates that are issued using the MD5 and SHA1 collision hash functions which allow attackers to create rogue certificates that appear legitimate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49567|2024-10-18T07:59:02.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49570|2024-10-18T08:07:18.810Z -- bitdefender -- total%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49570</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality where the software trusts a certificate issued by an entity that isn't authorized to issue certificates. This occurs when the "Basic Constraints" extension in the certificate indicates that it is meant to be an "End Entity”. This flaw could allow an attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack, intercepting and potentially altering communications between the user and the website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49570|2024-10-18T08:07:18.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4177|2024-08-01T20:33:52.891Z -- bitdefender -- gravityzone%20console%20on-premise</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4177</link>
      <description>A host whitelist parser issue in the proxy service implemented in the GravityZone Update Server allows an attacker to cause a server-side request forgery. This issue only affects GravityZone Console versions before 6.38.1-2 that are running only on premise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4177|2024-08-01T20:33:52.891Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 07:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6980|2024-07-31T14:25:18.592Z -- bitdefender -- gravityzone%20update%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6980</link>
      <description>A verbose error handling issue in the proxy service implemented in the GravityZone Update Server allows an attacker to cause a server-side request forgery. This issue only affects GravityZone Console versions before 6.38.1-5 running only on premise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6980|2024-07-31T14:25:18.592Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4177|2024-06-06T13:16:59.465Z -- bitdefender -- gravityzone%20console%20on-premise</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4177</link>
      <description>A host whitelist parser issue in the proxy service implemented in the GravityZone Update Server allows an attacker to cause a server-side request forgery. This issue only affects GravityZone Console versions before 6.38.1-2 that are running only on premise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4177|2024-06-06T13:16:59.465Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 07:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6980|2024-07-31T06:58:44.781Z -- bitdefender -- gravityzone%20update%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6980</link>
      <description>A verbose error handling issue in the proxy service implemented in the GravityZone Update Server allows an attacker to cause a server-side request forgery. This issue only affects GravityZone Console versions before 6.38.1-5 running only on premise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6980|2024-07-31T06:58:44.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6057|2024-10-18T07:38:23.788Z -- bitdefender -- total%20security</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6057</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been discovered in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality that results in the improper trust of certificates issued using the DSA signature algorithm. The product does not properly check the certificate chain, allowing an attacker to establish MITM SSL connections to arbitrary sites using a DSA-signed certificate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6057|2024-10-18T07:38:23.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6058|2024-10-18T07:52:08.678Z -- bitdefender -- total%20security</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6058</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in Bitdefender Safepay's handling of HTTPS connections. The issue arises when the product blocks a connection due to an untrusted server certificate but allows the user to add the site to exceptions, resulting in the product trusting the certificate for subsequent HTTPS scans. This vulnerability allows an attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack by using a self-signed certificate, which the product will trust after the site has been added to exceptions. This can lead to the interception and potential alteration of secure communications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6058|2024-10-18T07:52:08.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6056|2024-10-18T07:31:23.425Z -- bitdefender -- total%20security</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6056</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been discovered in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality that results in the improper trust of self-signed certificates. The product is found to trust certificates signed with the RIPEMD-160 hashing algorithm without proper validation, allowing an attacker to establish MITM SSL connections to arbitrary sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6056|2024-10-18T07:31:23.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6055|2024-10-18T07:17:02.731Z -- bitdefender -- total%20security</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6055</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality where the software fails to properly validate website certificates. Specifically, if a site certificate lacks the "Server Authentication" specification in the Extended Key Usage extension, the product does not verify the certificate's compliance with the site, deeming such certificates as valid. This flaw could allow an attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack, intercepting and potentially altering communications between the user and the website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6055|2024-10-18T07:17:02.731Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
