<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Progress -- OpenEdge</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/progress/openedge.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Progress -- OpenEdge</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 15:23:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7345|2024-09-03T14:50:15.520Z -- progress -- openedge
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7345</link>
      <description>Local ABL Client bypass of the required PASOE security checks may allow an attacker to commit unauthorized code injection into Multi-Session Agents on supported OpenEdge LTS platforms up to OpenEdge LTS 11.7.18 and LTS 12.2.13 on all supported release platforms</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7345|2024-09-03T14:50:15.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 14:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7346|2024-09-03T14:51:03.551Z -- progress -- openedge
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7346</link>
      <description>Host name validation for TLS certificates is bypassed when the installed OpenEdge default certificates are used to perform the TLS handshake for a networked connection.  This has been corrected so that default certificates are no longer capable of overriding host name validation and will need to be replaced where full TLS certificate validation is needed for network security.  The existing certificates should be replaced with CA-signed certificates from a recognized certificate authority that contain the necessary information to support host name validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7346|2024-09-03T14:51:03.551Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 14:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7654|2024-09-03T14:48:00.539Z -- progress -- openedge
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7654</link>
      <description>An ActiveMQ Discovery service was reachable by default from an OpenEdge Management installation when an OEE/OEM auto-discovery feature was activated.  Unauthorized access to the discovery service's UDP port allowed content injection into parts of the OEM web interface making it possible for other types of attack that could spoof or deceive web interface users.   Unauthorized use of the OEE/OEM discovery service was remediated by deactivating the discovery service by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7654|2024-09-03T14:48:00.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 14:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
