<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:23:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17554|2024-08-05T01:40:15.799Z -- apache -- olingo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17554</link>
      <description>The XML content type entity deserializer in Apache Olingo versions 4.0.0 to 4.6.0 is not configured to deny the resolution of external entities. Request with content type "application/xml", which trigger the deserialization of entities, can be used to trigger XXE attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17554|2024-08-05T01:40:15.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 16:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17570|2024-08-05T01:40:15.866Z -- apache -- apache%20xml-rpc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17570</link>
      <description>An untrusted deserialization was found in the org.apache.xmlrpc.parser.XmlRpcResponseParser:addResult method of Apache XML-RPC (aka ws-xmlrpc) library. A malicious XML-RPC server could target a XML-RPC client causing it to execute arbitrary code. Apache XML-RPC is no longer maintained and this issue will not be fixed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17570|2024-08-05T01:40:15.866Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17556|2024-08-05T01:40:15.833Z -- apache -- olingo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17556</link>
      <description>Apache Olingo versions 4.0.0 to 4.6.0 provide the AbstractService class, which is public API, uses ObjectInputStream and doesn't check classes being deserialized. If an attacker can feed malicious metadata to the class, then it may result in running attacker's code in the worse case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17556|2024-08-05T01:40:15.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 16:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17569|2024-08-05T01:40:15.855Z -- apache -- apache%20tomcat
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17569</link>
      <description>The refactoring present in Apache Tomcat 9.0.28 to 9.0.30, 8.5.48 to 8.5.50 and 7.0.98 to 7.0.99 introduced a regression. The result of the regression was that invalid Transfer-Encoding headers were incorrectly processed leading to a possibility of HTTP Request Smuggling if Tomcat was located behind a reverse proxy that incorrectly handled the invalid Transfer-Encoding header in a particular manner. Such a reverse proxy is considered unlikely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17569|2024-08-05T01:40:15.855Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 21:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17564|2024-08-05T01:40:15.977Z -- apache -- apache%20dubbo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17564</link>
      <description>Unsafe deserialization occurs within a Dubbo application which has HTTP remoting enabled. An attacker may submit a POST request with a Java object in it to completely compromise a Provider instance of Apache Dubbo, if this instance enables HTTP. This issue affected Apache Dubbo 2.7.0 to 2.7.4, 2.6.0 to 2.6.7, and all 2.5.x versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17564|2024-08-05T01:40:15.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 21:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17573|2024-08-05T01:47:12.612Z -- apache -- cxf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17573</link>
      <description>By default, Apache CXF creates a /services page containing a listing of the available endpoint names and addresses. This webpage is vulnerable to a reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack, which allows a malicious actor to inject javascript into the web page. Please note that the attack exploits a feature which is not typically not present in modern browsers, who remove dot segments before sending the request. However, Mobile applications may be vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17573|2024-08-05T01:47:12.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 17:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17555|2024-08-05T01:40:15.978Z -- apache -- olingo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17555</link>
      <description>The AsyncResponseWrapperImpl class in Apache Olingo versions 4.0.0 to 4.6.0 reads the Retry-After header and passes it to the Thread.sleep() method without any check. If a malicious server returns a huge value in the header, then it can help to implement a DoS attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17555|2024-08-05T01:40:15.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 17:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
