<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache -- VCL</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache/vcl.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache -- VCL</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:24:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11772|2024-08-05T08:17:09.112Z -- apache -- vcl
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11772</link>
      <description>Apache VCL versions 2.1 through 2.5 do not properly validate cookie input when determining what node (if any) was previously selected in the privilege tree. The cookie data is then used in an SQL statement. This allows for an SQL injection attack. Access to this portion of a VCL system requires admin level rights. Other layers of security seem to protect against malicious attack. However, all VCL systems running versions earlier than 2.5.1 should be upgraded or patched. This vulnerability was found and reported to the Apache VCL project by ADLab of Venustech.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11772|2024-08-05T08:17:09.112Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 18:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11774|2024-08-05T08:17:09.236Z -- apache -- vcl
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11774</link>
      <description>Apache VCL versions 2.1 through 2.5 do not properly validate form input when adding and removing VMs to and from hosts. The form data is then used in SQL statements. This allows for an SQL injection attack. Access to this portion of a VCL system requires admin level rights. Other layers of security seem to protect against malicious attack. However, all VCL systems running versions earlier than 2.5.1 should be upgraded or patched. This vulnerability was found and reported to the Apache VCL project by ADLab of Venustech.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11774|2024-08-05T08:17:09.236Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 18:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11773|2024-08-05T08:17:09.198Z -- apache -- vcl
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11773</link>
      <description>Apache VCL versions 2.1 through 2.5 do not properly validate form input when processing a submitted block allocation. The form data is then used as an argument to the php built in function strtotime. This allows for an attack against the underlying implementation of that function. The implementation of strtotime at the time the issue was discovered appeared to be resistant to a malicious attack. However, all VCL systems running versions earlier than 2.5.1 should be upgraded or patched. This vulnerability was found and reported to the Apache VCL project by ADLab of Venustech.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11773|2024-08-05T08:17:09.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 18:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
