<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for PrestaShop -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/prestashop/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for PrestaShop -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39527|2023-08-07T20:32:45.203Z -- prestashop -- prestashop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39527</link>
      <description>PrestaShop is an open source e-commerce web application. Versions prior to 1.7.8.10, 8.0.5, and 8.1.1 are vulnerable to cross-site scripting through the `isCleanHTML` method. Versions 1.7.8.10, 8.0.5, and 8.1.1 contain a patch. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39527|2023-08-07T20:32:45.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39530|2023-08-07T20:51:52.155Z -- prestashop -- prestashop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39530</link>
      <description>PrestaShop is an open source e-commerce web application. Prior to version 8.1.1, it is possible to delete files from the server via the CustomerMessage API. Version 8.1.1 contains a patch for this issue. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39530|2023-08-07T20:51:52.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39526|2023-08-07T20:28:59.051Z -- prestashop -- prestashop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39526</link>
      <description>PrestaShop is an open source e-commerce web application. Versions prior to 1.7.8.10, 8.0.5, and 8.1.1 are vulnerable to remote code execution through SQL injection and arbitrary file write in the back office. Versions 1.7.8.10, 8.0.5, and 8.1.1 contain a patch. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39526|2023-08-07T20:28:59.051Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39529|2023-08-07T20:37:15.946Z -- prestashop -- prestashop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39529</link>
      <description>PrestaShop is an open source e-commerce web application. Prior to version 8.1.1, it is possible to delete a file from the server by using the Attachments controller and the Attachments API. Version 8.1.1 contains a patch for this issue. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39529|2023-08-07T20:37:15.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39525|2023-08-07T20:23:53.884Z -- prestashop -- prestashop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39525</link>
      <description>PrestaShop is an open source e-commerce web application. Prior to version 8.1.1, in the back office, files can be compromised using path traversal by replaying the import file deletion query with a specified file path that uses the traversal path. Version 8.1.1 contains a patch for this issue. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39525|2023-08-07T20:23:53.884Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39524|2023-08-07T19:48:21.994Z -- prestashop -- prestashop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39524</link>
      <description>PrestaShop is an open source e-commerce web application. Prior to version 8.1.1, SQL injection possible in the product search field, in BO's product page. Version 8.1.1 contains a patch for this issue. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39524|2023-08-07T19:48:21.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 19:48:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39528|2023-08-07T20:35:07.663Z -- prestashop -- prestashop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39528</link>
      <description>PrestaShop is an open source e-commerce web application. Prior to version 8.1.1, the `displayAjaxEmailHTML` method can be used to read any file on the server, potentially even outside of the project if the server is not correctly configured. Version 8.1.1 contains a patch for this issue. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39528|2023-08-07T20:35:07.663Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-47109|2023-11-08T21:37:53.660Z -- prestashop -- blockreassurance
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-47109</link>
      <description>PrestaShop blockreassurance adds an information block aimed at offering helpful information to reassure customers that the store is trustworthy. When adding a block in blockreassurance module, a BO user can modify the http request and give the path of any file in the project instead of an image. When deleting the block from the BO, the file will be deleted. It is possible to make the website completely unavailable by removing index.php for example. This issue has been patched in version 5.1.4.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-47109|2023-11-08T21:37:53.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 21:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-47110|2023-11-09T15:24:15.247Z -- prestashop -- blockreassurance
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-47110</link>
      <description>blockreassurance adds an information block aimed at offering helpful information to reassure customers that their store is trustworthy. An ajax function in module blockreassurance allows modifying any value in the configuration table. This vulnerability has been patched in version 5.1.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-47110|2023-11-09T15:24:15.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 15:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43664|2023-09-28T18:16:57.658Z -- prestashop -- prestashop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43664</link>
      <description>PrestaShop is an Open Source e-commerce web application. In the Prestashop Back office interface, an employee can list all modules without any access rights: method `ajaxProcessGetPossibleHookingListForModule` doesn't check access rights. This issue has been addressed in commit `15bd281c` which is included in version 8.1.2. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workaround for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43664|2023-09-28T18:16:57.658Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43663|2023-09-28T18:13:49.216Z -- prestashop -- prestashop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43663</link>
      <description>PrestaShop is an Open Source e-commerce web application. In affected versions any module can be disabled or uninstalled from back office, even with low user right. This allows low privileged users to disable portions of a shops functionality. Commit `ce1f6708` addresses this issue and is included in version 8.1.2. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43663|2023-09-28T18:13:49.216Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-30839|2023-04-25T18:41:38.777Z -- prestashop -- prestashop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-30839</link>
      <description>PrestaShop is an Open Source e-commerce web application. Versions prior to 8.0.4 and 1.7.8.9 contain a SQL filtering vulnerability. A BO user can write, update, and delete in the database, even without having specific rights. PrestaShop 8.0.4 and 1.7.8.9 contain a patch for this issue. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-30839|2023-04-25T18:41:38.777Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 18:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-30838|2023-04-25T18:22:54.521Z -- prestashop -- prestashop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-30838</link>
      <description>PrestaShop is an Open Source e-commerce web application. Prior to versions 8.0.4 and 1.7.8.9, the `ValidateCore::isCleanHTML()` method of Prestashop misses hijackable events which can lead to cross-site scripting (XSS) injection, allowed by the presence of pre-setup `@keyframes` methods. This XSS, which hijacks HTML attributes, can be triggered without any interaction by the visitor/administrator, which makes it as dangerous as a trivial XSS attack. Contrary to other attacks which target HTML attributes and are triggered without user interaction (such as onload / onerror which suffer from a very limited scope), this one can hijack every HTML element, which increases the danger due to a complete HTML elements scope. Versions 8.0.4 and 1.7.8.9 contain a fix for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-30838|2023-04-25T18:22:54.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 18:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-30545|2023-04-25T17:47:01.579Z -- prestashop -- prestashop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-30545</link>
      <description>PrestaShop is an Open Source e-commerce web application. Prior to versions 8.0.4 and 1.7.8.9, it is possible for a user with access to the SQL Manager (Advanced Options -&gt; Database) to arbitrarily read any file on the operating system when using SQL function `LOAD_FILE` in a `SELECT` request. This gives the user access to critical information. A patch is available in PrestaShop 8.0.4 and PS 1.7.8.9
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-30545|2023-04-25T17:47:01.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 17:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25170|2023-03-13T16:55:24.523Z -- prestashop -- prestashop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-25170</link>
      <description>PrestaShop is an open source e-commerce web application that, prior to version 8.0.1, is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery (CSRF). When authenticating users, PrestaShop preserves session attributes. Because this does not clear CSRF tokens upon login, this might enable same-site attackers to bypass the CSRF protection mechanism by performing an attack similar to a session-fixation. The problem is fixed in version 8.0.1.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25170|2023-03-13T16:55:24.523Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 16:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26129|2024-02-19T21:59:54.426Z -- prestashop -- prestashop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-26129</link>
      <description>PrestaShop is an open-source e-commerce platform. Starting in version 8.1.0 and prior to version 8.1.4, PrestaShop is vulnerable to path disclosure in a JavaScript variable. A patch is available in version 8.1.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26129|2024-02-19T21:59:54.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 21:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34717|2024-06-04T17:41:41.822Z -- prestashop -- prestashop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34717</link>
      <description>PrestaShop is an open source e-commerce web application. In PrestaShop 8.1.5, any invoice can be downloaded from front-office in anonymous mode, by supplying a random secure_key parameter in the url. This issue is patched in version 8.1.6. No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34717|2024-06-04T17:41:41.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 15:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34716|2024-06-11T20:43:10.450Z -- prestashop -- prestashop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34716</link>
      <description>PrestaShop is an open source e-commerce web application. A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability that only affects PrestaShops with customer-thread feature flag enabled is present starting from PrestaShop 8.1.0 and prior to PrestaShop 8.1.6. When the customer thread feature flag is enabled through the front-office contact form, a hacker can upload a malicious file containing an XSS that will be executed when an admin opens the attached file in back office. The script injected can access the session and the security token, which allows it to perform any authenticated action in the scope of the administrator's right. This vulnerability is patched in 8.1.6. A workaround is to disable the customer-thread feature-flag.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34716|2024-06-11T20:43:10.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 15:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21628|2024-01-02T21:17:14.733Z -- prestashop -- prestashop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21628</link>
      <description>PrestaShop is an open-source e-commerce platform. Prior to version 8.1.3, the isCleanHtml method is not used on this this form, which makes it possible to store a cross-site scripting payload in the database. The impact is low because the HTML is not interpreted in BO, thanks to twig's escape mechanism. In FO, the cross-site scripting attack is effective, but only impacts the customer sending it, or the customer session from which it was sent. This issue affects those who have a module fetching these messages from the DB and displaying it without escaping HTML. Version 8.1.3 contains a patch for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21628|2024-01-02T21:17:14.733Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 21:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21627|2024-01-02T21:03:17.816Z -- prestashop -- prestashop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21627</link>
      <description>PrestaShop is an open-source e-commerce platform. Prior to versions 8.1.3 and 1.7.8.11, some event attributes are not detected by the `isCleanHTML` method. Some modules using the `isCleanHTML` method could be vulnerable to cross-site scripting. Versions 8.1.3 and 1.7.8.11 contain a patch for this issue. The best workaround is to use the `HTMLPurifier` library to sanitize html input coming from users. The library is already available as a dependency in the PrestaShop project. Beware though that in legacy object models, fields of `HTML` type will call `isCleanHTML`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21627|2024-01-02T21:03:17.816Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 21:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
