<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for librespeed -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/librespeed/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for librespeed -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 14:22:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4957|2024-08-03T01:55:46.148Z -- librespeed -- speedtest
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4957</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in librespeed speedtest up to 5.2.4. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file results/stats.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 5.2.5 is able to address this issue. The patch is named a85f2c086f3449dffa8fe2edb5e2ef3ee72dc0e9. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246643.
In librespeed speedtest bis 5.2.4 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei results/stats.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 5.2.5 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als a85f2c086f3449dffa8fe2edb5e2ef3ee72dc0e9 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4957|2024-08-03T01:55:46.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 19:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32890|2024-05-01T06:34:13.364Z -- librespeed -- speedtest</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32890</link>
      <description>librespeed/speedtest is an open source, self-hosted speed test for HTML5. In affected versions missing neutralization of the ISP information in a speedtest result leads to stored Cross-site scripting in the JSON API. The `processedString` field in the `ispinfo` parameter is missing neutralization. It is stored when a user submits a speedtest result to the telemetry API (`results/telemetry.php`) and returned in the JSON API (`results/json.php`). This vulnerability has been introduced in commit 3937b94. This vulnerability affects LibreSpeed speedtest instances running version 5.2.5 or higher which have telemetry enabled and has been addressed in version 5.3.1. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32890|2024-05-01T06:34:13.364Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 06:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32890|2024-08-02T02:20:35.643Z -- librespeed -- speedtest</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32890</link>
      <description>librespeed/speedtest is an open source, self-hosted speed test for HTML5. In affected versions missing neutralization of the ISP information in a speedtest result leads to stored Cross-site scripting in the JSON API. The `processedString` field in the `ispinfo` parameter is missing neutralization. It is stored when a user submits a speedtest result to the telemetry API (`results/telemetry.php`) and returned in the JSON API (`results/json.php`). This vulnerability has been introduced in commit 3937b94. This vulnerability affects LibreSpeed speedtest instances running version 5.2.5 or higher which have telemetry enabled and has been addressed in version 5.3.1. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32890|2024-08-02T02:20:35.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 06:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
