<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Palantir -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/palantir/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Palantir -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27892|2024-08-03T05:41:10.811Z -- palantir -- gotham
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27892</link>
      <description>Palantir Gotham versions prior to 3.22.11.2 included an unauthenticated endpoint that would have allowed an attacker to exhaust the memory of the Gotham dispatch service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27892|2024-08-03T05:41:10.811Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27897|2024-08-03T05:41:10.543Z -- palantir -- gotham
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27897</link>
      <description>Palantir Gotham versions prior to 3.22.11.2 included an unauthenticated endpoint that would load portions of maliciously crafted zip files to memory. An attacker could repeatedly upload a malicious zip file, which would allow them to exhaust memory resources on the dispatch server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27897|2024-08-03T05:41:10.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27891|2024-08-03T05:41:10.603Z -- palantir -- gotham
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27891</link>
      <description>Palantir Gotham included an unauthenticated endpoint that listed all active usernames on the stack with an active session. The affected services have been patched and automatically deployed to all Apollo-managed Gotham instances. It is highly recommended that customers upgrade all affected services to the latest version. This issue affects: Palantir Gotham versions prior to 103.30221005.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27891|2024-08-03T05:41:10.603Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27894|2024-08-03T05:41:11.040Z -- palantir -- foundry%20blobster%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27894</link>
      <description>The Foundry Blobster service was found to have a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could have allowed an attacker with access to Foundry to launch attacks against other users. This vulnerability is resolved in Blobster 3.228.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27894|2024-08-03T05:41:11.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27895|2024-08-03T05:41:10.879Z -- palantir -- foundry%20build2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27895</link>
      <description>Information Exposure Through Log Files vulnerability discovered in Foundry when logs were captured using an underlying library known as Build2. This issue was present in versions earlier than 1.785.0. Upgrade to Build2 version 1.785.0 or greater.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27895|2024-08-03T05:41:10.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-48306|2024-08-03T15:10:59.646Z -- palantir -- palantir%20gotham%20chat%20irc%20helper
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48306</link>
      <description>Improper Validation of Certificate with Host Mismatch vulnerability in Gotham Chat IRC helper of Palantir Gotham allows A malicious attacker in a privileged network position could abuse this to perform a man-in-the-middle attack. A successful man-in-the-middle attack would allow them to intercept, read, or modify network communications to and from the affected service. This issue affects: Palantir Palantir Gotham Chat IRC helper versions prior to 30221005.210011.9242.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-48306|2024-08-03T15:10:59.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27888|2024-08-03T05:41:10.540Z -- palantir -- foundry%20issues
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27888</link>
      <description>Foundry Issues service versions 2.244.0 to 2.249.0 was found to be logging in a manner that captured sensitive information (session tokens). This issue was fixed in 2.249.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27888|2024-08-03T05:41:10.540Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-48308|2024-08-03T15:10:59.729Z -- palantir -- sls-logging
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48308</link>
      <description>It was discovered that the sls-logging was not verifying hostnames in TLS certificates due to a misuse of the javax.net.ssl.SSLSocketFactory API. A malicious attacker in a privileged network position could abuse this to perform a man-in-the-middle attack. A successful man-in-the-middle attack would allow them to intercept, read, or modify network communications to and from the affected service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-48308|2024-08-03T15:10:59.729Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27896|2024-08-03T05:41:10.751Z -- palantir -- foundry%20code-workbooks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27896</link>
      <description>Information Exposure Through Log Files vulnerability discovered in Foundry Code-Workbooks where the endpoint backing that console was generating service log records of any Python code being run. These service logs included the Foundry token that represents the Code-Workbooks Python console. Upgrade to Code-Workbooks version 4.461.0. This issue affects Palantir Foundry Code-Workbooks version 4.144 to version 4.460.0 and is resolved in 4.461.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27896|2024-08-03T05:41:10.751Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27890|2024-08-03T05:41:10.808Z -- palantir -- atlasdb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27890</link>
      <description>It was discovered that the sls-logging was not verifying hostnames in TLS certificates due to a misuse of the javax.net.ssl.SSLSocketFactory API. A malicious attacker in a privileged network position could abuse this to perform a man-in-the-middle attack. A successful man-in-the-middle attack would allow them to intercept, read, or modify network communications to and from the affected service. In the case of AtlasDB, the vulnerability was mitigated by other network controls such as two-way TLS when deployed as part of a Palantir platform. Palantir still recommends upgrading to a non-vulnerable version out of an abundance of caution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27890|2024-08-03T05:41:10.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27893|2024-08-03T05:41:10.982Z -- palantir -- foundry%20magritte%20plugin%20osisoft-pi-web-connector
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27893</link>
      <description>The Foundry Magritte plugin osisoft-pi-web-connector versions 0.15.0 - 0.43.0 was found to be logging in a manner that captured authentication requests. This vulnerability is resolved in osisoft-pi-web-connector version 0.44.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27893|2024-08-03T05:41:10.982Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-48307|2024-08-03T15:10:59.695Z -- palantir -- foundry%20magritte
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48307</link>
      <description>It was discovered that the Magritte-ftp was not verifying hostnames in TLS certificates due to a misuse of the javax.net.ssl.SSLSocketFactory API. A malicious attacker in a privileged network position could abuse this to perform a man-in-the-middle attack. A successful man-in-the-middle attack would allow them to intercept, read, or modify network communications to and from the affected service. In the case of a successful man in the middle attack on magritte-ftp, an attacker would be able to read and modify network traffic such as authentication tokens or raw data entering a Palantir Foundry stack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-48307|2024-08-03T15:10:59.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27889|2024-08-03T05:41:10.599Z -- palantir -- foundry%20multipass
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27889</link>
      <description>The Multipass service was found to have code paths that could be abused to cause a denial of service for authentication or authorization operations. A malicious attacker could perform an application-level denial of service attack, potentially causing authentication and/or authorization operations to fail for the duration of the attack. This could lead to performance degradation or login failures for customer Palantir Foundry environments. This vulnerability is resolved in Multipass 3.647.0. This issue affects: Palantir Foundry Multipass versions prior to 3.647.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27889|2024-08-03T05:41:10.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-30968|2024-08-02T14:45:24.296Z -- palantir -- com.palantir.acme.gaia%3Agaia</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30968</link>
      <description>One of Gotham Gaia services was found to be vulnerable to a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could have allowed an attacker to bypass CSP and get a persistent cross site scripting payload on the stack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-30968|2024-08-02T14:45:24.296Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 19:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-30968|2024-03-12T19:39:24.226Z -- palantir -- com.palantir.acme.gaia%3Agaia</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-30968</link>
      <description>One of Gotham Gaia services was found to be vulnerable to a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could have allowed an attacker to bypass CSP and get a persistent cross site scripting payload on the stack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-30968|2024-03-12T19:39:24.226Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 19:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
