<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for openSUSE -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/opensuse/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for openSUSE -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:25:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18903|2024-09-17T01:00:28.473Z -- opensuse -- leap%2015.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18903</link>
      <description>A Use After Free vulnerability in wicked of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15; openSUSE Leap 15.1, Factory allows remote attackers to cause DoS or potentially code execution. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 wicked versions prior to 0.6.60-2.18.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 wicked versions prior to 0.6.60-28.26.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 wicked versions prior to 0.6.60-lp151.2.9.1. openSUSE Factory wicked versions prior to 0.6.62.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18903|2024-09-17T01:00:28.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 16:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18902|2024-09-17T02:41:08.903Z -- opensuse -- leap%2015.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18902</link>
      <description>A Use After Free vulnerability in wicked of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15; openSUSE Leap 15.1, Factory allows remote attackers to cause DoS or potentially code execution. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 wicked versions prior to 0.6.60-3.5.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 wicked versions prior to 0.6.60-3.21.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 wicked versions prior to 0.6.60-lp151.2.6.1. openSUSE Factory wicked versions prior to 0.6.62.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18902|2024-09-17T02:41:08.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 16:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3697|2024-09-17T01:31:57.295Z -- opensuse -- leap%2015.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3697</link>
      <description>UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the packaging of gnump3d in openSUSE Leap 15.1 allows local attackers to escalate from user gnump3d to root. This issue affects: openSUSE Leap 15.1 gnump3d version 3.0-lp151.2.1 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3697|2024-09-17T01:31:57.295Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 12:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21946|2024-09-17T01:21:54.785Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21946</link>
      <description>A Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in the sudoers configuration in cscreen of openSUSE Factory allows any local users to gain the privileges of the tty and dialout groups and access and manipulate any running cscreen seesion. This issue affects: openSUSE Factory cscreen version 1.2-1.3 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21946|2024-09-17T01:21:54.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 10:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3681|2024-09-17T03:28:54.416Z -- opensuse -- opensuse%20leap%2015.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3681</link>
      <description>A External Control of File Name or Path vulnerability in osc of SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Development Tools 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP5, SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP4; openSUSE Leap 15.1, openSUSE Factory allowed remote attackers that can change downloaded packages to overwrite arbitrary files. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Development Tools 15 osc versions prior to 0.169.1-3.20.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP5 osc versions prior to 0.162.1-15.9.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP4 osc versions prior to 0.162.1-15.9.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 osc versions prior to 0.169.1-lp151.2.15.1. openSUSE Factory osc versions prior to 0.169.0 .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3681|2024-09-17T03:28:54.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 12:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25322|2024-09-17T03:02:08.344Z -- opensuse -- leap%2015.2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25322</link>
      <description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in python-HyperKitty of openSUSE Leap 15.2, Factory allows local attackers to escalate privileges from the user hyperkitty or hyperkitty-admin to root. This issue affects: openSUSE Leap 15.2 python-HyperKitty version 1.3.2-lp152.2.3.1 and prior versions. openSUSE Factory python-HyperKitty versions prior to 1.3.4-5.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25322|2024-09-17T03:02:08.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 11:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18899|2024-09-17T01:25:34.093Z -- opensuse -- leap%2015.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18899</link>
      <description>The apt-cacher-ng package of openSUSE Leap 15.1 runs operations in user owned directory /run/apt-cacher-ng with root privileges. This can allow local attackers to influence the outcome of these operations. This issue affects: openSUSE Leap 15.1 apt-cacher-ng versions prior to 3.1-lp151.3.3.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18899|2024-09-17T01:25:34.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 15:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2013-3703|2024-09-17T02:21:03.060Z -- opensuse -- open%20build%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-3703</link>
      <description>The controller of the Open Build Service API prior to version 2.4.4 is missing a write permission check, allowing an authenticated attacker to add or remove user roles from packages and/or project meta data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2013-3703|2024-09-17T02:21:03.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12475|2024-09-17T00:36:57.174Z -- opensuse -- open%20build%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12475</link>
      <description>A Externally Controlled Reference to a Resource in Another Sphere vulnerability in obs-service-download_files of openSUSE Open Build Service allows authenticated users to generate HTTP request against internal networks and potentially downloading data that is exposed there. This issue affects: openSUSE Open Build Service .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12475|2024-09-17T00:36:57.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 11:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12466|2024-09-17T00:40:29.176Z -- opensuse -- openbuildservice
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12466</link>
      <description>openSUSE openbuildservice before 9.2.4 allowed authenticated users to delete packages on specific projects with project links.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12466|2024-09-17T00:40:29.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21945|2024-09-17T00:40:49.798Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21945</link>
      <description>A Insecure Temporary File vulnerability in cscreen of openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to cause DoS for cscreen and a system DoS for non-default systems. This issue affects: openSUSE Factory cscreen version 1.2-1.3 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21945|2024-09-17T00:40:49.798Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 10:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25317|2024-09-17T00:32:16.952Z -- opensuse -- opensuse%20leap%2015.2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25317</link>
      <description>A Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in the packaging of cups of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11-SP4-LTSS, SUSE Manager Server 4.0, SUSE OpenStack Cloud Crowbar 9; openSUSE Leap 15.2, Factory allows local attackers with control of the lp users to create files as root with 0644 permissions without the ability to set the content. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11-SP4-LTSS cups versions prior to 1.3.9. SUSE Manager Server 4.0 cups versions prior to 2.2.7. SUSE OpenStack Cloud Crowbar 9 cups versions prior to 1.7.5. openSUSE Leap 15.2 cups versions prior to 2.2.7. openSUSE Factory cups version 2.3.3op2-2.1 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25317|2024-09-17T00:32:16.952Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 09:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8024|2024-09-17T01:21:22.130Z -- opensuse -- opensuse%20leap%2015.2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8024</link>
      <description>A Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in the packaging of hylafax+ of openSUSE Leap 15.2, openSUSE Leap 15.1, openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to escalate from user uucp to users calling hylafax binaries. This issue affects: openSUSE Leap 15.2 hylafax+ versions prior to 7.0.2-lp152.2.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 hylafax+ version 5.6.1-lp151.3.7 and prior versions. openSUSE Factory hylafax+ versions prior to 7.0.2-2.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8024|2024-09-17T01:21:22.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 07:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3700|2024-09-17T01:26:30.443Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3700</link>
      <description>yast2-security didn't use secure defaults to protect passwords. This became a problem on 2019-10-07 when configuration files that set secure settings were moved to a different location. As of the 20191022 snapshot the insecure default settings were used until yast2-security switched to stronger defaults in 4.2.6 and used the new configuration file locations. Password created during this time used DES password encryption and are not properly protected against attackers that are able to access the password hashes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3700|2024-09-17T01:26:30.443Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 12:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31250|2024-09-17T01:06:35.227Z -- opensuse -- tumbleweed
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31250</link>
      <description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in keylime of openSUSE Tumbleweed allows local attackers to escalate from the keylime user to root. This issue affects: openSUSE Tumbleweed keylime versions prior to 6.4.2-1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31250|2024-09-17T01:06:35.227Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 07:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8017|2024-09-17T01:50:50.369Z -- opensuse -- opensuse%20leap%2015.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8017</link>
      <description>A Race Condition Enabling Link Following vulnerability in the cron job shipped with texlive-filesystem of SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Desktop Applications 15-SP1, SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP4, SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP5; openSUSE Leap 15.1 allows local users in group mktex to delete arbitrary files on the system This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Desktop Applications 15-SP1 texlive-filesystem versions prior to 2017.135-9.5.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP4 texlive-filesystem versions prior to 2013.74-16.5.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP5 texlive-filesystem versions prior to 2013.74-16.5.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 texlive-filesystem versions prior to 2017.135-lp151.8.3.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8017|2024-09-17T01:50:50.369Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 14:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8019|2024-09-17T03:43:09.266Z -- opensuse -- opensuse%20backports%20sle-15-sp1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8019</link>
      <description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the packaging of syslog-ng of SUSE Linux Enterprise Debuginfo 11-SP3, SUSE Linux Enterprise Debuginfo 11-SP4, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Legacy Software 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Point of Sale 11-SP3, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11-SP4-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP1; openSUSE Backports SLE-15-SP1, openSUSE Leap 15.1 allowed local attackers controlling the user news to escalate their privileges to root. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Debuginfo 11-SP3 syslog-ng versions prior to 2.0.9-27.34.40.5.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Debuginfo 11-SP4 syslog-ng versions prior to 2.0.9-27.34.40.5.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Legacy Software 12 syslog-ng versions prior to 3.6.4-12.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Point of Sale 11-SP3 syslog-ng versions prior to 2.0.9-27.34.40.5.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11-SP4-LTSS syslog-ng versions prior to 2.0.9-27.34.40.5.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP1 syslog-ng versions prior to 3.6.4-12.8.1. openSUSE Backports SLE-15-SP1 syslog-ng versions prior to 3.19.1-bp151.4.6.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 syslog-ng versions prior to 3.19.1-lp151.3.6.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8019|2024-09-17T03:43:09.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 11:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8014|2024-09-17T03:13:57.674Z -- opensuse -- opensuse%20leap%2015.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8014</link>
      <description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the packaging of kopano-spamd of openSUSE Leap 15.1, openSUSE Tumbleweed allowed local attackers with the privileges of the kopano user to escalate to root. This issue affects: openSUSE Leap 15.1 kopano-spamd versions prior to 10.0.5-lp151.4.1. openSUSE Tumbleweed kopano-spamd versions prior to 10.0.5-1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8014|2024-09-17T03:13:57.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 12:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3693|2024-09-17T02:46:37.656Z -- opensuse -- leap%2015.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3693</link>
      <description>A symlink following vulnerability in the packaging of mailman in SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12; openSUSE Leap 15.1 allowed local attackers to escalate their privileges from user wwwrun to root. Additionally arbitrary files could be changed to group mailman. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11 mailman versions prior to 2.1.15-9.6.15.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 mailman versions prior to 2.1.17-3.11.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 mailman version 2.1.29-lp151.2.14 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3693|2024-09-17T02:46:37.656Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 10:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21950|2024-09-17T02:32:53.607Z -- opensuse -- opensuse%20backports%20sle-15-sp3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21950</link>
      <description>A Improper Access Control vulnerability in the systemd service of cana in openSUSE Backports SLE-15-SP3, openSUSE Backports SLE-15-SP4 allows local users to hijack the UNIX domain socket This issue affects: openSUSE Backports SLE-15-SP3 canna versions prior to canna-3.7p3-bp153.2.3.1. openSUSE Backports SLE-15-SP4 canna versions prior to 3.7p3-bp154.3.3.1. openSUSE Factory was also affected. Instead of fixing the package it was deleted there.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21950|2024-09-17T02:32:53.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 08:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18897|2024-09-17T01:21:20.067Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18897</link>
      <description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the packaging of salt of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15; openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to escalate privileges from user salt to root. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 salt-master version 2019.2.0-46.83.1 and prior versions. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 salt-master version 2019.2.0-6.21.1 and prior versions. openSUSE Factory salt-master version 2019.2.2-3.1 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18897|2024-09-17T01:21:20.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 15:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3694|2024-09-17T00:26:07.628Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3694</link>
      <description>A Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the packaging of munin in openSUSE Factory, Leap 15.1 allows local attackers to escalate from user munin to root. This issue affects: openSUSE Factory munin version 2.0.49-4.2 and prior versions. openSUSE Leap 15.1 munin version 2.0.40-lp151.1.1 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3694|2024-09-17T00:26:07.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 10:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
