<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for openSUSE -- Factory</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/opensuse/factory.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for openSUSE -- Factory</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:42:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31253|2024-09-16T19:05:13.222Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31253</link>
      <description>A Untrusted Search Path vulnerability in openldap2 of openSUSE Factory allows local attackers with control of the ldap user or group to change ownership of arbitrary directory entries to this user/group, leading to escalation to root. This issue affects: openSUSE Factory openldap2 versions prior to 2.6.3-404.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31253|2024-09-16T19:05:13.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 13:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8015|2024-09-16T19:46:31.907Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8015</link>
      <description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the packaging of exim in openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to escalate from user mail to root. This issue affects: openSUSE Factory exim versions prior to 4.93.0.4-3.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8015|2024-09-16T19:46:31.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 07:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25321|2024-09-16T18:43:24.802Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25321</link>
      <description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in arpwatch of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11-SP4-LTSS, SUSE Manager Server 4.0, SUSE OpenStack Cloud Crowbar 9; openSUSE Factory, Leap 15.2 allows local attackers with control of the runtime user to run arpwatch as to escalate to root upon the next restart of arpwatch. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11-SP4-LTSS arpwatch versions prior to 2.1a15. SUSE Manager Server 4.0 arpwatch versions prior to 2.1a15. SUSE OpenStack Cloud Crowbar 9 arpwatch versions prior to 2.1a15. openSUSE Factory arpwatch version 2.1a15-169.5 and prior versions. openSUSE Leap 15.2 arpwatch version 2.1a15-lp152.5.5 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25321|2024-09-16T18:43:24.802Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 08:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3698|2024-09-16T16:33:41.138Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3698</link>
      <description>UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the cronjob shipped with nagios of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11; openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to cause cause DoS or potentially escalate privileges by winning a race. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 nagios version 3.5.1-5.27 and prior versions. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11 nagios version 3.0.6-1.25.36.3.1 and prior versions. openSUSE Factory nagios version 4.4.5-2.1 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3698|2024-09-16T16:33:41.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 13:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32000|2024-09-16T17:48:09.451Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32000</link>
      <description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the clone-master-clean-up.sh script of clone-master-clean-up in SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 SP3, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 SP1; openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to delete arbitrary files. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 SP3 clone-master-clean-up version 1.6-4.6.1 and prior versions. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 SP1 clone-master-clean-up version 1.6-3.9.1 and prior versions. openSUSE Factory clone-master-clean-up version 1.6-1.4 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32000|2024-09-16T17:48:09.451Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 09:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18898|2024-09-16T18:24:53.684Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18898</link>
      <description>UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the trousers package of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 SP1; openSUSE Factory allowed local attackers escalate privileges from user tss to root. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 SP1 trousers versions prior to 0.3.14-6.3.1. openSUSE Factory trousers versions prior to 0.3.14-7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18898|2024-09-16T18:24:53.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 14:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8032|2024-09-16T20:03:06.806Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8032</link>
      <description>A Insecure Temporary File vulnerability in the packaging of cyrus-sasl of openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to escalate to root. This issue affects: openSUSE Factory cyrus-sasl version 2.1.27-4.2 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8032|2024-09-16T20:03:06.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 09:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12476|2024-09-16T20:52:13.615Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12476</link>
      <description>Relative Path Traversal vulnerability in obs-service-tar_scm of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15; openSUSE Factory allows remote attackers with control over a repository to overwrite files on the machine of the local user if a malicious service is executed. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 obs-service-tar_scm versions prior to 0.9.2.1537788075.fefaa74:. openSUSE Factory obs-service-tar_scm versions prior to 0.9.2.1537788075.fefaa74.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12476|2024-09-16T20:52:13.615Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 08:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3692|2024-09-16T20:51:57.334Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3692</link>
      <description>The packaging of inn on SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11; openSUSE Factory, Leap 15.1 allows local attackers to escalate from user inn to root via symlink attacks. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11 inn version 2.4.2-170.21.3.1 and prior versions. openSUSE Factory inn version 2.6.2-2.2 and prior versions. openSUSE Leap 15.1 inn version 2.5.4-lp151.2.47 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3692|2024-09-16T20:51:57.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 08:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36781|2024-09-16T18:39:32.233Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36781</link>
      <description>A Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in the parsec package of openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to imitate the service leading to DoS or clients talking to an imposter service. This issue affects: openSUSE Factory parsec versions prior to 0.8.1-1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36781|2024-09-16T18:39:32.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 10:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
