<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for openSUSE -- Factory</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/opensuse/factory.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for openSUSE -- Factory</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3698|2024-08-04T19:19:17.452Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3698</link>
      <description>UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the cronjob shipped with nagios of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11; openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to cause cause DoS or potentially escalate privileges by winning a race. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 nagios version 3.5.1-5.27 and prior versions. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11 nagios version 3.0.6-1.25.36.3.1 and prior versions. openSUSE Factory nagios version 4.4.5-2.1 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3698|2024-08-04T19:19:17.452Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36781|2024-08-04T01:01:59.391Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36781</link>
      <description>A Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in the parsec package of openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to imitate the service leading to DoS or clients talking to an imposter service. This issue affects: openSUSE Factory parsec versions prior to 0.8.1-1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36781|2024-08-04T01:01:59.391Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3692|2024-08-04T19:19:17.781Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3692</link>
      <description>The packaging of inn on SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11; openSUSE Factory, Leap 15.1 allows local attackers to escalate from user inn to root via symlink attacks. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11 inn version 2.4.2-170.21.3.1 and prior versions. openSUSE Factory inn version 2.6.2-2.2 and prior versions. openSUSE Leap 15.1 inn version 2.5.4-lp151.2.47 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3692|2024-08-04T19:19:17.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3691|2024-08-04T19:19:16.810Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3691</link>
      <description>A Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the packaging of munge in SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15; openSUSE Factory allowed local attackers to escalate privileges from user munge to root. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 munge versions prior to 0.5.13-4.3.1. openSUSE Factory munge versions prior to 0.5.13-6.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3691|2024-08-04T19:19:16.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3694|2024-08-04T19:19:17.485Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3694</link>
      <description>A Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the packaging of munin in openSUSE Factory, Leap 15.1 allows local attackers to escalate from user munin to root. This issue affects: openSUSE Factory munin version 2.0.49-4.2 and prior versions. openSUSE Leap 15.1 munin version 2.0.40-lp151.1.1 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3694|2024-08-04T19:19:17.485Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3700|2024-08-04T19:19:16.823Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3700</link>
      <description>yast2-security didn't use secure defaults to protect passwords. This became a problem on 2019-10-07 when configuration files that set secure settings were moved to a different location. As of the 20191022 snapshot the insecure default settings were used until yast2-security switched to stronger defaults in 4.2.6 and used the new configuration file locations. Password created during this time used DES password encryption and are not properly protected against attackers that are able to access the password hashes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3700|2024-08-04T19:19:16.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8032|2024-08-04T09:48:24.966Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8032</link>
      <description>A Insecure Temporary File vulnerability in the packaging of cyrus-sasl of openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to escalate to root. This issue affects: openSUSE Factory cyrus-sasl version 2.1.27-4.2 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8032|2024-08-04T09:48:24.966Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8015|2024-08-04T09:48:25.101Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8015</link>
      <description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the packaging of exim in openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to escalate from user mail to root. This issue affects: openSUSE Factory exim versions prior to 4.93.0.4-3.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8015|2024-08-04T09:48:25.101Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
