<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for openSUSE -- Factory</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/opensuse/factory.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for openSUSE -- Factory</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 21:22:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21946|2024-09-17T01:21:54.785Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21946</link>
      <description>A Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in the sudoers configuration in cscreen of openSUSE Factory allows any local users to gain the privileges of the tty and dialout groups and access and manipulate any running cscreen seesion. This issue affects: openSUSE Factory cscreen version 1.2-1.3 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21946|2024-09-17T01:21:54.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 10:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21945|2024-09-17T00:40:49.798Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21945</link>
      <description>A Insecure Temporary File vulnerability in cscreen of openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to cause DoS for cscreen and a system DoS for non-default systems. This issue affects: openSUSE Factory cscreen version 1.2-1.3 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21945|2024-09-17T00:40:49.798Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 10:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3700|2024-09-17T01:26:30.443Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3700</link>
      <description>yast2-security didn't use secure defaults to protect passwords. This became a problem on 2019-10-07 when configuration files that set secure settings were moved to a different location. As of the 20191022 snapshot the insecure default settings were used until yast2-security switched to stronger defaults in 4.2.6 and used the new configuration file locations. Password created during this time used DES password encryption and are not properly protected against attackers that are able to access the password hashes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3700|2024-09-17T01:26:30.443Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 12:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18897|2024-09-17T01:21:20.067Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18897</link>
      <description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the packaging of salt of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15; openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to escalate privileges from user salt to root. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 salt-master version 2019.2.0-46.83.1 and prior versions. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 salt-master version 2019.2.0-6.21.1 and prior versions. openSUSE Factory salt-master version 2019.2.2-3.1 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18897|2024-09-17T01:21:20.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 15:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3694|2024-09-17T00:26:07.628Z -- opensuse -- factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3694</link>
      <description>A Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the packaging of munin in openSUSE Factory, Leap 15.1 allows local attackers to escalate from user munin to root. This issue affects: openSUSE Factory munin version 2.0.49-4.2 and prior versions. openSUSE Leap 15.1 munin version 2.0.40-lp151.1.1 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3694|2024-09-17T00:26:07.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 10:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
