<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Jahastech -- NxFilter</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/jahastech/nxfilter.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Jahastech -- NxFilter</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:22:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6904|2024-08-02T08:42:08.475Z -- jahastech -- nxfilter
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6904</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Jahastech NxFilter 4.3.2.5. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /config,admin.jsp. The manipulation of the argument admin_name leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. VDB-248266 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Jahastech NxFilter 4.3.2.5 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /config,admin.jsp. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments admin_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross-site request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6904|2024-08-02T08:42:08.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 23:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6905|2024-08-02T08:42:08.644Z -- jahastech -- nxfilter
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6905</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Jahastech NxFilter 4.3.2.5. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file user,adap.jsp?actionFlag=test&amp;id=1 of the component Bind Request Handler. The manipulation leads to ldap injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248267. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Jahastech NxFilter 4.3.2.5 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei user,adap.jsp?actionFlag=test&amp;id=1 der Komponente Bind Request Handler. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine ldap injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6905|2024-08-02T08:42:08.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 23:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
