<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Tuya -- SDK</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tuya/sdk.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Tuya -- SDK</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-3764|2024-04-16T07:08:26.203Z -- Tuya -- SDK
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3764</link><description>** DISPUTED ** A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Tuya SDK up to 5.0.x. Affected is an unknown function of the component MQTT Packet Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. Upgrading to version 5.1.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260604. NOTE: The vendor explains that a malicious actor would have to crack TLS first or use a legitimate login to initiate the attack.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Tuya SDK bis 5.0.x entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Komponente MQTT Packet Handler. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Die wahre Existenz der vermeintlichen Schwachstelle wird zur Zeit in Frage gestellt. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 5.1.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3764|2024-04-16T07:08:26.203Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 22:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>