<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for FreeRDP -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/freerdp/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for FreeRDP -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-22211|2024-01-19T19:54:32.837Z -- FreeRDP -- FreeRDP
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22211</link><description>FreeRDP is a set of free and open source remote desktop protocol library and clients. In affected versions an integer overflow in `freerdp_bitmap_planar_context_reset` leads to heap-buffer overflow. This affects FreeRDP based clients. FreeRDP based server implementations and proxy are not affected. A malicious server could prepare a `RDPGFX_RESET_GRAPHICS_PDU` to allocate too small buffers, possibly triggering later out of bound read/write. Data extraction over network is not possible, the buffers are used to display an image. This issue has been addressed in version 2.11.5 and 3.2.0. Users are advised to upgrade. there are no know workarounds for this vulnerability.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22211|2024-01-19T19:54:32.837Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 19:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32039|2024-04-22T20:23:58.360Z -- FreeRDP -- FreeRDP
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32039</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients using a version of FreeRDP prior to 3.5.0 or 2.11.6 are vulnerable to integer overflow and out-of-bounds write. Versions 3.5.0 and 2.11.6 patch the issue. As a workaround, do not use `/gfx` options (e.g. deactivate with `/bpp:32` or `/rfx` as it is on by default).</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32039|2024-04-22T20:23:58.360Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 20:23:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32458|2024-04-22T20:52:45.457Z -- FreeRDP -- FreeRDP
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32458</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients that use a version of FreeRDP prior to 3.5.0 or 2.11.6 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read. Versions 3.5.0 and 2.11.6 patch the issue. As a workaround, use `/gfx` or `/rfx` modes (on by default, require server side support).</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32458|2024-04-22T20:52:45.457Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 20:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32659|2024-04-23T19:40:24.919Z -- FreeRDP -- FreeRDP
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32659</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients prior to version 3.5.1 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read if `((nWidth == 0) and (nHeight == 0))`. Version 3.5.1 contains a patch for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32659|2024-04-23T19:40:24.919Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32658|2024-04-23T17:41:21.212Z -- FreeRDP -- FreeRDP
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32658</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients prior to version 3.5.1 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read. Version 3.5.1 contains a patch for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32658|2024-04-23T17:41:21.212Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32459|2024-04-22T21:32:57.478Z -- FreeRDP -- FreeRDP
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32459</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients and servers that use a version of FreeRDP prior to 3.5.0 or 2.11.6 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read. Versions 3.5.0 and 2.11.6 patch the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32459|2024-04-22T21:32:57.478Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:32:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32662|2024-04-23T20:17:30.949Z -- FreeRDP -- FreeRDP
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32662</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients prior to version 3.5.1 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read. This occurs when `WCHAR` string is read with twice the size it has and converted to `UTF-8`, `base64` decoded. The string is only used to compare against the redirection server certificate. Version 3.5.1 contains a patch for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32662|2024-04-23T20:17:30.949Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:17:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32460|2024-04-22T21:49:30.911Z -- FreeRDP -- FreeRDP
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32460</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based based clients using `/bpp:32` legacy `GDI` drawing path with a version of FreeRDP prior to 3.5.0 or 2.11.6 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read. Versions 3.5.0 and 2.11.6 patch the issue. As a workaround, use modern drawing paths (e.g. `/rfx` or `/gfx` options). The workaround requires server side support.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32460|2024-04-22T21:49:30.911Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32661|2024-04-23T20:05:50.310Z -- FreeRDP -- FreeRDP
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32661</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients prior to version 3.5.1 are vulnerable to a possible `NULL` access and crash. Version 3.5.1 contains a patch for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32661|2024-04-23T20:05:50.310Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:05:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32660|2024-04-23T20:04:09.052Z -- FreeRDP -- FreeRDP
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32660</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.5.1, a malicious server can crash the FreeRDP client by sending invalid huge allocation size. Version 3.5.1 contains a patch for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32660|2024-04-23T20:04:09.052Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:03:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32041|2024-04-22T20:39:47.048Z -- FreeRDP -- FreeRDP
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32041</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients that use a version of FreeRDP prior to 3.5.0 or 2.11.6 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read. Versions 3.5.0 and 2.11.6 patch the issue. As a workaround, deactivate `/gfx` (on by default, set `/bpp` or `/rfx` options instead.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32041|2024-04-22T20:39:47.048Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 20:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32040|2024-04-22T20:36:45.439Z -- FreeRDP -- FreeRDP
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32040</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients that use a version of FreeRDP prior to 3.5.0 or 2.11.6 and have connections to servers using the `NSC` codec are vulnerable to integer underflow. Versions 3.5.0 and 2.11.6 patch the issue. As a workaround, do not use the NSC codec (e.g. use `-nsc`).</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32040|2024-04-22T20:36:45.439Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 20:36:45 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>