<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apple -- iOS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apple/ios.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apple -- iOS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:22:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4444|2024-08-05T05:18:25.525Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4444</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 12.0.2, iOS 12.1.1, tvOS 12.1.1, iTunes 12.9.2 for Windows. Processing maliciously crafted web content may disclose sensitive user information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4444|2024-08-05T05:18:25.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 19:19:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4448|2024-08-05T05:18:25.552Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4448</link>
      <description>A memory initialization issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Mojave 10.14.4, Security Update 2019-002 High Sierra, Security Update 2019-002 Sierra, iOS 12.1.1, watchOS 5.1.2, macOS Mojave 10.14.2, Security Update 2018-003 High Sierra, Security Update 2018-006 Sierra, tvOS 12.1.1. A local user may be able to read kernel memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4448|2024-08-05T05:18:25.552Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 19:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4474|2024-08-05T05:18:26.488Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4474</link>
      <description>A memory consumption issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iCloud for Windows 7.7, watchOS 5, Safari 12, iOS 12, iTunes 12.9 for Windows, tvOS 12. Unexpected interaction causes an ASSERT failure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4474|2024-08-05T05:18:26.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 19:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4381|2024-08-05T05:11:22.682Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4381</link>
      <description>A resource exhaustion issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in tvOS 12.1, iOS 12.1. Processing a maliciously crafted message may lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4381|2024-08-05T05:11:22.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 19:18:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4428|2024-08-05T05:11:22.931Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4428</link>
      <description>A lock screen issue allowed access to the share function on a locked device. This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 12.1.1. A local attacker may be able to share items from the lock screen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4428|2024-08-05T05:11:22.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 19:19:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4339|2024-08-05T05:11:22.657Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4339</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed with a new entitlement. This issue is fixed in iOS 12.1. A local user may be able to read a persistent device identifier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4339|2024-08-05T05:11:22.657Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 19:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4302|2024-08-05T05:11:22.509Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4302</link>
      <description>A null pointer dereference was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS High Sierra 10.13, iCloud for Windows 7.0, watchOS 4, iOS 11, iTunes 12.7 for Windows. Processing maliciously crafted XML may lead to an unexpected application termination or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4302|2024-08-05T05:11:22.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 19:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4433|2024-08-05T05:11:22.928Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4433</link>
      <description>A configuration issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Mojave 10.14.4, Security Update 2019-002 High Sierra, Security Update 2019-002 Sierra, watchOS 5, iOS 12, tvOS 12, macOS Mojave 10.14. A malicious application may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4433|2024-08-05T05:11:22.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 19:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-25071|2024-08-05T03:00:19.391Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25071</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Apple iPhone up to 12.4.1. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is Siri. Playing an audio or video file might be able to initiate Siri on the same device which makes it possible to execute commands remotely. Exploit details have been disclosed to the public. The existence and implications of this vulnerability are doubted by Apple even though multiple public videos demonstrating the attack exist. Upgrading to version 13.0 migt be able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade affected devices. NOTE: Apple claims, that after examining the report they do not see any actual security implications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-25071|2024-08-05T03:00:19.391Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 06:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2375|2024-08-05T13:55:04.109Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2375</link>
      <description>An issue existed in preventing the uploading of CallKit call history to iCloud. This issue was addressed through improved logic. This issue is fixed in iOS 10.2.1. Updates for CallKit call history are sent to iCloud.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2375|2024-08-05T13:55:04.109Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 19:48:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
