<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apple -- iOS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apple/ios.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apple -- iOS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:19:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3828|2024-08-04T07:44:51.473Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3828</link>
      <description>A lock screen issue allowed access to contacts on a locked device. This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1. A person with physical access to an iOS device may be able to access contacts from the lock screen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3828|2024-08-04T07:44:51.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9850|2024-08-04T10:43:05.439Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9850</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5, Safari 13.1.1, iTunes 12.10.7 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.2, iCloud for Windows 7.19. A remote attacker may be able to cause arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9850|2024-08-04T10:43:05.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3918|2024-08-04T07:52:20.579Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3918</link>
      <description>An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, macOS Catalina 10.15.4, tvOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2. A local user may be able to view sensitive user information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3918|2024-08-04T07:52:20.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9958|2024-08-04T10:50:57.832Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9958</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 14.0 and iPadOS 14.0. An application may be able to cause unexpected system termination or write kernel memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9958|2024-08-04T10:50:57.832Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9793|2024-08-04T10:43:04.587Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9793</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. A remote attacker may be able to cause arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9793|2024-08-04T10:43:04.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3883|2024-08-04T07:44:51.428Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3883</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, macOS Catalina 10.15.4, tvOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2. An application may be able to use arbitrary entitlements.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3883|2024-08-04T07:44:51.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9878|2024-08-04T10:43:05.469Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9878</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8. Processing a maliciously crafted USD file may lead to unexpected application termination or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9878|2024-08-04T10:43:05.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9802|2024-08-04T10:43:05.152Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9802</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5, Safari 13.1.1, iTunes 12.10.7 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.2, iCloud for Windows 7.19. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9802|2024-08-04T10:43:05.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3859|2024-08-04T07:44:51.225Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3859</link>
      <description>An inconsistent user interface issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1. A person with physical access to an iOS device may be able to access contacts from the lock screen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3859|2024-08-04T07:44:51.225Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3831|2024-08-04T07:44:51.060Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3831</link>
      <description>A race condition was addressed with improved locking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3831|2024-08-04T07:44:51.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3897|2024-08-04T07:52:19.726Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3897</link>
      <description>A type confusion issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, tvOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2, Safari 13.1, iTunes for Windows 12.10.5, iCloud for Windows 10.9.3, iCloud for Windows 7.18. A remote attacker may be able to cause arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3897|2024-08-04T07:52:19.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9919|2024-08-04T10:43:05.419Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9919</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9919|2024-08-04T10:43:05.419Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3869|2024-08-04T07:44:51.305Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3869</link>
      <description>An issue existed in the handling of the local user's self-view. The issue was corrected with improved logic. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1. A remote FaceTime user may be able to cause the local user's camera self-view to display the incorrect camera.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3869|2024-08-04T07:44:51.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9882|2024-08-04T10:43:05.469Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9882</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, watchOS 6.2.8. Processing a maliciously crafted USD file may lead to unexpected application termination or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9882|2024-08-04T10:43:05.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9819|2024-08-04T10:43:05.138Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9819</link>
      <description>A memory consumption issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, iOS 12.4.7, watchOS 6.2.5, watchOS 5.3.7. Processing a maliciously crafted mail message may lead to heap corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9819|2024-08-04T10:43:05.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3836|2024-08-04T07:44:51.287Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3836</link>
      <description>An access issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, macOS Catalina 10.15.3, tvOS 13.3.1, watchOS 6.1.2. A malicious application may be able to determine kernel memory layout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3836|2024-08-04T07:44:51.287Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9791|2024-08-04T10:43:04.628Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9791</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. Processing a maliciously crafted audio file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9791|2024-08-04T10:43:04.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9843|2024-08-04T10:43:05.397Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9843</link>
      <description>An input validation issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5, Safari 13.1.1, iTunes 12.10.7 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.2, iCloud for Windows 7.19. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to a cross site scripting attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9843|2024-08-04T10:43:05.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9790|2024-08-04T10:43:04.803Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9790</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5, iTunes 12.10.7 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.2, iCloud for Windows 7.19. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9790|2024-08-04T10:43:04.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9768|2024-08-04T10:43:05.148Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9768</link>
      <description>A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, tvOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with system privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9768|2024-08-04T10:43:05.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9916|2024-08-04T10:43:05.505Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9916</link>
      <description>A URL Unicode encoding issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, Safari 13.1.2, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. A malicious attacker may be able to conceal the destination of a URL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9916|2024-08-04T10:43:05.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9813|2024-08-04T10:43:05.141Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9813</link>
      <description>A logic issue existed resulting in memory corruption. This was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. A malicious application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9813|2024-08-04T10:43:05.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9795|2024-08-04T10:43:05.138Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9795</link>
      <description>A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9795|2024-08-04T10:43:05.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9976|2024-08-04T10:50:57.312Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9976</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 14.0 and iPadOS 14.0, tvOS 14.0, watchOS 7.0. A malicious application may be able to leak sensitive user information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9976|2024-08-04T10:50:57.312Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9816|2024-08-04T10:43:05.091Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9816</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. Opening a maliciously crafted PDF file may lead to an unexpected application termination or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9816|2024-08-04T10:43:05.091Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9844|2024-08-04T10:43:05.284Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9844</link>
      <description>A double free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5. A remote attacker may be able to cause unexpected system termination or corrupt kernel memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9844|2024-08-04T10:43:05.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9968|2024-08-04T10:50:57.394Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9968</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 14.0 and iPadOS 14.0, macOS Catalina 10.15.7, tvOS 14.0, watchOS 7.0. A malicious application may be able to access restricted files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9968|2024-08-04T10:50:57.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9984|2024-08-04T10:50:57.248Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9984</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9984|2024-08-04T10:50:57.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9985|2024-08-04T10:50:57.409Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9985</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, watchOS 6.2.8. Processing a maliciously crafted USD file may lead to unexpected application termination or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9985|2024-08-04T10:50:57.409Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9854|2024-08-04T10:43:05.359Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9854</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5. An application may be able to gain elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9854|2024-08-04T10:43:05.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:54:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3865|2024-08-04T07:44:51.495Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3865</link>
      <description>Multiple memory corruption issues were addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, tvOS 13.3.1, Safari 13.0.5, iTunes for Windows 12.10.4, iCloud for Windows 11.0, iCloud for Windows 7.17. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3865|2024-08-04T07:44:51.495Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3887|2024-08-04T07:52:19.930Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3887</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, tvOS 13.4, Safari 13.1, iTunes for Windows 12.10.5, iCloud for Windows 10.9.3, iCloud for Windows 7.18. A download's origin may be incorrectly associated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3887|2024-08-04T07:52:19.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9808|2024-08-04T10:43:05.270Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9808</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. An application may be able to cause unexpected system termination or write kernel memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9808|2024-08-04T10:43:05.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9820|2024-08-04T10:43:05.188Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9820</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5. A remote attacker may be able to modify the file system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9820|2024-08-04T10:43:05.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9931|2024-08-04T10:43:05.447Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9931</link>
      <description>A denial of service issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6. A remote attacker may cause an unexpected application termination.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9931|2024-08-04T10:43:05.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3891|2024-08-04T07:52:19.520Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3891</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2. A person with physical access to a locked iOS device may be able to respond to messages even when replies are disabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3891|2024-08-04T07:52:19.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9829|2024-08-04T10:43:05.259Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9829</link>
      <description>A validation issue was addressed with improved input sanitization. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. Processing a maliciously crafted text message may lead to application denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9829|2024-08-04T10:43:05.259Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27929|2024-08-04T16:25:44.100Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27929</link>
      <description>A logic issue existed in the handling of Group FaceTime calls. The issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 12.4.9. A user may send video in Group FaceTime calls without knowing that they have done so.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27929|2024-08-04T16:25:44.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9911|2024-08-04T10:43:05.403Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9911</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, Safari 13.1.2. An issue in Safari Reader mode may allow a remote attacker to bypass the Same Origin Policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9911|2024-08-04T10:43:05.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9895|2024-08-04T10:43:05.474Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9895</link>
      <description>A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, Safari 13.1.2, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. A remote attacker may be able to cause unexpected application termination or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9895|2024-08-04T10:43:05.474Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9881|2024-08-04T10:43:05.480Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9881</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, watchOS 6.2.8. Processing a maliciously crafted USD file may lead to unexpected application termination or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9881|2024-08-04T10:43:05.480Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3919|2024-08-04T07:52:20.510Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3919</link>
      <description>A memory initialization issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, macOS Catalina 10.15.4, tvOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2. A malicious application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3919|2024-08-04T07:52:20.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9809|2024-08-04T10:43:05.132Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9809</link>
      <description>An information disclosure issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. A malicious application may be able to determine kernel memory layout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9809|2024-08-04T10:43:05.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9923|2024-08-04T10:43:05.408Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9923</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, watchOS 6.2.8. A malicious application may be able to execute arbitrary code with system privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9923|2024-08-04T10:43:05.408Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9898|2024-08-04T10:43:05.417Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9898</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed with improved entitlements. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6. A sandboxed process may be able to circumvent sandbox restrictions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9898|2024-08-04T10:43:05.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3916|2024-08-04T07:52:20.387Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3916</link>
      <description>An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2. Setting an alternate app icon may disclose a photo without needing permission to access photos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3916|2024-08-04T07:52:20.387Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3858|2024-08-04T07:44:51.273Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3858</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3858|2024-08-04T07:44:51.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3829|2024-08-04T07:44:51.281Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3829</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, macOS Catalina 10.15.3, tvOS 13.3.1, watchOS 6.1.2. An application may be able to gain elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3829|2024-08-04T07:44:51.281Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9940|2024-08-04T10:50:56.257Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9940</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8. Processing a maliciously crafted USD file may lead to unexpected application termination or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9940|2024-08-04T10:50:56.257Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9880|2024-08-04T10:43:05.400Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9880</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8. Processing a maliciously crafted USD file may lead to unexpected application termination or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9880|2024-08-04T10:43:05.400Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9900|2024-08-04T10:43:05.450Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9900</link>
      <description>An issue existed within the path validation logic for symlinks. This issue was addressed with improved path sanitization. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8. A local attacker may be able to elevate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9900|2024-08-04T10:43:05.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3890|2024-08-04T07:52:19.497Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3890</link>
      <description>The issue was addressed with improved deletion. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4. Deleted messages groups may still be suggested as an autocompletion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3890|2024-08-04T07:52:19.497Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9914|2024-08-04T10:43:05.467Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9914</link>
      <description>An input validation issue existed in Bluetooth. This issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, tvOS 13.4.8. An attacker in a privileged network position may be able to perform denial of service attack using malformed Bluetooth packets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9914|2024-08-04T10:43:05.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:46:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3900|2024-08-04T07:52:19.674Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3900</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, tvOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2, Safari 13.1, iTunes for Windows 12.10.5, iCloud for Windows 10.9.3, iCloud for Windows 7.18. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3900|2024-08-04T07:52:19.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9797|2024-08-04T10:43:05.100Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9797</link>
      <description>An information disclosure issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. A malicious application may be able to determine another application's memory layout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9797|2024-08-04T10:43:05.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:02:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3914|2024-08-04T07:52:19.968Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3914</link>
      <description>A memory initialization issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, macOS Catalina 10.15.4, tvOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2. An application may be able to read restricted memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3914|2024-08-04T07:52:19.968Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3853|2024-08-04T07:44:51.339Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3853</link>
      <description>A type confusion issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, macOS Catalina 10.15.3, tvOS 13.3.1, watchOS 6.1.2. A malicious application may be able to execute arbitrary code with system privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3853|2024-08-04T07:44:51.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9934|2024-08-04T10:50:56.270Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9934</link>
      <description>An issue existed in the handling of environment variables. This issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6. A local user may be able to view sensitive user information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9934|2024-08-04T10:50:56.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9783|2024-08-04T10:43:04.501Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9783</link>
      <description>A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, tvOS 13.4, Safari 13.1, iTunes for Windows 12.10.5, iCloud for Windows 10.9.3, iCloud for Windows 7.18. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9783|2024-08-04T10:43:04.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9770|2024-08-04T10:43:04.974Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9770</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4. An attacker in a privileged network position may be able to intercept Bluetooth traffic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9770|2024-08-04T10:43:04.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9865|2024-08-04T10:43:05.474Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9865</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8. A malicious application may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9865|2024-08-04T10:43:05.474Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9902|2024-08-04T10:43:05.401Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9902</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8. A malicious application may be able to determine kernel memory layout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9902|2024-08-04T10:43:05.401Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:04:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3841|2024-08-04T07:44:51.215Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3841</link>
      <description>The issue was addressed with improved UI handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, Safari 13.0.5. A local user may unknowingly send a password unencrypted over the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3841|2024-08-04T07:44:51.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3860|2024-08-04T07:44:51.420Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3860</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, watchOS 6.1.2. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3860|2024-08-04T07:44:51.420Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9870|2024-08-04T10:43:05.407Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9870</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8. An attacker with memory write capability may be able to bypass pointer authentication codes and run arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9870|2024-08-04T10:43:05.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:33:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9827|2024-08-04T10:43:05.335Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9827</link>
      <description>A denial of service issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. A remote attacker may be able to cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9827|2024-08-04T10:43:05.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9821|2024-08-04T10:43:05.158Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9821</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. A malicious application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9821|2024-08-04T10:43:05.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9807|2024-08-04T10:43:05.197Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9807</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5, Safari 13.1.1, iTunes 12.10.7 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.2, iCloud for Windows 7.19. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9807|2024-08-04T10:43:05.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9907|2024-08-04T10:43:05.471Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9907</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, tvOS 13.4.8. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9907|2024-08-04T10:43:05.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3901|2024-08-04T07:52:20.492Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3901</link>
      <description>A type confusion issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, tvOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2, Safari 13.1, iTunes for Windows 12.10.5, iCloud for Windows 10.9.3, iCloud for Windows 7.18. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3901|2024-08-04T07:52:20.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3911|2024-08-04T07:52:20.540Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3911</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, macOS Catalina 10.15.4, tvOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2, iTunes for Windows 12.10.5, iCloud for Windows 10.9.3, iCloud for Windows 7.18. Multiple issues in libxml2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3911|2024-08-04T07:52:20.540Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9794|2024-08-04T10:43:04.957Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9794</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5, iTunes 12.10.7 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.2, iCloud for Windows 7.19. A malicious application may cause a denial of service or potentially disclose memory contents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9794|2024-08-04T10:43:04.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3868|2024-08-04T07:44:51.252Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3868</link>
      <description>Multiple memory corruption issues were addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, tvOS 13.3.1, Safari 13.0.5, iTunes for Windows 12.10.4, iCloud for Windows 11.0, iCloud for Windows 7.17. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3868|2024-08-04T07:44:51.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9872|2024-08-04T10:43:05.445Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9872</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9872|2024-08-04T10:43:05.445Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9884|2024-08-04T10:43:05.390Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9884</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8. Processing a maliciously crafted audio file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9884|2024-08-04T10:43:05.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9917|2024-08-04T10:43:05.428Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9917</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6. A remote attacker may be able to cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9917|2024-08-04T10:43:05.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9806|2024-08-04T10:43:05.087Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9806</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5, Safari 13.1.1, iTunes 12.10.7 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.2, iCloud for Windows 7.19. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9806|2024-08-04T10:43:05.087Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9891|2024-08-04T10:43:05.494Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9891</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8. Processing a maliciously crafted audio file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9891|2024-08-04T10:43:05.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:39:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9885|2024-08-04T10:43:05.388Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9885</link>
      <description>An issue existed in the handling of iMessage tapbacks. The issue was resolved with additional verification. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8. A user that is removed from an iMessage group could rejoin the group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9885|2024-08-04T10:43:05.388Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3909|2024-08-04T07:52:20.628Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3909</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, macOS Catalina 10.15.4, tvOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2, iTunes for Windows 12.10.5, iCloud for Windows 10.9.3, iCloud for Windows 7.18. Multiple issues in libxml2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3909|2024-08-04T07:52:20.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9920|2024-08-04T10:43:05.478Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9920</link>
      <description>A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, watchOS 6.2.8. A malicious mail server may overwrite arbitrary mail files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9920|2024-08-04T10:43:05.478Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9792|2024-08-04T10:43:04.546Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9792</link>
      <description>A validation issue was addressed with improved input sanitization. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5. A USB device may be able to cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9792|2024-08-04T10:43:04.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 15:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9904|2024-08-04T10:43:05.496Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9904</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9904|2024-08-04T10:43:05.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9946|2024-08-04T10:50:56.779Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9946</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 14.0 and iPadOS 14.0, watchOS 7.0. The screen lock may not engage after the specified time period.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9946|2024-08-04T10:50:56.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9980|2024-08-04T10:50:57.376Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9980</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8. Processing a maliciously crafted font file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9980|2024-08-04T10:50:57.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9910|2024-08-04T10:43:05.498Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9910</link>
      <description>Multiple issues were addressed with improved logic. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, Safari 13.1.2, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. A malicious attacker with arbitrary read and write capability may be able to bypass Pointer Authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9910|2024-08-04T10:43:05.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9877|2024-08-04T10:43:05.447Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9877</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9877|2024-08-04T10:43:05.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9871|2024-08-04T10:43:05.361Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9871</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9871|2024-08-04T10:43:05.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:54:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9835|2024-08-04T10:43:05.255Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9835</link>
      <description>An issue existed in the pausing of FaceTime video. The issue was resolved with improved logic. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5. A users video may not be paused in a FaceTime call if they exit the FaceTime app while the call is ringing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9835|2024-08-04T10:43:05.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9937|2024-08-04T10:50:56.257Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9937</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9937|2024-08-04T10:50:56.257Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9789|2024-08-04T10:43:04.600Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9789</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5, iTunes 12.10.7 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.2, iCloud for Windows 7.19. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9789|2024-08-04T10:43:04.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9875|2024-08-04T10:43:05.474Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9875</link>
      <description>An integer overflow was addressed through improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9875|2024-08-04T10:43:05.474Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:58:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9936|2024-08-04T10:50:56.227Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9936</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9936|2024-08-04T10:50:56.227Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3913|2024-08-04T07:52:19.856Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3913</link>
      <description>A permissions issue existed. This issue was addressed with improved permission validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, macOS Catalina 10.15.4, watchOS 6.2. A malicious application may be able to elevate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3913|2024-08-04T07:52:19.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:53:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3862|2024-08-04T07:44:51.432Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3862</link>
      <description>A denial of service issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, tvOS 13.3.1, Safari 13.0.5, iTunes for Windows 12.10.4, iCloud for Windows 11.0, iCloud for Windows 7.17. A malicious website may be able to cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3862|2024-08-04T07:44:51.432Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9814|2024-08-04T10:43:05.244Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9814</link>
      <description>A logic issue existed resulting in memory corruption. This was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. A malicious application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9814|2024-08-04T10:43:05.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9874|2024-08-04T10:43:05.409Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9874</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9874|2024-08-04T10:43:05.409Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3846|2024-08-04T07:44:51.418Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3846</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow was addressed with improved size validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, macOS Catalina 10.15.3, tvOS 13.3.1, watchOS 6.1.2, iTunes for Windows 12.10.4, iCloud for Windows 11.0, iCloud for Windows 7.17. Processing maliciously crafted XML may lead to an unexpected application termination or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3846|2024-08-04T07:44:51.418Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9781|2024-08-04T10:43:04.611Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9781</link>
      <description>The issue was addressed by clearing website permission prompts after navigation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4. A user may grant website permissions to a site they didn't intend to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9781|2024-08-04T10:43:04.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3837|2024-08-04T07:44:51.194Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3837</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, macOS Catalina 10.15.3, tvOS 13.3.1, watchOS 6.1.2. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3837|2024-08-04T07:44:51.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9811|2024-08-04T10:43:05.171Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9811</link>
      <description>An information disclosure issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. A local user may be able to read kernel memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9811|2024-08-04T10:43:05.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:08:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9959|2024-08-04T10:50:57.173Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9959</link>
      <description>A lock screen issue allowed access to messages on a locked device. This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 14.0 and iPadOS 14.0. A person with physical access to an iOS device may be able to view notification contents from the lockscreen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9959|2024-08-04T10:50:57.173Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3899|2024-08-04T07:52:19.621Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3899</link>
      <description>A memory consumption issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, tvOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2, Safari 13.1, iTunes for Windows 12.10.5, iCloud for Windows 10.9.3, iCloud for Windows 7.18. A remote attacker may be able to cause arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3899|2024-08-04T07:52:19.621Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3874|2024-08-04T07:44:51.471Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3874</link>
      <description>An issued existed in the naming of screenshots. The issue was corrected with improved naming. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1. Screenshots of the Messages app may reveal additional message content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3874|2024-08-04T07:44:51.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9909|2024-08-04T10:43:05.490Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9909</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8. An attacker that has already achieved kernel code execution may be able to bypass kernel memory mitigations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9909|2024-08-04T10:43:05.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:43:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9925|2024-08-04T10:43:05.423Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9925</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, Safari 13.1.2, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to universal cross site scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9925|2024-08-04T10:43:05.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9812|2024-08-04T10:43:05.328Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9812</link>
      <description>An information disclosure issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. A local user may be able to read kernel memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9812|2024-08-04T10:43:05.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9826|2024-08-04T10:43:05.143Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9826</link>
      <description>A denial of service issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5. A remote attacker may be able to cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9826|2024-08-04T10:43:05.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9992|2024-08-04T10:50:57.526Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9992</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed by encrypting communications over the network to devices running iOS 14, iPadOS 14, tvOS 14, and watchOS 7. This issue is fixed in iOS 14.0 and iPadOS 14.0, Xcode 12.0. An attacker in a privileged network position may be able to execute arbitrary code on a paired device during a debug session over the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9992|2024-08-04T10:50:57.526Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3895|2024-08-04T07:52:19.842Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3895</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, tvOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2, Safari 13.1, iTunes for Windows 12.10.5, iCloud for Windows 10.9.3, iCloud for Windows 7.18. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3895|2024-08-04T07:52:19.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:49:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9876|2024-08-04T10:43:05.452Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9876</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. Opening a maliciously crafted PDF file may lead to an unexpected application termination or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9876|2024-08-04T10:43:05.452Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3867|2024-08-04T07:44:51.335Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3867</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, tvOS 13.3.1, Safari 13.0.5, iTunes for Windows 12.10.4, iCloud for Windows 11.0, iCloud for Windows 7.17. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to universal cross site scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3867|2024-08-04T07:44:51.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9892|2024-08-04T10:43:05.492Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9892</link>
      <description>Multiple memory corruption issues were addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8. A malicious application may be able to execute arbitrary code with system privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9892|2024-08-04T10:43:05.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3872|2024-08-04T07:44:51.244Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3872</link>
      <description>A memory initialization issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, macOS Catalina 10.15.3, tvOS 13.3.1, watchOS 6.1.2. An application may be able to read restricted memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3872|2024-08-04T07:44:51.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3910|2024-08-04T07:52:20.343Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3910</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow was addressed with improved size validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, macOS Catalina 10.15.4, tvOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2, iTunes for Windows 12.10.5, iCloud for Windows 10.9.3, iCloud for Windows 7.18. Multiple issues in libxml2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3910|2024-08-04T07:52:20.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9894|2024-08-04T10:43:05.493Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9894</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, Safari 13.1.2, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. A remote attacker may be able to cause unexpected application termination or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9894|2024-08-04T10:43:05.493Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9842|2024-08-04T10:43:05.397Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9842</link>
      <description>An entitlement parsing issue was addressed with improved parsing. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. A malicious application could interact with system processes to access private information and perform privileged actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9842|2024-08-04T10:43:05.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9915|2024-08-04T10:43:05.492Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9915</link>
      <description>An access issue existed in Content Security Policy. This issue was addressed with improved access restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, Safari 13.1.2, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. Processing maliciously crafted web content may prevent Content Security Policy from being enforced.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9915|2024-08-04T10:43:05.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9903|2024-08-04T10:43:05.371Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9903</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, Safari 13.1.2. A malicious attacker may cause Safari to suggest a password for the wrong domain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9903|2024-08-04T10:43:05.371Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9868|2024-08-04T10:43:05.479Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9868</link>
      <description>A certificate validation issue existed when processing administrator added certificates. This issue was addressed with improved certificate validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8. An attacker may have been able to impersonate a trusted website using shared key material for an administrator added certificate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9868|2024-08-04T10:43:05.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9879|2024-08-04T10:43:05.495Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9879</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9879|2024-08-04T10:43:05.495Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3878|2024-08-04T07:44:51.355Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3878</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5, iTunes 12.10.7 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.2, iCloud for Windows 7.19. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3878|2024-08-04T07:44:51.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9839|2024-08-04T10:43:05.374Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9839</link>
      <description>A race condition was addressed with improved state handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. An application may be able to gain elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9839|2024-08-04T10:43:05.374Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9883|2024-08-04T10:43:05.441Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9883</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9883|2024-08-04T10:43:05.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9818|2024-08-04T10:43:05.159Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9818</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, iOS 12.4.7, watchOS 6.2.5. Processing a maliciously crafted mail message may lead to unexpected memory modification or application termination.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9818|2024-08-04T10:43:05.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9848|2024-08-04T10:43:05.389Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9848</link>
      <description>An authorization issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5. A person with physical access to an iOS device may be able to view notification contents from the lockscreen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9848|2024-08-04T10:43:05.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9787|2024-08-04T10:43:04.613Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9787</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, macOS Catalina 10.15.4, tvOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2. Some websites may not have appeared in Safari Preferences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9787|2024-08-04T10:43:04.613Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:53:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3875|2024-08-04T07:44:51.369Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3875</link>
      <description>A validation issue was addressed with improved input sanitization. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, macOS Catalina 10.15.3, tvOS 13.3.1, watchOS 6.1.2. An application may be able to read restricted memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3875|2024-08-04T07:44:51.369Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3873|2024-08-04T07:44:51.278Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3873</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed with improved setting propagation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1. Turning off "Load remote content in messages may not apply to all mail previews.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3873|2024-08-04T07:44:51.278Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9933|2024-08-04T10:50:56.250Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9933</link>
      <description>An authorization issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8. A malicious application may be able to read sensitive location information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9933|2024-08-04T10:50:56.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3885|2024-08-04T07:52:19.494Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3885</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, tvOS 13.4, Safari 13.1, iTunes for Windows 12.10.5, iCloud for Windows 10.9.3, iCloud for Windows 7.18. A file URL may be incorrectly processed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3885|2024-08-04T07:52:19.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9830|2024-08-04T10:43:05.269Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9830</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9830|2024-08-04T10:43:05.269Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9823|2024-08-04T10:43:05.230Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9823</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5. Users removed from an iMessage conversation may still be able to alter state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9823|2024-08-04T10:43:05.230Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9859|2024-08-04T10:43:05.468Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9859</link>
      <description>A memory consumption issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5.1 and iPadOS 13.5.1, macOS Catalina 10.15.5 Supplemental Update, tvOS 13.4.6, watchOS 6.2.6. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9859|2024-08-04T10:43:05.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3917|2024-08-04T07:52:20.204Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3917</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed with a new entitlement. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, tvOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2. An application may be able to use an SSH client provided by private frameworks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3917|2024-08-04T07:52:20.204Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:54:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9780|2024-08-04T10:43:04.424Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9780</link>
      <description>The issue was resolved by clearing application previews when content is deleted. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4. A local user may be able to view deleted content in the app switcher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9780|2024-08-04T10:43:04.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9805|2024-08-04T10:43:05.197Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9805</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5, Safari 13.1.1, iTunes 12.10.7 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.2, iCloud for Windows 7.19. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to universal cross site scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9805|2024-08-04T10:43:05.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9772|2024-08-04T10:43:04.452Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9772</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, macOS Catalina 10.15.4, tvOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2. A sandboxed process may be able to circumvent sandbox restrictions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9772|2024-08-04T10:43:04.452Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9852|2024-08-04T10:43:05.411Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9852</link>
      <description>An integer overflow was addressed through improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. A malicious application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9852|2024-08-04T10:43:05.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:18:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3870|2024-08-04T07:44:51.251Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3870</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, macOS Catalina 10.15.3, tvOS 13.3.1, watchOS 6.1.2. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3870|2024-08-04T07:44:51.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9800|2024-08-04T10:43:05.081Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9800</link>
      <description>A type confusion issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5, Safari 13.1.1, iTunes 12.10.7 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.2, iCloud for Windows 7.19. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9800|2024-08-04T10:43:05.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9888|2024-08-04T10:43:05.477Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9888</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8. Processing a maliciously crafted audio file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9888|2024-08-04T10:43:05.477Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9803|2024-08-04T10:43:05.006Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9803</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5, Safari 13.1.1, iTunes 12.10.7 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.2, iCloud for Windows 7.19. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9803|2024-08-04T10:43:05.006Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3825|2024-08-04T07:44:51.279Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3825</link>
      <description>Multiple memory corruption issues were addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, tvOS 13.3.1, Safari 13.0.5, iTunes for Windows 12.10.4, iCloud for Windows 11.0, iCloud for Windows 7.17. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3825|2024-08-04T07:44:51.279Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3857|2024-08-04T07:44:51.383Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3857</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, macOS Catalina 10.15.3, tvOS 13.3.1, watchOS 6.1.2. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with system privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3857|2024-08-04T07:44:51.383Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9773|2024-08-04T10:43:05.126Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9773</link>
      <description>The issue was addressed with improved handling of icon caches. This issue is fixed in iOS 14.0 and iPadOS 14.0. A malicious application may be able to identify what other applications a user has installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9773|2024-08-04T10:43:05.126Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9964|2024-08-04T10:50:56.830Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9964</link>
      <description>A memory initialization issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 14.0 and iPadOS 14.0. A local user may be able to read kernel memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9964|2024-08-04T10:50:56.830Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9873|2024-08-04T10:43:05.481Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9873</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9873|2024-08-04T10:43:05.481Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9862|2024-08-04T10:43:05.449Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9862</link>
      <description>A command injection issue existed in Web Inspector. This issue was addressed with improved escaping. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, Safari 13.1.2, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. Copying a URL from Web Inspector may lead to command injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9862|2024-08-04T10:43:05.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3842|2024-08-04T07:44:51.179Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3842</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, macOS Catalina 10.15.3, tvOS 13.3.1, watchOS 6.1.2. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3842|2024-08-04T07:44:51.179Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9863|2024-08-04T10:43:05.416Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9863</link>
      <description>A memory initialization issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9863|2024-08-04T10:43:05.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 17:54:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9785|2024-08-04T10:43:04.518Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9785</link>
      <description>Multiple memory corruption issues were addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, macOS Catalina 10.15.4, tvOS 13.4, watchOS 6.2. A malicious application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9785|2024-08-04T10:43:04.518Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9994|2024-08-04T10:50:57.260Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9994</link>
      <description>A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. A malicious application may be able to overwrite arbitrary files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9994|2024-08-04T10:50:57.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9905|2024-08-04T10:43:05.567Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9905</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8. A remote attacker may be able to cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9905|2024-08-04T10:43:05.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9838|2024-08-04T10:43:05.336Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9838</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5. A remote attacker may be able to cause arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9838|2024-08-04T10:43:05.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3856|2024-08-04T07:44:51.283Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3856</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, macOS Catalina 10.15.3, tvOS 13.3.1, watchOS 6.1.2. Processing a maliciously crafted string may lead to heap corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3856|2024-08-04T07:44:51.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9952|2024-08-04T10:50:56.773Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9952</link>
      <description>An input validation issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 14.0 and iPadOS 14.0, tvOS 14.0, watchOS 7.0, Safari 14.0, iCloud for Windows 11.4, iCloud for Windows 7.21. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to a cross site scripting attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9952|2024-08-04T10:50:56.773Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9889|2024-08-04T10:43:05.495Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9889</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8. Processing a maliciously crafted audio file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9889|2024-08-04T10:43:05.495Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3888|2024-08-04T07:52:19.716Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3888</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4. A maliciously crafted page may interfere with other web contexts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3888|2024-08-04T07:52:19.716Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9825|2024-08-04T10:43:05.336Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9825</link>
      <description>An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5. A malicious application may be able to bypass Privacy preferences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9825|2024-08-04T10:43:05.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3844|2024-08-04T07:44:51.347Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3844</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1. Users removed from an iMessage conversation may still be able to alter state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3844|2024-08-04T07:44:51.347Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3902|2024-08-04T07:52:19.754Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3902</link>
      <description>An input validation issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, tvOS 13.4, Safari 13.1, iTunes for Windows 12.10.5, iCloud for Windows 10.9.3, iCloud for Windows 7.18. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to a cross site scripting attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3902|2024-08-04T07:52:19.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9938|2024-08-04T10:50:56.270Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9938</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9938|2024-08-04T10:50:56.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9906|2024-08-04T10:43:05.573Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9906</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, watchOS 6.2.8. A remote attacker may be able to cause unexpected system termination or corrupt kernel memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9906|2024-08-04T10:43:05.573Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9901|2024-08-04T10:43:05.482Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9901</link>
      <description>An issue existed within the path validation logic for symlinks. This issue was addressed with improved path sanitization. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8. A local attacker may be able to elevate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9901|2024-08-04T10:43:05.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 18:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3840|2024-08-04T07:44:51.195Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3840</link>
      <description>An off by one issue existed in the handling of racoon configuration files. This issue was addressed through improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, macOS Catalina 10.15.3, tvOS 13.3.1. Loading a maliciously crafted racoon configuration file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3840|2024-08-04T07:44:51.195Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9890|2024-08-04T10:43:05.507Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9890</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, macOS Catalina 10.15.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8. Processing a maliciously crafted audio file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9890|2024-08-04T10:43:05.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9777|2024-08-04T10:43:04.500Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9777</link>
      <description>An issue existed in the selection of video file by Mail. The issue was fixed by selecting the latest version of a video. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4. Cropped videos may not be shared properly via Mail.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9777|2024-08-04T10:43:04.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9837|2024-08-04T10:43:05.151Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9837</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5. A remote attacker may be able to leak memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9837|2024-08-04T10:43:05.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9893|2024-08-04T10:43:05.478Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9893</link>
      <description>A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.6 and iPadOS 13.6, tvOS 13.4.8, watchOS 6.2.8, Safari 13.1.2, iTunes 12.10.8 for Windows, iCloud for Windows 11.3, iCloud for Windows 7.20. A remote attacker may be able to cause unexpected application termination or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9893|2024-08-04T10:43:05.478Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3826|2024-08-04T07:44:51.025Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3826</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, macOS Catalina 10.15.3, tvOS 13.3.1, watchOS 6.1.2, iTunes for Windows 12.10.4, iCloud for Windows 11.0, iCloud for Windows 7.17. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3826|2024-08-04T07:44:51.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3838|2024-08-04T07:44:51.242Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3838</link>
      <description>The issue was addressed with improved permissions logic. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.3.1 and iPadOS 13.3.1, macOS Catalina 10.15.3, tvOS 13.3.1, watchOS 6.1.2. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with system privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3838|2024-08-04T07:44:51.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9775|2024-08-04T10:43:04.399Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9775</link>
      <description>An issue existed in the handling of tabs displaying picture in picture video. The issue was corrected with improved state handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4. A user's private browsing activity may be unexpectedly saved in Screen Time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9775|2024-08-04T10:43:04.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3894|2024-08-04T07:52:19.503Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3894</link>
      <description>A race condition was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.4 and iPadOS 13.4, tvOS 13.4, Safari 13.1, iTunes for Windows 12.10.5, iCloud for Windows 10.9.3, iCloud for Windows 7.18. An application may be able to read restricted memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3894|2024-08-04T07:52:19.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:49:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9815|2024-08-04T10:43:05.089Z -- apple -- ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9815</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iOS 13.5 and iPadOS 13.5, macOS Catalina 10.15.5, tvOS 13.4.5, watchOS 6.2.5. Processing a maliciously crafted audio file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9815|2024-08-04T10:43:05.089Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
