<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apple -- tvOS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apple/tvos.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apple -- tvOS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 19:22:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38598|2024-10-22T18:12:03.173Z -- apple -- tvos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38598</link>
      <description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 9.6, macOS Big Sur 11.7.9, iOS 15.7.8 and iPadOS 15.7.8, macOS Monterey 12.6.8, tvOS 16.6, iOS 16.6 and iPadOS 16.6, macOS Ventura 13.5. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38598|2024-10-22T18:12:03.173Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 04:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38590|2024-10-22T18:20:32.157Z -- apple -- tvos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38590</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 9.6, macOS Big Sur 11.7.9, iOS 15.7.8 and iPadOS 15.7.8, macOS Monterey 12.6.8, tvOS 16.6, iOS 16.6 and iPadOS 16.6, macOS Ventura 13.5. A remote user may be able to cause unexpected system termination or corrupt kernel memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38590|2024-10-22T18:20:32.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 04:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38604|2024-10-22T18:12:54.427Z -- apple -- tvos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38604</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in watchOS 9.6, macOS Big Sur 11.7.9, iOS 15.7.8 and iPadOS 15.7.8, macOS Monterey 12.6.8, tvOS 16.6, iOS 16.6 and iPadOS 16.6, macOS Ventura 13.5. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38604|2024-10-22T18:12:54.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 04:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36495|2024-10-22T18:13:41.737Z -- apple -- tvos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36495</link>
      <description>An integer overflow was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in watchOS 9.6, macOS Monterey 12.6.8, iOS 15.7.8 and iPadOS 15.7.8, tvOS 16.6, iOS 16.6 and iPadOS 16.6, macOS Ventura 13.5. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36495|2024-10-22T18:13:41.737Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 04:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
