<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apple -- tvOS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apple/tvos.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apple -- tvOS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 19:20:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32441|2024-10-23T14:00:48.028Z -- apple -- tvos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32441</link>
      <description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.6.8, iOS 15.7.8 and iPadOS 15.7.8, iOS 16.6 and iPadOS 16.6, tvOS 16.6, macOS Big Sur 11.7.9, macOS Ventura 13.5, watchOS 9.6. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32441|2024-10-23T14:00:48.028Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32381|2024-10-23T14:07:57.496Z -- apple -- tvos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32381</link>
      <description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.6.8, iOS 16.6 and iPadOS 16.6, tvOS 16.6, macOS Big Sur 11.7.9, macOS Ventura 13.5, watchOS 9.6. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32381|2024-10-23T14:07:57.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 23:52:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32433|2024-10-23T14:41:58.983Z -- apple -- tvos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32433</link>
      <description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.6.8, iOS 15.7.8 and iPadOS 15.7.8, iOS 16.6 and iPadOS 16.6, tvOS 16.6, macOS Big Sur 11.7.9, macOS Ventura 13.5, watchOS 9.6. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32433|2024-10-23T14:41:58.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 23:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38606|2024-10-23T13:56:03.332Z -- apple -- tvos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38606</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.6.8, iOS 15.7.8 and iPadOS 15.7.8, iOS 16.6 and iPadOS 16.6, tvOS 16.6, macOS Big Sur 11.7.9, macOS Ventura 13.5, watchOS 9.6. An app may be able to modify sensitive kernel state. Apple is aware of a report that this issue may have been actively exploited against versions of iOS released before iOS 15.7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38606|2024-10-23T13:56:03.332Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 23:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
