<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apple -- watchOS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apple/watchos.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apple -- watchOS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:22:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30995|2024-08-03T22:48:14.302Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30995</link>
      <description>A race condition was addressed with improved state handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.6.2, tvOS 15.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, Security Update 2021-008 Catalina, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. A malicious application may be able to elevate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30995|2024-08-03T22:48:14.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26702|2024-08-03T05:11:44.241Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26702</link>
      <description>A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 8.6, tvOS 15.5, iOS 15.5 and iPadOS 15.5. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26702|2024-08-03T05:11:44.241Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1814|2024-08-03T16:25:05.983Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1814</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.3, watchOS 7.4. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1814|2024-08-03T16:25:05.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 14:54:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30958|2024-08-03T22:48:14.297Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30958</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.6.2, tvOS 15.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, Security Update 2021-008 Catalina, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. Playing a malicious audio file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30958|2024-08-03T22:48:14.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30984|2024-08-03T22:48:14.319Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30984</link>
      <description>A race condition was addressed with improved state handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 15.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, Safari 15.2, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30984|2024-08-03T22:48:14.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30943|2024-08-03T22:48:14.246Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30943</link>
      <description>An issue in the handling of group membership was resolved with improved logic. This issue is fixed in iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3, macOS Monterey 12.1. A malicious user may be able to leave a messages group but continue to receive messages in that group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30943|2024-08-03T22:48:14.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30927|2024-08-03T22:48:14.223Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30927</link>
      <description>A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.6.2, tvOS 15.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, Security Update 2021-008 Catalina, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30927|2024-08-03T22:48:14.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26714|2024-08-03T05:11:45.073Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26714</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in tvOS 15.5, iOS 15.5 and iPadOS 15.5, Security Update 2022-004 Catalina, watchOS 8.6, macOS Big Sur 11.6.6, macOS Monterey 12.4. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26714|2024-08-03T05:11:45.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 18:49:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26757|2024-08-03T05:11:44.272Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26757</link>
      <description>A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 15.5, iOS 15.5 and iPadOS 15.5, Security Update 2022-004 Catalina, watchOS 8.6, macOS Big Sur 11.6.6, macOS Monterey 12.4. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26757|2024-08-03T05:11:44.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 19:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26763|2024-08-03T05:11:44.915Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26763</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in tvOS 15.5, iOS 15.5 and iPadOS 15.5, Security Update 2022-004 Catalina, watchOS 8.6, macOS Big Sur 11.6.6, macOS Monterey 12.4. A malicious application may be able to execute arbitrary code with system privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26763|2024-08-03T05:11:44.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 19:19:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30953|2024-08-03T22:48:14.262Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30953</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in tvOS 15.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, Safari 15.2, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30953|2024-08-03T22:48:14.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26726|2024-08-03T05:11:44.862Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26726</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in Security Update 2022-004 Catalina, watchOS 8.6, macOS Monterey 12.4, macOS Big Sur 11.6.6. An app may be able to capture a user's screen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26726|2024-08-03T05:11:44.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 18:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30964|2024-08-03T22:48:14.212Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30964</link>
      <description>An inherited permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.1, watchOS 8.3, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2. A malicious application may be able to bypass Privacy preferences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30964|2024-08-03T22:48:14.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30957|2024-08-03T22:48:14.249Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30957</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.1, watchOS 8.3, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, tvOS 15.2. Processing a maliciously crafted audio file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30957|2024-08-03T22:48:14.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30993|2024-08-03T22:48:14.216Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30993</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.1, watchOS 8.3, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, tvOS 15.2. An attacker in a privileged network position may be able to execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30993|2024-08-03T22:48:14.216Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30947|2024-08-03T22:48:14.201Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30947</link>
      <description>An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.6.2, tvOS 15.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. An application may be able to access a user's files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30947|2024-08-03T22:48:14.201Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30955|2024-08-03T22:48:14.250Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30955</link>
      <description>A race condition was addressed with improved state handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.1, watchOS 8.3, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, tvOS 15.2. A malicious application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30955|2024-08-03T22:48:14.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30951|2024-08-03T22:48:14.448Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30951</link>
      <description>A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 15.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, Safari 15.2, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30951|2024-08-03T22:48:14.448Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26771|2024-08-03T05:11:44.487Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26771</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 8.6, tvOS 15.5, iOS 15.5 and iPadOS 15.5. A malicious application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26771|2024-08-03T05:11:44.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 19:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30934|2024-08-03T22:48:14.225Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30934</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 15.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, Safari 15.2, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30934|2024-08-03T22:48:14.225Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26706|2024-08-03T05:11:44.450Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26706</link>
      <description>An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions on third-party applications. This issue is fixed in tvOS 15.5, iOS 15.5 and iPadOS 15.5, watchOS 8.6, macOS Big Sur 11.6.6, macOS Monterey 12.4. A sandboxed process may be able to circumvent sandbox restrictions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26706|2024-08-03T05:11:44.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 18:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26711|2024-08-03T05:11:44.271Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26711</link>
      <description>An integer overflow issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in tvOS 15.5, iTunes 12.12.4 for Windows, iOS 15.5 and iPadOS 15.5, watchOS 8.6, macOS Monterey 12.4. A remote attacker may be able to cause unexpected application termination or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26711|2024-08-03T05:11:44.271Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 18:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30937|2024-08-03T22:48:14.228Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30937</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability was addressed with improved locking. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.6.2, tvOS 15.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, Security Update 2021-008 Catalina, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. A malicious application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30937|2024-08-03T22:48:14.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30980|2024-08-03T22:48:14.261Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30980</link>
      <description>A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.6.2, tvOS 15.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, Security Update 2021-008 Catalina, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30980|2024-08-03T22:48:14.261Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30946|2024-08-03T22:48:14.214Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30946</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.1, watchOS 8.3, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, macOS Big Sur 11.6.2. A malicious application may be able to bypass certain Privacy preferences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30946|2024-08-03T22:48:14.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30952|2024-08-03T22:48:14.237Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30952</link>
      <description>An integer overflow was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in tvOS 15.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, Safari 15.2, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30952|2024-08-03T22:48:14.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31000|2024-08-03T22:48:14.252Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31000</link>
      <description>A permissions issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3, macOS Monterey 12.1, tvOS 15.2. A malicious application may be able to read sensitive contact information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31000|2024-08-03T22:48:14.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30960|2024-08-03T22:48:14.196Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30960</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.1, watchOS 8.3, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, tvOS 15.2. Parsing a maliciously crafted audio file may lead to disclosure of user information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30960|2024-08-03T22:48:14.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30945|2024-08-03T22:48:14.261Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30945</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.6.2, tvOS 15.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, Security Update 2021-008 Catalina, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. A local attacker may be able to elevate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30945|2024-08-03T22:48:14.261Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30926|2024-08-03T22:48:14.249Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30926</link>
      <description>Description: A memory corruption issue in the processing of ICC profiles was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.1, watchOS 8.3, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, tvOS 15.2. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30926|2024-08-03T22:48:14.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30944|2024-08-03T22:48:14.200Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30944</link>
      <description>Description: A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3, macOS Monterey 12.1, tvOS 15.2. A malicious app may be able to access data from other apps by enabling additional logging.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30944|2024-08-03T22:48:14.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26768|2024-08-03T05:11:44.500Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26768</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.4, watchOS 8.6, tvOS 15.5, macOS Big Sur 11.6.6. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26768|2024-08-03T05:11:44.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 19:23:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1880|2024-08-03T16:25:06.339Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1880</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.3, watchOS 7.4. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1880|2024-08-03T16:25:06.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 14:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26765|2024-08-03T05:11:44.486Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26765</link>
      <description>A race condition was addressed with improved state handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 8.6, tvOS 15.5, macOS Monterey 12.4, iOS 15.5 and iPadOS 15.5. A malicious attacker with arbitrary read and write capability may be able to bypass Pointer Authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26765|2024-08-03T05:11:44.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 19:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26764|2024-08-03T05:11:44.538Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26764</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in watchOS 8.6, tvOS 15.5, macOS Monterey 12.4, iOS 15.5 and iPadOS 15.5. An attacker that has already achieved kernel code execution may be able to bypass kernel memory mitigations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26764|2024-08-03T05:11:44.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 19:20:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30966|2024-08-03T22:48:14.283Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30966</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Monterey 12.1, watchOS 8.3, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, tvOS 15.2. User traffic might unexpectedly be leaked to a proxy server despite PAC configurations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30966|2024-08-03T22:48:14.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30954|2024-08-03T22:48:14.215Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30954</link>
      <description>A type confusion issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in tvOS 15.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, Safari 15.2, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30954|2024-08-03T22:48:14.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26766|2024-08-03T05:11:44.410Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26766</link>
      <description>A certificate parsing issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 15.5, iOS 15.5 and iPadOS 15.5, Security Update 2022-004 Catalina, watchOS 8.6, macOS Big Sur 11.6.6, macOS Monterey 12.4. A malicious app may be able to bypass signature validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26766|2024-08-03T05:11:44.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 19:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30942|2024-08-03T22:48:14.226Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30942</link>
      <description>Description: A memory corruption issue in the processing of ICC profiles was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.6.2, tvOS 15.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, Security Update 2021-008 Catalina, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30942|2024-08-03T22:48:14.226Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30949|2024-08-03T22:48:14.253Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30949</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.6.2, tvOS 15.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, Security Update 2021-008 Catalina, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. A malicious application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30949|2024-08-03T22:48:14.253Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30939|2024-08-03T22:48:14.178Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30939</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.6.2, tvOS 15.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, Security Update 2021-008 Catalina, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30939|2024-08-03T22:48:14.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30767|2024-08-03T22:40:32.143Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30767</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.6.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, Security Update 2021-008 Catalina, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. A local user may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30767|2024-08-03T22:40:32.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 19:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30968|2024-08-03T22:48:14.211Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30968</link>
      <description>A validation issue related to hard link behavior was addressed with improved sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.6.2, tvOS 15.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, Security Update 2021-008 Catalina, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. A malicious application may be able to bypass certain Privacy preferences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30968|2024-08-03T22:48:14.211Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30936|2024-08-03T22:48:14.180Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30936</link>
      <description>A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in tvOS 15.2, macOS Monterey 12.1, Safari 15.2, iOS 15.2 and iPadOS 15.2, watchOS 8.3. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30936|2024-08-03T22:48:14.180Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27814|2024-08-02T00:41:55.425Z -- apple -- watchos</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27814</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.5. A person with physical access to a device may be able to view contact information from the lock screen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27814|2024-08-02T00:41:55.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 20:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27814|2024-06-11T19:06:32.639Z -- apple -- watchos</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27814</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.5. A person with physical access to a device may be able to view contact information from the lock screen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27814|2024-06-11T19:06:32.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 20:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
