<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apple -- watchOS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apple/watchos.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apple -- watchOS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27927|2024-08-04T16:25:44.140Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27927</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, tvOS 14.2, watchOS 7.1. Processing a maliciously crafted font file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27927|2024-08-04T16:25:44.140Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27918|2024-08-04T16:25:43.860Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27918</link>
      <description>A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, watchOS 7.1, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, iCloud for Windows 11.5, Safari 14.0.1, tvOS 14.2, iTunes 12.11 for Windows. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27918|2024-08-04T16:25:43.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 21:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27899|2024-08-04T16:25:43.673Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27899</link>
      <description>A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, watchOS 7.1, tvOS 14.2. A local attacker may be able to elevate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27899|2024-08-04T16:25:43.673Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 17:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27930|2024-08-04T16:25:44.098Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27930</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, watchOS 7.1, iOS 12.4.9, watchOS 6.2.9, Security Update 2020-006 High Sierra, Security Update 2020-006 Mojave, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, watchOS 5.3.9, macOS Catalina 10.15.7 Supplemental Update, macOS Catalina 10.15.7 Update. Processing a maliciously crafted font may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27930|2024-08-04T16:25:44.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27923|2024-08-04T16:25:44.114Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27923</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.1, Security Update 2020-001 Catalina, Security Update 2020-007 Mojave, macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, watchOS 7.1, tvOS 14.2. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27923|2024-08-04T16:25:44.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 17:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10017|2024-08-04T10:50:57.392Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10017</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, tvOS 14.2, watchOS 7.1. Processing a maliciously crafted audio file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10017|2024-08-04T10:50:57.392Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10010|2024-08-04T10:50:57.446Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10010</link>
      <description>A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, tvOS 14.2, watchOS 7.1. A local attacker may be able to elevate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10010|2024-08-04T10:50:57.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27922|2024-08-04T16:25:44.123Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27922</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.1, Security Update 2020-001 Catalina, Security Update 2020-007 Mojave, macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, watchOS 7.1, tvOS 14.2. Processing a maliciously crafted font file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27922|2024-08-04T16:25:44.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 17:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8766|2024-08-04T21:31:36.287Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8766</link>
      <description>Multiple memory corruption issues were addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 6.1, iCloud for Windows 11.0. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8766|2024-08-04T21:31:36.287Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 17:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27911|2024-08-04T16:25:43.939Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27911</link>
      <description>An integer overflow was addressed through improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, watchOS 7.1, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, iCloud for Windows 11.5, tvOS 14.2, iTunes 12.11 for Windows. A remote attacker may be able to cause unexpected application termination or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27911|2024-08-04T16:25:43.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27917|2024-08-04T16:25:44.150Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27917</link>
      <description>A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, watchOS 7.1, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, iCloud for Windows 11.5, tvOS 14.2, iTunes 12.11 for Windows. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27917|2024-08-04T16:25:44.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8750|2024-08-04T21:31:35.806Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8750</link>
      <description>Multiple memory corruption issues were addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in watchOS 6.1, iCloud for Windows 11.0. Multiple issues in libxslt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8750|2024-08-04T21:31:35.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 17:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8624|2024-08-04T21:24:28.628Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8624</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in watchOS 5.3. A remote attacker may be able to leak memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8624|2024-08-04T21:24:28.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 17:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27924|2024-08-04T16:25:43.939Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27924</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.1, Security Update 2020-001 Catalina, Security Update 2020-007 Mojave, macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, watchOS 7.1, tvOS 14.2. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27924|2024-08-04T16:25:43.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 17:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10002|2024-08-04T10:50:57.464Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10002</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, watchOS 7.1, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, iCloud for Windows 11.5, tvOS 14.2, iTunes 12.11 for Windows. A local user may be able to read arbitrary files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10002|2024-08-04T10:50:57.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 19:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27920|2024-08-04T16:25:43.909Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27920</link>
      <description>A use after free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.1, Security Update 2020-001 Catalina, Security Update 2020-007 Mojave, macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, watchOS 7.1, tvOS 14.2. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27920|2024-08-04T16:25:43.909Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 17:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27932|2024-08-04T16:25:43.916Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27932</link>
      <description>A type confusion issue was addressed with improved state handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, watchOS 7.1, iOS 12.4.9, watchOS 6.2.9, Security Update 2020-006 High Sierra, Security Update 2020-006 Mojave, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, watchOS 5.3.9, macOS Catalina 10.15.7 Supplemental Update, macOS Catalina 10.15.7 Update. A malicious application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27932|2024-08-04T16:25:43.916Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27950|2024-08-04T16:25:43.906Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27950</link>
      <description>A memory initialization issue was addressed. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, watchOS 7.1, iOS 12.4.9, watchOS 6.2.9, Security Update 2020-006 High Sierra, Security Update 2020-006 Mojave, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, watchOS 5.3.9, macOS Catalina 10.15.7 Supplemental Update, macOS Catalina 10.15.7 Update. A malicious application may be able to disclose kernel memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27950|2024-08-04T16:25:43.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27908|2024-08-04T16:25:43.967Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27908</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.1, Security Update 2020-001 Catalina, Security Update 2020-007 Mojave, macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, watchOS 7.1, tvOS 14.2. Processing a maliciously crafted audio file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27908|2024-08-04T16:25:43.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 17:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10016|2024-08-04T10:50:57.352Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10016</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, tvOS 14.2, watchOS 7.1. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10016|2024-08-04T10:50:57.352Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8743|2024-08-04T21:24:29.613Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8743</link>
      <description>Multiple memory corruption issues were addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 6.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8743|2024-08-04T21:24:29.613Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 17:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8764|2024-08-04T21:31:36.675Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8764</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 6.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to universal cross site scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8764|2024-08-04T21:31:36.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 17:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8659|2024-08-04T21:24:29.524Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8659</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 5.3. Users removed from an iMessage conversation may still be able to alter state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8659|2024-08-04T21:24:29.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 17:33:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27912|2024-08-04T16:25:43.896Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27912</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, watchOS 7.1, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, iCloud for Windows 11.5, tvOS 14.2, iTunes 12.11 for Windows. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27912|2024-08-04T16:25:43.896Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9989|2024-08-04T10:50:57.216Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9989</link>
      <description>The issue was addressed with improved deletion. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, watchOS 7.0, iOS 14.0 and iPadOS 14.0. A local user may be able to discover a user’s deleted messages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9989|2024-08-04T10:50:57.216Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 19:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27910|2024-08-04T16:25:43.957Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27910</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, tvOS 14.2, watchOS 7.1. Processing a maliciously crafted audio file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27910|2024-08-04T16:25:43.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8548|2024-08-04T21:24:27.664Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8548</link>
      <description>An issue existed where partially entered passcodes may not clear when the device went to sleep. This issue was addressed by clearing the passcode when a locked device sleeps. This issue is fixed in watchOS 5.2. A partially entered passcode may not clear when the device goes to sleep.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8548|2024-08-04T21:24:27.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 17:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10003|2024-08-04T10:50:57.240Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10003</link>
      <description>An issue existed within the path validation logic for symlinks. This issue was addressed with improved path sanitization. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, tvOS 14.2, watchOS 7.1. A local attacker may be able to elevate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10003|2024-08-04T10:50:57.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27935|2024-08-04T16:25:44.185Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27935</link>
      <description>Multiple issues were addressed with improved logic. This issue is fixed in iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, watchOS 7.1, tvOS 14.2. A sandboxed process may be able to circumvent sandbox restrictions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27935|2024-08-04T16:25:44.185Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 17:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27905|2024-08-04T16:25:43.624Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27905</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, tvOS 14.2, watchOS 7.1. A malicious application may be able to execute arbitrary code with system privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27905|2024-08-04T16:25:43.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8747|2024-08-04T21:31:35.690Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8747</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability was addressed with improved locking. This issue is fixed in watchOS 6.1. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8747|2024-08-04T21:31:35.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 17:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8765|2024-08-04T21:31:37.497Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8765</link>
      <description>Multiple memory corruption issues were addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 6.1. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8765|2024-08-04T21:31:37.497Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 17:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27916|2024-08-04T16:25:43.987Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27916</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, tvOS 14.2, watchOS 7.1. Processing a maliciously crafted audio file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27916|2024-08-04T16:25:43.987Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9974|2024-08-04T10:50:57.262Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9974</link>
      <description>A logic issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Big Sur 11.0.1, iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, tvOS 14.2, watchOS 7.1. A malicious application may be able to determine kernel memory layout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9974|2024-08-04T10:50:57.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 19:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27909|2024-08-04T16:25:43.802Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27909</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in iOS 14.2 and iPadOS 14.2, tvOS 14.2, watchOS 7.1. Processing a maliciously crafted audio file may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27909|2024-08-04T16:25:43.802Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3834|2024-08-04T07:44:50.984Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3834</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 6.1.2. An application may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3834|2024-08-04T07:44:50.984Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9993|2024-08-04T10:50:57.253Z -- apple -- watchos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9993</link>
      <description>The issue was addressed with improved UI handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 7.0, Safari 14.0, iOS 14.0 and iPadOS 14.0. Visiting a malicious website may lead to address bar spoofing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9993|2024-08-04T10:50:57.253Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 19:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27814|2024-08-02T00:41:55.425Z -- apple -- watchos</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27814</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.5. A person with physical access to a device may be able to view contact information from the lock screen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27814|2024-08-02T00:41:55.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 20:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27814|2024-06-11T19:06:32.639Z -- apple -- watchos</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27814</link>
      <description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.5. A person with physical access to a device may be able to view contact information from the lock screen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27814|2024-06-11T19:06:32.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 20:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
