<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apex Softcell -- LD DP Back Office</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apex%20softcell/ld%20dp%20back%20office.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apex Softcell -- LD DP Back Office</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 07:22:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-47085|2024-09-19T06:21:05.655Z -- apex%20softcell -- ld%20dp%20back%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47085</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exists in Apex Softcell LD DP Back Office due to improper validation of certain parameters “cCdslClicentcode” and “cLdClientCode” in the API endpoint. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating parameters in the API request body leading to exposure of sensitive information belonging to other users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-47085|2024-09-19T06:21:05.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 05:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-47086|2024-09-19T06:19:50.229Z -- apex%20softcell -- ld%20dp%20back%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47086</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exists in Apex Softcell LD DP Back Office due to improper implementation of OTP validation mechanism in certain API endpoints. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by providing arbitrary OTP value for authentication and subsequently changing its API response.  

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to bypass OTP verification for other user accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-47086|2024-09-19T06:19:50.229Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 06:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-47085|2024-09-19T05:56:23.460Z -- apex%20softcell -- ld%20dp%20back%20office</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47085</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exists in LD DP Back Office due to improper validation of certain parameters “cCdslClicentcode” and “cLdClientCode” in the API endpoint. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating parameters in the API request body leading to exposure of sensitive information belonging to other users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-47085|2024-09-19T05:56:23.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 05:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
