<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for opencast -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/opencast/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for opencast -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21318|2024-08-03T18:09:15.422Z -- opencast -- opencast
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21318</link>
      <description>Opencast is a free, open-source platform to support the management of educational audio and video content. In Opencast before version 9.2 there is a vulnerability in which publishing an episode with strict access rules will overwrite the currently set series access. This allows for an easy denial of access for all users without superuser privileges, effectively hiding the series. Access to series and series metadata on the search service (shown in media module and player) depends on the events published which are part of the series. Publishing an event will automatically publish a series and update access to it. Removing an event or republishing the event should do the same. Affected versions of Opencast may not update the series access or remove a published series if an event is being removed. On removal of an episode, this may lead to an access control list for series metadata with broader access rules than the merged access rules of all remaining events, or the series metadata still being available although all episodes of that series have been removed. This problem is fixed in Opencast 9.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21318|2024-08-03T18:09:15.422Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 17:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41965|2024-08-03T12:56:39.128Z -- opencast -- opencast
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41965</link>
      <description>Opencast is a free, open-source platform to support the management of educational audio and video content. Prior to Opencast 12.5, Opencast's Paella authentication page could be used to redirect to an arbitrary URL for authenticated users. The vulnerability allows attackers to redirect users to sites outside of one's Opencast install, potentially facilitating phishing attacks or other security issues. This issue is fixed in Opencast 12.5 and newer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41965|2024-08-03T12:56:39.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29237|2024-08-03T06:17:54.538Z -- opencast -- opencast
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29237</link>
      <description>Opencast is a free and open source solution for automated video capture and distribution at scale. Prior to Opencast 10.14 and 11.7, users could pass along URLs for files belonging to organizations other than the user's own, which Opencast would then import into the current organization, bypassing organizational barriers. Attackers must have full access to Opencast's ingest REST interface, and also know internal links to resources in another organization of the same Opencast cluster. Users who do not run a multi-tenant cluster are not affected by this issue. This issue is fixed in Opencast 10.14 and 11.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29237|2024-08-03T06:17:54.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 14:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
