<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for opencast -- opencast</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/opencast/opencast.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for opencast -- opencast</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 06:24:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43821|2024-08-04T04:03:08.978Z -- opencast -- opencast
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43821</link>
      <description>Opencast is an Open Source Lecture Capture &amp; Video Management for Education. Opencast before version 9.10 or 10.6 allows references to local file URLs in ingested media packages, allowing attackers to include local files from Opencast's host machines and making them available via the web interface. Before Opencast 9.10 and 10.6, Opencast would open and include local files during ingests. Attackers could exploit this to include most local files the process has read access to, extracting secrets from the host machine. An attacker would need to have the privileges required to add new media to exploit this. But these are often widely given. The issue has been fixed in Opencast 10.6 and 11.0. You can mitigate this issue by narrowing down the read access Opencast has to files on the file system using UNIX permissions or mandatory access control systems like SELinux. This cannot prevent access to files Opencast needs to read though and we highly recommend updating.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43821|2024-08-04T04:03:08.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 19:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43807|2024-08-04T04:03:08.669Z -- opencast -- opencast
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43807</link>
      <description>Opencast is an Open Source Lecture Capture &amp; Video Management for Education. Opencast versions prior to 9.10 allow HTTP method spoofing, allowing to change the assumed HTTP method via URL parameter. This allows attackers to turn HTTP GET requests into PUT requests or an HTTP form to send DELETE requests. This bypasses restrictions otherwise put on these types of requests and aids in cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks, which would otherwise not be possible. The vulnerability allows attackers to craft links or forms which may change the server state. This issue is fixed in Opencast 9.10 and 10.0. You can mitigate the problem by setting the `SameSite=Strict` attribute for your cookies. If this is a viable option for you depends on your integrations. We strongly recommend updating in any case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43807|2024-08-04T04:03:08.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 18:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
