<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell EMC -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell%20emc/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell EMC -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:42:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8023|2024-09-16T17:19:13.577Z -- dell%20emc -- networker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8023</link>
      <description>EMC NetWorker may potentially be vulnerable to an unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability in the Networker Client execution service (nsrexecd) when oldauth authentication method is used. An unauthenticated remote attacker could send arbitrary commands via RPC service to be executed on the host system with the privileges of the nsrexecd service, which runs with administrative privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8023|2024-09-16T17:19:13.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 20:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1204|2024-09-16T17:42:39.998Z -- dell%20emc -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1204</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon OneFS versions between 8.1.0.0 - 8.1.0.1, 8.0.1.0 - 8.0.1.2, and 8.0.0.0 - 8.0.0.6, versions 7.2.1.x, and version 7.1.1.11 is affected by a path traversal vulnerability in the isi_phone_home tool. A malicious compadmin may potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1204|2024-09-16T17:42:39.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3753|2024-09-16T20:48:15.827Z -- dell%20emc -- powerconnect%208024
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3753</link>
      <description>Dell EMC PowerConnect 8024, 7000, M6348, M6220, M8024 and M8024-K running firmware versions prior to 5.1.15.2 contain a plain-text password storage vulnerability. TACACS\Radius credentials are stored in plain text in the system settings menu. An authenticated malicious user with access to the system settings menu may obtain the exposed password to use it in further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3753|2024-09-16T20:48:15.827Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 18:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11072|2024-09-16T19:57:00.694Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20digital%20delivery
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11072</link>
      <description>Dell Digital Delivery versions prior to 3.5.1 contain a DLL Injection Vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user with advance knowledge of the application workflow could potentially load and execute a malicious DLL with administrator privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11072|2024-09-16T19:57:00.694Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1189|2024-09-16T20:12:06.865Z -- dell%20emc -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1189</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon versions between 8.1.0.0 - 8.1.0.1, 8.0.1.0 - 8.0.1.2, and 8.0.0.0 - 8.0.0.6, versions 7.2.1.x, and version 7.1.1.11 is affected by a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Antivirus Page within the OneFS web administration interface. A malicious administrator may potentially inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code in the user's browser session in the context of the OneFS website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1189|2024-09-16T20:12:06.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3721|2024-09-16T19:20:31.480Z -- dell%20emc -- open%20manage%20system%20administrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3721</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Open Manage System Administrator (OMSA) versions prior to 9.3.0 contain an Improper Range Header Processing Vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker may send crafted requests with overlapping ranges to cause the application to compress each of the requested bytes, resulting in a crash due to excessive memory consumption and preventing users from accessing the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3721|2024-09-16T19:20:31.480Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 20:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11076|2024-09-16T20:32:06.321Z -- dell%20emc -- avamar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11076</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Avamar Server versions 7.2.0, 7.2.1, 7.3.0, 7.3.1, 7.4.0 and 7.4.1 and Dell EMC Integrated Data Protection Appliance (IDPA) 2.0 are affected by an information exposure vulnerability. Avamar Java management console's SSL/TLS private key may be leaked in the Avamar Java management client package. The private key could potentially be used by an unauthenticated attacker on the same data-link layer to initiate a MITM attack on management console users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11076|2024-09-16T20:32:06.321Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1244|2024-09-16T16:53:27.629Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac7
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1244</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC7/iDRAC8, versions prior to 2.60.60.60, and iDRAC9 versions prior to 3.21.21.21 contain a command injection vulnerability in the SNMP agent. A remote authenticated malicious iDRAC user with configuration privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands on the iDRAC where SNMP alerting is enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1244|2024-09-16T16:53:27.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11065|2024-09-16T17:32:44.141Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20archer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11065</link>
      <description>The WorkPoint component, which is embedded in all RSA Archer, versions 6.1.x, 6.2.x, 6.3.x prior to 6.3.0.7 and 6.4.x prior to 6.4.0.1, contains a SQL injection vulnerability. A malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute SQL commands on the back-end database to read certain data. Embedded WorkPoint is upgraded to version 4.10.16, which contains a fix for the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11065|2024-09-16T17:32:44.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11060|2024-09-16T16:58:13.454Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20archer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11060</link>
      <description>RSA Archer, versions prior to 6.4.0.1, contain an authorization bypass vulnerability in the REST API. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to elevate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11060|2024-09-16T16:58:13.454Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3737|2024-09-16T19:50:59.459Z -- dell%20emc -- avamar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3737</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Avamar ADMe Web Interface 1.0.50 and 1.0.51 are affected by an LFI vulnerability which may allow a malicious user to download arbitrary files from the affected system by sending a specially crafted request to the Web Interface application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3737|2024-09-16T19:50:59.459Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 22:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-5350|2024-09-16T17:38:47.368Z -- dell%20emc -- garden%20nstar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-5350</link>
      <description>In Garden versions 0.22.0-0.329.0, a vulnerability has been discovered in the garden-linux nstar executable that allows access to files on the host system. By staging an application on Cloud Foundry using Diego and Garden installations with a malicious custom buildpack an end user could read files on the host system that the BOSH-created vcap user has permissions to read and then package them into their app droplet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-5350|2024-09-16T17:38:47.368Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1233|2024-09-16T19:56:31.343Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20authentication%20agent%20for%20web%20for%20iis%2C%20rsa%20authentication%20agent%20for%20web%20for%20apache%20web%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1233</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Agent version 8.0.1 and earlier for Web for both IIS and Apache Web Server are affected by a cross-site scripting vulnerability. The attackers could potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code in the user's browser session in the context of the affected website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1233|2024-09-16T19:56:31.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3726|2024-09-16T17:58:10.848Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20servers%3A%20networking%20and%20fibre%20channel%20drivers%3A%20dell%20update%20package%20%28dup%29%20framework%20file
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3726</link>
      <description>An Uncontrolled Search Path Vulnerability is applicable to the following: Dell Update Package (DUP) Framework file versions prior to 19.1.0.413, and Framework file versions prior to 103.4.6.69 used in Dell EMC Servers. Dell Update Package (DUP) Framework file versions prior to 3.8.3.67 used in Dell Client Platforms. The vulnerability is limited to the DUP framework during the time window when a DUP is being executed by an administrator. During this time window, a locally authenticated low privilege malicious user potentially could exploit this vulnerability by tricking an administrator into running a trusted binary, causing it to load a malicious DLL and allowing the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the victim system. The vulnerability does not affect the actual binary payload that the DUP delivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3726|2024-09-16T17:58:10.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 15:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11078|2024-09-16T18:43:20.109Z -- dell%20emc -- vplex%20software%3A%20geosynchrony
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11078</link>
      <description>Dell EMC VPlex GeoSynchrony, versions prior to 6.1, contains an Insecure File Permissions vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious user could read from VPN configuration files on and potentially author a MITM attack on the VPN traffic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11078|2024-09-16T18:43:20.109Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11070|2024-09-16T19:36:17.519Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20bsafe%20crypto-j
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11070</link>
      <description>RSA BSAFE Crypto-J versions prior to 6.2.4 and RSA BSAFE SSL-J versions prior to 6.2.4 contain a Covert Timing Channel vulnerability during PKCS #1 unpadding operations, also known as a Bleichenbacher attack. A remote attacker may be able to recover a RSA key.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11070|2024-09-16T19:36:17.519Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1238|2024-09-16T20:06:14.715Z -- dell%20emc -- scaleio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1238</link>
      <description>Dell EMC ScaleIO versions prior to 2.5, contain a command injection vulnerability in the Light Installation Agent (LIA). This component is used for central management of ScaleIO deployment and uses shell commands for certain actions. A remote malicious user, with network access to LIA and knowledge of the LIA administrative password, could potentially exploit this vulnerability to run arbitrary commands as root on the systems where LIAs are installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1238|2024-09-16T20:06:14.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9880|2024-09-16T19:31:47.833Z -- dell%20emc -- gemfire%20broker%20for%20cloud%20foundry
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9880</link>
      <description>The GemFire broker for Cloud Foundry 1.6.x before 1.6.5 and 1.7.x before 1.7.1 has multiple API endpoints which do not require authentication and could be used to gain access to the cluster managed by the broker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9880|2024-09-16T19:31:47.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3741|2024-09-16T19:29:55.995Z -- dell%20emc -- unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3741</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity and UnityVSA versions prior to 5.0.0.0.5.116 contain a plain-text password storage vulnerability. A Unisphere user’s (including the admin privilege user) password is stored in a plain text in Unity Data Collection bundle (logs files for troubleshooting). A local authenticated attacker with access to the Data Collection bundle may use the exposed password to gain access with the privileges of the compromised user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3741|2024-09-16T19:29:55.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 15:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1242|2024-09-16T20:32:13.130Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20recoverpoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1242</link>
      <description>Dell EMC RecoverPoint versions prior to 5.1.2 and RecoverPoint for VMs versions prior to 5.1.1.3, contains a command injection vulnerability in the Boxmgmt CLI. An authenticated malicious user with boxmgmt privileges may potentially exploit this vulnerability to read RPA files. Note that files that require root permission cannot be read.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1242|2024-09-16T20:32:13.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1235|2024-09-16T19:20:40.439Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20recoverpoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1235</link>
      <description>Dell EMC RecoverPoint versions prior to 5.1.2 and RecoverPoint for VMs versions prior to 5.1.1.3, contain a command injection vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker may potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands on the affected system with root privilege.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1235|2024-09-16T19:20:40.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11069|2024-09-16T19:35:24.862Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20bsafe%20ssl-j
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11069</link>
      <description>RSA BSAFE SSL-J versions prior to 6.2.4 contain a Covert Timing Channel vulnerability during RSA decryption, also known as a Bleichenbacher attack on RSA decryption. A remote attacker may be able to recover a RSA key.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11069|2024-09-16T19:35:24.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3707|2024-09-16T18:09:07.804Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3707</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC9 versions prior to 3.30.30.30 contain an authentication bypass vulnerability. A remote attacker may potentially exploit this vulnerability to bypass authentication and gain access to the system by sending specially crafted input data to the WS-MAN interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3707|2024-09-16T18:09:07.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 18:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3734|2024-09-16T20:27:42.264Z -- dell%20emc -- unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3734</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity and UnityVSA versions prior to 5.0.0.0.5.116 contain an improper authorization vulnerability in NAS Server quotas configuration. A remote authenticated Unisphere Operator could potentially exploit this vulnerability to edit quota configuration of other users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3734|2024-09-16T20:27:42.264Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 15:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1183|2024-09-16T17:58:56.361Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20unisphere%20for%20vmax%20virtual%20appliance%2C%20dell%20emc%20solutions%20enabler%20virtual%20appliance%2C%20dell%20emc%20vasa%20provider%20virtual%20appliance%2C%20dell%20emc%20smis%2C%20dell%20emc%20vmax%20embedded%20management%20%28e
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1183</link>
      <description>In Dell EMC Unisphere for VMAX Virtual Appliance versions prior to 8.4.0.8, Dell EMC Solutions Enabler Virtual Appliance versions prior to 8.4.0.8, Dell EMC VASA Provider Virtual Appliance versions prior to 8.4.0.512, Dell EMC SMIS versions prior to 8.4.0.6, Dell EMC VMAX Embedded Management (eManagement) versions prior to and including 1.4.0.347, Dell EMC VNX2 Operating Environment (OE) for File versions prior to 8.1.9.231, Dell EMC VNX2 Operating Environment (OE) for Block versions prior to 05.33.009.5.231, Dell EMC VNX1 Operating Environment (OE) for File versions prior to 7.1.82.0, Dell EMC VNX1 Operating Environment (OE) for Block versions prior to 05.32.000.5.225, Dell EMC VNXe3200 Operating Environment (OE) all versions, Dell EMC VNXe1600 Operating Environment (OE) versions prior to 3.1.9.9570228, Dell EMC VNXe 3100/3150/3300 Operating Environment (OE) all versions, Dell EMC ViPR SRM versions 3.7, 3.7.1, 3.7.2 (only if using Dell EMC Host Interface for Windows), Dell EMC ViPR SRM versions 4.0, 4.0.1, 4.0.2, 4.0.3 (only if using Dell EMC Host Interface for Windows), Dell EMC XtremIO versions 4.x, Dell EMC VMAX eNAS version 8.x, Dell EMC Unity Operating Environment (OE) versions prior to 4.3.0.1522077968, ECOM is affected by a XXE injection vulnerability due to the configuration of the XML parser shipped with the product. XXE Injection attack may occur when XML input containing a reference to an external entity (defined by the attacker) is processed by an affected XML parser. XXE Injection may allow attackers to gain unauthorized access to files containing sensitive information or may be used to cause denial-of-service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1183|2024-09-16T17:58:56.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1217|2024-09-16T19:47:17.864Z -- dell%20emc -- avamar%2C%20integrated%20data%20protection%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1217</link>
      <description>Avamar Installation Manager in Dell EMC Avamar Server 7.3.1, 7.4.1, and 7.5.0, and Dell EMC Integrated Data Protection Appliance 2.0 and 2.1, is affected by a missing access control check vulnerability which could potentially allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to read or change the Local Download Service (LDLS) credentials. The LDLS credentials are used to connect to Dell EMC Online Support. If the LDLS configuration was changed to an invalid configuration, then Avamar Installation Manager may not be able to connect to Dell EMC Online Support web site successfully. The remote unauthenticated attacker can also read and use the credentials to login to Dell EMC Online Support, impersonating the AVI service actions using those credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1217|2024-09-16T19:47:17.864Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1197|2024-09-16T18:49:32.654Z -- dell%20emc -- windows%20stemcells
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1197</link>
      <description>In Windows Stemcells versions prior to 1200.14, apps running inside containers in Windows on Google Cloud Platform are able to access the metadata endpoint. A malicious developer could use this access to gain privileged credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1197|2024-09-16T18:49:32.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11059|2024-09-16T19:14:28.788Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20archer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11059</link>
      <description>RSA Archer, versions prior to 6.4.0.1, contain a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to store malicious HTML or JavaScript code in a trusted application data store. When application users access the corrupted data store through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11059|2024-09-16T19:14:28.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1239|2024-09-16T16:33:38.146Z -- dell%20emc -- unity%20operating%20environment%20%28oe%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1239</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity Operating Environment (OE) versions prior to 4.3.0.1522077968 are affected by multiple OS command injection vulnerabilities. A remote application admin user could potentially exploit the vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary OS commands as system root on the system where Dell EMC Unity is installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1239|2024-09-16T16:33:38.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1211|2024-09-16T20:22:05.961Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac7%2Fidrac8
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1211</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC7/iDRAC8, versions prior to 2.52.52.52, contain a path traversal vulnerability in its Web server's URI parser which could be used to obtain specific sensitive data without authentication. A remote unauthenticated attacker may be able to read configuration settings from the iDRAC by querying specific URI strings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1211|2024-09-16T20:22:05.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1196|2024-09-16T17:27:35.008Z -- dell%20emc -- spring%20boot
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1196</link>
      <description>Spring Boot supports an embedded launch script that can be used to easily run the application as a systemd or init.d linux service. The script included with Spring Boot 1.5.9 and earlier and 2.0.0.M1 through 2.0.0.M7 is susceptible to a symlink attack which allows the "run_user" to overwrite and take ownership of any file on the same system. In order to instigate the attack, the application must be installed as a service and the "run_user" requires shell access to the server. Spring Boot application that are not installed as a service, or are not using the embedded launch script are not susceptible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1196|2024-09-16T17:27:35.008Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3704|2024-09-16T17:58:08.973Z -- dell%20emc -- vnx%20control%20station%20in%20dell%20emc%20vnx2%20oe%20for%20file
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3704</link>
      <description>VNX Control Station in Dell EMC VNX2 OE for File versions prior to 8.1.9.236 contains OS command injection vulnerability. Due to inadequate restriction configured in sudores, a local authenticated malicious user could potentially execute arbitrary OS commands as root by exploiting this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3704|2024-09-16T17:58:08.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8013|2024-09-16T16:58:08.085Z -- dell%20emc -- emc%20data%20protection%20advisor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8013</link>
      <description>EMC Data Protection Advisor 6.3.x before patch 67 and 6.4.x before patch 130 contains undocumented accounts with hard-coded passwords and various privileges. Affected accounts are: "Apollo System Test", "emc.dpa.agent.logon" and "emc.dpa.metrics.logon". An attacker with knowledge of the password could potentially use these accounts via REST APIs to gain unauthorized access to EMC Data Protection Advisor (including potentially access with administrative privileges).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8013|2024-09-16T16:58:08.085Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11053|2024-09-16T17:03:39.073Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac%20service%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11053</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC Service Module for all supported Linux and XenServer versions v3.0.1, v3.0.2, v3.1.0, v3.2.0, when started, changes the default file permission of the hosts file of the host operating system (/etc/hosts) to world writable. A malicious low privileged operating system user or process could modify the host file and potentially redirect traffic from the intended destination to sites hosting malicious or unwanted content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11053|2024-09-16T17:03:39.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1247|2024-09-16T16:39:05.452Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20authentication%20manager%20security%20console
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1247</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Manager Security Console, version 8.3 and earlier, contains a XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability. This could potentially allow admin users to cause a denial of service or extract server data via injecting a maliciously crafted DTD in an XML file submitted to the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1247|2024-09-16T16:39:05.452Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11062|2024-09-16T18:04:27.800Z -- dell%20emc -- integrated%20data%20protection%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11062</link>
      <description>Integrated Data Protection Appliance versions 2.0, 2.1, and 2.2 contain undocumented accounts named 'support' and 'admin' that are protected with default passwords. These accounts have limited privileges and can access certain system files only. A malicious user with the knowledge of the default passwords may potentially log in to the system and gain read and write access to certain system files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11062|2024-09-16T18:04:27.800Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3709|2024-09-16T20:21:39.930Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20isilonsd%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3709</link>
      <description>IsilonSD Management Server 1.1.0 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability while registering vCenter servers. A remote attacker can trick an admin user to potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute malicious HTML or JavaScript code in the context of the admin user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3709|2024-09-16T20:21:39.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 13:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1248|2024-09-16T16:13:25.346Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20authentication%20manager%20security%20console%2C%20operation%20console%20and%20self-service%20console
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1248</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Manager Security Console, Operation Console and Self-Service Console, version 8.3 and earlier, is affected by a Host header injection vulnerability. This could allow a remote attacker to potentially poison HTTP cache and subsequently redirect users to arbitrary web domains.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1248|2024-09-16T16:13:25.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1200|2024-09-16T16:17:36.254Z -- dell%20emc -- apps%20manager%20for%20pcf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1200</link>
      <description>Apps Manager for PCF (Pivotal Application Service 1.11.x before 1.11.26, 1.12.x before 1.12.14, and 2.0.x before 2.0.5) allows unprivileged remote file read in its container via specially-crafted links.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1200|2024-09-16T16:17:36.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1195|2024-09-16T20:52:50.610Z -- dell%20emc -- cloud%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1195</link>
      <description>In Cloud Controller versions prior to 1.46.0, cf-deployment versions prior to 1.3.0, and cf-release versions prior to 283, Cloud Controller accepts refresh tokens for authentication where access tokens are expected. This exposes a vulnerability where a refresh token that would otherwise be insufficient to obtain an access token, either due to lack of client credentials or revocation, would allow authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1195|2024-09-16T20:52:50.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1243|2024-09-16T19:20:22.599Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac6
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1243</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC6, versions prior to 2.91, iDRAC7/iDRAC8, versions prior to 2.60.60.60 and iDRAC9, versions prior to 3.21.21.21, contain a weak CGI session ID vulnerability. The sessions invoked via CGI binaries use 96-bit numeric-only session ID values, which makes it easier for remote attackers to perform bruteforce session guessing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1243|2024-09-16T19:20:22.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15765|2024-09-16T19:36:30.744Z -- dell%20emc -- esrs%20virtual%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15765</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Secure Remote Services, versions prior to 3.32.00.08, contains an Information Exposure vulnerability. The log file contents store sensitive data including executed commands to generate authentication tokens which may prove useful to an attacker for crafting malicious authentication tokens for querying the application and subsequent attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15765|2024-09-16T19:36:30.744Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3723|2024-09-16T19:05:23.583Z -- dell%20emc -- openmanage%20server%20administrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3723</link>
      <description>Dell EMC OpenManage Server Administrator (OMSA) versions prior to 9.1.0.3 and prior to 9.2.0.4 contain a web parameter tampering vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially manipulate parameters of web requests to OMSA to create arbitrary files with empty content or delete the contents of any existing file, due to improper input parameter validation</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3723|2024-09-16T19:05:23.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 19:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1199|2024-09-16T16:13:09.643Z -- dell%20emc -- spring%20by%20pivotal
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1199</link>
      <description>Spring Security (Spring Security 4.1.x before 4.1.5, 4.2.x before 4.2.4, and 5.0.x before 5.0.1; and Spring Framework 4.3.x before 4.3.14 and 5.0.x before 5.0.3) does not consider URL path parameters when processing security constraints. By adding a URL path parameter with special encodings, an attacker may be able to bypass a security constraint. The root cause of this issue is a lack of clarity regarding the handling of path parameters in the Servlet Specification. Some Servlet containers include path parameters in the value returned for getPathInfo() and some do not. Spring Security uses the value returned by getPathInfo() as part of the process of mapping requests to security constraints. In this particular attack, different character encodings used in path parameters allows secured Spring MVC static resource URLs to be bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1199|2024-09-16T16:13:09.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11050|2024-09-16T19:51:06.826Z -- dell%20emc -- networker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11050</link>
      <description>Dell EMC NetWorker versions between 9.0 and 9.1.1.8 through 9.2.1.3, and the version 18.1.0.1 contain a Clear-Text authentication over network vulnerability in the Rabbit MQ Advanced Message Queuing Protocol (AMQP) component. User credentials are sent unencrypted to the remote AMQP service. An unauthenticated attacker in the same network collision domain, could potentially sniff the password from the network and use it to access the component using the privileges of the compromised user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11050|2024-09-16T19:51:06.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3720|2024-09-16T16:32:39.543Z -- dell%20emc -- open%20manage%20system%20administrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3720</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Open Manage System Administrator (OMSA) versions prior to 9.3.0 contain a Directory Traversal Vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious user with admin privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain unauthorized access to the file system by exploiting insufficient sanitization of input parameters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3720|2024-09-16T16:32:39.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 20:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1205|2024-09-16T17:33:25.660Z -- dell%20emc -- scaleio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1205</link>
      <description>Dell EMC ScaleIO, versions prior to 2.5, do not properly handle some packet data in the MDM service. As a result, a remote attacker could potentially send specifically crafted packet data to the MDM service causing it to crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1205|2024-09-16T17:33:25.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1203|2024-09-16T19:20:35.231Z -- dell%20emc -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1203</link>
      <description>In Dell EMC Isilon OneFS, the compadmin is able to run tcpdump binary with root privileges. In versions between 8.1.0.0 - 8.1.0.1, 8.0.1.0 - 8.0.1.2, and 8.0.0.0 - 8.0.0.6, the tcpdump binary, being run with sudo, may potentially be used by compadmin to execute arbitrary code with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1203|2024-09-16T19:20:35.231Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1251|2024-09-16T18:03:36.680Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1251</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity and UnityVSA versions prior to 4.3.1.1525703027 contains a URL Redirection vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to redirect Unity users to arbitrary web URLs by tricking the victim user to click on a maliciously crafted Unisphere URL. Attacker could potentially phish information, including Unisphere users' credentials, from the victim once they are redirected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1251|2024-09-16T18:03:36.680Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1234|2024-09-16T18:44:10.804Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20authentication%20agent%20for%20web%20for%20iis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1234</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Agent version 8.0.1 and earlier for Web for IIS is affected by a problem where access control list (ACL) permissions on a Windows Named Pipe were not sufficient to prevent access by unauthorized users. The attacker with local access to the system can exploit this vulnerability to read configuration properties for the authentication agent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1234|2024-09-16T18:44:10.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1240|2024-09-16T20:31:57.816Z -- dell%20emc -- vipr%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1240</link>
      <description>Dell EMC ViPR Controller, versions after 3.0.0.38, contain an information exposure vulnerability in the VRRP. VRRP defaults to an insecure configuration in Linux's keepalived component which sends the cluster password in plaintext through multicast. A malicious user, having access to the vCloud subnet where ViPR is deployed, could potentially sniff the password and use it to take over the cluster's virtual IP and cause a denial of service on that ViPR Controller system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1240|2024-09-16T20:31:57.816Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3722|2024-09-16T17:22:35.591Z -- dell%20emc -- openmanage%20server%20administrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3722</link>
      <description>Dell EMC OpenManage Server Administrator (OMSA) versions prior to 9.1.0.3 and prior to 9.2.0.4 contain an XML external entity (XXE) injection vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to read arbitrary server system files by supplying specially crafted document type definitions (DTDs) in an XML request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3722|2024-09-16T17:22:35.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 19:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
