<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell EMC -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell%20emc/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell EMC -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 05:23:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1183|2024-08-05T03:51:49.021Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20unisphere%20for%20vmax%20virtual%20appliance%2C%20dell%20emc%20solutions%20enabler%20virtual%20appliance%2C%20dell%20emc%20vasa%20provider%20virtual%20appliance%2C%20dell%20emc%20smis%2C%20dell%20emc%20vmax%20embedded%20management%20%28e
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1183</link>
      <description>In Dell EMC Unisphere for VMAX Virtual Appliance versions prior to 8.4.0.8, Dell EMC Solutions Enabler Virtual Appliance versions prior to 8.4.0.8, Dell EMC VASA Provider Virtual Appliance versions prior to 8.4.0.512, Dell EMC SMIS versions prior to 8.4.0.6, Dell EMC VMAX Embedded Management (eManagement) versions prior to and including 1.4.0.347, Dell EMC VNX2 Operating Environment (OE) for File versions prior to 8.1.9.231, Dell EMC VNX2 Operating Environment (OE) for Block versions prior to 05.33.009.5.231, Dell EMC VNX1 Operating Environment (OE) for File versions prior to 7.1.82.0, Dell EMC VNX1 Operating Environment (OE) for Block versions prior to 05.32.000.5.225, Dell EMC VNXe3200 Operating Environment (OE) all versions, Dell EMC VNXe1600 Operating Environment (OE) versions prior to 3.1.9.9570228, Dell EMC VNXe 3100/3150/3300 Operating Environment (OE) all versions, Dell EMC ViPR SRM versions 3.7, 3.7.1, 3.7.2 (only if using Dell EMC Host Interface for Windows), Dell EMC ViPR SRM versions 4.0, 4.0.1, 4.0.2, 4.0.3 (only if using Dell EMC Host Interface for Windows), Dell EMC XtremIO versions 4.x, Dell EMC VMAX eNAS version 8.x, Dell EMC Unity Operating Environment (OE) versions prior to 4.3.0.1522077968, ECOM is affected by a XXE injection vulnerability due to the configuration of the XML parser shipped with the product. XXE Injection attack may occur when XML input containing a reference to an external entity (defined by the attacker) is processed by an affected XML parser. XXE Injection may allow attackers to gain unauthorized access to files containing sensitive information or may be used to cause denial-of-service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1183|2024-08-05T03:51:49.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1189|2024-08-05T03:51:48.962Z -- dell%20emc -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1189</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon versions between 8.1.0.0 - 8.1.0.1, 8.0.1.0 - 8.0.1.2, and 8.0.0.0 - 8.0.0.6, versions 7.2.1.x, and version 7.1.1.11 is affected by a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Antivirus Page within the OneFS web administration interface. A malicious administrator may potentially inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code in the user's browser session in the context of the OneFS website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1189|2024-08-05T03:51:48.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1241|2024-08-05T03:51:49.168Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20recoverpoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1241</link>
      <description>Dell EMC RecoverPoint versions prior to 5.1.2 and RecoverPoint for VMs versions prior to 5.1.1.3, under certain conditions, may leak LDAP password in plain-text into the RecoverPoint log file. An authenticated malicious user with access to the RecoverPoint log files may obtain the exposed LDAP password to use it in further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1241|2024-08-05T03:51:49.168Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1250|2024-08-05T03:51:49.038Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1250</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity and UnityVSA versions prior to 4.3.1.1525703027 contains an Authorization Bypass vulnerability. A remote authenticated user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to read files in NAS server by directly interacting with certain APIs of Unity OE, bypassing Role-Based Authorization control implemented only in Unisphere GUI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1250|2024-08-05T03:51:49.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1238|2024-08-05T03:51:48.950Z -- dell%20emc -- scaleio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1238</link>
      <description>Dell EMC ScaleIO versions prior to 2.5, contain a command injection vulnerability in the Light Installation Agent (LIA). This component is used for central management of ScaleIO deployment and uses shell commands for certain actions. A remote malicious user, with network access to LIA and knowledge of the LIA administrative password, could potentially exploit this vulnerability to run arbitrary commands as root on the systems where LIAs are installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1238|2024-08-05T03:51:48.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1202|2024-08-05T03:51:48.980Z -- dell%20emc -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1202</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon versions between 8.1.0.0 - 8.1.0.1, 8.0.1.0 - 8.0.1.2, and 8.0.0.0 - 8.0.0.6, and version 7.1.1.11 is affected by a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the NDMP Page within the OneFS web administration interface. A malicious administrator may potentially inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code in the user's browser session in the context of the OneFS website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1202|2024-08-05T03:51:48.980Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1211|2024-08-05T03:51:48.979Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac7%2Fidrac8
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1211</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC7/iDRAC8, versions prior to 2.52.52.52, contain a path traversal vulnerability in its Web server's URI parser which could be used to obtain specific sensitive data without authentication. A remote unauthenticated attacker may be able to read configuration settings from the iDRAC by querying specific URI strings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1211|2024-08-05T03:51:48.979Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1186|2024-08-05T03:51:48.905Z -- dell%20emc -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1186</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon versions between 8.1.0.0 - 8.1.0.1, 8.0.1.0 - 8.0.1.2, and 8.0.0.0 - 8.0.0.6, versions 7.2.1.x, and version 7.1.1.11 is affected by a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Cluster description of the OneFS web administration interface. A malicious administrator may potentially inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code in the user's browser session in the context of the OneFS website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1186|2024-08-05T03:51:48.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1240|2024-08-05T03:51:49.040Z -- dell%20emc -- vipr%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1240</link>
      <description>Dell EMC ViPR Controller, versions after 3.0.0.38, contain an information exposure vulnerability in the VRRP. VRRP defaults to an insecure configuration in Linux's keepalived component which sends the cluster password in plaintext through multicast. A malicious user, having access to the vCloud subnet where ViPR is deployed, could potentially sniff the password and use it to take over the cluster's virtual IP and cause a denial of service on that ViPR Controller system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1240|2024-08-05T03:51:49.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1201|2024-08-05T03:51:49.100Z -- dell%20emc -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1201</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon versions between 8.1.0.0 - 8.1.0.1, 8.0.1.0 - 8.0.1.2, and 8.0.0.0 - 8.0.0.6, versions 7.2.1.x, and version 7.1.1.11 is affected by a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Job Operations Page within the OneFS web administration interface. A malicious administrator may potentially inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code in the user's browser session in the context of the OneFS website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1201|2024-08-05T03:51:49.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1247|2024-08-05T03:51:49.045Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20authentication%20manager%20security%20console
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1247</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Manager Security Console, version 8.3 and earlier, contains a XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability. This could potentially allow admin users to cause a denial of service or extract server data via injecting a maliciously crafted DTD in an XML file submitted to the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1247|2024-08-05T03:51:49.045Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1196|2024-08-05T03:51:48.918Z -- dell%20emc -- spring%20boot
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1196</link>
      <description>Spring Boot supports an embedded launch script that can be used to easily run the application as a systemd or init.d linux service. The script included with Spring Boot 1.5.9 and earlier and 2.0.0.M1 through 2.0.0.M7 is susceptible to a symlink attack which allows the "run_user" to overwrite and take ownership of any file on the same system. In order to instigate the attack, the application must be installed as a service and the "run_user" requires shell access to the server. Spring Boot application that are not installed as a service, or are not using the embedded launch script are not susceptible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1196|2024-08-05T03:51:48.918Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1237|2024-08-05T03:51:48.906Z -- dell%20emc -- scaleio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1237</link>
      <description>Dell EMC ScaleIO versions prior to 2.5, contain improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts on the Light installation Agent (LIA). This component is deployed on every server in the ScaleIO cluster and is used for central management of ScaleIO nodes. A remote malicious user, having network access to LIA, could potentially exploit this vulnerability to launch brute force guessing of user names and passwords of user accounts on the LIA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1237|2024-08-05T03:51:48.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1249|2024-08-05T03:51:49.108Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1249</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC9 versions prior to 3.21.21.21 did not enforce the use of TLS/SSL for a connection to iDRAC web server for certain URLs. A man-in-the-middle attacker could use this vulnerability to strip the SSL/TLS protection from a connection between a client and a server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1249|2024-08-05T03:51:49.108Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1242|2024-08-05T03:51:48.997Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20recoverpoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1242</link>
      <description>Dell EMC RecoverPoint versions prior to 5.1.2 and RecoverPoint for VMs versions prior to 5.1.1.3, contains a command injection vulnerability in the Boxmgmt CLI. An authenticated malicious user with boxmgmt privileges may potentially exploit this vulnerability to read RPA files. Note that files that require root permission cannot be read.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1242|2024-08-05T03:51:48.997Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1243|2024-08-05T03:51:48.924Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac6
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1243</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC6, versions prior to 2.91, iDRAC7/iDRAC8, versions prior to 2.60.60.60 and iDRAC9, versions prior to 3.21.21.21, contain a weak CGI session ID vulnerability. The sessions invoked via CGI binaries use 96-bit numeric-only session ID values, which makes it easier for remote attackers to perform bruteforce session guessing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1243|2024-08-05T03:51:48.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1218|2024-08-05T03:51:48.895Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20networker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1218</link>
      <description>In Dell EMC NetWorker versions prior to 9.2.1.1, versions prior to 9.1.1.6, 9.0.x, and versions prior to 8.2.4.11, the 'nsrd' daemon causes a buffer overflow condition when handling certain messages. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to cause a denial of service to the users of NetWorker systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1218|2024-08-05T03:51:48.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1197|2024-08-05T03:51:48.989Z -- dell%20emc -- windows%20stemcells
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1197</link>
      <description>In Windows Stemcells versions prior to 1200.14, apps running inside containers in Windows on Google Cloud Platform are able to access the metadata endpoint. A malicious developer could use this access to gain privileged credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1197|2024-08-05T03:51:48.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1232|2024-08-05T03:51:48.928Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20authentication%20agent%20for%20web%20for%20iis%2C%20rsa%20authentication%20agent%20for%20web%20for%20apache%20web%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1232</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Agent version 8.0.1 and earlier for Web for both IIS and Apache Web Server are impacted by a stack-based buffer overflow which may occur when handling certain malicious web cookies that have invalid formats. The attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the authentication agent and cause a denial-of-service situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1232|2024-08-05T03:51:48.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1234|2024-08-05T03:51:49.014Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20authentication%20agent%20for%20web%20for%20iis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1234</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Agent version 8.0.1 and earlier for Web for IIS is affected by a problem where access control list (ACL) permissions on a Windows Named Pipe were not sufficient to prevent access by unauthorized users. The attacker with local access to the system can exploit this vulnerability to read configuration properties for the authentication agent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1234|2024-08-05T03:51:49.014Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1233|2024-08-05T03:51:49.069Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20authentication%20agent%20for%20web%20for%20iis%2C%20rsa%20authentication%20agent%20for%20web%20for%20apache%20web%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1233</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Agent version 8.0.1 and earlier for Web for both IIS and Apache Web Server are affected by a cross-site scripting vulnerability. The attackers could potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code in the user's browser session in the context of the affected website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1233|2024-08-05T03:51:49.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1205|2024-08-05T03:51:49.125Z -- dell%20emc -- scaleio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1205</link>
      <description>Dell EMC ScaleIO, versions prior to 2.5, do not properly handle some packet data in the MDM service. As a result, a remote attacker could potentially send specifically crafted packet data to the MDM service causing it to crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1205|2024-08-05T03:51:49.125Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1187|2024-08-05T03:51:48.990Z -- dell%20emc -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1187</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon versions between 8.1.0.0 - 8.1.0.1, 8.0.1.0 - 8.0.1.2, and 8.0.0.0 - 8.0.0.6 is affected by a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Network Configuration page within the OneFS web administration interface. A malicious administrator may potentially inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code in the user's browser session in the context of the OneFS website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1187|2024-08-05T03:51:48.990Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1217|2024-08-05T03:51:49.069Z -- dell%20emc -- avamar%2C%20integrated%20data%20protection%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1217</link>
      <description>Avamar Installation Manager in Dell EMC Avamar Server 7.3.1, 7.4.1, and 7.5.0, and Dell EMC Integrated Data Protection Appliance 2.0 and 2.1, is affected by a missing access control check vulnerability which could potentially allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to read or change the Local Download Service (LDLS) credentials. The LDLS credentials are used to connect to Dell EMC Online Support. If the LDLS configuration was changed to an invalid configuration, then Avamar Installation Manager may not be able to connect to Dell EMC Online Support web site successfully. The remote unauthenticated attacker can also read and use the credentials to login to Dell EMC Online Support, impersonating the AVI service actions using those credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1217|2024-08-05T03:51:49.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1212|2024-08-05T03:51:48.999Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac6%20%28monolithic%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1212</link>
      <description>The web-based diagnostics console in Dell EMC iDRAC6 (Monolithic versions prior to 2.91 and Modular all versions) contains a command injection vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious iDRAC user with access to the diagnostics console could potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands as root on the affected iDRAC system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1212|2024-08-05T03:51:48.999Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1199|2024-08-05T03:51:48.970Z -- dell%20emc -- spring%20by%20pivotal
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1199</link>
      <description>Spring Security (Spring Security 4.1.x before 4.1.5, 4.2.x before 4.2.4, and 5.0.x before 5.0.1; and Spring Framework 4.3.x before 4.3.14 and 5.0.x before 5.0.3) does not consider URL path parameters when processing security constraints. By adding a URL path parameter with special encodings, an attacker may be able to bypass a security constraint. The root cause of this issue is a lack of clarity regarding the handling of path parameters in the Servlet Specification. Some Servlet containers include path parameters in the value returned for getPathInfo() and some do not. Spring Security uses the value returned by getPathInfo() as part of the process of mapping requests to security constraints. In this particular attack, different character encodings used in path parameters allows secured Spring MVC static resource URLs to be bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1199|2024-08-05T03:51:48.970Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1213|2024-08-05T03:51:48.981Z -- dell%20emc -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1213</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon OneFS versions between 8.1.0.0 - 8.1.0.1, 8.0.1.0 - 8.0.1.2, and 8.0.0.0 - 8.0.0.6, versions 7.2.1.x, and version 7.1.1.11 and 8.1.0.2 is affected by a cross-site request forgery vulnerability. A malicious user may potentially exploit this vulnerability to send unauthorized requests to the server on behalf of authenticated users of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1213|2024-08-05T03:51:48.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1188|2024-08-05T03:51:48.937Z -- dell%20emc -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1188</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon versions between 8.1.0.0 - 8.1.0.1, 8.0.1.0 - 8.0.1.2, and 8.0.0.0 - 8.0.0.6, and versions 7.2.1.x is affected by a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Authorization Providers page within the OneFS web administration interface. A malicious administrator may potentially inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code in the user's browser session in the context of the OneFS website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1188|2024-08-05T03:51:48.937Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1203|2024-08-05T03:51:49.081Z -- dell%20emc -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1203</link>
      <description>In Dell EMC Isilon OneFS, the compadmin is able to run tcpdump binary with root privileges. In versions between 8.1.0.0 - 8.1.0.1, 8.0.1.0 - 8.0.1.2, and 8.0.0.0 - 8.0.0.6, the tcpdump binary, being run with sudo, may potentially be used by compadmin to execute arbitrary code with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1203|2024-08-05T03:51:49.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1251|2024-08-05T03:51:49.174Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1251</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity and UnityVSA versions prior to 4.3.1.1525703027 contains a URL Redirection vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to redirect Unity users to arbitrary web URLs by tricking the victim user to click on a maliciously crafted Unisphere URL. Attacker could potentially phish information, including Unisphere users' credentials, from the victim once they are redirected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1251|2024-08-05T03:51:49.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1239|2024-08-05T03:51:48.971Z -- dell%20emc -- unity%20operating%20environment%20%28oe%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1239</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity Operating Environment (OE) versions prior to 4.3.0.1522077968 are affected by multiple OS command injection vulnerabilities. A remote application admin user could potentially exploit the vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary OS commands as system root on the system where Dell EMC Unity is installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1239|2024-08-05T03:51:48.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1248|2024-08-05T03:51:49.048Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20authentication%20manager%20security%20console%2C%20operation%20console%20and%20self-service%20console
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1248</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Manager Security Console, Operation Console and Self-Service Console, version 8.3 and earlier, is affected by a Host header injection vulnerability. This could allow a remote attacker to potentially poison HTTP cache and subsequently redirect users to arbitrary web domains.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1248|2024-08-05T03:51:49.048Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1244|2024-08-05T03:51:48.994Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac7
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1244</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC7/iDRAC8, versions prior to 2.60.60.60, and iDRAC9 versions prior to 3.21.21.21 contain a command injection vulnerability in the SNMP agent. A remote authenticated malicious iDRAC user with configuration privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands on the iDRAC where SNMP alerting is enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1244|2024-08-05T03:51:48.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1195|2024-08-05T03:51:48.983Z -- dell%20emc -- cloud%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1195</link>
      <description>In Cloud Controller versions prior to 1.46.0, cf-deployment versions prior to 1.3.0, and cf-release versions prior to 283, Cloud Controller accepts refresh tokens for authentication where access tokens are expected. This exposes a vulnerability where a refresh token that would otherwise be insufficient to obtain an access token, either due to lack of client credentials or revocation, would allow authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1195|2024-08-05T03:51:48.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1204|2024-08-05T03:51:49.011Z -- dell%20emc -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1204</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon OneFS versions between 8.1.0.0 - 8.1.0.1, 8.0.1.0 - 8.0.1.2, and 8.0.0.0 - 8.0.0.6, versions 7.2.1.x, and version 7.1.1.11 is affected by a path traversal vulnerability in the isi_phone_home tool. A malicious compadmin may potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1204|2024-08-05T03:51:49.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1246|2024-08-05T03:51:49.039Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1246</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity and UnityVSA contains reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability by tricking a victim application user to supply malicious HTML or Java Script code to Unisphere, which is then reflected back to the victim and executed by the web browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1246|2024-08-05T03:51:49.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1235|2024-08-05T03:51:48.954Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20recoverpoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1235</link>
      <description>Dell EMC RecoverPoint versions prior to 5.1.2 and RecoverPoint for VMs versions prior to 5.1.1.3, contain a command injection vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker may potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands on the affected system with root privilege.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1235|2024-08-05T03:51:48.954Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1221|2024-08-05T03:51:48.984Z -- dell%20emc -- the%20cloud%20foundry%20gorouter
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1221</link>
      <description>In cf-deployment before 1.14.0 and routing-release before 0.172.0, the Cloud Foundry Gorouter mishandles WebSocket requests for AWS Application Load Balancers (ALBs) and some other HTTP-aware Load Balancers. A user with developer privileges could use this vulnerability to steal data or cause denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1221|2024-08-05T03:51:48.984Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1200|2024-08-05T03:51:49.055Z -- dell%20emc -- apps%20manager%20for%20pcf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1200</link>
      <description>Apps Manager for PCF (Pivotal Application Service 1.11.x before 1.11.26, 1.12.x before 1.12.14, and 2.0.x before 2.0.5) allows unprivileged remote file read in its container via specially-crafted links.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1200|2024-08-05T03:51:49.055Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
