<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell EMC -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell%20emc/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell EMC -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 01:37:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1241|2024-09-17T01:21:43.931Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20recoverpoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1241</link>
      <description>Dell EMC RecoverPoint versions prior to 5.1.2 and RecoverPoint for VMs versions prior to 5.1.1.3, under certain conditions, may leak LDAP password in plain-text into the RecoverPoint log file. An authenticated malicious user with access to the RecoverPoint log files may obtain the exposed LDAP password to use it in further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1241|2024-09-17T01:21:43.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1221|2024-09-17T01:15:36.021Z -- dell%20emc -- the%20cloud%20foundry%20gorouter
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1221</link>
      <description>In cf-deployment before 1.14.0 and routing-release before 0.172.0, the Cloud Foundry Gorouter mishandles WebSocket requests for AWS Application Load Balancers (ALBs) and some other HTTP-aware Load Balancers. A user with developer privileges could use this vulnerability to steal data or cause denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1221|2024-09-17T01:15:36.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1186|2024-09-17T01:16:00.737Z -- dell%20emc -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1186</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon versions between 8.1.0.0 - 8.1.0.1, 8.0.1.0 - 8.0.1.2, and 8.0.0.0 - 8.0.0.6, versions 7.2.1.x, and version 7.1.1.11 is affected by a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Cluster description of the OneFS web administration interface. A malicious administrator may potentially inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code in the user's browser session in the context of the OneFS website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1186|2024-09-17T01:16:00.737Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15772|2024-09-17T01:10:33.151Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20recoverpoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15772</link>
      <description>Dell EMC RecoverPoint versions prior to 5.1.2.1 and RecoverPoint for VMs versions prior to 5.2.0.2 contain an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability. A malicious boxmgmt user may potentially be able to consume large amount of CPU bandwidth to make the system slow or to determine the existence of any system file via Boxmgmt CLI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15772|2024-09-17T01:10:33.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1202|2024-09-17T00:11:13.380Z -- dell%20emc -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1202</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon versions between 8.1.0.0 - 8.1.0.1, 8.0.1.0 - 8.0.1.2, and 8.0.0.0 - 8.0.0.6, and version 7.1.1.11 is affected by a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the NDMP Page within the OneFS web administration interface. A malicious administrator may potentially inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code in the user's browser session in the context of the OneFS website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1202|2024-09-17T00:11:13.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3706|2024-09-17T00:26:34.078Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3706</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC9 versions prior to 3.24.24.24, 3.21.26.22, 3.22.22.22 and 3.21.25.22 contain an authentication bypass vulnerability. A remote attacker may potentially exploit this vulnerability to bypass authentication and gain access to the system by sending specially crafted data to the iDRAC web interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3706|2024-09-17T00:26:34.078Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 18:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3708|2024-09-17T00:36:59.730Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20isilonsd%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3708</link>
      <description>IsilonSD Management Server 1.1.0 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability while uploading an OVA file. A remote attacker can trick an admin user to potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute malicious HTML or JavaScript code in the context of the admin user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3708|2024-09-17T00:36:59.730Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 13:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11067|2024-09-17T00:11:44.344Z -- dell%20emc -- avamar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11067</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Avamar Client Manager in Dell EMC Avamar Server versions 7.2.0, 7.2.1, 7.3.0, 7.3.1, 7.4.0, 7.4.1, 7.5.0, 7.5.1, 18.1 and Dell EMC Integrated Data Protection Appliance (IDPA) versions 2.0, 2.1 and 2.2 contain an open redirection vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to redirect application users to arbitrary web URLs by tricking the victim users to click on maliciously crafted links. The vulnerability could be used to conduct phishing attacks that cause users to unknowingly visit malicious sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11067|2024-09-17T00:11:44.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1232|2024-09-17T00:25:34.327Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20authentication%20agent%20for%20web%20for%20iis%2C%20rsa%20authentication%20agent%20for%20web%20for%20apache%20web%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1232</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Agent version 8.0.1 and earlier for Web for both IIS and Apache Web Server are impacted by a stack-based buffer overflow which may occur when handling certain malicious web cookies that have invalid formats. The attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the authentication agent and cause a denial-of-service situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1232|2024-09-17T00:25:34.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11061|2024-09-17T01:06:59.417Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20netwitness
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11061</link>
      <description>RSA NetWitness Platform versions prior to 11.1.0.2 and RSA Security Analytics versions prior to 10.6.6 are vulnerable to a server-side template injection vulnerability due to insecure configuration of the template engine used in the product. A remote authenticated malicious RSA NetWitness Server user with an Admin or Operator role could exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands on the server with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11061|2024-09-17T01:06:59.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
