<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell EMC -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell%20emc/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell EMC -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3721|2024-08-04T19:19:18.354Z -- dell%20emc -- open%20manage%20system%20administrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3721</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Open Manage System Administrator (OMSA) versions prior to 9.3.0 contain an Improper Range Header Processing Vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker may send crafted requests with overlapping ranges to cause the application to compress each of the requested bytes, resulting in a crash due to excessive memory consumption and preventing users from accessing the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3721|2024-08-04T19:19:18.354Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3726|2024-08-04T19:19:17.986Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20servers%3A%20networking%20and%20fibre%20channel%20drivers%3A%20dell%20update%20package%20%28dup%29%20framework%20file
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3726</link>
      <description>An Uncontrolled Search Path Vulnerability is applicable to the following: Dell Update Package (DUP) Framework file versions prior to 19.1.0.413, and Framework file versions prior to 103.4.6.69 used in Dell EMC Servers. Dell Update Package (DUP) Framework file versions prior to 3.8.3.67 used in Dell Client Platforms. The vulnerability is limited to the DUP framework during the time window when a DUP is being executed by an administrator. During this time window, a locally authenticated low privilege malicious user potentially could exploit this vulnerability by tricking an administrator into running a trusted binary, causing it to load a malicious DLL and allowing the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the victim system. The vulnerability does not affect the actual binary payload that the DUP delivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3726|2024-08-04T19:19:17.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3705|2024-08-04T19:19:17.425Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3705</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC6 versions prior to 2.92, iDRAC7/iDRAC8 versions prior to 2.61.60.60, and iDRAC9 versions prior to 3.20.21.20, 3.21.24.22, 3.21.26.22 and 3.23.23.23 contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker may potentially exploit this vulnerability to crash the webserver or execute arbitrary code on the system with privileges of the webserver by sending specially crafted input data to the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3705|2024-08-04T19:19:17.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3727|2024-08-04T19:19:18.102Z -- dell%20emc -- recoverpoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3727</link>
      <description>Dell EMC RecoverPoint versions prior to 5.1.3 and RecoverPoint for VMs versions prior to 5.2.0.2 contain an OS command injection vulnerability in the installation feature of Boxmgmt CLI. A malicious boxmgmt user may potentially be able to execute arbitrary commands as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3727|2024-08-04T19:19:18.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3734|2024-08-04T19:19:18.329Z -- dell%20emc -- unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3734</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity and UnityVSA versions prior to 5.0.0.0.5.116 contain an improper authorization vulnerability in NAS Server quotas configuration. A remote authenticated Unisphere Operator could potentially exploit this vulnerability to edit quota configuration of other users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3734|2024-08-04T19:19:18.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3741|2024-08-04T19:19:18.340Z -- dell%20emc -- unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3741</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity and UnityVSA versions prior to 5.0.0.0.5.116 contain a plain-text password storage vulnerability. A Unisphere user’s (including the admin privilege user) password is stored in a plain text in Unity Data Collection bundle (logs files for troubleshooting). A local authenticated attacker with access to the Data Collection bundle may use the exposed password to gain access with the privileges of the compromised user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3741|2024-08-04T19:19:18.340Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3706|2024-08-04T19:19:17.489Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3706</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC9 versions prior to 3.24.24.24, 3.21.26.22, 3.22.22.22 and 3.21.25.22 contain an authentication bypass vulnerability. A remote attacker may potentially exploit this vulnerability to bypass authentication and gain access to the system by sending specially crafted data to the iDRAC web interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3706|2024-08-04T19:19:17.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3737|2024-08-04T19:19:17.569Z -- dell%20emc -- avamar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3737</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Avamar ADMe Web Interface 1.0.50 and 1.0.51 are affected by an LFI vulnerability which may allow a malicious user to download arbitrary files from the affected system by sending a specially crafted request to the Web Interface application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3737|2024-08-04T19:19:17.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3722|2024-08-04T19:19:18.254Z -- dell%20emc -- openmanage%20server%20administrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3722</link>
      <description>Dell EMC OpenManage Server Administrator (OMSA) versions prior to 9.1.0.3 and prior to 9.2.0.4 contain an XML external entity (XXE) injection vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to read arbitrary server system files by supplying specially crafted document type definitions (DTDs) in an XML request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3722|2024-08-04T19:19:18.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3754|2024-08-04T19:19:18.181Z -- dell%20emc -- unity%20operating%20environment
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3754</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity Operating Environment versions prior to 5.0.0.0.5.116, Dell EMC UnityVSA versions prior to 5.0.0.0.5.116 and Dell EMC VNXe3200 versions prior to 3.1.10.9946299 contain a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability on the cas/logout page. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability by tricking a victim application user to supply malicious HTML or Java Script code to Unisphere, which is then reflected back to the victim and executed by the web browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3754|2024-08-04T19:19:18.181Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3710|2024-08-04T19:19:17.923Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20networking%20os10
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3710</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Networking OS10 versions prior to 10.4.3 contain a cryptographic key vulnerability due to an underlying application using undocumented, pre-installed X.509v3 key/certificate pairs. An unauthenticated remote attacker with the knowledge of the default keys may potentially be able to intercept communications or operate the system with elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3710|2024-08-04T19:19:17.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 17:58:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3751|2024-08-04T19:19:18.413Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20enterprise%20copy%20data%20management%20%28ecdm%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3751</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Enterprise Copy Data Management (eCDM) versions 1.0, 1.1, 2.0, 2.1, and 3.0 contain a certificate validation vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker may potentially exploit this vulnerability to carry out a man-in-the-middle attack by supplying a crafted certificate and intercepting the victim's traffic to view or modify a victim’s data in transit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3751|2024-08-04T19:19:18.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3723|2024-08-04T19:19:17.606Z -- dell%20emc -- openmanage%20server%20administrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3723</link>
      <description>Dell EMC OpenManage Server Administrator (OMSA) versions prior to 9.1.0.3 and prior to 9.2.0.4 contain a web parameter tampering vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially manipulate parameters of web requests to OMSA to create arbitrary files with empty content or delete the contents of any existing file, due to improper input parameter validation</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3723|2024-08-04T19:19:17.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3707|2024-08-04T19:19:17.547Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3707</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC9 versions prior to 3.30.30.30 contain an authentication bypass vulnerability. A remote attacker may potentially exploit this vulnerability to bypass authentication and gain access to the system by sending specially crafted input data to the WS-MAN interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3707|2024-08-04T19:19:17.547Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3753|2024-08-04T19:19:18.453Z -- dell%20emc -- powerconnect%208024
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3753</link>
      <description>Dell EMC PowerConnect 8024, 7000, M6348, M6220, M8024 and M8024-K running firmware versions prior to 5.1.15.2 contain a plain-text password storage vulnerability. TACACS\Radius credentials are stored in plain text in the system settings menu. An authenticated malicious user with access to the system settings menu may obtain the exposed password to use it in further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3753|2024-08-04T19:19:18.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3709|2024-08-04T19:19:17.423Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20isilonsd%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3709</link>
      <description>IsilonSD Management Server 1.1.0 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability while registering vCenter servers. A remote attacker can trick an admin user to potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute malicious HTML or JavaScript code in the context of the admin user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3709|2024-08-04T19:19:17.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3720|2024-08-04T19:19:17.870Z -- dell%20emc -- open%20manage%20system%20administrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3720</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Open Manage System Administrator (OMSA) versions prior to 9.3.0 contain a Directory Traversal Vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious user with admin privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain unauthorized access to the file system by exploiting insufficient sanitization of input parameters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3720|2024-08-04T19:19:17.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3708|2024-08-04T19:19:17.689Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20isilonsd%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3708</link>
      <description>IsilonSD Management Server 1.1.0 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability while uploading an OVA file. A remote attacker can trick an admin user to potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute malicious HTML or JavaScript code in the context of the admin user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3708|2024-08-04T19:19:17.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3704|2024-08-04T19:19:18.184Z -- dell%20emc -- vnx%20control%20station%20in%20dell%20emc%20vnx2%20oe%20for%20file
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3704</link>
      <description>VNX Control Station in Dell EMC VNX2 OE for File versions prior to 8.1.9.236 contains OS command injection vulnerability. Due to inadequate restriction configured in sudores, a local authenticated malicious user could potentially execute arbitrary OS commands as root by exploiting this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3704|2024-08-04T19:19:18.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
