<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell EMC -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell%20emc/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell EMC -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 17:22:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1244|2024-09-16T16:53:27.629Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac7
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1244</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC7/iDRAC8, versions prior to 2.60.60.60, and iDRAC9 versions prior to 3.21.21.21 contain a command injection vulnerability in the SNMP agent. A remote authenticated malicious iDRAC user with configuration privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands on the iDRAC where SNMP alerting is enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1244|2024-09-16T16:53:27.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11060|2024-09-16T16:58:13.454Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20archer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11060</link>
      <description>RSA Archer, versions prior to 6.4.0.1, contain an authorization bypass vulnerability in the REST API. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to elevate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11060|2024-09-16T16:58:13.454Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1239|2024-09-16T16:33:38.146Z -- dell%20emc -- unity%20operating%20environment%20%28oe%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1239</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity Operating Environment (OE) versions prior to 4.3.0.1522077968 are affected by multiple OS command injection vulnerabilities. A remote application admin user could potentially exploit the vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary OS commands as system root on the system where Dell EMC Unity is installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1239|2024-09-16T16:33:38.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8013|2024-09-16T16:58:08.085Z -- dell%20emc -- emc%20data%20protection%20advisor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8013</link>
      <description>EMC Data Protection Advisor 6.3.x before patch 67 and 6.4.x before patch 130 contains undocumented accounts with hard-coded passwords and various privileges. Affected accounts are: "Apollo System Test", "emc.dpa.agent.logon" and "emc.dpa.metrics.logon". An attacker with knowledge of the password could potentially use these accounts via REST APIs to gain unauthorized access to EMC Data Protection Advisor (including potentially access with administrative privileges).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8013|2024-09-16T16:58:08.085Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1247|2024-09-16T16:39:05.452Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20authentication%20manager%20security%20console
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1247</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Manager Security Console, version 8.3 and earlier, contains a XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability. This could potentially allow admin users to cause a denial of service or extract server data via injecting a maliciously crafted DTD in an XML file submitted to the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1247|2024-09-16T16:39:05.452Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1248|2024-09-16T16:13:25.346Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20authentication%20manager%20security%20console%2C%20operation%20console%20and%20self-service%20console
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1248</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Manager Security Console, Operation Console and Self-Service Console, version 8.3 and earlier, is affected by a Host header injection vulnerability. This could allow a remote attacker to potentially poison HTTP cache and subsequently redirect users to arbitrary web domains.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1248|2024-09-16T16:13:25.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1200|2024-09-16T16:17:36.254Z -- dell%20emc -- apps%20manager%20for%20pcf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1200</link>
      <description>Apps Manager for PCF (Pivotal Application Service 1.11.x before 1.11.26, 1.12.x before 1.12.14, and 2.0.x before 2.0.5) allows unprivileged remote file read in its container via specially-crafted links.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1200|2024-09-16T16:17:36.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1199|2024-09-16T16:13:09.643Z -- dell%20emc -- spring%20by%20pivotal
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1199</link>
      <description>Spring Security (Spring Security 4.1.x before 4.1.5, 4.2.x before 4.2.4, and 5.0.x before 5.0.1; and Spring Framework 4.3.x before 4.3.14 and 5.0.x before 5.0.3) does not consider URL path parameters when processing security constraints. By adding a URL path parameter with special encodings, an attacker may be able to bypass a security constraint. The root cause of this issue is a lack of clarity regarding the handling of path parameters in the Servlet Specification. Some Servlet containers include path parameters in the value returned for getPathInfo() and some do not. Spring Security uses the value returned by getPathInfo() as part of the process of mapping requests to security constraints. In this particular attack, different character encodings used in path parameters allows secured Spring MVC static resource URLs to be bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1199|2024-09-16T16:13:09.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3720|2024-09-16T16:32:39.543Z -- dell%20emc -- open%20manage%20system%20administrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3720</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Open Manage System Administrator (OMSA) versions prior to 9.3.0 contain a Directory Traversal Vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious user with admin privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain unauthorized access to the file system by exploiting insufficient sanitization of input parameters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3720|2024-09-16T16:32:39.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 20:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
