<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell EMC -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell%20emc/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell EMC -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 04:24:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11052|2024-09-17T04:00:07.900Z -- dell%20emc -- ecs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11052</link>
      <description>Dell EMC ECS versions 3.2.0.0 and 3.2.0.1 contain an authentication bypass vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability to read and modify S3 objects by supplying specially crafted S3 requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11052|2024-09-17T04:00:07.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1249|2024-09-17T03:19:03.618Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1249</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC9 versions prior to 3.21.21.21 did not enforce the use of TLS/SSL for a connection to iDRAC web server for certain URLs. A man-in-the-middle attacker could use this vulnerability to strip the SSL/TLS protection from a connection between a client and a server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1249|2024-09-17T03:19:03.618Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-3626|2024-09-17T03:59:34.272Z -- dell%20emc -- grails%20by%20pivotal
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-3626</link>
      <description>The Grails Resource Plugin often has to exchange URIs for resources with other internal components. Those other components will decode any URI passed to them. To protect against directory traversal the Grails Resource Plugin did the following: normalized the URI, checked the normalized URI did not step outside the appropriate root directory (e.g. the web application root), decoded the URI and checked that this did not introduce additional /../ (and similar) sequences. A bug was introduced where the Grails Resource Plugin before 1.2.13 returned the decoded version of the URI rather than the normalized version of the URI after the directory traversal check. This exposed a double decoding vulnerability. To address this issue, the Grails Resource Plugin now repeatedly decodes the URI up to three times or until decoding no longer changes the URI. If the decode limit of 3 is exceeded the URI is rejected. A side-effect of this is that the Grails Resource Plugin is unable to serve a resource that includes a '%' character in the full path to the resource. Not all environments are vulnerable because of the differences in URL resolving in different servlet containers. Applications deployed to Tomcat 8 and Jetty 9 were found not not be vulnerable, however applications deployed to JBoss EAP 6.3 / JBoss AS 7.4 and JBoss AS 7.1 were found to be vulnerable (other JBoss versions weren't tested). In certain cases JBoss returns JBoss specific vfs protocol urls from URL resolution methods (ClassLoader.getResources). The JBoss vfs URL protocol supports resolving any file on the filesystem. This made the directory traversal possible. There may be other containers, in addition to JBoss, on which this vulnerability is exposed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-3626|2024-09-17T03:59:34.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15771|2024-09-17T03:58:36.708Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20recoverpoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15771</link>
      <description>Dell EMC RecoverPoint versions prior to 5.1.2.1 and RecoverPoint for VMs versions prior to 5.2.0.2 contain an information disclosure vulnerability. A malicious boxmgmt user may potentially be able to determine the existence of any system file via Boxmgmt CLI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15771|2024-09-17T03:58:36.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1218|2024-09-17T02:16:47.701Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20networker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1218</link>
      <description>In Dell EMC NetWorker versions prior to 9.2.1.1, versions prior to 9.1.1.6, 9.0.x, and versions prior to 8.2.4.11, the 'nsrd' daemon causes a buffer overflow condition when handling certain messages. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to cause a denial of service to the users of NetWorker systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1218|2024-09-17T02:16:47.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11061|2024-09-17T01:06:59.417Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20netwitness
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11061</link>
      <description>RSA NetWitness Platform versions prior to 11.1.0.2 and RSA Security Analytics versions prior to 10.6.6 are vulnerable to a server-side template injection vulnerability due to insecure configuration of the template engine used in the product. A remote authenticated malicious RSA NetWitness Server user with an Admin or Operator role could exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands on the server with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11061|2024-09-17T01:06:59.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1202|2024-09-17T00:11:13.380Z -- dell%20emc -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1202</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon versions between 8.1.0.0 - 8.1.0.1, 8.0.1.0 - 8.0.1.2, and 8.0.0.0 - 8.0.0.6, and version 7.1.1.11 is affected by a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the NDMP Page within the OneFS web administration interface. A malicious administrator may potentially inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code in the user's browser session in the context of the OneFS website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1202|2024-09-17T00:11:13.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1186|2024-09-17T01:16:00.737Z -- dell%20emc -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1186</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon versions between 8.1.0.0 - 8.1.0.1, 8.0.1.0 - 8.0.1.2, and 8.0.0.0 - 8.0.0.6, versions 7.2.1.x, and version 7.1.1.11 is affected by a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Cluster description of the OneFS web administration interface. A malicious administrator may potentially inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code in the user's browser session in the context of the OneFS website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1186|2024-09-17T01:16:00.737Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11080|2024-09-17T02:52:05.343Z -- dell%20emc -- esrs%20virtual%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11080</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Secure Remote Services, versions prior to 3.32.00.08, contains Improper File Permission Vulnerabilities. The application contains multiple configuration files with world-readable permissions that could allow an authenticated malicious user to utilize the file contents to potentially elevate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11080|2024-09-17T02:52:05.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3708|2024-09-17T00:36:59.730Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20isilonsd%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3708</link>
      <description>IsilonSD Management Server 1.1.0 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability while uploading an OVA file. A remote attacker can trick an admin user to potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute malicious HTML or JavaScript code in the context of the admin user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3708|2024-09-17T00:36:59.730Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 13:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11066|2024-09-17T03:43:20.412Z -- dell%20emc -- avamar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11066</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Avamar Client Manager in Dell EMC Avamar Server versions 7.2.0, 7.2.1, 7.3.0, 7.3.1, 7.4.0, 7.4.1, 7.5.0, 7.5.1, 18.1 and Dell EMC Integrated Data Protection Appliance (IDPA) versions 2.0, 2.1 and 2.2 contain a Remote Code Execution vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11066|2024-09-17T03:43:20.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15774|2024-09-17T01:36:18.120Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15774</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC7/iDRAC8 versions prior to 2.61.60.60 and iDRAC9 versions prior to 3.20.21.20, 3.21.24.22, 3.21.26.22, and 3.23.23.23 contain a privilege escalation vulnerability. An authenticated malicious iDRAC user with operator privileges could potentially exploit a permissions check flaw in the Redfish interface to gain administrator access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15774|2024-09-17T01:36:18.120Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11079|2024-09-17T01:26:15.649Z -- dell%20emc -- esrs%20virtual%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11079</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Secure Remote Services, versions prior to 3.32.00.08, contains a Plaintext Password Storage vulnerability. Database credentials are stored in plaintext in a configuration file. An authenticated malicious user with access to the configuration file may obtain the exposed password to gain access to the application database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11079|2024-09-17T01:26:15.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1221|2024-09-17T01:15:36.021Z -- dell%20emc -- the%20cloud%20foundry%20gorouter
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1221</link>
      <description>In cf-deployment before 1.14.0 and routing-release before 0.172.0, the Cloud Foundry Gorouter mishandles WebSocket requests for AWS Application Load Balancers (ALBs) and some other HTTP-aware Load Balancers. A user with developer privileges could use this vulnerability to steal data or cause denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1221|2024-09-17T01:15:36.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3751|2024-09-17T02:47:44.353Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20enterprise%20copy%20data%20management%20%28ecdm%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3751</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Enterprise Copy Data Management (eCDM) versions 1.0, 1.1, 2.0, 2.1, and 3.0 contain a certificate validation vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker may potentially exploit this vulnerability to carry out a man-in-the-middle attack by supplying a crafted certificate and intercepting the victim's traffic to view or modify a victim’s data in transit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3751|2024-09-17T02:47:44.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 16:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1241|2024-09-17T01:21:43.931Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20recoverpoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1241</link>
      <description>Dell EMC RecoverPoint versions prior to 5.1.2 and RecoverPoint for VMs versions prior to 5.1.1.3, under certain conditions, may leak LDAP password in plain-text into the RecoverPoint log file. An authenticated malicious user with access to the RecoverPoint log files may obtain the exposed LDAP password to use it in further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1241|2024-09-17T01:21:43.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1212|2024-09-17T01:37:02.877Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac6%20%28monolithic%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1212</link>
      <description>The web-based diagnostics console in Dell EMC iDRAC6 (Monolithic versions prior to 2.91 and Modular all versions) contains a command injection vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious iDRAC user with access to the diagnostics console could potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands as root on the affected iDRAC system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1212|2024-09-17T01:37:02.877Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3706|2024-09-17T00:26:34.078Z -- dell%20emc -- idrac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3706</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC9 versions prior to 3.24.24.24, 3.21.26.22, 3.22.22.22 and 3.21.25.22 contain an authentication bypass vulnerability. A remote attacker may potentially exploit this vulnerability to bypass authentication and gain access to the system by sending specially crafted data to the iDRAC web interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3706|2024-09-17T00:26:34.078Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 18:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3727|2024-09-17T03:42:56.299Z -- dell%20emc -- recoverpoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3727</link>
      <description>Dell EMC RecoverPoint versions prior to 5.1.3 and RecoverPoint for VMs versions prior to 5.2.0.2 contain an OS command injection vulnerability in the installation feature of Boxmgmt CLI. A malicious boxmgmt user may potentially be able to execute arbitrary commands as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3727|2024-09-17T03:42:56.299Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 15:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1232|2024-09-17T00:25:34.327Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20authentication%20agent%20for%20web%20for%20iis%2C%20rsa%20authentication%20agent%20for%20web%20for%20apache%20web%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1232</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Agent version 8.0.1 and earlier for Web for both IIS and Apache Web Server are impacted by a stack-based buffer overflow which may occur when handling certain malicious web cookies that have invalid formats. The attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the authentication agent and cause a denial-of-service situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1232|2024-09-17T00:25:34.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15772|2024-09-17T01:10:33.151Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20recoverpoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15772</link>
      <description>Dell EMC RecoverPoint versions prior to 5.1.2.1 and RecoverPoint for VMs versions prior to 5.2.0.2 contain an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability. A malicious boxmgmt user may potentially be able to consume large amount of CPU bandwidth to make the system slow or to determine the existence of any system file via Boxmgmt CLI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15772|2024-09-17T01:10:33.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3754|2024-09-17T02:00:48.399Z -- dell%20emc -- unity%20operating%20environment
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3754</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity Operating Environment versions prior to 5.0.0.0.5.116, Dell EMC UnityVSA versions prior to 5.0.0.0.5.116 and Dell EMC VNXe3200 versions prior to 3.1.10.9946299 contain a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability on the cas/logout page. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability by tricking a victim application user to supply malicious HTML or Java Script code to Unisphere, which is then reflected back to the victim and executed by the web browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3754|2024-09-17T02:00:48.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 16:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11077|2024-09-17T03:06:58.660Z -- dell%20emc -- avamar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11077</link>
      <description>'getlogs' utility in Dell EMC Avamar Server versions 7.2.0, 7.2.1, 7.3.0, 7.3.1, 7.4.0, 7.4.1, 7.5.0, 7.5.1 and 18.1 and Dell EMC Integrated Data Protection Appliance (IDPA) versions 2.0, 2.1 and 2.2 is affected by an OS command injection vulnerability. A malicious Avamar admin user may potentially be able to execute arbitrary commands under root privilege.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11077|2024-09-17T03:06:58.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11067|2024-09-17T00:11:44.344Z -- dell%20emc -- avamar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11067</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Avamar Client Manager in Dell EMC Avamar Server versions 7.2.0, 7.2.1, 7.3.0, 7.3.1, 7.4.0, 7.4.1, 7.5.0, 7.5.1, 18.1 and Dell EMC Integrated Data Protection Appliance (IDPA) versions 2.0, 2.1 and 2.2 contain an open redirection vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to redirect application users to arbitrary web URLs by tricking the victim users to click on maliciously crafted links. The vulnerability could be used to conduct phishing attacks that cause users to unknowingly visit malicious sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11067|2024-09-17T00:11:44.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1246|2024-09-17T03:14:02.750Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1246</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity and UnityVSA contains reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability by tricking a victim application user to supply malicious HTML or Java Script code to Unisphere, which is then reflected back to the victim and executed by the web browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1246|2024-09-17T03:14:02.750Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11048|2024-09-17T01:56:30.207Z -- dell%20emc -- data%20protection%20advisor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11048</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Data Protection Advisor, versions 6.2, 6,3, 6.4, 6.5 and Dell EMC Integrated Data Protection Appliance (IDPA) versions 2.0, 2.1 contain a XML External Entity (XXE) Injection vulnerability in the REST API. An authenticated remote malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to read certain system files in the server or cause denial of service by supplying specially crafted Document Type Definitions (DTDs) in an XML request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11048|2024-09-17T01:56:30.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1201|2024-09-17T03:24:01.982Z -- dell%20emc -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1201</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon versions between 8.1.0.0 - 8.1.0.1, 8.0.1.0 - 8.0.1.2, and 8.0.0.0 - 8.0.0.6, versions 7.2.1.x, and version 7.1.1.11 is affected by a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Job Operations Page within the OneFS web administration interface. A malicious administrator may potentially inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code in the user's browser session in the context of the OneFS website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1201|2024-09-17T03:24:01.982Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
