<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell EMC -- Dell EMC Unity</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell%20emc/dell%20emc%20unity.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell EMC -- Dell EMC Unity</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 07:21:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1250|2024-08-05T03:51:49.038Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1250</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity and UnityVSA versions prior to 4.3.1.1525703027 contains an Authorization Bypass vulnerability. A remote authenticated user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to read files in NAS server by directly interacting with certain APIs of Unity OE, bypassing Role-Based Authorization control implemented only in Unisphere GUI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1250|2024-08-05T03:51:49.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1251|2024-08-05T03:51:49.174Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1251</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity and UnityVSA versions prior to 4.3.1.1525703027 contains a URL Redirection vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to redirect Unity users to arbitrary web URLs by tricking the victim user to click on a maliciously crafted Unisphere URL. Attacker could potentially phish information, including Unisphere users' credentials, from the victim once they are redirected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1251|2024-08-05T03:51:49.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1246|2024-08-05T03:51:49.039Z -- dell%20emc -- dell%20emc%20unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1246</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity and UnityVSA contains reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability by tricking a victim application user to supply malicious HTML or Java Script code to Unisphere, which is then reflected back to the victim and executed by the web browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1246|2024-08-05T03:51:49.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
