<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell EMC -- RSA Archer</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell%20emc/rsa%20archer.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell EMC -- RSA Archer</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 08:24:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11060|2024-08-05T07:54:36.587Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20archer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11060</link>
      <description>RSA Archer, versions prior to 6.4.0.1, contain an authorization bypass vulnerability in the REST API. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to elevate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11060|2024-08-05T07:54:36.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11065|2024-08-05T07:54:36.650Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20archer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11065</link>
      <description>The WorkPoint component, which is embedded in all RSA Archer, versions 6.1.x, 6.2.x, 6.3.x prior to 6.3.0.7 and 6.4.x prior to 6.4.0.1, contains a SQL injection vulnerability. A malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute SQL commands on the back-end database to read certain data. Embedded WorkPoint is upgraded to version 4.10.16, which contains a fix for the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11065|2024-08-05T07:54:36.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11059|2024-08-05T07:54:36.636Z -- dell%20emc -- rsa%20archer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11059</link>
      <description>RSA Archer, versions prior to 6.4.0.1, contain a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to store malicious HTML or JavaScript code in a trusted application data store. When application users access the corrupted data store through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11059|2024-08-05T07:54:36.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
