<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell EMC -- ScaleIO</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell%20emc/scaleio.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell EMC -- ScaleIO</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 09:23:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1238|2024-08-05T03:51:48.950Z -- dell%20emc -- scaleio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1238</link>
      <description>Dell EMC ScaleIO versions prior to 2.5, contain a command injection vulnerability in the Light Installation Agent (LIA). This component is used for central management of ScaleIO deployment and uses shell commands for certain actions. A remote malicious user, with network access to LIA and knowledge of the LIA administrative password, could potentially exploit this vulnerability to run arbitrary commands as root on the systems where LIAs are installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1238|2024-08-05T03:51:48.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1237|2024-08-05T03:51:48.906Z -- dell%20emc -- scaleio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1237</link>
      <description>Dell EMC ScaleIO versions prior to 2.5, contain improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts on the Light installation Agent (LIA). This component is deployed on every server in the ScaleIO cluster and is used for central management of ScaleIO nodes. A remote malicious user, having network access to LIA, could potentially exploit this vulnerability to launch brute force guessing of user names and passwords of user accounts on the LIA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1237|2024-08-05T03:51:48.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1205|2024-08-05T03:51:49.125Z -- dell%20emc -- scaleio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1205</link>
      <description>Dell EMC ScaleIO, versions prior to 2.5, do not properly handle some packet data in the MDM service. As a result, a remote attacker could potentially send specifically crafted packet data to the MDM service causing it to crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1205|2024-08-05T03:51:49.125Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
