<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for xwiki -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/xwiki/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for xwiki -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-21648|2024-01-08T23:31:50.298Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21648</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. The rollback action is missing a right protection, a user can rollback to a previous version of the page to gain rights they don't have anymore. The problem has been patched in XWiki 14.10.17, 15.5.3 and 15.8-rc-1 by ensuring that the rights are checked before performing the rollback. </description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21648|2024-01-08T23:31:50.298Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 23:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21651|2024-01-08T23:30:03.580Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21651</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. A user able to attach a file to a page can post a malformed TAR file by manipulating file modification times headers, which when parsed by Tika, could cause a denial of service issue via CPU consumption. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.18, 15.5.3 and 15.8 RC1.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21651|2024-01-08T23:30:03.580Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 23:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21650|2024-01-08T15:18:12.782Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21650</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. XWiki is vulnerable to a remote code execution (RCE) attack through its user registration feature. This issue allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code by crafting malicious payloads in the "first name" or "last name" fields during user registration. This impacts all installations that have user registration enabled for guests. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.17, 15.5.3 and 15.8 RC1.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21650|2024-01-08T15:18:12.782Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 15:18:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31985|2024-04-10T20:25:56.501Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31985</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 3.1 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, it is possible to schedule/trigger/unschedule existing jobs by having an admin visit the Job Scheduler page through a predictable URL, for example by embedding such an URL in any content as an image. The vulnerability has been fixed in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.5, and 15.9. As a workaround, manually apply the patch by modifying the `Scheduler.WebHome` page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31985|2024-04-10T20:25:56.501Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31984|2024-04-10T20:11:03.857Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31984</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 7.2-rc-1 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, by creating a document with a specially crafted title, it is possible to trigger remote code execution in the (Solr-based) search in XWiki. This allows any user who can edit the title of a space (all users by default) to execute any Groovy code in the XWiki installation which compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10 RC1. As a workaround, manually apply the patch to the `Main.SolrSpaceFacet` page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31984|2024-04-10T20:11:03.857Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:53:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31988|2024-04-10T20:40:36.954Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31988</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 13.9-rc-1 and prior to versions 4.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, when the realtime editor is installed in XWiki, it allows arbitrary remote code execution with the interaction of an admin user with programming right. More precisely, by getting an admin user to either visit a crafted URL or to view an image with this URL that could be in a comment, the attacker can get the admin to execute arbitrary XWiki syntax including scripting macros with Groovy or Python code. This compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.4 and 15.9. As a workaround, one may update `RTFrontend.ConvertHTML` manually with the patch. This will, however, break some synchronization processes in the realtime editor, so upgrading should be the preferred way on installations where this editor is used.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31988|2024-04-10T20:40:36.954Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31983|2024-04-10T19:52:42.048Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31983</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. In multilingual wikis, translations can be edited by any user who has edit right, circumventing the rights that are normally required for authoring translations (script right for user-scope translations, wiki admin for translations on the wiki). Starting in version 4.3-milestone-2 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, this can be exploited for remote code execution if the translation value is not properly escaped where it is used. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10RC1. As a workaround, one may restrict edit rights on documents that contain translations.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31983|2024-04-10T19:52:42.048Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31464|2024-04-10T18:14:37.224Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31464</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 5.0-rc-1 and prior to versions 14.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.9-rc-1, it is possible to access the hash of a password by using the diff feature of the history whenever the object storing the password is deleted. Using that vulnerability it's possible for an attacker to have access to the hash password of a user if they have rights to edit the users' page.  With the default right scheme in XWiki this vulnerability is normally prevented on user profiles, except by users with Admin rights. Note that this vulnerability also impacts any extensions that might use passwords stored in xobjects: for those usecases it depends on the right of those pages. There is currently no way to be 100% sure that this vulnerability has been exploited, as an attacker with enough privilege could have deleted the revision where the xobject was deleted after rolling-back the deletion. But again, this operation requires high privileges on the target page (Admin right). A page with a user password xobject which have in its history a revision where the object has been deleted should be considered at risk and the password should be changed there. a diff, to ensure it's not coming from a password field. As another mitigation, admins should ensure that the user pages are properly protected: the edit right shouldn't be allowed for other users than Admin and owner of the profile (which is the default right). There is not much workaround possible for a privileged user other than upgrading XWiki.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31464|2024-04-10T18:14:37.224Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 18:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31465|2024-04-10T19:12:35.517Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31465</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 5.0-rc-1 and prior to versions 14.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.9-rc-1, any user with edit right on any page can execute any code on the server by adding an object of type `XWiki.SearchSuggestSourceClass` to their user profile or any other page. This compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10 RC1. As a workaround, manually apply the patch to the document `XWiki.SearchSuggestSourceSheet`.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31465|2024-04-10T19:12:35.517Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31982|2024-04-10T19:38:01.879Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31982</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 2.4-milestone-1 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, XWiki's database search allows remote code execution through the search text. This allows remote code execution for any visitor of a public wiki or user of a closed wiki as the database search is by default accessible for all users. This impacts the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10RC1. As a workaround, one may manually apply the patch to the page `Main.DatabaseSearch`. Alternatively, unless database search is explicitly used by users, this page can be deleted as this is not the default search interface of XWiki.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31982|2024-04-10T19:38:01.879Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31997|2024-04-10T21:55:43.475Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31997</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Prior to versions 4.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, parameters of UI extensions are always interpreted as Velocity code and executed with programming rights. Any user with edit right on any document like the user's own profile can create UI extensions. This allows remote code execution and thereby impacts the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.4 and 15.9-RC1. No known workarounds are available.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31997|2024-04-10T21:55:43.475Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 21:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31981|2024-04-10T19:22:57.494Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31981</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 3.0.1 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, remote code execution is possible via PDF export templates. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10-rc-1. If PDF templates are not typically used on the instance, an administrator can create the document `XWiki.PDFClass` and block its edition, after making sure that it does not contain a `style` attribute. Otherwise, there are no known workarounds aside from upgrading.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31981|2024-04-10T19:22:57.494Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31996|2024-04-10T20:46:19.929Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-commons
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31996</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 3.0.1 and prior to versions 4.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, the HTML escaping of escaping tool that is used in XWiki doesn't escape `{`, which, when used in certain places, allows XWiki syntax injection and thereby remote code execution. The vulnerability has been fixed in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.5, and 15.9 RC1. Apart from upgrading, there is no generic workaround. However, replacing `$escapetool.html` by `$escapetool.xml` in XWiki documents fixes the vulnerability. In a standard XWiki installation, the maintainers are only aware of the document `Panels.PanelLayoutUpdate` that exposes this vulnerability, patching this document is thus a workaround. Any extension could expose this vulnerability and might thus require patching, too.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31996|2024-04-10T20:46:19.929Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31987|2024-04-10T20:32:39.317Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31987</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 6.4-milestone-1 and prior to versions 4.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, any user who can edit any page like their profile can create a custom skin with a template override that is executed with programming right, thus allowing remote code execution. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.4 and 15.10RC1. No known workarounds are available except for upgrading.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31987|2024-04-10T20:32:39.317Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31986|2024-04-10T20:27:29.600Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31986</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 3.1 and prior to versions 4.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, by creating a document with a special crafted documented reference and an `XWiki.SchedulerJobClass` XObject, it is possible to execute arbitrary code on the server whenever an admin visits the scheduler page or the scheduler page is referenced, e.g., via an image in a comment on a page in the wiki. The vulnerability has been fixed in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.5, and 15.9. As a workaround, apply the patch manually by modifying the `Scheduler.WebHome` page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31986|2024-04-10T20:27:29.600Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>