<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/xwiki/xwiki-platform.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for xwiki -- xwiki-platform</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 21:22:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46731|2024-09-05T14:34:27.189Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46731</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. XWiki doesn't properly escape the section URL parameter that is used in the code for displaying administration sections. This allows any user with read access to the document `XWiki.AdminSheet` (by default, everyone including unauthenticated users) to execute code including Groovy code. This impacts the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki instance. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.14, 15.6 RC1 and 15.5.1. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unablr to upgrade may apply the fix in commit `fec8e0e53f9` manually. Alternatively, to protect against attacks from unauthenticated users, view right for guests can be removed from this document (it is only needed for space and wiki admins).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46731|2024-09-05T14:34:27.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 18:47:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46732|2024-09-05T13:31:18.349Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46732</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. XWiki is vulnerable to reflected cross-site scripting (RXSS) via the `rev` parameter that is used in the content of the content menu without escaping. If an attacker can convince a user to visit a link with a crafted parameter, this allows the attacker to execute arbitrary actions in the name of the user, including remote code (Groovy) execution in the case of a user with programming right, compromising the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This has been patched in XWiki 15.6 RC1, 15.5.1 and 14.10.14. The patch in commit `04e325d57` can be manually applied without upgrading (or restarting) the instance. Users are advised to upgrade or to manually apply the patch. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46732|2024-09-05T13:31:18.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 18:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-43400|2024-08-22T14:00:37.297Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43400</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. It is possible for a user without Script or Programming rights to craft a URL pointing to a page with arbitrary JavaScript. This requires social engineer to trick a user to follow the URL. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5, 15.10.6 and 16.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-43400|2024-08-22T14:00:37.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31982|2024-08-20T19:02:45.798Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31982</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 2.4-milestone-1 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, XWiki's database search allows remote code execution through the search text. This allows remote code execution for any visitor of a public wiki or user of a closed wiki as the database search is by default accessible for all users. This impacts the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10RC1. As a workaround, one may manually apply the patch to the page `Main.DatabaseSearch`. Alternatively, unless database search is explicitly used by users, this page can be deleted as this is not the default search interface of XWiki.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31982|2024-08-20T19:02:45.798Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31987|2024-08-20T18:00:36.216Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31987</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 6.4-milestone-1 and prior to versions 4.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, any user who can edit any page like their profile can create a custom skin with a template override that is executed with programming right, thus allowing remote code execution. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.4 and 15.10RC1. No known workarounds are available except for upgrading.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31987|2024-08-20T18:00:36.216Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-43400|2024-08-19T18:01:33.898Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43400</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. It is possible for a user without Script or Programming rights to craft a URL pointing to a page with arbitrary JavaScript. This requires social engineer to trick a user to follow the URL. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5, 15.10.6 and 16.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-43400|2024-08-19T18:01:33.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-41947|2024-08-13T13:36:59.723Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41947</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. By creating a conflict when another user with more rights is currently editing a page, it is possible to execute JavaScript snippets on the side of the other user, which compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This has been patched in XWiki 15.10.8 and 16.3.0RC1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-41947|2024-08-13T13:36:59.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31984|2024-08-13T13:37:31.192Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31984</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 7.2-rc-1 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, by creating a document with a specially crafted title, it is possible to trigger remote code execution in the (Solr-based) search in XWiki. This allows any user who can edit the title of a space (all users by default) to execute any Groovy code in the XWiki installation which compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10 RC1. As a workaround, manually apply the patch to the `Main.SolrSpaceFacet` page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31984|2024-08-13T13:37:31.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31464|2024-08-13T13:37:19.841Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31464</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 5.0-rc-1 and prior to versions 14.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.9-rc-1, it is possible to access the hash of a password by using the diff feature of the history whenever the object storing the password is deleted. Using that vulnerability it's possible for an attacker to have access to the hash password of a user if they have rights to edit the users' page.  With the default right scheme in XWiki this vulnerability is normally prevented on user profiles, except by users with Admin rights. Note that this vulnerability also impacts any extensions that might use passwords stored in xobjects: for those usecases it depends on the right of those pages. There is currently no way to be 100% sure that this vulnerability has been exploited, as an attacker with enough privilege could have deleted the revision where the xobject was deleted after rolling-back the deletion. But again, this operation requires high privileges on the target page (Admin right). A page with a user password xobject which have in its history a revision where the object has been deleted should be considered at risk and the password should be changed there. a diff, to ensure it's not coming from a password field. As another mitigation, admins should ensure that the user pages are properly protected: the edit right shouldn't be allowed for other users than Admin and owner of the profile (which is the default right). There is not much workaround possible for a privileged user other than upgrading XWiki.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31464|2024-08-13T13:37:19.841Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 18:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31981|2024-08-13T13:37:34.850Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31981</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 3.0.1 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, remote code execution is possible via PDF export templates. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10-rc-1. If PDF templates are not typically used on the instance, an administrator can create the document `XWiki.PDFClass` and block its edition, after making sure that it does not contain a `style` attribute. Otherwise, there are no known workarounds aside from upgrading.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31981|2024-08-13T13:37:34.850Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37900|2024-08-13T13:37:13.581Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37900</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. When uploading an attachment with a malicious filename, malicious JavaScript code could be executed. This requires a social engineering attack to get the victim into uploading a file with a malicious name. The malicious code is solely executed during the upload and affects only the user uploading the attachment. While this allows performing actions in the name of that user, it seems unlikely that a user wouldn't notice the malicious filename while uploading the attachment. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5, 15.10.6 and 16.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37900|2024-08-13T13:37:13.581Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31997|2024-08-13T13:49:14.493Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31997</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Prior to versions 4.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, parameters of UI extensions are always interpreted as Velocity code and executed with programming rights. Any user with edit right on any document like the user's own profile can create UI extensions. This allows remote code execution and thereby impacts the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.4 and 15.9-RC1. No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31997|2024-08-13T13:49:14.493Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 21:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31983|2024-08-13T13:54:49.159Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31983</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. In multilingual wikis, translations can be edited by any user who has edit right, circumventing the rights that are normally required for authoring translations (script right for user-scope translations, wiki admin for translations on the wiki). Starting in version 4.3-milestone-2 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, this can be exploited for remote code execution if the translation value is not properly escaped where it is used. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10RC1. As a workaround, one may restrict edit rights on documents that contain translations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31983|2024-08-13T13:54:49.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31988|2024-08-13T13:37:25.766Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31988</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 13.9-rc-1 and prior to versions 4.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, when the realtime editor is installed in XWiki, it allows arbitrary remote code execution with the interaction of an admin user with programming right. More precisely, by getting an admin user to either visit a crafted URL or to view an image with this URL that could be in a comment, the attacker can get the admin to execute arbitrary XWiki syntax including scripting macros with Groovy or Python code. This compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.4 and 15.9. As a workaround, one may update `RTFrontend.ConvertHTML` manually with the patch. This will, however, break some synchronization processes in the realtime editor, so upgrading should be the preferred way on installations where this editor is used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31988|2024-08-13T13:37:25.766Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31465|2024-08-13T13:56:21.898Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31465</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 5.0-rc-1 and prior to versions 14.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.9-rc-1, any user with edit right on any page can execute any code on the server by adding an object of type `XWiki.SearchSuggestSourceClass` to their user profile or any other page. This compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10 RC1. As a workaround, manually apply the patch to the document `XWiki.SearchSuggestSourceSheet`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31465|2024-08-13T13:56:21.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37899|2024-08-13T13:51:01.754Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37899</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. When an admin disables a user account, the user's profile is executed with the admin's rights. This allows a user to place malicious code in the user profile before getting an admin to disable the user account. To reproduce, as a user without script nor programming rights, edit the about section of your user profile and add `{{groovy}}services.logging.getLogger("attacker").error("Hello from Groovy!"){{/groovy}}`.
As an admin, go to the user profile and click the "Disable this account" button. Then, reload the page. If the logs show `attacker - Hello from Groovy!` then the instance is vulnerable. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5, 15.10.6 and 16.0.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.

### Workarounds
We're not aware of any workaround except upgrading.

### References
* https://jira.xwiki.org/browse/XWIKI-21611
* https://github.com/xwiki/xwiki-platform/commit/f89c8f47fad6e5cc7e68c69a7e0acde07f5eed5a</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37899|2024-08-13T13:51:01.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 22:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37901|2024-08-13T13:37:05.363Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37901</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. Any user with edit right on any page can perform arbitrary remote code execution by adding instances of `XWiki.SearchSuggestConfig` and `XWiki.SearchSuggestSourceClass` to their user profile or any other page. This compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5 and 15.10.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37901|2024-08-13T13:37:05.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37901|2024-08-06T19:03:01.206Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37901</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. Any user with edit right on any page can perform arbitrary remote code execution by adding instances of `XWiki.SearchSuggestConfig` and `XWiki.SearchSuggestSourceClass` to their user profile or any other page. This compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5 and 15.10.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37901|2024-08-06T19:03:01.206Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38369|2024-08-02T04:04:25.248Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38369</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. The content of a document included using `{{include reference="targetdocument"/}}` is executed with the right of the includer and not with the right of its author. This means that any user able to modify the target document can impersonate the author of the content which used the `include` macro. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 15.0 RC1 by making the default behavior safe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38369|2024-08-02T04:04:25.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37899|2024-08-02T04:04:23.403Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37899</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. When an admin disables a user account, the user's profile is executed with the admin's rights. This allows a user to place malicious code in the user profile before getting an admin to disable the user account. To reproduce, as a user without script nor programming rights, edit the about section of your user profile and add `{{groovy}}services.logging.getLogger("attacker").error("Hello from Groovy!"){{/groovy}}`.
As an admin, go to the user profile and click the "Disable this account" button. Then, reload the page. If the logs show `attacker - Hello from Groovy!` then the instance is vulnerable. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5, 15.10.6 and 16.0.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.

### Workarounds
We're not aware of any workaround except upgrading.

### References
* https://jira.xwiki.org/browse/XWIKI-21611
* https://github.com/xwiki/xwiki-platform/commit/f89c8f47fad6e5cc7e68c69a7e0acde07f5eed5a</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37899|2024-08-02T04:04:23.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 22:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37898|2024-07-31T17:36:54.705Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37898</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. When a user has view but not edit right on a page in XWiki, that user can delete the page and replace it by a page with new content without having delete right. The previous version of the page is moved into the recycle bin and can be restored from there by an admin. As the user is recorded as deleter, the user would in theory also be able to view the deleted content, but this is not directly possible as rights of the previous version are transferred to the new page and thus the user still doesn't have view right on the page. It therefore doesn't seem to be possible to exploit this to gain any rights. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5 and 15.10.6 by cancelling save operations by users when a new document shall be saved despite the document's existing already.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37898|2024-07-31T17:36:54.705Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31464|2024-07-31T14:35:44.503Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31464</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 5.0-rc-1 and prior to versions 14.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.9-rc-1, it is possible to access the hash of a password by using the diff feature of the history whenever the object storing the password is deleted. Using that vulnerability it's possible for an attacker to have access to the hash password of a user if they have rights to edit the users' page.  With the default right scheme in XWiki this vulnerability is normally prevented on user profiles, except by users with Admin rights. Note that this vulnerability also impacts any extensions that might use passwords stored in xobjects: for those usecases it depends on the right of those pages. There is currently no way to be 100% sure that this vulnerability has been exploited, as an attacker with enough privilege could have deleted the revision where the xobject was deleted after rolling-back the deletion. But again, this operation requires high privileges on the target page (Admin right). A page with a user password xobject which have in its history a revision where the object has been deleted should be considered at risk and the password should be changed there. a diff, to ensure it's not coming from a password field. As another mitigation, admins should ensure that the user pages are properly protected: the edit right shouldn't be allowed for other users than Admin and owner of the profile (which is the default right). There is not much workaround possible for a privileged user other than upgrading XWiki.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31464|2024-07-31T14:35:44.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 18:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31988|2024-07-08T15:17:30.185Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31988</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 13.9-rc-1 and prior to versions 4.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, when the realtime editor is installed in XWiki, it allows arbitrary remote code execution with the interaction of an admin user with programming right. More precisely, by getting an admin user to either visit a crafted URL or to view an image with this URL that could be in a comment, the attacker can get the admin to execute arbitrary XWiki syntax including scripting macros with Groovy or Python code. This compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.4 and 15.9. As a workaround, one may update `RTFrontend.ConvertHTML` manually with the patch. This will, however, break some synchronization processes in the realtime editor, so upgrading should be the preferred way on installations where this editor is used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31988|2024-07-08T15:17:30.185Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37899|2024-07-01T18:34:54.198Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37899</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. When an admin disables a user account, the user's profile is executed with the admin's rights. This allows a user to place malicious code in the user profile before getting an admin to disable the user account. To reproduce, as a user without script nor programming rights, edit the about section of your user profile and add `{{groovy}}services.logging.getLogger("attacker").error("Hello from Groovy!"){{/groovy}}`.
As an admin, go to the user profile and click the "Disable this account" button. Then, reload the page. If the logs show `attacker - Hello from Groovy!` then the instance is vulnerable. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5, 15.10.6 and 16.0.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.

### Workarounds
We're not aware of any workaround except upgrading.

### References
* https://jira.xwiki.org/browse/XWIKI-21611
* https://github.com/xwiki/xwiki-platform/commit/f89c8f47fad6e5cc7e68c69a7e0acde07f5eed5a</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37899|2024-07-01T18:34:54.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 22:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38369|2024-06-24T20:36:42.653Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38369</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. The content of a document included using `{{include reference="targetdocument"/}}` is executed with the right of the includer and not with the right of its author. This means that any user able to modify the target document can impersonate the author of the content which used the `include` macro. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 15.0 RC1 by making the default behavior safe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38369|2024-06-24T20:36:42.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37899|2024-06-20T22:13:59.450Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37899</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. When an admin disables a user account, the user's profile is executed with the admin's rights. This allows a user to place malicious code in the user profile before getting an admin to disable the user account. To reproduce, as a user without script nor programming rights, edit the about section of your user profile and add `{{groovy}}services.logging.getLogger("attacker").error("Hello from Groovy!"){{/groovy}}`.
As an admin, go to the user profile and click the "Disable this account" button. Then, reload the page. If the logs show `attacker - Hello from Groovy!` then the instance is vulnerable. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5, 15.10.6 and 16.0.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.

### Workarounds
We're not aware of any workaround except upgrading.

### References
* https://jira.xwiki.org/browse/XWIKI-21611
* https://github.com/xwiki/xwiki-platform/commit/f89c8f47fad6e5cc7e68c69a7e0acde07f5eed5a</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37899|2024-06-20T22:13:59.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 22:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31986|2024-04-10T20:27:29.600Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31986</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 3.1 and prior to versions 4.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, by creating a document with a special crafted documented reference and an `XWiki.SchedulerJobClass` XObject, it is possible to execute arbitrary code on the server whenever an admin visits the scheduler page or the scheduler page is referenced, e.g., via an image in a comment on a page in the wiki. The vulnerability has been fixed in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.5, and 15.9. As a workaround, apply the patch manually by modifying the `Scheduler.WebHome` page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31986|2024-04-10T20:27:29.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31987|2024-04-10T20:32:39.317Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31987</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 6.4-milestone-1 and prior to versions 4.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, any user who can edit any page like their profile can create a custom skin with a template override that is executed with programming right, thus allowing remote code execution. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.4 and 15.10RC1. No known workarounds are available except for upgrading.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31987|2024-04-10T20:32:39.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31981|2024-04-10T19:22:57.494Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31981</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 3.0.1 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, remote code execution is possible via PDF export templates. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10-rc-1. If PDF templates are not typically used on the instance, an administrator can create the document `XWiki.PDFClass` and block its edition, after making sure that it does not contain a `style` attribute. Otherwise, there are no known workarounds aside from upgrading.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31981|2024-04-10T19:22:57.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31997|2024-04-10T21:55:43.475Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31997</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Prior to versions 4.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, parameters of UI extensions are always interpreted as Velocity code and executed with programming rights. Any user with edit right on any document like the user's own profile can create UI extensions. This allows remote code execution and thereby impacts the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.4 and 15.9-RC1. No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31997|2024-04-10T21:55:43.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 21:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31982|2024-04-10T19:38:01.879Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31982</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 2.4-milestone-1 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, XWiki's database search allows remote code execution through the search text. This allows remote code execution for any visitor of a public wiki or user of a closed wiki as the database search is by default accessible for all users. This impacts the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10RC1. As a workaround, one may manually apply the patch to the page `Main.DatabaseSearch`. Alternatively, unless database search is explicitly used by users, this page can be deleted as this is not the default search interface of XWiki.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31982|2024-04-10T19:38:01.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31465|2024-06-04T17:36:47.631Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31465</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 5.0-rc-1 and prior to versions 14.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.9-rc-1, any user with edit right on any page can execute any code on the server by adding an object of type `XWiki.SearchSuggestSourceClass` to their user profile or any other page. This compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10 RC1. As a workaround, manually apply the patch to the document `XWiki.SearchSuggestSourceSheet`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31465|2024-06-04T17:36:47.631Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31464|2024-04-10T18:14:37.224Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31464</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 5.0-rc-1 and prior to versions 14.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.9-rc-1, it is possible to access the hash of a password by using the diff feature of the history whenever the object storing the password is deleted. Using that vulnerability it's possible for an attacker to have access to the hash password of a user if they have rights to edit the users' page.  With the default right scheme in XWiki this vulnerability is normally prevented on user profiles, except by users with Admin rights. Note that this vulnerability also impacts any extensions that might use passwords stored in xobjects: for those usecases it depends on the right of those pages. There is currently no way to be 100% sure that this vulnerability has been exploited, as an attacker with enough privilege could have deleted the revision where the xobject was deleted after rolling-back the deletion. But again, this operation requires high privileges on the target page (Admin right). A page with a user password xobject which have in its history a revision where the object has been deleted should be considered at risk and the password should be changed there. a diff, to ensure it's not coming from a password field. As another mitigation, admins should ensure that the user pages are properly protected: the edit right shouldn't be allowed for other users than Admin and owner of the profile (which is the default right). There is not much workaround possible for a privileged user other than upgrading XWiki.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31464|2024-04-10T18:14:37.224Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 18:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31983|2024-06-04T17:36:56.997Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31983</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. In multilingual wikis, translations can be edited by any user who has edit right, circumventing the rights that are normally required for authoring translations (script right for user-scope translations, wiki admin for translations on the wiki). Starting in version 4.3-milestone-2 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, this can be exploited for remote code execution if the translation value is not properly escaped where it is used. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10RC1. As a workaround, one may restrict edit rights on documents that contain translations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31983|2024-06-04T17:36:56.997Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31988|2024-04-10T20:40:36.954Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31988</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 13.9-rc-1 and prior to versions 4.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, when the realtime editor is installed in XWiki, it allows arbitrary remote code execution with the interaction of an admin user with programming right. More precisely, by getting an admin user to either visit a crafted URL or to view an image with this URL that could be in a comment, the attacker can get the admin to execute arbitrary XWiki syntax including scripting macros with Groovy or Python code. This compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.4 and 15.9. As a workaround, one may update `RTFrontend.ConvertHTML` manually with the patch. This will, however, break some synchronization processes in the realtime editor, so upgrading should be the preferred way on installations where this editor is used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31988|2024-04-10T20:40:36.954Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31984|2024-04-10T20:11:03.857Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31984</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 7.2-rc-1 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, by creating a document with a specially crafted title, it is possible to trigger remote code execution in the (Solr-based) search in XWiki. This allows any user who can edit the title of a space (all users by default) to execute any Groovy code in the XWiki installation which compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10 RC1. As a workaround, manually apply the patch to the `Main.SolrSpaceFacet` page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31984|2024-04-10T20:11:03.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31985|2024-06-04T17:37:18.406Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31985</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 3.1 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, it is possible to schedule/trigger/unschedule existing jobs by having an admin visit the Job Scheduler page through a predictable URL, for example by embedding such an URL in any content as an image. The vulnerability has been fixed in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.5, and 15.9. As a workaround, manually apply the patch by modifying the `Scheduler.WebHome` page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31985|2024-06-04T17:37:18.406Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38369|2024-06-24T16:39:37.695Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38369</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. The content of a document included using `{{include reference="targetdocument"/}}` is executed with the right of the includer and not with the right of its author. This means that any user able to modify the target document can impersonate the author of the content which used the `include` macro. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 15.0 RC1 by making the default behavior safe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38369|2024-06-24T16:39:37.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31981|2024-06-26T17:36:02.483Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31981</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 3.0.1 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, remote code execution is possible via PDF export templates. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10-rc-1. If PDF templates are not typically used on the instance, an administrator can create the document `XWiki.PDFClass` and block its edition, after making sure that it does not contain a `style` attribute. Otherwise, there are no known workarounds aside from upgrading.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31981|2024-06-26T17:36:02.483Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31984|2024-07-05T12:48:25.074Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31984</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 7.2-rc-1 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, by creating a document with a specially crafted title, it is possible to trigger remote code execution in the (Solr-based) search in XWiki. This allows any user who can edit the title of a space (all users by default) to execute any Groovy code in the XWiki installation which compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10 RC1. As a workaround, manually apply the patch to the `Main.SolrSpaceFacet` page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31984|2024-07-05T12:48:25.074Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31986|2024-07-19T21:06:21.946Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31986</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 3.1 and prior to versions 4.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, by creating a document with a special crafted documented reference and an `XWiki.SchedulerJobClass` XObject, it is possible to execute arbitrary code on the server whenever an admin visits the scheduler page or the scheduler page is referenced, e.g., via an image in a comment on a page in the wiki. The vulnerability has been fixed in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.5, and 15.9. As a workaround, apply the patch manually by modifying the `Scheduler.WebHome` page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31986|2024-07-19T21:06:21.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37901|2024-07-31T15:19:36.588Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37901</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. Any user with edit right on any page can perform arbitrary remote code execution by adding instances of `XWiki.SearchSuggestConfig` and `XWiki.SearchSuggestSourceClass` to their user profile or any other page. This compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5 and 15.10.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37901|2024-07-31T15:19:36.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37898|2024-07-31T15:12:22.468Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37898</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. When a user has view but not edit right on a page in XWiki, that user can delete the page and replace it by a page with new content without having delete right. The previous version of the page is moved into the recycle bin and can be restored from there by an admin. As the user is recorded as deleter, the user would in theory also be able to view the deleted content, but this is not directly possible as rights of the previous version are transferred to the new page and thus the user still doesn't have view right on the page. It therefore doesn't seem to be possible to exploit this to gain any rights. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5 and 15.10.6 by cancelling save operations by users when a new document shall be saved despite the document's existing already.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37898|2024-07-31T15:12:22.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-41947|2024-07-31T15:58:35.101Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41947</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. By creating a conflict when another user with more rights is currently editing a page, it is possible to execute JavaScript snippets on the side of the other user, which compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This has been patched in XWiki 15.10.8 and 16.3.0RC1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-41947|2024-07-31T15:58:35.101Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37900|2024-07-31T15:15:31.013Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37900</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. When uploading an attachment with a malicious filename, malicious JavaScript code could be executed. This requires a social engineering attack to get the victim into uploading a file with a malicious name. The malicious code is solely executed during the upload and affects only the user uploading the attachment. While this allows performing actions in the name of that user, it seems unlikely that a user wouldn't notice the malicious filename while uploading the attachment. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5, 15.10.6 and 16.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37900|2024-07-31T15:15:31.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37900|2024-08-01T14:50:10.293Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37900</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. When uploading an attachment with a malicious filename, malicious JavaScript code could be executed. This requires a social engineering attack to get the victim into uploading a file with a malicious name. The malicious code is solely executed during the upload and affects only the user uploading the attachment. While this allows performing actions in the name of that user, it seems unlikely that a user wouldn't notice the malicious filename while uploading the attachment. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5, 15.10.6 and 16.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37900|2024-08-01T14:50:10.293Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31985|2024-08-02T01:59:50.770Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31985</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 3.1 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, it is possible to schedule/trigger/unschedule existing jobs by having an admin visit the Job Scheduler page through a predictable URL, for example by embedding such an URL in any content as an image. The vulnerability has been fixed in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.5, and 15.9. As a workaround, manually apply the patch by modifying the `Scheduler.WebHome` page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31985|2024-08-02T01:59:50.770Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31981|2024-08-02T01:59:50.691Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31981</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 3.0.1 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, remote code execution is possible via PDF export templates. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10-rc-1. If PDF templates are not typically used on the instance, an administrator can create the document `XWiki.PDFClass` and block its edition, after making sure that it does not contain a `style` attribute. Otherwise, there are no known workarounds aside from upgrading.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31981|2024-08-02T01:59:50.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31464|2024-08-02T01:52:57.144Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31464</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 5.0-rc-1 and prior to versions 14.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.9-rc-1, it is possible to access the hash of a password by using the diff feature of the history whenever the object storing the password is deleted. Using that vulnerability it's possible for an attacker to have access to the hash password of a user if they have rights to edit the users' page.  With the default right scheme in XWiki this vulnerability is normally prevented on user profiles, except by users with Admin rights. Note that this vulnerability also impacts any extensions that might use passwords stored in xobjects: for those usecases it depends on the right of those pages. There is currently no way to be 100% sure that this vulnerability has been exploited, as an attacker with enough privilege could have deleted the revision where the xobject was deleted after rolling-back the deletion. But again, this operation requires high privileges on the target page (Admin right). A page with a user password xobject which have in its history a revision where the object has been deleted should be considered at risk and the password should be changed there. a diff, to ensure it's not coming from a password field. As another mitigation, admins should ensure that the user pages are properly protected: the edit right shouldn't be allowed for other users than Admin and owner of the profile (which is the default right). There is not much workaround possible for a privileged user other than upgrading XWiki.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31464|2024-08-02T01:52:57.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 18:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31997|2024-08-02T01:59:50.826Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31997</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Prior to versions 4.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, parameters of UI extensions are always interpreted as Velocity code and executed with programming rights. Any user with edit right on any document like the user's own profile can create UI extensions. This allows remote code execution and thereby impacts the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.4 and 15.9-RC1. No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31997|2024-08-02T01:59:50.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 21:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31986|2024-08-02T01:59:50.842Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31986</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 3.1 and prior to versions 4.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, by creating a document with a special crafted documented reference and an `XWiki.SchedulerJobClass` XObject, it is possible to execute arbitrary code on the server whenever an admin visits the scheduler page or the scheduler page is referenced, e.g., via an image in a comment on a page in the wiki. The vulnerability has been fixed in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.5, and 15.9. As a workaround, apply the patch manually by modifying the `Scheduler.WebHome` page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31986|2024-08-02T01:59:50.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31988|2024-08-02T01:59:50.859Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31988</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 13.9-rc-1 and prior to versions 4.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, when the realtime editor is installed in XWiki, it allows arbitrary remote code execution with the interaction of an admin user with programming right. More precisely, by getting an admin user to either visit a crafted URL or to view an image with this URL that could be in a comment, the attacker can get the admin to execute arbitrary XWiki syntax including scripting macros with Groovy or Python code. This compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.4 and 15.9. As a workaround, one may update `RTFrontend.ConvertHTML` manually with the patch. This will, however, break some synchronization processes in the realtime editor, so upgrading should be the preferred way on installations where this editor is used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31988|2024-08-02T01:59:50.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31465|2024-08-02T01:52:57.115Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31465</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 5.0-rc-1 and prior to versions 14.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.9-rc-1, any user with edit right on any page can execute any code on the server by adding an object of type `XWiki.SearchSuggestSourceClass` to their user profile or any other page. This compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10 RC1. As a workaround, manually apply the patch to the document `XWiki.SearchSuggestSourceSheet`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31465|2024-08-02T01:52:57.115Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31983|2024-08-02T01:59:50.829Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31983</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. In multilingual wikis, translations can be edited by any user who has edit right, circumventing the rights that are normally required for authoring translations (script right for user-scope translations, wiki admin for translations on the wiki). Starting in version 4.3-milestone-2 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, this can be exploited for remote code execution if the translation value is not properly escaped where it is used. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10RC1. As a workaround, one may restrict edit rights on documents that contain translations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31983|2024-08-02T01:59:50.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31982|2024-08-02T01:59:50.834Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31982</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 2.4-milestone-1 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, XWiki's database search allows remote code execution through the search text. This allows remote code execution for any visitor of a public wiki or user of a closed wiki as the database search is by default accessible for all users. This impacts the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10RC1. As a workaround, one may manually apply the patch to the page `Main.DatabaseSearch`. Alternatively, unless database search is explicitly used by users, this page can be deleted as this is not the default search interface of XWiki.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31982|2024-08-02T01:59:50.834Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31984|2024-08-02T01:59:50.883Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31984</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 7.2-rc-1 and prior to versions 4.10.20, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, by creating a document with a specially crafted title, it is possible to trigger remote code execution in the (Solr-based) search in XWiki. This allows any user who can edit the title of a space (all users by default) to execute any Groovy code in the XWiki installation which compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.20, 15.5.4 and 15.10 RC1. As a workaround, manually apply the patch to the `Main.SolrSpaceFacet` page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31984|2024-08-02T01:59:50.883Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31987|2024-08-02T01:59:50.698Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31987</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. Starting in version 6.4-milestone-1 and prior to versions 4.10.19, 15.5.4, and 15.10-rc-1, any user who can edit any page like their profile can create a custom skin with a template override that is executed with programming right, thus allowing remote code execution. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.19, 15.5.4 and 15.10RC1. No known workarounds are available except for upgrading.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31987|2024-08-02T01:59:50.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-41947|2024-08-12T20:05:28.337Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41947</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. By creating a conflict when another user with more rights is currently editing a page, it is possible to execute JavaScript snippets on the side of the other user, which compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This has been patched in XWiki 15.10.8 and 16.3.0RC1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-41947|2024-08-12T20:05:28.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-43401|2024-08-19T16:24:29.698Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43401</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. A user without script/programming right can trick a user with elevated rights to edit a content with a malicious payload using a WYSIWYG editor. The user with elevated rights is not warned beforehand that they are going to edit possibly dangerous content. The payload is executed at edit time. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 15.10RC1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-43401|2024-08-19T16:24:29.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-43400|2024-08-19T16:24:40.900Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43400</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. It is possible for a user without Script or Programming rights to craft a URL pointing to a page with arbitrary JavaScript. This requires social engineer to trick a user to follow the URL. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5, 15.10.6 and 16.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-43400|2024-08-19T16:24:40.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-43400|2024-08-20T16:00:37.079Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43400</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. It is possible for a user without Script or Programming rights to craft a URL pointing to a page with arbitrary JavaScript. This requires social engineer to trick a user to follow the URL. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5, 15.10.6 and 16.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-43400|2024-08-20T16:00:37.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-43401|2024-08-21T14:23:29.403Z -- xwiki -- xwiki-platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43401</link>
      <description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. A user without script/programming right can trick a user with elevated rights to edit a content with a malicious payload using a WYSIWYG editor. The user with elevated rights is not warned beforehand that they are going to edit possibly dangerous content. The payload is executed at edit time. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 15.10RC1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-43401|2024-08-21T14:23:29.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
