<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for DEMON1A -- Discord-Recon</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/demon1a/discord-recon.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for DEMON1A -- Discord-Recon</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29466|2024-08-03T22:11:05.521Z -- demon1a -- discord-recon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29466</link>
      <description>Discord-Recon is a bot for the Discord chat service. In versions of Discord-Recon 0.0.3 and prior, a remote attacker is able to read local files from the server that can disclose important information. As a workaround, a bot maintainer can locate the file `app.py` and add `.replace('..', '')` into the `Path` variable inside of the `recon` function. The vulnerability is patched in version 0.0.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29466|2024-08-03T22:11:05.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29461|2024-08-03T22:02:51.928Z -- demon1a -- discord-recon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29461</link>
      <description>Discord Recon Server is a bot that allows one to do one's reconnaissance process from one's Discord. A vulnerability in Discord Recon Server prior to 0.0.3 could be exploited to read internal files from the system and write files into the system resulting in remote code execution. This issue has been fixed in version 0.0.3. As a workaround, one may copy the code from `assets/CommandInjection.py` in the Discord Recon Server code repository and overwrite vulnerable code from one's own Discord Recon Server implementation with code that contains the patch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29461|2024-08-03T22:02:51.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 19:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29465|2024-08-03T22:11:05.365Z -- demon1a -- discord-recon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29465</link>
      <description>Discord-Recon is a bot for the Discord chat service. Versions of Discord-Recon 0.0.3 and prior contain a vulnerability in which a remote attacker is able to overwrite any file on the system with the command results. This can result in remote code execution when the user overwrite important files on the system. As a workaround, bot maintainers can edit their `setting.py` file then add `&lt;` and `&gt;` into the `RCE` variable inside of it to fix the issue without an update. The vulnerability is patched in version 0.0.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29465|2024-08-03T22:11:05.365Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21433|2024-08-03T18:16:22.283Z -- demon1a -- discord-recon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21433</link>
      <description>Discord Recon Server is a bot that allows you to do your reconnaissance process from your Discord. Remote code execution in version 0.0.1 would allow remote users to execute commands on the server resulting in serious issues. This flaw is patched in 0.0.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21433|2024-08-03T18:16:22.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 17:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
