<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for avo-hq -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/avo-hq/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for avo-hq -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34102|2023-06-05T22:16:43.861Z -- avo-hq -- avo
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34102</link>
      <description>Avo is an open source ruby on rails admin panel creation framework. The polymorphic field type stores the classes to operate on when updating a record with user input, and does not validate them in the back end. This can lead to unexpected behavior, remote code execution, or application crashes when viewing a manipulated record. This issue has been addressed in commit `ec117882d` which is expected to be included in subsequent releases. Users are advised to limit access to untrusted users until a new release is made.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34102|2023-06-05T22:16:43.861Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 22:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34103|2023-06-05T22:13:21.458Z -- avo-hq -- avo
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34103</link>
      <description>Avo is an open source ruby on rails admin panel creation framework. In affected versions some avo fields are vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) when rendering html based content. Attackers do need form edit privilege in order to successfully exploit this vulnerability, but the results are stored and no specific timing is required. This issue has been addressed in commit `7891c01e` which is expected to be included in the next release of avo. Users are advised to configure CSP headers for their application and to limit untrusted user access as a mitigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34103|2023-06-05T22:13:21.458Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 22:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22411|2024-01-19T17:24:40.497Z -- avo-hq -- avo
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22411</link>
      <description>Avo is a framework to create admin panels for Ruby on Rails apps. In Avo 3 pre12, any HTML inside text that is passed to `error` or `succeed` in an `Avo::BaseAction` subclass will be rendered directly without sanitization in the toast/notification that appears in the UI on Action completion. A malicious user could exploit this vulnerability to trigger a cross site scripting attack on an unsuspecting user. This issue has been addressed in the 3.3.0 and 2.47.0 releases of Avo. Users are advised to upgrade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22411|2024-01-19T17:24:40.497Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22191|2024-01-18T15:13:57.372Z -- avo-hq -- avo
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22191</link>
      <description>Avo is a framework to create admin panels for Ruby on Rails apps. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in the key_value field of Avo v3.2.3 and v2.46.0. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim's browser. The value of the key_value is inserted directly into the HTML code. In the current version of Avo (possibly also older versions), the value is not properly sanitized before it is inserted into the HTML code. This vulnerability could be used to steal sensitive information from victims that could be used to hijack victims' accounts or redirect them to malicious websites. Avo 3.2.4 and 2.47.0 include a fix for this issue. Users are advised to upgrade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22191|2024-01-18T15:13:57.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:57:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
