<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for avo-hq -- avo</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/avo-hq/avo.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for avo-hq -- avo</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:20:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34103|2024-08-02T16:01:54.127Z -- avo-hq -- avo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34103</link>
      <description>Avo is an open source ruby on rails admin panel creation framework. In affected versions some avo fields are vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) when rendering html based content. Attackers do need form edit privilege in order to successfully exploit this vulnerability, but the results are stored and no specific timing is required. This issue has been addressed in commit `7891c01e` which is expected to be included in the next release of avo. Users are advised to configure CSP headers for their application and to limit untrusted user access as a mitigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34103|2024-08-02T16:01:54.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 22:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34102|2024-08-02T16:01:54.061Z -- avo-hq -- avo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34102</link>
      <description>Avo is an open source ruby on rails admin panel creation framework. The polymorphic field type stores the classes to operate on when updating a record with user input, and does not validate them in the back end. This can lead to unexpected behavior, remote code execution, or application crashes when viewing a manipulated record. This issue has been addressed in commit `ec117882d` which is expected to be included in subsequent releases. Users are advised to limit access to untrusted users until a new release is made.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34102|2024-08-02T16:01:54.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 22:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
