<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for migrate -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/migrate/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for migrate -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:23:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0958|2024-08-02T05:32:46.051Z -- migrate -- backup%20migration
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0958</link>
      <description>Several plugins for WordPress by Inisev are vulnerable to unauthorized installation of plugins due to a missing capability check on the handle_installation function that is called via the inisev_installation AJAX aciton in various versions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with minimal permissions, such as subscribers, to install select plugins from Inisev on vulnerable sites. CVE-2023-38514 appears to be a duplicate of this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0958|2024-08-02T05:32:46.051Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 04:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6971|2024-08-02T08:50:06.712Z -- migrate -- backup%20migration
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6971</link>
      <description>The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote File Inclusion in versions 1.0.8 to 1.3.9 via the 'content-dir' HTTP header. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include remote files on the server, resulting in code execution. NOTE: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires that the target server's php.ini is configured with 'allow_url_include' set to 'on'. This feature is deprecated as of PHP 7.4 and is disabled by default, but can still be explicitly enabled in later versions of PHP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6971|2024-08-02T08:50:06.712Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 01:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6266|2024-08-02T08:28:20.189Z -- migrate -- backup%20migration
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6266</link>
      <description>The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to insufficient path and file validation on the BMI_BACKUP case of the handle_downloading function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download back-up files which can contain sensitive information such as user passwords, PII,  database credentials, and much more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6266|2024-08-02T08:28:20.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6553|2024-08-02T08:35:14.821Z -- migrate -- backup%20migration
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6553</link>
      <description>The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.7 via the /includes/backup-heart.php file. This is due to an attacker being able to control the values passed to an include, and subsequently leverage that to achieve remote code execution. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to easily execute code on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6553|2024-08-02T08:35:14.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 10:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6972|2024-08-02T08:50:06.839Z -- migrate -- backup%20migration
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6972</link>
      <description>The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.9 via the 'content-backups' and 'content-name', 'content-manifest', or 'content-bmitmp' and 'content-identy' HTTP headers. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files, including the wp-config.php file, which can make site takeover and remote code execution possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6972|2024-08-02T08:50:06.839Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 01:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7002|2024-08-02T08:50:07.660Z -- migrate -- backup%20migration
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7002</link>
      <description>The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to OS Command Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.9  via the 'url' parameter. This vulnerability allows authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to execute arbitrary commands on the host operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7002|2024-08-02T08:50:07.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 01:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3977|2024-08-02T07:08:50.857Z -- migrate -- backup%20migration
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3977</link>
      <description>Several plugins for WordPress by Inisev are vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery to unauthorized installation of plugins due to a missing nonce check on the handle_installation function that is called via the inisev_installation AJAX aciton in various versions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to install plugins from the limited list via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3977|2024-08-02T07:08:50.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 04:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
