<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Unified Automation -- UaGateway</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/unified%20automation/uagateway.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Unified Automation -- UaGateway</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 22:22:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32171|2024-06-05T19:43:35.903Z -- unified%20automation -- uagateway</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32171</link>
      <description>Unified Automation UaGateway OPC UA Server Null Pointer Dereference Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Unified Automation UaGateway. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the ImportCsv method. A crafted XML payload can cause a null pointer dereference. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-20495.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32171|2024-06-05T19:43:35.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41185|2024-05-03T02:11:46.261Z -- unified%20automation -- uagateway</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41185</link>
      <description>Unified Automation UaGateway Certificate Parsing Integer Overflow Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Unified Automation UaGateway. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of client certificates. When parsing the certificate length field, the process does not properly validate user-supplied data, which can result in an integer overflow. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-20353.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41185|2024-05-03T02:11:46.261Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
