<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Uniview -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/uniview/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Uniview -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0773|2023-09-19T09:33:42.479Z -- uniview -- uniview%20ip%20camera%20ipc322lb-sf28-a
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0773</link>
      <description>The vulnerability exists in Uniview IP Camera due to identification and authentication failure at its web-based management interface. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specially crafted HTTP requests to the vulnerable device.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to gain complete control of the targeted device.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0773|2023-09-19T09:33:42.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 09:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0778|2024-01-22T16:00:06.512Z -- uniview -- isc%202500-s
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0778</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Uniview ISC 2500-S up to 20210930. Affected by this issue is the function setNatConfig of the file /Interface/DevManage/VM.php. The manipulation of the argument natAddress/natPort/natServerPort leads to os command injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251696. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Uniview ISC 2500-S bis 20210930 entdeckt. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion setNatConfig der Datei /Interface/DevManage/VM.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments natAddress/natPort/natServerPort mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0778|2024-01-22T16:00:06.512Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 16:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3850|2024-06-10T16:46:42.766Z -- uniview -- nvr301-04s2-p4
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3850</link>
      <description>Uniview NVR301-04S2-P4 is vulnerable to reflected cross-site scripting attack (XSS). An attacker could send a user a URL that if clicked on could execute malicious JavaScript in their browser. This vulnerability also requires authentication before it can be exploited, so the scope and severity is limited. Also, even if JavaScript is executed, no additional benefits are obtained.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3850|2024-06-10T16:46:42.766Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
