<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Hikvision -- Intercom Broadcasting System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/hikvision/intercom%20broadcasting%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Hikvision -- Intercom Broadcasting System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:24:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6895|2024-08-02T08:42:08.393Z -- hikvision -- intercom%20broadcasting%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6895</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Hikvision Intercom Broadcasting System 3.0.3_20201113_RELEASE(HIK). It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /php/ping.php. The manipulation of the argument jsondata[ip] with the input netstat -ano leads to os command injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.1.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-248254 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Hikvision Intercom Broadcasting System 3.0.3_20201113_RELEASE(HIK) wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /php/ping.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments jsondata[ip] mit der Eingabe netstat -ano mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 4.1.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6895|2024-08-02T08:42:08.393Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 08:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6894|2024-08-02T08:42:08.429Z -- hikvision -- intercom%20broadcasting%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6894</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Hikvision Intercom Broadcasting System 3.0.3_20201113_RELEASE(HIK). It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file access/html/system.html of the component Log File Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.1.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-248253 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Hikvision Intercom Broadcasting System 3.0.3_20201113_RELEASE(HIK) ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei access/html/system.html der Komponente Log File Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 4.1.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6894|2024-08-02T08:42:08.429Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 07:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6893|2024-08-02T08:42:08.394Z -- hikvision -- intercom%20broadcasting%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6893</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Hikvision Intercom Broadcasting System 3.0.3_20201113_RELEASE(HIK) and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /php/exportrecord.php. The manipulation of the argument downname with the input C:\ICPAS\Wnmp\WWW\php\conversion.php leads to path traversal. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.1.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248252.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Hikvision Intercom Broadcasting System 3.0.3_20201113_RELEASE(HIK) gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /php/exportrecord.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments downname mit der Eingabe C:\ICPAS\Wnmp\WWW\php\conversion.php mit unbekannten Daten kann eine path traversal-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 4.1.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6893|2024-08-02T08:42:08.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 06:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
