<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for aprokopenko -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/aprokopenko/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for aprokopenko -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 09:22:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6168|2024-07-09T08:33:09.117Z -- aprokopenko -- just%20custom%20fields
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6168</link>
      <description>The Just Custom Fields plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on several AJAX function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to invoke this functionality intended for admin users via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. This enables subscribers to manage field groups, change visibility of items among other things.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6168|2024-07-09T08:33:09.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 08:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6167|2024-07-09T08:33:02.369Z -- aprokopenko -- just%20custom%20fields
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6167</link>
      <description>The Just Custom Fields plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of functionality due to a missing capability check on several AJAX functions in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to invoke this functionality intended for admin users. This enables subscribers to manage field groups, change visibility of items among other things.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6167|2024-07-09T08:33:02.369Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 08:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
