<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for jeecgboot -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/jeecgboot/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for jeecgboot -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 13:24:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4450|2024-08-02T07:24:04.986Z -- jeecgboot -- jimureport
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4450</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in jeecgboot JimuReport up to 1.6.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Template Handler. The manipulation leads to injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.6.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-237571.
In jeecgboot JimuReport bis 1.6.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Komponente Template Handler. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.6.1 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4450|2024-08-02T07:24:04.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 02:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6307|2024-08-02T08:28:21.356Z -- jeecgboot -- jimureport
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6307</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in jeecgboot JimuReport up to 1.6.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /download/image. The manipulation of the argument imageUrl leads to relative path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-246133 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In jeecgboot JimuReport bis 1.6.1 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /download/image. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments imageUrl mit unbekannten Daten kann eine relative path traversal-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6307|2024-08-02T08:28:21.356Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 01:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
