<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SAP -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sap/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SAP -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 16:24:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41262|2024-08-03T12:42:43.970Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20for%20java%20%28http%20provider%20service%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41262</link>
      <description>Due to insufficient input validation, SAP NetWeaver AS Java (HTTP Provider Service) - version 7.50, allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject a script into a web request header. On successful exploitation, an attacker can view or modify information causing a limited impact on the confidentiality and integrity of the application.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41262|2024-08-03T12:42:43.970Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 21:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41261|2024-08-03T12:42:43.976Z -- sap -- solution%20manager%20%28diagnostic%20agent%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41261</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager (Diagnostic Agent) - version 7.20, allows an authenticated attacker on Windows system to access a file containing sensitive data which can be used to access a configuration file which contains credentials to access other system files. Successful exploitation can make the attacker access files and systems for which he/she is not authorized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41261|2024-08-03T12:42:43.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 21:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41267|2024-08-03T12:42:44.072Z -- sap -- businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41267</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Platform - versions 420, and 430, allows an attacker with normal BI user privileges to upload/replace any file on Business Objects server at the operating system level, enabling the attacker to take full control of the system causing a high impact on confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41267|2024-08-03T12:42:44.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 02:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41272|2024-08-03T12:42:43.986Z -- sap -- netweaver%20process%20integration
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41272</link>
      <description>An unauthenticated attacker over the network can attach to an open interface exposed through JNDI by the User Defined Search (UDS) of SAP NetWeaver Process Integration (PI) - version 7.50 and make use of an open naming and directory API to access services which can be used to perform unauthorized operations affecting users and data across the entire system. This allows the attacker to have full read access to user data, make limited modifications to user data, and degrade the performance of the system, leading to a high impact on confidentiality and a limited impact on the availability and integrity of the application.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41272|2024-08-03T12:42:43.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 03:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41263|2024-08-03T12:42:44.077Z -- sap -- business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20intelligence%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41263</link>
      <description>Due to a missing authentication check, SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence) - versions 420, 430, allows an authenticated non-administrator attacker to modify the data source information for a document that is otherwise restricted. On successful exploitation, the attacker can modify information causing a limited impact on the integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41263|2024-08-03T12:42:44.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 21:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41275|2024-08-03T12:42:45.882Z -- sap -- solution%20manager%20%28enterprise%20search%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41275</link>
      <description>In SAP Solution Manager (Enterprise Search) - versions 740, and 750, an unauthenticated attacker can generate a link that, if clicked by a logged-in user, can be redirected to a malicious page that could read or modify sensitive information, or expose the user to a phishing attack, with little impact on confidentiality and integrity.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41275|2024-08-03T12:42:45.882Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41271|2024-08-03T12:42:43.981Z -- sap -- netweaver%20process%20integration
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41271</link>
      <description>An unauthenticated user can attach to an open interface exposed through JNDI by the Messaging System of SAP NetWeaver Process Integration (PI) - version 7.50. This user can make use of an open naming and directory API to access services that could perform unauthorized operations. The vulnerability affects local users and data, leading to a considerable impact on confidentiality as well as availability and a limited impact on the integrity of the application. These operations can be used to:

  *  Read any information
  *  Modify sensitive information
  *  Denial of Service attacks (DoS)
  *  SQL Injection




</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41271|2024-08-03T12:42:43.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 02:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31596|2024-08-03T07:25:59.498Z -- sap -- sap%20business%20objects%20platform%20%28monitoring%20db%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31596</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, an attacker authenticated as a CMS administrator and with high privileges access to the Network in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Monitoring DB) - version 430, can access BOE Monitoring database to retrieve and modify (non-personal) system data which would otherwise be restricted. Also, a potential attack could be used to leave the CMS's scope and impact the database. 



A successful attack could have a low impact on confidentiality, a high impact on integrity, and a low impact on availability.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31596|2024-08-03T07:25:59.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 03:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41264|2024-08-03T12:42:44.052Z -- sap -- basis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41264</link>
      <description>Due to the unrestricted scope of the RFC function module, SAP BASIS - versions 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 757, 789, 790, 791, allows an authenticated non-administrator attacker to access a system class and execute any of its public methods with parameters provided by the attacker. On successful exploitation the attacker can have full control of the system to which the class belongs, causing a high impact on the integrity of the application.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41264|2024-08-03T12:42:44.052Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 02:27:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41266|2024-08-03T12:42:44.067Z -- sap -- commerce%20webservices%202.0%20%28swagger%20ui%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41266</link>
      <description>Due to a lack of proper input validation, SAP Commerce Webservices 2.0 (Swagger UI) - versions 1905, 2005, 2105, 2011, 2205, allows malicious inputs from untrusted sources, which can be leveraged by an attacker to execute a DOM Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack.  As a result, an attacker may be able to steal user tokens and achieve a full account takeover including access to administrative tools in SAP Commerce.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41266|2024-08-03T12:42:44.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 02:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41273|2024-08-03T12:42:43.986Z -- sap -- sourcing%20and%20sap%20contract%20lifecycle%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41273</link>
      <description>Due to improper input sanitization in SAP Sourcing and SAP Contract Lifecycle Management - version 1100, an attacker can redirect a user to a malicious website. In order to perform this attack, the attacker sends an email to the victim with a manipulated link that appears to be a legitimate SAP Sourcing URL, since the victim doesn’t suspect the threat, they click on the link, log in to SAP Sourcing and CLM and at this point, they get redirected to a malicious website.            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41273|2024-08-03T12:42:43.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 03:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41274|2024-08-03T12:42:44.061Z -- sap -- disclosure%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41274</link>
      <description>SAP Disclosure Management - version 10.1, allows an authenticated attacker to exploit certain misconfigured application endpoints to read sensitive data. These endpoints are normally exposed over the network and successful exploitation can lead to the exposure of data like financial reports.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41274|2024-08-03T12:42:44.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 03:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41268|2024-08-03T12:42:43.986Z -- sap -- business%20planning%20and%20consolidation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41268</link>
      <description>In some SAP standard roles in SAP Business Planning and Consolidation - versions - SAP_BW 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 757, DWCORE 200, 300, CPMBPC 810, a transaction code reserved for the customer is used. By implementing such transaction code, a malicious user may execute unauthorized transaction functionality. Under specific circumstances, a successful attack could enable an adversary to escalate their privileges to be able to read, change or delete system data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41268|2024-08-03T12:42:43.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 02:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
