<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SAP -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sap/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SAP -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:22:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29109|2024-08-02T14:00:15.862Z -- sap -- application%20interface%20framework%20%28message%20dashboard%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29109</link>
      <description>The SAP Application Interface Framework (Message Dashboard) - versions AIF 703, AIFX 702, S4CORE 101, SAP_BASIS 755, 756, SAP_ABA 75C, 75D, 75E, application allows an Excel formula injection. An authorized attacker can inject arbitrary Excel formulas into fields like the Tooltip of the Custom Hints List. Once the victim opens the downloaded Excel document, the formula will be executed. As a result, an attacker can cause limited impact on the confidentiality and integrity of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29109|2024-08-02T14:00:15.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 02:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27896|2024-08-02T12:23:30.578Z -- sap -- businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20services%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27896</link>
      <description>In SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform - version 420, 430, an attacker can control a malicious BOE server, forcing the application server to connect to its own CMS, leading to a high impact on availability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27896|2024-08-02T12:23:30.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 05:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29186|2024-08-02T14:00:15.983Z -- sap -- netweaver%20%28bi%20cont%20addon%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29186</link>
      <description>In SAP NetWeaver (BI CONT ADDON) - versions 707, 737, 747, 757, an attacker can exploit a directory traversal flaw in a report to upload and overwrite files on the SAP server. Data cannot be read but if a remote attacker has sufficient (administrative) privileges then potentially critical OS files can be overwritten making the system unavailable.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29186|2024-08-02T14:00:15.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 03:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25617|2024-08-02T11:25:19.328Z -- sap -- business%20objects%20%28adaptive%20job%20server%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25617</link>
      <description>SAP Business Object (Adaptive Job Server) - versions 420, 430, allows remote execution of arbitrary commands on Unix, when program objects execution is enabled, to authenticated users with scheduling rights, using the BI Launchpad, Central Management Console or a custom application based on the public java SDK. Programs could impact the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25617|2024-08-02T11:25:19.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 04:42:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26457|2024-08-02T11:53:53.766Z -- sap -- content%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26457</link>
      <description>SAP Content Server - version 7.53, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. After successful exploitation, an attacker can read and modify some sensitive information but cannot delete the data.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26457|2024-08-02T11:53:53.766Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 04:53:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25615|2024-08-02T11:25:19.251Z -- sap -- abap%C2%A0platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25615</link>
      <description>Due to insufficient input sanitization, SAP ABAP - versions 751, 753, 753, 754, 756, 757, 791, allows an authenticated high privileged user to alter the current session of the user by injecting the malicious database queries over the network and gain access to the unintended data. This may lead to a high impact on the confidentiality and no impact on the availability and integrity of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25615|2024-08-02T11:25:19.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 04:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29111|2024-08-02T14:00:14.938Z -- sap -- application%20interface%20framework%20%28odata%20service%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29111</link>
      <description>The SAP AIF (ODATA service) - versions 755, 756, discloses more detailed information than is required. An authorized attacker can use the collected information possibly to exploit the component. As a result, an attacker can cause a low impact on the confidentiality of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29111|2024-08-02T14:00:14.938Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 03:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23851|2024-08-02T10:42:26.843Z -- sap -- business%20planning%20and%20consolidation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23851</link>
      <description>SAP Business Planning and Consolidation - versions 200, 300, allows an attacker with business authorization to upload any files (including web pages) without the proper file format validation. If other users visit the uploaded malicious web page, the attacker may perform actions on behalf of the users without their consent impacting the confidentiality and integrity of the system.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23851|2024-08-02T10:42:26.843Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0022|2024-08-02T04:54:32.575Z -- sap -- businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28analysis%20edition%20for%20olap%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0022</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Analysis edition for OLAP allows an authenticated attacker to inject malicious code that can be executed by the application over the network. On successful exploitation, an attacker can perform operations that may completely compromise the application causing a high impact on the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0022|2024-08-02T04:54:32.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 03:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23859|2024-08-02T10:42:27.061Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23859</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS for ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 757, 789, 790, allows an unauthenticated attacker to craft a malicious link, which when clicked by an unsuspecting user, can be used to read or modify some sensitive information.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23859|2024-08-02T10:42:27.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26461|2024-08-02T11:53:52.901Z -- sap -- netweaver%20%28sap%20enterprise%20portal%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26461</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver allows (SAP Enterprise Portal) - version 7.50, allows an authenticated attacker with sufficient privileges to access the XML parser which can submit a crafted XML file which when parsed will enable them to access but not modify sensitive files and data. It allows the attacker to view sensitive data which is owned by certain privileges.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26461|2024-08-02T11:53:52.901Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 04:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24527|2024-08-02T10:56:04.429Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20java%20for%20deploy%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24527</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS Java for Deploy Service - version 7.5, does not perform any access control checks for functionalities that require user identity enabling an unauthenticated attacker to attach to an open interface and make use of an open naming and directory API to access a service which will enable them to access but not modify server settings and data with no effect on availability and integrity.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24527|2024-08-02T10:56:04.429Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 02:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26460|2024-08-02T11:53:53.988Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20for%20java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26460</link>
      <description>Cache Management Service in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for Java - version 7.50, does not perform any authentication checks for functionalities that require user identity

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26460|2024-08-02T11:53:53.988Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 04:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24528|2024-08-02T10:56:04.225Z -- sap -- fiori%20apps%201.0%20for%20travel%20management%20in%20sap%20erp%20%28my%20travel%20requests%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24528</link>
      <description>SAP Fiori apps for Travel Management in SAP ERP (My Travel Requests) - version 600,  allows an authenticated attacker to exploit a certain misconfigured application endpoint to view sensitive data. This endpoint is normally exposed over the network and successful exploitation can lead to exposure of data like travel documents.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24528|2024-08-02T10:56:04.225Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0023|2024-08-02T04:54:32.614Z -- sap -- bank%20account%20management%20%28manage%20banks%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0023</link>
      <description>In SAP Bank Account Management (Manage Banks) application, when a user clicks a smart link to navigate to another app, personal data is shown directly in the URL. They might get captured in log files, bookmarks, and so on disclosing sensitive data of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0023|2024-08-02T04:54:32.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 03:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23854|2024-08-02T10:42:26.812Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23854</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23854|2024-08-02T10:42:26.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29110|2024-08-02T14:00:15.878Z -- sap -- application%20interface%20framework%20%28message%20dashboard%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29110</link>
      <description>The SAP Application Interface (Message Dashboard) - versions AIF 703, AIFX 702, S4CORE 100, 101, SAP_BASIS 755, 756, SAP_ABA 75C, 75D, 75E, application allows the usage HTML tags. An authorized attacker can use some of the basic HTML codes such as heading, basic formatting and lists, then an attacker can inject images from the foreign domains. After successful exploitations, an attacker can cause limited impact on the confidentiality and integrity of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29110|2024-08-02T14:00:15.878Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 03:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27501|2024-08-02T12:16:35.453Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27501</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS for ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 757, 791, allows an attacker to exploit insufficient validation of path information provided by users, thus exploiting a directory traversal flaw in an available service to delete system files. In this attack, no data can be read but potentially critical OS files can be deleted making the system unavailable, causing significant impact on both availability and integrity

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27501|2024-08-02T12:16:35.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 05:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25614|2024-08-02T11:25:19.310Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20abap%20%28bsp%20framework%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25614</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP (BSP Framework) application - versions 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 757, allow an unauthenticated attacker to inject the code that can be executed by the application over the network. On successful exploitation it can gain access to the sensitive information which leads to a limited impact on the confidentiality and the integrity of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25614|2024-08-02T11:25:19.310Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27270|2024-08-02T12:09:41.807Z -- sap -- netweaver%20application%20server%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27270</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 757, 791, has multiple vulnerabilities in a class for test purposes in which an attacker authenticated as a non-administrative user can craft a request with certain parameters, which will consume the server's resources sufficiently to make it unavailable. There is no ability to view or modify any information.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27270|2024-08-02T12:09:41.807Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 04:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24523|2024-08-02T10:56:04.370Z -- sap -- host%20agent%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24523</link>
      <description>An attacker authenticated as a non-admin user with local access to a server port assigned to the SAP Host Agent (Start Service) - versions 7.21, 7.22, can submit a crafted ConfigureOutsideDiscovery request with an operating system command which will be executed with administrator privileges.  The OS command can read or modify any user or system data and can make the system unavailable.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24523|2024-08-02T10:56:04.370Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24525|2024-08-02T10:56:04.230Z -- sap -- crm%20%28webclient%20ui%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24525</link>
      <description>SAP CRM WebClient UI - versions WEBCUIF 748, 800, 801, S4FND 102, 103, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. On successful exploitation an authenticated attacker can cause limited impact on confidentiality of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24525|2024-08-02T10:56:04.230Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27897|2024-08-02T12:23:30.151Z -- sap -- crm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27897</link>
      <description>In SAP CRM - versions 700, 701, 702, 712, 713, an attacker who is authenticated with a non-administrative role and a common remote execution authorization can use a vulnerable interface to execute an application function to perform actions which they would not normally be permitted to perform. Depending on the function executed, the attack can can have limited impact on confidentiality and integrity of non-critical user or application data and application availability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27897|2024-08-02T12:23:30.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 02:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29189|2024-08-02T14:00:15.877Z -- sap -- crm%20%28webclient%20ui%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29189</link>
      <description>SAP CRM (WebClient UI) - versions S4FND 102, 103, 104, 105, 106, 107, WEBCUIF, 700, 701, 731, 730, 746, 747, 748, 800, 801, allows an authenticated attacker to modify HTTP verbs used in requests to the web server. This application is exposed over the network and successful exploitation can lead to exposure of form fields

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29189|2024-08-02T14:00:15.877Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 03:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26459|2024-08-02T11:53:52.946Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26459</link>
      <description>Due to improper input controls In SAP NetWeaver AS for ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 757, 791, an attacker authenticated as a non-administrative user can craft a request which will trigger the application server to send a request to an arbitrary URL which can reveal, modify or make unavailable non-sensitive information, leading to low impact on Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26459|2024-08-02T11:53:52.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 04:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28763|2024-08-02T13:51:38.228Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28763</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS for ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 757, 791, allows an attacker authenticated as a non-administrative user to craft a request with certain parameters which can consume the server's resources sufficiently to make it unavailable over the network without any user interaction.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28763|2024-08-02T13:51:38.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 02:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0016|2024-08-02T04:54:32.704Z -- sap -- sap%20bpc%20ms%2010.0
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0016</link>
      <description>SAP BPC MS 10.0 - version 810, allows an unauthorized attacker to execute crafted database queries. The exploitation of this issue could lead to SQL injection vulnerability and could allow an attacker to access, modify, and/or delete data from the backend database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0016|2024-08-02T04:54:32.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 03:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29187|2024-08-02T14:00:15.993Z -- sap -- sapsetup%20%28software%20installation%20program%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29187</link>
      <description>A Windows user with basic user authorization can exploit a DLL hijacking attack in SapSetup (Software Installation Program) - version 9.0, resulting in a privilege escalation running code as administrator of the very same Windows PC. A successful attack depends on various preconditions beyond the attackers control.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29187|2024-08-02T14:00:15.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 03:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26458|2024-08-02T11:53:52.754Z -- sap -- landscape%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26458</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in SAP Landscape Management - version 3.0, enterprise edition. It allows an authenticated SAP Landscape Management user to obtain privileged access to other systems making those other systems vulnerable to information disclosure and modification.The disclosed information is for Diagnostics Agent Connection via Java SCS Message Server of an SAP Solution Manager system and can only be accessed by authenticated SAP Landscape Management users, but they can escalate their privileges to the SAP Solution Manager system.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26458|2024-08-02T11:53:52.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 02:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0014|2024-08-02T04:54:32.596Z -- sap -- netweaver%20abap%20server%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0014</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver ABAP Server and ABAP Platform - versions SAP_BASIS 700, 701, 702, 710, 711, 730, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 757, KERNEL 7.22, 7.53, 7.77, 7.81, 7.85, 7.89, KRNL64UC 7.22, 7.22EXT, 7.53, KRNL64NUC 7.22, 7.22EXT, creates information about system identity in an ambiguous format. This could lead to capture-replay vulnerability and may be exploited by malicious users to obtain illegitimate access to the system.


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0014|2024-08-02T04:54:32.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 03:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29112|2024-08-02T14:00:15.216Z -- sap -- application%20interface%20framework%20%28message%20monitoring%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29112</link>
      <description>The SAP Application Interface (Message Monitoring) - versions 600, 700, allows an authorized attacker to input links or headings with custom CSS classes into a comment. The comment will render links and custom CSS classes as HTML objects. After successful exploitations, an attacker can cause limited impact on the confidentiality and integrity of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29112|2024-08-02T14:00:15.216Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 03:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24521|2024-08-02T10:56:04.371Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20abap%20%28bsp%20framework%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24521</link>
      <description>Due to insufficient input sanitization, SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP (BSP Framework) - versions 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 757, allows an unauthenticated user to alter the current session of the user by injecting the malicious code over the network and gain access to the unintended data. This may lead to a limited impact on the confidentiality and the integrity of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24521|2024-08-02T10:56:04.371Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27267|2024-08-02T12:09:42.300Z -- sap -- diagnostics%20agent%20%28oscommand%20bridge%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27267</link>
      <description>Due to missing authentication and insufficient input validation, the OSCommand Bridge of SAP Diagnostics Agent - version 720, allows an attacker with deep knowledge of the system to execute scripts on all connected Diagnostics Agents. On successful exploitation, the attacker can completely compromise confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27267|2024-08-02T12:09:42.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 02:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27893|2024-08-02T12:23:30.612Z -- sap -- solution%20manager%20and%20abap%20managed%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27893</link>
      <description>An attacker authenticated as a user with a non-administrative role and a common remote execution authorization in SAP Solution Manager and ABAP managed systems (ST-PI) - versions 2088_1_700, 2008_1_710, 740, can use a vulnerable interface to execute an application function to perform actions which they would not normally be permitted to perform.  Depending on the function executed, the attack can read or modify any user or application data and can make the application unavailable.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27893|2024-08-02T12:23:30.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 05:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27271|2024-08-02T12:09:41.854Z -- sap -- businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20services%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27271</link>
      <description>In SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Services) - versions 420, 430, an attacker can control a malicious BOE server, forcing the application server to connect to its own admintools, leading to a high impact on availability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27271|2024-08-02T12:09:41.854Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 05:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23855|2024-08-02T10:42:26.959Z -- sap -- solution%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23855</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager - version 720, allows an authenticated attacker to redirect users to a malicious site due to insufficient URL validation. A successful attack could lead an attacker to read or modify the information or expose the user to a phishing attack. As a result, it has a low impact to confidentiality, integrity and availability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23855|2024-08-02T10:42:26.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24530|2024-08-02T10:56:04.364Z -- sap -- businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28cmc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24530</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (CMC) - versions 420, 430, allows an authenticated admin user to upload malicious code that can be executed by the application over the network. On successful exploitation, attacker can perform operations that may completely compromise the application causing high impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24530|2024-08-02T10:56:04.364Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24529|2024-08-02T10:56:04.273Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20abap%20%28business%20server%20pages%20application%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24529</link>
      <description>Due to lack of proper input validation, BSP application (CRM_BSP_FRAME) - versions 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 75C, 75D, 75E, 75F, 75G, 75H, allow malicious inputs from untrusted sources, which can be leveraged by an attacker to execute a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack. As a result, an attacker may be able to hijack a user session, read and modify some sensitive information.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24529|2024-08-02T10:56:04.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0013|2024-08-02T04:54:32.608Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0013</link>
      <description>The ABAP Keyword Documentation of SAP NetWeaver Application Server - versions 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 757, for ABAP and ABAP Platform does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. On successful exploitation an attacker can cause limited impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0013|2024-08-02T04:54:32.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 02:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25616|2024-08-02T11:25:19.235Z -- sap -- business%20objects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28cmc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25616</link>
      <description>In some scenario, SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform (CMC) - versions 420, 430, Program Object execution can lead to code injection vulnerability which could allow an attacker to gain access to resources that are allowed by extra privileges. Successful attack could highly impact the confidentiality, Integrity, and Availability of the system.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25616|2024-08-02T11:25:19.235Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 04:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0017|2024-08-02T04:54:32.802Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20for%20java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0017</link>
      <description>An unauthenticated attacker in SAP NetWeaver AS for Java - version 7.50, due to improper access control, can attach to an open interface and make use of an open naming and directory API to access services which can be used to perform unauthorized operations affecting users and data on the current system. This could allow the attacker to have full read access to user data, make modifications to user data, and make services within the system unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0017|2024-08-02T04:54:32.802Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 03:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0015|2024-08-02T04:54:32.587Z -- sap -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0015</link>
      <description>In SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence user interface) - version 420, some calls return json with wrong content type in the header of the response. As a result, a custom application that calls directly the jsp of Web Intelligence DHTML may be vulnerable to XSS attacks. On successful exploitation an attacker can cause limited impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0015|2024-08-02T04:54:32.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 03:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24526|2024-08-02T10:56:04.231Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20java%20for%20classload%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24526</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server Java for Classload Service - version 7.50, does not perform any authentication checks for functionalities that require user identity, resulting in escalation of privileges. This failure has a low impact on confidentiality of the data such that an unassigned user can read non-sensitive server data.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24526|2024-08-02T10:56:04.231Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 04:38:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29185|2024-08-02T14:00:15.869Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20for%20abap%20%28business%20server%20pages%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29185</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS for ABAP (Business Server Pages) - versions 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 757, allows an attacker authenticated as a non-administrative user to craft a request with certain parameters in certain circumstances which can consume the server's resources sufficiently to make it unavailable over the network without any user interaction.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29185|2024-08-02T14:00:15.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 03:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0025|2024-08-02T04:54:32.567Z -- sap -- solution%20manager%20%28bsp%20application%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0025</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager (BSP Application) - version 720, allows an authenticated attacker to craft a malicious link, which when clicked by an unsuspecting user, can be used to read or modify some sensitive information or craft a payload which may restrict access to the desired resources.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0025|2024-08-02T04:54:32.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27500|2024-08-02T12:16:35.333Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform%20%28saprsbro%20program%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27500</link>
      <description>An attacker with non-administrative authorizations can exploit a directory traversal flaw in program SAPRSBRO to over-write system files. In this attack, no data can be read but potentially critical OS files can be over-written making the system unavailable.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27500|2024-08-02T12:16:35.333Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 05:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0012|2024-08-02T04:54:32.561Z -- sap -- host%20agent%20%28windows%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0012</link>
      <description>In SAP Host Agent (Windows) - versions 7.21, 7.22, an attacker who gains local membership to SAP_LocalAdmin could be able to replace executables with a malicious file that will be started under a privileged account. Note that by default all user members of SAP_LocaAdmin are denied the ability to logon locally by security policy so that this can only occur if the system has already been compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0012|2024-08-02T04:54:32.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 02:44:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1903|2024-08-02T06:05:27.060Z -- sap -- hcm%20fiori%20app%20my%20forms%20%28fiori%202.0%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1903</link>
      <description>SAP HCM Fiori App My Forms (Fiori 2.0) - version 605, does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user exposing the restricted header data.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1903|2024-08-02T06:05:27.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 02:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23857|2024-08-02T10:42:26.822Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20for%20java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23857</link>
      <description>Due to missing authentication check, SAP NetWeaver AS for Java - version 7.50, allows an unauthenticated attacker to attach to an open interface and make use of an open naming and directory API to access services which can be used to perform unauthorized operations affecting users and services across systems. On a successful exploitation, the attacker can read and modify some sensitive information but can also be used to lock up any element or operation of the system making that it unresponsive or unavailable.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23857|2024-08-02T10:42:26.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 04:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24522|2024-08-02T10:56:04.378Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20abap%20%28bsp%20framework%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24522</link>
      <description>Due to insufficient input sanitization, SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP (Business Server Pages) - versions 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, allows an unauthenticated user to alter the current session of the user by injecting the malicious code over the network and gain access to the unintended data. This may lead to a limited impact on the confidentiality and the integrity of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24522|2024-08-02T10:56:04.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27895|2024-08-02T12:23:30.589Z -- sap -- authenticator%20for%20android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27895</link>
      <description>SAP Authenticator for Android - version 1.3.0, allows the screen to be captured, if an authorized attacker installs a malicious app on the mobile device. The attacker could extract the currently views of the OTP and the secret OTP alphanumeric token during the token setup. On successful exploitation, an attacker can read some sensitive information but cannot modify and delete the data.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27895|2024-08-02T12:23:30.589Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 05:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0018|2024-08-02T04:54:32.580Z -- sap -- businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28central%20management%20console%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0018</link>
      <description>Due to improper input sanitization of user-controlled input in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform CMC application - versions 420, and 430, an attacker with basic user-level privileges can modify/upload crystal reports containing a malicious payload. Once these reports are viewable, anyone who opens those reports would be susceptible to stored XSS attacks. As a result of the attack, information maintained in the victim's web browser can be read, modified, and sent to the attacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0018|2024-08-02T04:54:32.580Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 03:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23860|2024-08-02T10:42:27.121Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23860</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS for ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 757, 789, 790, allows an unauthenticated attacker to craft a link, which when clicked by an unsuspecting user can be used to redirect a user to a malicious site which could read or modify some sensitive information or expose the victim to a phishing attack.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23860|2024-08-02T10:42:27.121Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28765|2024-08-02T13:51:37.306Z -- sap -- businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28promotion%20management%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28765</link>
      <description>An attacker with basic privileges in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Promotion Management) - versions 420, 430, can get access to lcmbiar file and further decrypt the file. After this attacker can gain access to BI user’s passwords and depending on the privileges of the BI user, the attacker can perform operations that can completely compromise the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28765|2024-08-02T13:51:37.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 02:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25618|2024-08-02T11:25:19.274Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25618</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 757, 791, has multiple vulnerabilities in an unused class for error handling in which an attacker authenticated as a non-administrative user can craft a request with certain parameters which will consume the server's resources sufficiently to make it unavailable. There is no ability to view or modify any information.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25618|2024-08-02T11:25:19.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 04:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29108|2024-08-02T14:00:15.410Z -- sap -- abap%20platform%20and%20sap%20web%20dispatcher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29108</link>
      <description>The IP filter in ABAP Platform and SAP Web Dispatcher - versions WEBDISP 7.85, 7.89, KERNEL 7.85, 7.89, 7.91, may be vulnerable by erroneous IP netmask handling. This may enable access to backend applications from unwanted sources.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29108|2024-08-02T14:00:15.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 02:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27497|2024-08-02T12:16:35.432Z -- sap -- diagnostics%20agent%20%28eventlogservicecollector%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27497</link>
      <description>Due to missing authentication and input sanitization of code the EventLogServiceCollector of SAP Diagnostics Agent - version 720, allows an attacker to execute malicious scripts on all connected Diagnostics Agents running on Windows. On successful exploitation, the attacker can completely compromise confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27497|2024-08-02T12:16:35.432Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 02:37:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27498|2024-08-02T12:16:36.830Z -- sap -- host%20agent%20%28saposcol%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27498</link>
      <description>SAP Host Agent (SAPOSCOL) - version 7.22, allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to a server port assigned to the SAP Start Service to submit a crafted request which results in a memory corruption error. This error can be used to reveal but not modify any technical information about the server. It can also make a particular service temporarily unavailable

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27498|2024-08-02T12:16:36.830Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 05:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27268|2024-08-02T12:09:41.865Z -- sap -- netweaver%20as%20java%20%28object%20analyzing%20service%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27268</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS Java (Object Analyzing Service) - version 7.50, does not perform necessary authorization checks, allowing an unauthenticated attacker to attach to an open interface and make use of an open naming and directory API to access a service which will enable them to access but not modify server settings and data with no effect on availability., resulting in escalation of privileges.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27268|2024-08-02T12:09:41.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 04:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24524|2024-08-02T10:56:04.281Z -- sap -- s%2F4%20hana%20%28map%20treasury%20correspondence%20format%20data%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24524</link>
      <description>SAP S/4 HANA Map Treasury Correspondence Format Data does not perform necessary authorization check for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. This could allow an attacker to delete the data with a high impact to availability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24524|2024-08-02T10:56:04.281Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0024|2024-08-02T04:54:32.588Z -- sap -- solution%20manager%20%28bsp%20application%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0024</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager (BSP Application) - version 720, allows an authenticated attacker to craft a malicious link, which when clicked by an unsuspecting user, can be used to read or modify some sensitive information or craft a payload which may restrict access to the desired resources, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0024|2024-08-02T04:54:32.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27894|2024-08-02T12:23:29.758Z -- sap -- businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28web%20services%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27894</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Services) - versions 420, 430, allows an attacker to inject arbitrary values as CMS parameters to perform lookups on the internal network which is otherwise not accessible externally. On successful exploitation, attacker can scan internal network to determine internal infrastructure for further attacks like remote file inclusion, retrieve server files, bypass firewall and force the vulnerable server to execute malicious requests, resulting in sensitive information disclosure. This causes limited impact on confidentiality of data.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27894|2024-08-02T12:23:29.758Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 05:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27269|2024-08-02T12:09:41.843Z -- sap -- netweaver%20application%20server%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27269</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 757, 791, allows an attacker with non-administrative authorizations to exploit a directory traversal flaw in an available service to overwrite the system files.  In this attack, no data can be read but potentially critical OS files can be overwritten making the system unavailable.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27269|2024-08-02T12:09:41.843Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 04:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23852|2024-08-02T10:42:27.212Z -- sap -- solution%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23852</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager (System Monitoring) - version 720, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23852|2024-08-02T10:42:27.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23853|2024-08-02T10:42:27.066Z -- sap -- netweaver%20application%20server%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23853</link>
      <description>An unauthenticated attacker in AP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 700, 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 757, 789, 790, can craft a link which when clicked by an unsuspecting user can be used to redirect a user to a malicious site which could read or modify some sensitive information or expose the victim to a phishing attack.  Vulnerability has no direct impact on availability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23853|2024-08-02T10:42:27.066Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:13:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28761|2024-08-02T13:51:38.211Z -- sap -- netweaver%20enterprise%20portal
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28761</link>
      <description>In SAP NetWeaver Enterprise Portal - version 7.50, an unauthenticated attacker can attach to an open interface and make use of an open API to access a service which will enable them to access or modify server settings and data, leading to limited impact on confidentiality and integrity.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28761|2024-08-02T13:51:38.211Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 02:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
