<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SAP -- NetWeaver Process Integration</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sap/netweaver%20process%20integration.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SAP -- NetWeaver Process Integration</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41272|2024-08-03T12:42:43.986Z -- sap -- netweaver%20process%20integration
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41272</link>
      <description>An unauthenticated attacker over the network can attach to an open interface exposed through JNDI by the User Defined Search (UDS) of SAP NetWeaver Process Integration (PI) - version 7.50 and make use of an open naming and directory API to access services which can be used to perform unauthorized operations affecting users and data across the entire system. This allows the attacker to have full read access to user data, make limited modifications to user data, and degrade the performance of the system, leading to a high impact on confidentiality and a limited impact on the availability and integrity of the application.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41272|2024-08-03T12:42:43.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 03:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41271|2024-08-03T12:42:43.981Z -- sap -- netweaver%20process%20integration
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41271</link>
      <description>An unauthenticated user can attach to an open interface exposed through JNDI by the Messaging System of SAP NetWeaver Process Integration (PI) - version 7.50. This user can make use of an open naming and directory API to access services that could perform unauthorized operations. The vulnerability affects local users and data, leading to a considerable impact on confidentiality as well as availability and a limited impact on the integrity of the application. These operations can be used to:

  *  Read any information
  *  Modify sensitive information
  *  Denial of Service attacks (DoS)
  *  SQL Injection




</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41271|2024-08-03T12:42:43.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 02:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
