<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SAP -- SAP HANA Extended Application Services</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sap/sap%20hana%20extended%20application%20services.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SAP -- SAP HANA Extended Application Services</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:22:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2451|2024-08-05T04:21:34.168Z -- sap -- sap%20hana%20extended%20application%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2451</link>
      <description>XS Command-Line Interface (CLI) user sessions with the SAP HANA Extended Application Services (XS), version 1, advanced server may have an unintentional prolonged period of validity. Consequently, a platform user could access controller resources via active CLI session even after corresponding authorizations have been revoked meanwhile by an administrator user. Similarly, an attacker who managed to gain access to the platform user's session might misuse the session token even after the session has been closed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2451|2024-08-05T04:21:34.168Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16687|2024-08-05T20:35:19.897Z -- sap -- sap%20hana%20extended%20application%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16687</link>
      <description>The user self-service tools of SAP HANA extended application services, classic user self-service, a part of SAP HANA Database versions 1.00 and 2.00, can be misused to enumerate valid and invalid user accounts. An unauthenticated user could use the error messages to determine if a given username is valid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16687|2024-08-05T20:35:19.897Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16680|2024-08-05T20:35:19.955Z -- sap -- sap%20hana%20extended%20application%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16680</link>
      <description>Two potential audit log injections in SAP HANA extended application services 1.0, advanced model: 1) Certain HTTP/REST endpoints of controller service are missing user input validation which could allow unprivileged attackers to forge audit log lines. Hence the interpretation of audit log files could be hindered or misdirected. 2) User Account and Authentication writes audit logs into syslog and additionally writes the same audit entries into a log file. Entries in the log file miss escaping. Hence the interpretation of audit log files could be hindered or misdirected, while the entries in syslog are correct.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16680|2024-08-05T20:35:19.955Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
