<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for CodeAstro -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/codeastro/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for CodeAstro -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 21:21:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5694|2024-06-05T20:01:50.492Z -- codeastro -- internet%20banking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5694</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Internet Banking System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file pages_system_settings.php. The manipulation of the argument sys_name with the input &lt;ScRiPt &gt;alert(991)&lt;/ScRiPt&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243132.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in CodeAstro Internet Banking System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei pages_system_settings.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments sys_name mit der Eingabe &lt;ScRiPt &gt;alert(991)&lt;/ScRiPt&gt; mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5694|2024-06-05T20:01:50.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 22:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2076|2024-03-01T18:31:07.093Z -- codeastro -- house%20rental%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2076</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro House Rental Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file booking.php/owner.php/tenant.php. The manipulation leads to missing authentication. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255392.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in CodeAstro House Rental Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei booking.php/owner.php/tenant.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine missing authentication-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2076|2024-03-01T18:31:07.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 18:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
