<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for CodeAstro -- POS System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/codeastro/pos%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for CodeAstro -- POS System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 22:22:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5796|2024-09-09T16:19:02.349Z -- codeastro -- pos%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5796</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro POS System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /setting of the component Logo Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-243602 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in CodeAstro POS System 1.0 ausgemacht. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /setting der Komponente Logo Handler. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5796|2024-09-09T16:19:02.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5795|2024-09-09T16:21:47.285Z -- codeastro -- pos%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5795</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro POS System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /profil of the component Profile Picture Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-243601 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In CodeAstro POS System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /profil der Komponente Profile Picture Handler. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5795|2024-09-09T16:21:47.285Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
