<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Honeywell -- ControlEdge UOC</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/honeywell/controledge%20uoc.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Honeywell -- ControlEdge UOC</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:20:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5389|2024-08-02T07:59:44.048Z -- honeywell -- controledge%20uoc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5389</link>
      <description>
An attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the ability to modify files on Honeywell Experion ControlEdge VirtualUOC and ControlEdge UOC . This exploit could be used to write a file that may result in unexpected behavior based on configuration changes or updating of files that could result in subsequent execution of a malicious application if triggered. Honeywell recommends updating to the most recent version of the product. See Honeywell Security Notification for recommendations on upgrading and versioning. </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5389|2024-08-02T07:59:44.048Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 20:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5390|2024-08-02T07:59:44.316Z -- honeywell -- controledge%20uoc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5390</link>
      <description>An attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to files being read from the Honeywell Experion ControlEdge VirtualUOC and ControlEdge UOC. This exploit could be used to read files from the controller that may expose limited information from the device. Honeywell recommends updating to the most recent version of the product. See Honeywell Security Notification for recommendations on upgrading and versioning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5390|2024-08-02T07:59:44.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 17:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
