<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for 82Flex -- WEIPDCRM</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/82flex/weipdcrm.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for 82Flex -- WEIPDCRM</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:22:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-10008|2024-08-06T08:58:25.829Z -- 82flex -- weipdcrm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10008</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in 82Flex WEIPDCRM. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier of the patch is 43bad79392332fa39e31b95268e76fbda9fec3a4. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-217185 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in 82Flex WEIPDCRM ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Patch wird als 43bad79392332fa39e31b95268e76fbda9fec3a4 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-10008|2024-08-06T08:58:25.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 10:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-10007|2024-08-06T08:58:24.619Z -- 82flex -- weipdcrm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10007</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in 82Flex WEIPDCRM and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The name of the patch is 43bad79392332fa39e31b95268e76fbda9fec3a4. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-217184. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in 82Flex WEIPDCRM gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Patch wird als 43bad79392332fa39e31b95268e76fbda9fec3a4 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-10007|2024-08-06T08:58:24.619Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 10:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
