<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Open-Xchange GmbH -- OX App Suite</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/open-xchange%20gmbh/ox%20app%20suite.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Open-Xchange GmbH -- OX App Suite</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 16:24:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29051|2024-08-02T14:00:14.833Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29051</link>
      <description>User-defined OXMF templates could be used to access a limited part of the internal OX App Suite Java API. The existing switch to disable the feature by default was not effective in this case. Unauthorized users could discover and modify application state, including objects related to other users and contexts. We now make sure that the switch to disable user-generated templates by default works as intended and will remove the feature in future generations of the product. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29051|2024-08-02T14:00:14.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29049|2024-08-02T14:00:14.708Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29049</link>
      <description>The "upsell" widget at the portal page could be abused to inject arbitrary script code. Attackers that manage to lure users to a compromised account, or gain temporary access to a legitimate account, could inject script code to gain persistent code execution capabilities under a trusted domain. User input for this widget is now sanitized to avoid malicious content the be processed. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29049|2024-08-02T14:00:14.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 08:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29048|2024-08-02T14:00:14.594Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29048</link>
      <description>A component for parsing OXMF templates could be abused to execute arbitrary system commands that would be executed as the non-privileged runtime user. Users and attackers could run system commands with limited privilege to gain unauthorized access to confidential information and potentially violate integrity by modifying resources. The template engine has been reconfigured to deny execution of harmful commands on a system level. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29048|2024-08-02T14:00:14.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 08:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29050|2024-08-02T14:00:15.126Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29050</link>
      <description>The optional "LDAP contacts provider" could be abused by privileged users to inject LDAP filter strings that allow to access content outside of the intended hierarchy. Unauthorized users could break confidentiality of information in the directory and potentially cause high load on the directory server, leading to denial of service. Encoding has been added for user-provided fragments that are used when constructing the LDAP query. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29050|2024-08-02T14:00:15.126Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 08:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29052|2024-08-02T14:00:15.157Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29052</link>
      <description>Users were able to define disclaimer texts for an upsell shop dialog that would contain script code that was not sanitized correctly. Attackers could lure victims to user accounts with malicious script code and make them execute it in the context of a trusted domain. We added sanitization for this content. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29052|2024-08-02T14:00:15.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41706|2024-07-05T17:20:51.257Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41706</link>
      <description>Processing time of drive search expressions now gets monitored, and the related request is terminated if a resource threshold is reached. Availability of OX App Suite could be reduced due to high processing load. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Processing of user-defined drive search expressions is not limited No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41706|2024-07-05T17:20:51.257Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23191|2024-07-05T17:22:41.888Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23191</link>
      <description>Upsell advertisement information of an account can be manipulated to execute script code in the context of the users browser session. To exploit this an attacker would require temporary access to a users account or an successful social engineering attack to lure users to maliciously configured accounts. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Sanitization of user-defined upsell content has been improved. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23191|2024-07-05T17:22:41.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23189|2024-07-05T17:22:37.660Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23189</link>
      <description>Embedded content references at tasks could be used to temporarily execute script code in the context of the users browser session. To exploit this an attacker would require temporary access to the users account, access to another account within the same context or an successful social engineering attack to make users import external content. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Sanitization of user-generated content has been improved. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23189|2024-07-05T17:22:37.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23190|2024-07-05T17:22:36.922Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23190</link>
      <description>Upsell shop information of an account can be manipulated to execute script code in the context of the users browser session. To exploit this an attacker would require temporary access to a users account or an successful social engineering attack to lure users to maliciously configured accounts. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Sanitization of user-defined upsell content has been improved. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23190|2024-07-05T17:22:36.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41707|2024-07-05T17:20:50.823Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41707</link>
      <description>Processing of user-defined mail search expressions is not limited. Availability of OX App Suite could be reduced due to high processing load. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Processing time of mail search expressions now gets monitored, and the related request is terminated if a resource threshold is reached.
 No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41707|2024-07-05T17:20:50.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23193|2024-06-12T20:28:50.048Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23193</link>
      <description>E-Mails exported as PDF were stored in a cache that did not consider specific session information for the related user account. Users of the same service node could access other users E-Mails in case they were exported as PDF for a brief moment until caches were cleared. Successful exploitation requires good timing and modification of multiple request parameters. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. The cache for PDF exports now takes user session information into consideration when performing authorization decisions. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23193|2024-06-12T20:28:50.048Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23186|2024-06-04T17:45:38.374Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23186</link>
      <description>E-Mail containing malicious display-name information could trigger client-side script execution when using specific mobile devices. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. We now use safer methods of handling external content when embedding displayname information to the web interface. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23186|2024-06-04T17:45:38.374Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23190|2024-04-25T15:09:25.858Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23190</link>
      <description>Upsell shop information of an account can be manipulated to execute script code in the context of the users browser session. To exploit this an attacker would require temporary access to a users account or an successful social engineering attack to lure users to maliciously configured accounts. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Sanitization of user-defined upsell content has been improved. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23190|2024-04-25T15:09:25.858Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23191|2024-04-25T15:09:27.359Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23191</link>
      <description>Upsell advertisement information of an account can be manipulated to execute script code in the context of the users browser session. To exploit this an attacker would require temporary access to a users account or an successful social engineering attack to lure users to maliciously configured accounts. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Sanitization of user-defined upsell content has been improved. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23191|2024-04-25T15:09:27.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23187|2024-06-04T17:45:41.685Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23187</link>
      <description>Content-ID based embedding of resources in E-Mails could be abused to trigger client-side script code when using the "show more" option. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Exploiting the vulnerability requires user interaction. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. CID replacement has been hardened to omit invalid identifiers. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23187|2024-06-04T17:45:41.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:36:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23188|2024-06-04T17:46:06.917Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23188</link>
      <description>Maliciously crafted E-Mail attachment names could be used to temporarily execute script code in the context of the users browser session. Common user interaction is required for the vulnerability to trigger. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. We now use safer methods of handling external content when embedding attachment information to the web interface. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23188|2024-06-04T17:46:06.917Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23192|2024-04-25T15:09:28.850Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23192</link>
      <description>RSS feeds that contain malicious data- attributes could be abused to inject script code to a users browser session when reading compromised RSS feeds or successfully luring users to compromised accounts. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Potentially malicious attributes now get removed from external RSS content. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23192|2024-04-25T15:09:28.850Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23193|2024-05-06T06:36:40.941Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23193</link>
      <description>E-Mails exported as PDF were stored in a cache that did not consider specific session information for the related user account. Users of the same service node could access other users E-Mails in case they were exported as PDF for a brief moment until caches were cleared. Successful exploitation requires good timing and modification of multiple request parameters. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. The cache for PDF exports now takes user session information into consideration when performing authorization decisions. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23193|2024-05-06T06:36:40.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23189|2024-04-25T15:09:24.304Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23189</link>
      <description>Embedded content references at tasks could be used to temporarily execute script code in the context of the users browser session. To exploit this an attacker would require temporary access to the users account, access to another account within the same context or an successful social engineering attack to make users import external content. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Sanitization of user-generated content has been improved. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23189|2024-04-25T15:09:24.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41705|2024-02-16T14:08:50.608Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41705</link>
      <description>Processing of user-defined DAV user-agent strings is not limited. Availability of OX App Suite could be reduced due to high processing load. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Processing time of DAV user-agents now gets monitored, and the related request is terminated if a resource threshold is reached. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41705|2024-02-16T14:08:50.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41708|2024-02-16T14:08:54.485Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41708</link>
      <description>References to the "app loader" functionality could contain redirects to unexpected locations. Attackers could forge app references that bypass existing safeguards to inject malicious script code. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. References to apps are now controlled more strict to avoid relative references. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41708|2024-02-16T14:08:54.485Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41704|2024-02-16T14:08:49.359Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41704</link>
      <description>Processing of CID references at E-Mail can be abused to inject malicious script code that passes the sanitization engine. Malicious script code could be injected to a users sessions when interacting with E-Mails. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. CID handing has been improved and resulting content is checked for malicious content. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41704|2024-02-16T14:08:49.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41703|2024-06-04T17:21:38.083Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41703</link>
      <description>User ID references at mentions in document comments were not correctly sanitized. Script code could be injected to a users session when working with a malicious document. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. User-defined content like comments and mentions are now filtered to avoid potentially malicious content. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41703|2024-06-04T17:21:38.083Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41707|2024-02-16T14:08:53.186Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41707</link>
      <description>Processing of user-defined mail search expressions is not limited. Availability of OX App Suite could be reduced due to high processing load. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Processing time of mail search expressions now gets monitored, and the related request is terminated if a resource threshold is reached.
 No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41707|2024-02-16T14:08:53.186Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41706|2024-02-16T14:08:51.845Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41706</link>
      <description>Processing time of drive search expressions now gets monitored, and the related request is terminated if a resource threshold is reached. Availability of OX App Suite could be reduced due to high processing load. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Processing of user-defined drive search expressions is not limited No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41706|2024-02-16T14:08:51.845Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23192|2024-06-20T15:33:22.699Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23192</link>
      <description>RSS feeds that contain malicious data- attributes could be abused to inject script code to a users browser session when reading compromised RSS feeds or successfully luring users to compromised accounts. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Potentially malicious attributes now get removed from external RSS content. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23192|2024-06-20T15:33:22.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23186|2024-08-01T22:59:32.072Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23186</link>
      <description>E-Mail containing malicious display-name information could trigger client-side script execution when using specific mobile devices. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. We now use safer methods of handling external content when embedding displayname information to the web interface. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23186|2024-08-01T22:59:32.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23193|2024-08-01T22:59:32.057Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23193</link>
      <description>E-Mails exported as PDF were stored in a cache that did not consider specific session information for the related user account. Users of the same service node could access other users E-Mails in case they were exported as PDF for a brief moment until caches were cleared. Successful exploitation requires good timing and modification of multiple request parameters. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. The cache for PDF exports now takes user session information into consideration when performing authorization decisions. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23193|2024-08-01T22:59:32.057Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23190|2024-08-01T22:59:31.897Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23190</link>
      <description>Upsell shop information of an account can be manipulated to execute script code in the context of the users browser session. To exploit this an attacker would require temporary access to a users account or an successful social engineering attack to lure users to maliciously configured accounts. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Sanitization of user-defined upsell content has been improved. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23190|2024-08-01T22:59:31.897Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23187|2024-08-01T22:59:32.012Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23187</link>
      <description>Content-ID based embedding of resources in E-Mails could be abused to trigger client-side script code when using the "show more" option. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Exploiting the vulnerability requires user interaction. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. CID replacement has been hardened to omit invalid identifiers. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23187|2024-08-01T22:59:32.012Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:36:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23191|2024-08-01T22:59:31.835Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23191</link>
      <description>Upsell advertisement information of an account can be manipulated to execute script code in the context of the users browser session. To exploit this an attacker would require temporary access to a users account or an successful social engineering attack to lure users to maliciously configured accounts. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Sanitization of user-defined upsell content has been improved. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23191|2024-08-01T22:59:31.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23192|2024-08-01T22:59:32.065Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23192</link>
      <description>RSS feeds that contain malicious data- attributes could be abused to inject script code to a users browser session when reading compromised RSS feeds or successfully luring users to compromised accounts. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Potentially malicious attributes now get removed from external RSS content. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23192|2024-08-01T22:59:32.065Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23189|2024-08-01T22:59:32.094Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23189</link>
      <description>Embedded content references at tasks could be used to temporarily execute script code in the context of the users browser session. To exploit this an attacker would require temporary access to the users account, access to another account within the same context or an successful social engineering attack to make users import external content. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Sanitization of user-generated content has been improved. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23189|2024-08-01T22:59:32.094Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23188|2024-08-01T22:59:32.221Z -- open-xchange%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23188</link>
      <description>Maliciously crafted E-Mail attachment names could be used to temporarily execute script code in the context of the users browser session. Common user interaction is required for the vulnerability to trigger. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. We now use safer methods of handling external content when embedding attachment information to the web interface. No publicly available exploits are known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23188|2024-08-01T22:59:32.221Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
