<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Red Hat -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5178|2024-05-23T22:48:10.556Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5178</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability was found in drivers/nvme/target/tcp.c` in `nvmet_tcp_free_crypto` due to a logical bug in the NVMe/TCP subsystem in the Linux kernel. This issue may allow a malicious user to cause a use-after-free and double-free problem, which may permit remote code execution or lead to local privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5178|2024-05-23T22:48:10.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5379|2024-05-01T20:21:24.197Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20jboss%20enterprise%20application%20platform%207.1.0
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5379</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Undertow. When an AJP request is sent that exceeds the max-header-size attribute in ajp-listener, JBoss EAP is marked in an error state by mod_cluster in httpd, causing JBoss EAP to close the TCP connection without returning an AJP response. This happens because mod_proxy_cluster marks the JBoss EAP instance as an error worker when the TCP connection is closed from the backend after sending the AJP request without receiving an AJP response, and stops forwarding. This issue could allow a malicious user could to repeatedly send requests that exceed the max-header-size, causing a Denial of Service (DoS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5379|2024-05-01T20:21:24.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 21:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5115|2024-05-01T20:21:20.506Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20ansible%20automation%20platform%202.3%20for%20rhel%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5115</link>
      <description>An absolute path traversal attack exists in the Ansible automation platform. This flaw allows an attacker to craft a malicious Ansible role and make the victim execute the role. A symlink can be used to overwrite a file outside of the extraction path.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5115|2024-05-01T20:21:20.506Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5380|2024-05-29T21:02:55.433Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5380</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the xorg-x11-server. An X server crash may occur in a very specific and legacy configuration (a multi-screen setup with multiple protocol screens, also known as Zaphod mode) if the pointer is warped from within a window on one screen to the root window of the other screen and if the original window is destroyed followed by another window being destroyed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5380|2024-05-29T21:02:55.433Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5158|2024-01-23T01:02:35.622Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5158</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in vringh_kiov_advance in drivers/vhost/vringh.c in the host side of a virtio ring in the Linux Kernel. This issue may result in a denial of service from guest to host via zero length descriptor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5158|2024-01-23T01:02:35.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 15:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5764|2024-05-01T20:21:29.578Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20ansible%20automation%20platform%202.4%20for%20rhel%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5764</link>
      <description>A template injection flaw was found in Ansible where a user's controller internal templating operations may remove the unsafe designation from template data. This issue could allow an attacker to use a specially crafted file to introduce templating injection when supplying templating data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5764|2024-05-01T20:21:29.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 22:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5972|2024-02-28T12:38:05.880Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5972</link>
      <description>A null pointer dereference flaw was found in the nft_inner.c functionality of netfilter in the Linux kernel. This issue could allow a local user to crash the system or escalate their privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5972|2024-02-28T12:38:05.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 17:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5088|2024-05-29T23:04:46.938Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5088</link>
      <description>A bug in QEMU could cause a guest I/O operation otherwise addressed to an arbitrary disk offset to be targeted to offset 0 instead (potentially overwriting the VM's boot code). This could be used, for example, by L2 guests with a virtual disk (vdiskL2) stored on a virtual disk of an L1 (vdiskL1) hypervisor to read and/or write data to LBA 0 of vdiskL1, potentially gaining control of L1 at its next reboot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5088|2024-05-29T23:04:46.938Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 13:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5568|2024-01-23T01:26:11.228Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5568</link>
      <description>A heap-based Buffer Overflow flaw was discovered in Samba. It could allow a remote, authenticated attacker to exploit this vulnerability to cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5568|2024-01-23T01:26:11.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 21:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5349|2023-10-30T20:27:59.972Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%203scale%20api%20management%20platform%202
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5349</link>
      <description>A memory leak flaw was found in ruby-magick, an interface between Ruby and ImageMagick. This issue can lead to a denial of service (DOS) by memory exhaustion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5349|2023-10-30T20:27:59.972Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 20:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5871|2024-05-01T20:21:32.214Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5871</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in libnbd, due to a malicious Network Block Device (NBD), a protocol for accessing Block Devices such as hard disks over a Network. This issue may allow a malicious NBD server to cause a Denial of Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5871|2024-05-01T20:21:32.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 11:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5236|2024-05-01T20:21:23.158Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20data%20grid%208.4.4
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5236</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Infinispan, which does not detect circular object references when unmarshalling. An authenticated attacker with sufficient permissions could insert a maliciously constructed object into the cache and use it to cause out of memory errors and achieve a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5236|2024-05-01T20:21:23.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5685|2024-06-04T17:28:42.677Z -- red%20hat -- eap%207.4.14
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5685</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in XNIO. The XNIO NotifierState that can cause a Stack Overflow Exception when the chain of notifier states becomes problematically large can lead to uncontrolled resource management and a possible denial of service (DoS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5685|2024-06-04T17:28:42.677Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 18:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5056|2024-05-01T20:21:19.763Z -- red%20hat -- service%20interconnect%201%20for%20rhel%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5056</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Skupper operator, which may permit a certain configuration to create a service account that would allow an authenticated attacker in the adjacent cluster to view deployments in all namespaces in the cluster. This issue permits unauthorized viewing of information outside of the user's purview.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5056|2024-05-01T20:21:19.763Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5981|2024-05-01T20:21:32.577Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5981</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found that the response times to malformed ciphertexts in RSA-PSK ClientKeyExchange differ from response times of ciphertexts with correct PKCS#1 v1.5 padding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5981|2024-05-01T20:21:32.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 11:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5870|2024-05-01T20:21:31.861Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20advanced%20cluster%20security%204.2
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5870</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in PostgreSQL involving the pg_cancel_backend role that signals background workers, including the logical replication launcher, autovacuum workers, and the autovacuum launcher. Successful exploitation requires a non-core extension with a less-resilient background worker and would affect that specific background worker only. This issue may allow a remote high privileged user to launch a denial of service (DoS) attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5870|2024-05-01T20:21:31.861Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 17:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5574|2024-05-01T20:21:27.529Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5574</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in xorg-x11-server-Xvfb. This issue occurs in Xvfb with a very specific and legacy configuration (a multi-screen setup with multiple protocol screens, also known as Zaphod mode). If the pointer is warped from a screen 1 to a screen 0, a use-after-free issue may be triggered during shutdown or reset of the Xvfb server, allowing for possible escalation of privileges or denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5574|2024-05-01T20:21:27.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:47:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5625|2024-05-01T20:21:27.556Z -- red%20hat -- ironic%20content%20for%20red%20hat%20openshift%20container%20platform%204.12
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5625</link>
      <description>A regression was introduced in the Red Hat build of python-eventlet due to a change in the patch application strategy, resulting in a patch for CVE-2021-21419 not being applied for all builds of all products.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5625|2024-05-01T20:21:27.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 13:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5367|2024-05-29T23:05:07.641Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5367</link>
      <description>A out-of-bounds write flaw was found in the xorg-x11-server. This issue occurs due to an incorrect calculation of a buffer offset when copying data stored in the heap in the XIChangeDeviceProperty function in Xi/xiproperty.c and in RRChangeOutputProperty function in randr/rrproperty.c, allowing for possible escalation of privileges or denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5367|2024-05-29T23:05:07.641Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5408|2024-05-01T20:21:25.654Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openshift%20container%20platform%204.11
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5408</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation flaw was found in the node restriction admission plugin of the kubernetes api server of OpenShift. A remote attacker who modifies the node role label could steer workloads from the control plane and etcd nodes onto different worker nodes and gain broader access to the cluster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5408|2024-05-01T20:21:25.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5633|2024-06-04T17:28:39.386Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5633</link>
      <description>The reference count changes made as part of the CVE-2023-33951 and CVE-2023-33952 fixes exposed a use-after-free flaw in the way memory objects were handled when they were being used to store a surface. When running inside a VMware guest with 3D acceleration enabled, a local, unprivileged user could potentially use this flaw to escalate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5633|2024-06-04T17:28:39.386Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 21:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5189|2024-05-01T20:21:22.448Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20ansible%20automation%20platform%202.4%20for%20rhel%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5189</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in Ansible when extracting tarballs. An attacker could craft a malicious tarball so that when using the galaxy importer of Ansible Automation Hub, a symlink could be dropped on the disk, resulting in files being overwritten.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5189|2024-05-01T20:21:22.448Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5824|2024-05-01T20:21:30.251Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5824</link>
      <description>Squid is vulnerable to Denial of Service attack against HTTP and HTTPS clients due to an Improper Handling of Structural Elements bug.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5824|2024-05-01T20:21:30.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 07:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5557|2024-05-01T20:21:26.286Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5557</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the tracker-miners package. A weakness in the sandbox allows a maliciously-crafted file to execute code outside the sandbox if the tracker-extract process has first been compromised by a separate vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5557|2024-05-01T20:21:26.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 01:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5384|2024-06-04T17:28:38.094Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20data%20grid%208.4.6
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5384</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Infinispan. When serializing the configuration for a cache to XML/JSON/YAML, which contains credentials (JDBC store with connection pooling, remote store), the credentials are returned in clear text as part of the configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5384|2024-06-04T17:28:38.094Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5869|2024-05-01T20:21:31.327Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20advanced%20cluster%20security%204.2
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5869</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in PostgreSQL that allows authenticated database users to execute arbitrary code through missing overflow checks during SQL array value modification. This issue exists due to an integer overflow during array modification where a remote user can trigger the overflow by providing specially crafted data. This enables the execution of arbitrary code on the target system, allowing users to write arbitrary bytes to memory and extensively read the server's memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5869|2024-05-01T20:21:31.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 17:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5868|2024-05-01T20:21:30.459Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20advanced%20cluster%20security%204.2
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5868</link>
      <description>A memory disclosure vulnerability was found in PostgreSQL that allows remote users to access sensitive information by exploiting certain aggregate function calls with 'unknown'-type arguments. Handling 'unknown'-type values from string literals without type designation can disclose bytes, potentially revealing notable and confidential information. This issue exists due to excessive data output in aggregate function calls, enabling remote users to read some portion of system memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5868|2024-05-01T20:21:30.459Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 17:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5215|2024-05-01T20:21:22.207Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5215</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in libnbd. A server can reply with a block size larger than 2^63 (the NBD spec states the size is a 64-bit unsigned value). This issue could lead to an application crash or other unintended behavior for NBD clients that doesn't treat the return value of the nbd_get_size() function correctly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5215|2024-05-01T20:21:22.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 13:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5366|2023-10-06T17:43:34.376Z -- red%20hat -- fast%20datapath%20for%20rhel%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5366</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Open vSwitch that allows ICMPv6 Neighbor Advertisement packets between virtual machines to bypass OpenFlow rules. This issue may allow a local attacker to create specially crafted packets with a modified or spoofed target IP address field that can redirect ICMPv6 traffic to arbitrary IP addresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5366|2023-10-06T17:43:34.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 17:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5156|2024-04-25T15:04:12.336Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5156</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the GNU C Library. A recent fix for CVE-2023-4806 introduced the potential for a memory leak, which may result in an application crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5156|2024-04-25T15:04:12.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 15:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5455|2024-05-01T20:21:26.224Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5455</link>
      <description>A Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in ipa/session/login_password in all supported versions of IPA. This flaw allows an attacker to trick the user into submitting a request that could perform actions as the user, resulting in a loss of confidentiality and system integrity. During community penetration testing it was found that for certain HTTP end-points FreeIPA does not ensure CSRF protection. Due to implementation details one cannot use this flaw for reflection of a cookie representing already logged-in user. An attacker would always have to go through a new authentication attempt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5455|2024-05-01T20:21:26.224Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 12:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5992|2024-06-04T17:28:33.779Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5992</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in OpenSC where PKCS#1 encryption padding removal is not implemented as side-channel resistant. This issue may result in the potential leak of private data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5992|2024-06-04T17:28:33.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 14:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5341|2024-06-04T17:28:32.878Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5341</link>
      <description>A heap use-after-free flaw was found in coders/bmp.c in ImageMagick.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5341|2024-06-04T17:28:32.878Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 09:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5675|2024-06-04T17:28:32.010Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20quarkus%202.13.9.final
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5675</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Quarkus. When a Quarkus RestEasy Classic or Reactive JAX-RS endpoint has its methods declared in the abstract Java class or customized by Quarkus extensions using the annotation processor, the authorization of these methods will not be enforced if it is enabled by either 'quarkus.security.jaxrs.deny-unannotated-endpoints' or 'quarkus.security.jaxrs.default-roles-allowed' properties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5675|2024-06-04T17:28:32.010Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5090|2024-04-25T15:03:45.851Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5090</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in KVM. An improper check in svm_set_x2apic_msr_interception() may allow direct access to host x2apic msrs when the guest resets its apic, potentially leading to a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5090|2024-04-25T15:03:45.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 10:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5157|2024-05-01T20:21:21.091Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5157</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in MariaDB. An OpenVAS port scan on ports 3306 and 4567 allows a malicious remote client to cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5157|2024-05-01T20:21:21.091Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 13:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38473|2023-11-02T15:00:19.576Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38473</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Avahi. A reachable assertion exists in the avahi_alternative_host_name() function.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38473|2023-11-02T15:00:19.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 15:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38469|2023-11-02T14:49:26.283Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38469</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Avahi, where a reachable assertion exists in avahi_dns_packet_append_record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38469|2023-11-02T14:49:26.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 14:49:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38472|2023-11-02T14:59:24.996Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38472</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Avahi. A reachable assertion exists in the avahi_rdata_parse() function.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38472|2023-11-02T14:59:24.996Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 14:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38560|2024-06-04T17:28:23.033Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38560</link>
      <description>An integer overflow flaw was found in pcl/pl/plfont.c:418 in pl_glyph_name in ghostscript. This issue may allow a local attacker to cause a denial of service via transforming a crafted PCL file to PDF format.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38560|2024-06-04T17:28:23.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 16:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38253|2024-03-18T03:39:07.903Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38253</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read flaw was found in w3m, in the growbuf_to_Str function in indep.c. This issue may allow an attacker to cause a denial of service through a crafted HTML file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38253|2024-03-18T03:39:07.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 17:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38252|2024-04-25T13:10:36.816Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38252</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read flaw was found in w3m, in the Strnew_size function in Str.c. This issue may allow an attacker to cause a denial of service through a crafted HTML file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38252|2024-04-25T13:10:36.816Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 17:06:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38471|2023-11-02T14:58:22.628Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38471</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Avahi. A reachable assertion exists in the dbus_set_host_name function.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38471|2023-11-02T14:58:22.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 14:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38559|2024-05-01T20:20:51.137Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38559</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow flaw was found in base/gdevdevn.c:1973 in devn_pcx_write_rle() in ghostscript. This issue may allow a local attacker to cause a denial of service via outputting a crafted PDF file for a DEVN device with gs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38559|2024-05-01T20:20:51.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 16:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38200|2024-06-04T17:28:03.661Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38200</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Keylime. Due to their blocking nature, the Keylime registrar is subject to a remote denial of service against its SSL connections. This flaw allows an attacker to exhaust all available connections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38200|2024-06-04T17:28:03.661Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38201|2024-05-01T20:20:51.039Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38201</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Keylime registrar that could allow a bypass of the challenge-response protocol during agent registration. This issue may allow an attacker to impersonate an agent and hide the true status of a monitored machine if the fake agent is added to the verifier list by a legitimate user, resulting in a breach of the integrity of the registrar database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38201|2024-05-01T20:20:51.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 16:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38470|2023-11-02T14:57:28.872Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38470</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Avahi. A reachable assertion exists in the avahi_escape_label() function.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38470|2023-11-02T14:57:28.872Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 14:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1183|2023-07-10T15:04:30.740Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1183</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Libreoffice package. An attacker can craft an odb containing a "database/script" file with a SCRIPT command where the contents of the file could be written to a new file whose location was determined by the attacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1183|2023-07-10T15:04:30.740Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 15:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1584|2024-05-03T15:32:34.371Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20quarkus%202.13.8.final
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1584</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Quarkus. Quarkus OIDC can leak both ID and access tokens in the authorization code flow when an insecure HTTP protocol is used, which can allow attackers to access sensitive user data directly from the ID token or by using the access token to access user data from OIDC provider services. Please note that passwords are not stored in access tokens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1584|2024-05-03T15:32:34.371Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 10:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1194|2023-11-03T07:41:35.083Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1194</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds (OOB) memory read flaw was found in parse_lease_state in the KSMBD implementation of the in-kernel samba server and CIFS in the Linux kernel. When an attacker sends the CREATE command with a malformed payload to KSMBD, due to a missing check of `NameOffset` in the `parse_lease_state()` function, the `create_context` object can access invalid memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1194|2023-11-03T07:41:35.083Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 07:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1832|2023-10-04T13:05:37.522Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20satellite%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1832</link>
      <description>An improper access control flaw was found in Candlepin. An attacker can create data scoped under another customer/tenant, which can result in loss of confidentiality and availability for the affected customer/tenant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1832|2023-10-04T13:05:37.522Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 13:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1672|2023-07-11T11:47:35.363Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1672</link>
      <description>A race condition exists in the Tang server functionality for key generation and key rotation. This flaw results in a small time window where Tang private keys become readable by other processes on the same host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1672|2023-07-11T11:47:35.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1625|2023-09-24T00:08:12.738Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openstack%20platform%2013%20%28queens%29
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1625</link>
      <description>An information leak was discovered in OpenStack heat. This issue could allow a remote, authenticated attacker to use the 'stack show' command to reveal parameters which are supposed to remain hidden. This has a low impact to the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1625|2023-09-24T00:08:12.738Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1633|2023-09-24T00:09:50.215Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openstack%20platform%2013%20%28queens%29
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1633</link>
      <description>A credentials leak flaw was found in OpenStack Barbican. This flaw allows a local authenticated attacker to read the configuration file, gaining access to sensitive credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1633|2023-09-24T00:09:50.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:09:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1193|2023-11-01T19:10:14.210Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1193</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in setup_async_work in the KSMBD implementation of the in-kernel samba server and CIFS in the Linux kernel. This issue could allow an attacker to crash the system by accessing freed work.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1193|2023-11-01T19:10:14.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1192|2024-03-07T16:42:37.540Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1192</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in smb2_is_status_io_timeout() in CIFS in the Linux Kernel. After CIFS transfers response data to a system call, there are still local variable points to the memory region, and if the system call frees it faster than CIFS uses it, CIFS will access a free memory region, leading to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1192|2024-03-07T16:42:37.540Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1386|2024-04-17T17:34:27.317Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1386</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the 9p passthrough filesystem (9pfs) implementation in QEMU. When a local user in the guest writes an executable file with SUID or SGID, none of these privileged bits are correctly dropped. As a result, in rare circumstances, this flaw could be used by malicious users in the guest to elevate their privileges within the guest and help a host local user to elevate privileges on the host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1386|2024-04-17T17:34:27.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1108|2024-05-03T15:32:32.904Z -- red%20hat -- eap%207.4.10%20release
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1108</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in undertow. This issue makes achieving a denial of service possible due to an unexpected handshake status updated in SslConduit, where the loop never terminates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1108|2024-05-03T15:32:32.904Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 14:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1260|2024-05-03T15:32:33.416Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openshift%20container%20platform%204.10
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1260</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass vulnerability was discovered in kube-apiserver. This issue could allow a remote, authenticated attacker who has been given permissions "update, patch" the "pods/ephemeralcontainers" subresource beyond what the default is. They would then need to create a new pod or patch one that they already have access to. This might allow evasion of SCC admission restrictions, thereby gaining control of a privileged pod.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1260|2024-05-03T15:32:33.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1476|2024-05-03T15:32:33.878Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1476</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the Linux kernel’s mm/mremap memory address space accounting source code. This issue occurs due to a race condition between rmap walk and mremap, allowing a local user to crash the system or potentially escalate their privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1476|2024-05-03T15:32:33.878Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 08:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1636|2023-09-24T00:09:03.770Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openstack%20platform%2013%20%28queens%29
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1636</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in OpenStack Barbican containers. This vulnerability is only applicable to deployments that utilize an all-in-one configuration. Barbican containers share the same CGROUP, USER, and NET namespace with the host system and other OpenStack services. If any service is compromised, it could gain access to the data transmitted to and from Barbican.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1636|2023-09-24T00:09:03.770Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0462|2023-09-20T13:40:43.213Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20satellite%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0462</link>
      <description>An arbitrary code execution flaw was found in Foreman. This issue may allow an admin user to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system by setting global parameters with a YAML payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0462|2023-09-20T13:40:43.213Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 13:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0160|2023-07-18T16:08:23.653Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0160</link>
      <description>A deadlock flaw was found in the Linux kernel’s BPF subsystem. This flaw allows a local user to potentially crash the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0160|2023-07-18T16:08:23.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 16:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0833|2024-05-03T15:32:31.729Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20amq%20streams%202.2.1
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0833</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Red Hat's AMQ-Streams, which ships a version of the OKHttp component with an information disclosure flaw via an exception triggered by a header containing an illegal value. This issue could allow an authenticated attacker to access information outside of their regular permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0833|2024-05-03T15:32:31.729Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 13:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0813|2024-05-03T15:32:31.244Z -- red%20hat -- network-observability-1.1.0-rhel-8
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0813</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Network Observability plugin for OpenShift console. Unless the Loki authToken configuration is set to FORWARD mode, authentication is no longer enforced, allowing any user who can connect to the OpenShift Console in an OpenShift cluster to retrieve flows without authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0813|2024-05-03T15:32:31.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0923|2024-06-04T17:27:29.238Z -- red%20hat -- rhods-1.22-rhel-8
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0923</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Kubernetes service for notebooks in RHODS, where it does not prevent pods from other namespaces and applications from making requests to the Jupyter API. This flaw can lead to file content exposure and other issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0923|2024-06-04T17:27:29.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0456|2023-09-27T13:39:37.294Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%203scale%20api%20management%20platform%202
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0456</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in APICast, when 3Scale's OIDC module does not properly evaluate the response to a mismatched token from a separate realm. This could allow a separate realm to be accessible to an attacker, permitting access to unauthorized information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0456|2023-09-27T13:39:37.294Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 13:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0118|2024-05-03T15:32:29.709Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20satellite%206.11%20for%20rhel%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0118</link>
      <description>An arbitrary code execution flaw was found in Foreman. This flaw allows an admin user to bypass safe mode in templates and execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0118|2024-05-03T15:32:29.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 13:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0119|2024-05-03T15:32:30.715Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20satellite%206.13%20for%20rhel%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0119</link>
      <description>A stored Cross-site scripting vulnerability was found in foreman. The Comment section in the Hosts tab has incorrect filtering of user input data. As a result of the attack, an attacker with an existing account on the system can steal another user's session, make requests on behalf of the user, and obtain user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0119|2024-05-03T15:32:30.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 15:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29499|2023-09-14T19:06:17.810Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-29499</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in GLib. GVariant deserialization fails to validate that the input conforms to the expected format, leading to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29499|2023-09-14T19:06:17.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 19:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4155|2023-09-13T16:11:39.213Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4155</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in KVM AMD Secure Encrypted Virtualization (SEV) in the Linux kernel. A KVM guest using SEV-ES or SEV-SNP with multiple vCPUs can trigger a double fetch race condition vulnerability and invoke the `VMGEXIT` handler recursively. If an attacker manages to call the handler multiple times, they can trigger a stack overflow and cause a denial of service or potentially guest-to-host escape in kernel configurations without stack guard pages (`CONFIG_VMAP_STACK`).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4155|2023-09-13T16:11:39.213Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 16:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4010|2024-04-25T12:57:43.962Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4010</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the USB Host Controller Driver framework in the Linux kernel. The usb_giveback_urb function has a logic loophole in its implementation. Due to the inappropriate judgment condition of the goto statement, the function cannot return under the input of a specific malformed descriptor file, so it falls into an endless loop, resulting in a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4010|2024-04-25T12:57:43.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 16:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4456|2024-06-04T17:27:25.132Z -- red%20hat -- rhol-5.5-rhel-8
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4456</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in openshift-logging LokiStack. The key used for caching is just the token, which is too broad. This issue allows a user with a token valid for one action to execute other actions as long as the authorization allowing the original action is still cached.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4456|2024-06-04T17:27:25.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 15:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4641|2024-05-03T15:32:38.166Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4641</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in shadow-utils. When asking for a new password, shadow-utils asks the password twice. If the password fails on the second attempt, shadow-utils fails in cleaning the buffer used to store the first entry. This may allow an attacker with enough access to retrieve the password from the memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4641|2024-05-03T15:32:38.166Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 15:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4732|2024-05-23T22:29:24.434Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4732</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in pfn_swap_entry_to_page in memory management subsystem in the Linux Kernel. In this flaw, an attacker with a local user privilege may cause a denial of service problem due to a BUG statement referencing pmd_t x.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4732|2024-05-23T22:29:24.434Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 16:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4066|2024-05-01T20:21:01.538Z -- red%20hat -- rhel-8%20based%20middleware%20containers
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4066</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Red Hat's AMQ Broker, which stores certain passwords in a secret security-properties-prop-module, defined in ActivemqArtemisSecurity CR; however, they are shown in plaintext in the StatefulSet details yaml of AMQ Broker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4066|2024-05-01T20:21:01.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4135|2024-01-23T01:32:54.867Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4135</link>
      <description>A heap out-of-bounds memory read flaw was found in the virtual nvme device in QEMU. The QEMU process does not validate an offset provided by the guest before computing a host heap pointer, which is used for copying data back to the guest. Arbitrary heap memory relative to an allocated buffer can be disclosed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4135|2024-01-23T01:32:54.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4586|2024-05-01T20:21:13.519Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20data%20grid%208.4.6
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4586</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in the Hot Rod client. This security issue occurs as the Hot Rod client does not enable hostname validation when using TLS, possibly resulting in a man-in-the-middle (MITM) attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4586|2024-05-01T20:21:13.519Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 10:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4569|2024-01-23T01:46:50.244Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4569</link>
      <description>A memory leak flaw was found in nft_set_catchall_flush in net/netfilter/nf_tables_api.c in the Linux Kernel. This issue may allow a local attacker to cause double-deactivations of catchall elements, which can result in a memory leak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4569|2024-01-23T01:46:50.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 21:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4154|2024-01-23T01:33:49.736Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4154</link>
      <description>A design flaw was found in Samba's DirSync control implementation, which exposes passwords and secrets in Active Directory to privileged users and Read-Only Domain Controllers (RODCs). This flaw allows RODCs and users possessing the GET_CHANGES right to access all attributes, including sensitive secrets and passwords. Even in a default setup, RODC DC accounts, which should only replicate some passwords, can gain access to all domain secrets, including the vital krbtgt, effectively eliminating the RODC / DC distinction. Furthermore, the vulnerability fails to account for error conditions (fail open), like out-of-memory situations, potentially granting access to secret attributes, even under low-privileged attacker influence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4154|2024-01-23T01:33:49.736Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 19:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4380|2024-05-01T20:21:11.534Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20ansible%20automation%20platform%202.4%20for%20rhel%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4380</link>
      <description>A logic flaw exists in Ansible Automation platform. Whenever a private project is created with incorrect credentials, they are logged in plaintext. This flaw allows an attacker to retrieve the credentials from the log, resulting in the loss of confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4380|2024-05-01T20:21:11.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 14:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4237|2024-05-01T20:21:06.124Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20ansible%20automation%20platform%202.4%20for%20rhel%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4237</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Ansible Automation Platform. When creating a new keypair, the ec2_key module prints out the private key directly to the standard output. This flaw allows an attacker to fetch those keys from the log files, compromising the system's confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4237|2024-05-01T20:21:06.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 14:23:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4958|2024-05-03T15:32:38.712Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20advanced%20cluster%20security%204.2
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4958</link>
      <description>In Red Hat Advanced Cluster Security (RHACS), it was found that some security related HTTP headers were missing, allowing an attacker to exploit this with a clickjacking attack. An attacker could exploit this by convincing a valid RHACS user to visit an attacker-controlled web page, that deceptively points to valid RHACS endpoints, hijacking the user's account permissions to perform other actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4958|2024-05-03T15:32:38.712Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 10:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4535|2024-05-01T20:21:13.171Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4535</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability was found in OpenSC packages within the MyEID driver when handling symmetric key encryption. Exploiting this flaw requires an attacker to have physical access to the computer and a specially crafted USB device or smart card. This flaw allows the attacker to manipulate APDU responses and potentially gain unauthorized access to sensitive data, compromising the system's security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4535|2024-05-01T20:21:13.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 16:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4132|2024-06-04T17:27:22.320Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4132</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability was found in the siano smsusb module in the Linux kernel. The bug occurs during device initialization when the siano device is plugged in. This flaw allows a local user to crash the system, causing a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4132|2024-06-04T17:27:22.320Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4061|2024-06-04T17:27:21.909Z -- red%20hat -- eap%207.4.13
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4061</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in wildfly-core. A management user could use the resolve-expression in the HAL Interface to read possible sensitive information from the Wildfly system. This issue could allow a malicious user to access the system and obtain possible sensitive information from the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4061|2024-06-04T17:27:21.909Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4692|2024-05-29T22:14:59.233Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4692</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write flaw was found in grub2's NTFS filesystem driver. This issue may allow an attacker to present a specially crafted NTFS filesystem image, leading to grub's heap metadata corruption. In some circumstances, the attack may also corrupt the UEFI firmware heap metadata. As a result, arbitrary code execution and secure boot protection bypass may be achieved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4692|2024-05-29T22:14:59.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4387|2024-04-25T14:03:03.337Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4387</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in vmxnet3_rq_alloc_rx_buf in drivers/net/vmxnet3/vmxnet3_drv.c in VMware's vmxnet3 ethernet NIC driver in the Linux Kernel. This issue could allow a local attacker to crash the system due to a double-free while cleaning up vmxnet3_rq_cleanup_all, which could also lead to a kernel information leak problem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4387|2024-04-25T14:03:03.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 18:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4503|2024-05-03T15:32:37.712Z -- red%20hat -- eap%207.4.14
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4503</link>
      <description>An improper initialization vulnerability was found in Galleon. When using Galleon to provision custom EAP or EAP-XP servers, the servers are created unsecured. This issue could allow an attacker to access remote HTTP services available from the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4503|2024-05-03T15:32:37.712Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 08:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4611|2024-01-23T01:56:22.319Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4611</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in mm/mempolicy.c in the memory management subsystem in the Linux Kernel. This issue is caused by a race between mbind() and VMA-locked page fault, and may allow a local attacker to crash the system or lead to a kernel information leak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4611|2024-01-23T01:56:22.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 21:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4001|2024-05-01T20:20:56.178Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4001</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass flaw was found in GRUB due to the way that GRUB uses the UUID of a device to search for the configuration file that contains the password hash for the GRUB password protection feature. An attacker capable of attaching an external drive such as a USB stick containing a file system with a duplicate UUID (the same as in the "/boot/" file system) can bypass the GRUB password protection feature on UEFI systems, which enumerate removable drives before non-removable ones. This issue was introduced in a downstream patch in Red Hat's version of grub2 and does not affect the upstream package.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4001|2024-05-01T20:20:56.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 11:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4693|2024-05-29T22:15:06.298Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4693</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read flaw was found on grub2's NTFS filesystem driver. This issue may allow a physically present attacker to present a specially crafted NTFS file system image to read arbitrary memory locations. A successful attack allows sensitive data cached in memory or EFI variable values to be leaked, presenting a high Confidentiality risk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4693|2024-05-29T22:15:06.298Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4806|2024-05-23T22:29:52.161Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4806</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in glibc. In an extremely rare situation, the getaddrinfo function may access memory that has been freed, resulting in an application crash. This issue is only exploitable when a NSS module implements only the _nss_*_gethostbyname2_r and _nss_*_getcanonname_r hooks without implementing the _nss_*_gethostbyname3_r hook. The resolved name should return a large number of IPv6 and IPv4, and the call to the getaddrinfo function should have the AF_INET6 address family with AI_CANONNAME, AI_ALL and AI_V4MAPPED as flags.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4806|2024-05-23T22:29:52.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 16:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4133|2024-05-29T22:14:40.537Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4133</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability was found in the cxgb4 driver in the Linux kernel. The bug occurs when the cxgb4 device is detaching due to a possible rearming of the flower_stats_timer from the work queue. This flaw allows a local user to crash the system, causing a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4133|2024-05-29T22:14:40.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4959|2024-04-25T14:45:10.243Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20quay%203
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4959</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Quay. Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks force a user to perform unwanted actions in an application. During the pentest, it was detected that the config-editor page is vulnerable to CSRF. The config-editor page is used to configure the Quay instance. By coercing the victim’s browser into sending an attacker-controlled request from another domain, it is possible to reconfigure the Quay instance (including adding users with admin privileges).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4959|2024-04-25T14:45:10.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 09:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4918|2024-01-23T00:56:17.069Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20single%20sign-on%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4918</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Keycloak package, more specifically org.keycloak.userprofile. When a user registers itself through registration flow, the "password" and "password-confirm" field from the form will occur as regular user attributes. All users and clients with proper rights and roles are able to read users attributes, allowing a malicious user with minimal access to retrieve the users passwords in clear text, jeopardizing their environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4918|2024-01-23T00:56:17.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 19:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4389|2024-01-31T14:07:09.149Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4389</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in btrfs_get_root_ref in fs/btrfs/disk-io.c in the btrfs filesystem in the Linux Kernel due to a double decrement of the reference count. This issue may allow a local attacker with user privilege to crash the system or may lead to leaked internal kernel information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4389|2024-01-31T14:07:09.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 18:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4956|2024-04-25T14:44:40.147Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20quay%203
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4956</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Quay. Clickjacking is when an attacker uses multiple transparent or opaque layers to trick a user into clicking on a button or link on another page when they intend to click on the top-level page. During the pentest, it has been detected that the config-editor page is vulnerable to clickjacking. This flaw allows an attacker to trick an administrator user into clicking on buttons on the config-editor panel, possibly reconfiguring some parts of the Quay instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4956|2024-04-25T14:44:40.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 19:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4813|2024-05-23T22:30:56.442Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4813</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in glibc. In an uncommon situation, the gaih_inet function may use memory that has been freed, resulting in an application crash. This issue is only exploitable when the getaddrinfo function is called and the hosts database in /etc/nsswitch.conf is configured with SUCCESS=continue or SUCCESS=merge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4813|2024-05-23T22:30:56.442Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 21:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4147|2024-05-01T20:21:05.566Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4147</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the Linux kernel’s Netfilter functionality when adding a rule with NFTA_RULE_CHAIN_ID. This flaw allows a local user to crash or escalate their privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4147|2024-05-01T20:21:05.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 13:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4385|2024-04-25T14:02:39.197Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4385</link>
      <description>A NULL pointer dereference flaw was found in dbFree in fs/jfs/jfs_dmap.c in the journaling file system (JFS) in the Linux Kernel. This issue may allow a local attacker to crash the system due to a missing sanity check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4385|2024-04-25T14:02:39.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 16:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4042|2024-05-01T20:20:57.505Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4042</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in ghostscript. The fix for CVE-2020-16305 in ghostscript was not included in RHSA-2021:1852-06 advisory as it was claimed to be. This issue only affects the ghostscript package as shipped with Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4042|2024-05-01T20:20:57.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 12:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4853|2024-05-01T20:21:18.280Z -- red%20hat -- openshift%20serverless%201%20on%20rhel%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4853</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Quarkus where HTTP security policies are not sanitizing certain character permutations correctly when accepting requests, resulting in incorrect evaluation of permissions. This issue could allow an attacker to bypass the security policy altogether, resulting in unauthorized endpoint access and possibly a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4853|2024-05-01T20:21:18.280Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 09:47:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4886|2024-05-01T20:21:18.254Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20satellite%206.13%20for%20rhel%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4886</link>
      <description>A sensitive information exposure vulnerability was found in foreman. Contents of tomcat's server.xml file, which contain passwords to candlepin's keystore and truststore, were found to be world readable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4886|2024-05-01T20:21:18.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 14:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4194|2024-05-23T21:15:58.026Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4194</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's TUN/TAP functionality. This issue could allow a local user to bypass network filters and gain unauthorized access to some resources. The original patches fixing CVE-2023-1076 are incorrect or incomplete. The problem is that the following upstream commits - a096ccca6e50 ("tun: tun_chr_open(): correctly initialize socket uid"), - 66b2c338adce ("tap: tap_open(): correctly initialize socket uid"), pass "inode-&gt;i_uid" to sock_init_data_uid() as the last parameter and that turns out to not be accurate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4194|2024-05-23T21:15:58.026Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 13:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4004|2024-05-23T22:37:33.655Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4004</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the Linux kernel's netfilter in the way a user triggers the nft_pipapo_remove function with the element, without a NFT_SET_EXT_KEY_END. This issue could allow a local user to crash the system or potentially escalate their privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4004|2024-05-23T22:37:33.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 16:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4911|2024-05-23T19:33:10.799Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4911</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow was discovered in the GNU C Library's dynamic loader ld.so while processing the GLIBC_TUNABLES environment variable. This issue could allow a local attacker to use maliciously crafted GLIBC_TUNABLES environment variables when launching binaries with SUID permission to execute code with elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4911|2024-05-23T19:33:10.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 17:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4527|2024-05-01T20:21:12.525Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4527</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in glibc. When the getaddrinfo function is called with the AF_UNSPEC address family and the system is configured with no-aaaa mode via /etc/resolv.conf, a DNS response via TCP larger than 2048 bytes can potentially disclose stack contents through the function returned address data, and may cause a crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4527|2024-05-01T20:21:12.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 16:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4065|2024-06-04T17:27:15.178Z -- red%20hat -- rhel-8%20based%20middleware%20containers
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4065</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Red Hat AMQ Broker Operator, where it displayed a password defined in ActiveMQArtemisAddress CR, shown in plain text in the Operator Log. This flaw allows an authenticated local attacker to access information outside of their permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4065|2024-06-04T17:27:15.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 13:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4273|2024-05-01T20:21:06.606Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4273</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the exFAT driver of the Linux kernel. The vulnerability exists in the implementation of the file name reconstruction function, which is responsible for reading file name entries from a directory index and merging file name parts belonging to one file into a single long file name. Since the file name characters are copied into a stack variable, a local privileged attacker could use this flaw to overflow the kernel stack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4273|2024-05-01T20:21:06.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 14:53:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4320|2024-05-01T20:21:08.549Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20satellite%206.15%20for%20rhel%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4320</link>
      <description>An arithmetic overflow flaw was found in Satellite when creating a new personal access token. This flaw allows an attacker who uses this arithmetic overflow to create personal access tokens that are valid indefinitely, resulting in damage to the system's integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4320|2024-05-01T20:21:08.549Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4459|2024-05-23T22:28:24.983Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208.2%20advanced%20update%20support
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4459</link>
      <description>A NULL pointer dereference flaw was found in vmxnet3_rq_cleanup in drivers/net/vmxnet3/vmxnet3_drv.c in the networking sub-component in vmxnet3 in the Linux Kernel. This issue may allow a local attacker with normal user privilege to cause a denial of service due to a missing sanity check during cleanup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4459|2024-05-23T22:28:24.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 18:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4727|2024-06-11T20:44:08.706Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20certificate%20system%2010
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4727</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in dogtag-pki and pki-core. The token authentication scheme can be bypassed with a LDAP injection. By passing the query string parameter sessionID=*, an attacker can authenticate with an existing session saved in the LDAP directory server, which may lead to escalation of privilege.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4727|2024-06-11T20:44:08.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 19:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4910|2024-06-04T17:27:12.993Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%203scale%20api%20management%20platform%202
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4910</link>
      <description>A flaw was found In 3Scale Admin Portal. If a user logs out from the personal tokens page and then presses the back button in the browser, the tokens page is rendered from the browser cache.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4910|2024-06-04T17:27:12.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4156|2023-09-25T17:20:19.377Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4156</link>
      <description>A heap out-of-bounds read flaw was found in builtin.c in the gawk package. This issue may lead to a crash and could be used to read sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4156|2023-09-25T17:20:19.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 17:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4394|2024-01-23T01:41:31.767Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4394</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in btrfs_get_dev_args_from_path in fs/btrfs/volumes.c in btrfs file-system in the Linux Kernel. This flaw allows a local attacker with special privileges to cause a system crash or leak internal kernel information</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4394|2024-01-23T01:41:31.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 12:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4091|2024-06-04T17:27:11.711Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4091</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was discovered in Samba, where the flaw allows SMB clients to truncate files, even with read-only permissions when the Samba VFS module "acl_xattr" is configured with "acl_xattr:ignore system acls = yes". The SMB protocol allows opening files when the client requests read-only access but then implicitly truncates the opened file to 0 bytes if the client specifies a separate OVERWRITE create disposition request. The issue arises in configurations that bypass kernel file system permissions checks, relying solely on Samba's permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4091|2024-06-04T17:27:11.711Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 07:56:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39192|2024-06-04T17:27:09.160Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39192</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Netfilter subsystem in the Linux kernel. The xt_u32 module did not validate the fields in the xt_u32 structure. This flaw allows a local privileged attacker to trigger an out-of-bounds read by setting the size fields with a value beyond the array boundaries, leading to a crash or information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39192|2024-06-04T17:27:09.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 17:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39193|2024-05-22T16:40:54.180Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39193</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Netfilter subsystem in the Linux kernel. The sctp_mt_check did not validate the flag_count field. This flaw allows a local privileged (CAP_NET_ADMIN) attacker to trigger an out-of-bounds read, leading to a crash or information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39193|2024-05-22T16:40:54.180Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 17:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39189|2024-05-29T23:15:12.698Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39189</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Netfilter subsystem in the Linux kernel. The nfnl_osf_add_callback function did not validate the user mode controlled opt_num field. This flaw allows a local privileged (CAP_NET_ADMIN) attacker to trigger an out-of-bounds read, leading to a crash or information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39189|2024-05-29T23:15:12.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 17:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39194|2024-05-29T23:15:38.922Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39194</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the XFRM subsystem in the Linux kernel. The specific flaw exists within the processing of state filters, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. This flaw allows a local privileged (CAP_NET_ADMIN) attacker to trigger an out-of-bounds read, potentially leading to an information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39194|2024-05-29T23:15:38.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 17:57:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39198|2024-05-29T23:15:41.523Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39198</link>
      <description>A race condition was found in the QXL driver in the Linux kernel. The qxl_mode_dumb_create() function dereferences the qobj returned by the qxl_gem_object_create_with_handle(), but the handle is the only one holding a reference to it. This flaw allows an attacker to guess the returned handle value and trigger a use-after-free issue, potentially leading to a denial of service or privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39198|2024-05-29T23:15:41.523Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 19:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39418|2024-05-01T20:20:54.196Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39418</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PostgreSQL with the use of the MERGE command, which fails to test new rows against row security policies defined for UPDATE and SELECT. If UPDATE and SELECT policies forbid some rows that INSERT policies do not forbid, a user could store such rows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39418|2024-05-01T20:20:54.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39417|2024-05-01T20:20:54.402Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20advanced%20cluster%20security%204.2
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39417</link>
      <description>IN THE EXTENSION SCRIPT, a SQL Injection vulnerability was found in PostgreSQL if it uses @extowner@, @extschema@, or @extschema:...@ inside a quoting construct (dollar quoting, '', or ""). If an administrator has installed files of a vulnerable, trusted, non-bundled extension, an attacker with database-level CREATE privilege can execute arbitrary code as the bootstrap superuser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39417|2024-05-01T20:20:54.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39197|2024-04-25T13:24:20.911Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39197</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability was found in Netfilter Connection Tracking (conntrack) in the Linux kernel. This flaw allows a remote user to disclose sensitive information via the DCCP protocol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39197|2024-04-25T13:24:20.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 03:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39191|2024-05-01T20:20:52.222Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39191</link>
      <description>An improper input validation flaw was found in the eBPF subsystem in the Linux kernel. The issue occurs due to a lack of proper validation of dynamic pointers within user-supplied eBPF programs prior to executing them. This may allow an attacker with CAP_BPF privileges to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the kernel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39191|2024-05-01T20:20:52.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 18:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-47039|2024-03-28T14:05:42.607Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-47039</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Perl. This security issue occurs while Perl for Windows relies on the system path environment variable to find the shell (`cmd.exe`). When running an executable that uses the Windows Perl interpreter, Perl attempts to find and execute `cmd.exe` within the operating system. However, due to path search order issues, Perl initially looks for cmd.exe in the current working directory. This flaw allows an attacker with limited privileges to place`cmd.exe` in locations with weak permissions, such as `C:\ProgramData`. By doing so, arbitrary code can be executed when an administrator attempts to use this executable from these compromised locations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-47039|2024-03-28T14:05:42.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-47038|2024-05-30T14:07:03.418Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-47038</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in perl 5.30.0 through 5.38.0. This issue occurs when a crafted regular expression is compiled by perl, which can allow an attacker controlled byte buffer overflow in a heap allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-47038|2024-05-30T14:07:03.418Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32248|2024-01-23T03:27:39.926Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32248</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ksmbd, a high-performance in-kernel SMB server. The specific flaw exists within the handling of SMB2_TREE_CONNECT and SMB2_QUERY_INFO commands. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a pointer prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32248|2024-01-23T03:27:39.926Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32252|2024-01-23T03:28:10.819Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32252</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ksmbd, a high-performance in-kernel SMB server. The specific flaw exists within the handling of SMB2_LOGOFF commands. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a pointer prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32252|2024-01-23T03:28:10.819Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32254|2023-07-10T15:11:25.707Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32254</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ksmbd, a high-performance in-kernel SMB server. The specific flaw exists within the processing of SMB2_TREE_DISCONNECT commands. The issue results from the lack of proper locking when performing operations on an object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the kernel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32254|2023-07-10T15:11:25.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 15:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32258|2024-01-23T03:29:15.355Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32258</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ksmbd, a high-performance in-kernel SMB server. The specific flaw exists within the processing of SMB2_LOGOFF and SMB2_CLOSE commands. The issue results from the lack of proper locking when performing operations on an object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the kernel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32258|2024-01-23T03:29:15.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32665|2023-09-14T19:03:58.229Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32665</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in GLib. GVariant deserialization is vulnerable to an exponential blowup issue where a crafted GVariant can cause excessive processing, leading to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32665|2023-09-14T19:03:58.229Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 19:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32627|2023-07-10T17:15:42.063Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32627</link>
      <description>A floating point exception vulnerability was found in sox, in the read_samples function at sox/src/voc.c:334:18. This flaw can lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32627|2023-07-10T17:15:42.063Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 17:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32257|2024-01-23T03:30:20.769Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32257</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ksmbd, a high-performance in-kernel SMB server. The specific flaw exists within the processing of SMB2_SESSION_SETUP and SMB2_LOGOFF commands. The issue results from the lack of proper locking when performing operations on an object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the kernel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32257|2024-01-23T03:30:20.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32611|2023-09-14T19:07:19.011Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32611</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in GLib. GVariant deserialization is vulnerable to a slowdown issue where a crafted GVariant can cause excessive processing, leading to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32611|2023-09-14T19:07:19.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 19:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32247|2024-01-23T03:27:09.893Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32247</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ksmbd, a high-performance in-kernel SMB server. The specific flaw exists within the handling of SMB2_SESSION_SETUP commands. The issue results from the lack of control of resource consumption. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32247|2024-01-23T03:27:09.893Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32250|2023-07-10T15:09:37.474Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32250</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ksmbd, a high-performance in-kernel SMB server. The specific flaw exists within the processing of SMB2_SESSION_SETUP commands. The issue results from the lack of proper locking when performing operations on an object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the kernel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32250|2023-07-10T15:09:37.474Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 15:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43789|2024-05-29T22:22:20.308Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43789</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in libXpm where a vulnerability exists due to a boundary condition, a local user can trigger an out-of-bounds read error and read contents of memory on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43789|2024-05-29T22:22:20.308Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 11:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43785|2024-06-04T17:26:00.384Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43785</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in libX11 due to a boundary condition within the _XkbReadKeySyms() function. This flaw allows a local user to trigger an out-of-bounds read error and read the contents of memory on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43785|2024-06-04T17:26:00.384Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 12:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43788|2024-05-29T22:22:18.680Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43788</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in libXpm due to a boundary condition within the XpmCreateXpmImageFromBuffer() function. This flaw allows a local attacker to trigger an out-of-bounds read error and read the contents of memory on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43788|2024-05-29T22:22:18.680Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 12:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43787|2024-05-29T22:21:56.846Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43787</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in libX11 due to an integer overflow within the XCreateImage() function. This flaw allows a local user to trigger an integer overflow and execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43787|2024-05-29T22:21:56.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 12:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43786|2024-06-04T17:25:57.723Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43786</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in libX11 due to an infinite loop within the PutSubImage() function. This flaw allows a local user to consume all available system resources and cause a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43786|2024-06-04T17:25:57.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 12:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26590|2023-07-10T17:14:14.297Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26590</link>
      <description>A floating point exception vulnerability was found in sox, in the lsx_aiffstartwrite function at sox/src/aiff.c:622:58. This flaw can lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26590|2023-07-10T17:14:14.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 17:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42669|2024-05-23T21:18:30.190Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42669</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Samba's "rpcecho" development server, a non-Windows RPC server used to test Samba's DCE/RPC stack elements. This vulnerability stems from an RPC function that can be blocked indefinitely. The issue arises because the "rpcecho" service operates with only one worker in the main RPC task, allowing calls to the "rpcecho" server to be blocked for a specified time, causing service disruptions. This disruption is triggered by a "sleep()" call in the "dcesrv_echo_TestSleep()" function under specific conditions. Authenticated users or attackers can exploit this vulnerability to make calls to the "rpcecho" server, requesting it to block for a specified duration, effectively disrupting most services and leading to a complete denial of service on the AD DC. The DoS affects all other services as "rpcecho" runs in the main RPC task.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42669|2024-05-23T21:18:30.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 06:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42756|2024-05-01T20:21:08.205Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42756</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Netfilter subsystem of the Linux kernel. A race condition between IPSET_CMD_ADD and IPSET_CMD_SWAP can lead to a kernel panic due to the invocation of `__ip_set_put` on a wrong `set`. This issue may allow a local user to crash the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42756|2024-05-01T20:21:08.205Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 13:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42753|2024-05-23T21:19:24.462Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42753</link>
      <description>An array indexing vulnerability was found in the netfilter subsystem of the Linux kernel. A missing macro could lead to a miscalculation of the `h-&gt;nets` array offset, providing attackers with the primitive to arbitrarily increment/decrement a memory buffer out-of-bound. This issue may allow a local user to crash the system or potentially escalate their privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42753|2024-05-23T21:19:24.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 20:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42752|2024-01-23T02:24:21.308Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42752</link>
      <description>An integer overflow flaw was found in the Linux kernel. This issue leads to the kernel allocating `skb_shared_info` in the userspace, which is exploitable in systems without SMAP protection since `skb_shared_info` contains references to function pointers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42752|2024-01-23T02:24:21.308Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 01:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42755|2024-05-29T23:16:47.579Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42755</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the IPv4 Resource Reservation Protocol (RSVP) classifier in the Linux kernel. The xprt pointer may go beyond the linear part of the skb, leading to an out-of-bounds read in the `rsvp_classify` function. This issue may allow a local user to crash the system and cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42755|2024-05-29T23:16:47.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 18:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42670|2024-01-23T02:23:44.541Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42670</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Samba. It is susceptible to a vulnerability where multiple incompatible RPC listeners can be initiated, causing disruptions in the AD DC service. When Samba's RPC server experiences a high load or unresponsiveness, servers intended for non-AD DC purposes (for example, NT4-emulation "classic DCs") can erroneously start and compete for the same unix domain sockets. This issue leads to partial query responses from the AD DC, causing issues such as "The procedure number is out of range" when using tools like Active Directory Users. This flaw allows an attacker to disrupt AD DC services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42670|2024-01-23T02:23:44.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 07:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42754|2024-05-22T16:41:29.829Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42754</link>
      <description>A NULL pointer dereference flaw was found in the Linux kernel ipv4 stack. The socket buffer (skb) was assumed to be associated with a device before calling __ip_options_compile, which is not always the case if the skb is re-routed by ipvs. This issue may allow a local user with CAP_NET_ADMIN privileges to crash the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42754|2024-05-22T16:41:29.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 18:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-52356|2024-04-25T15:16:53.813Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-52356</link>
      <description>A segment fault (SEGV) flaw was found in libtiff that could be triggered by passing a crafted tiff file to the TIFFReadRGBATileExt() API. This flaw allows a remote attacker to cause a heap-buffer overflow, leading to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-52356|2024-04-25T15:16:53.813Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 20:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-52355|2024-04-25T15:16:31.162Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-52355</link>
      <description>An out-of-memory flaw was found in libtiff that could be triggered by passing a crafted tiff file to the TIFFRasterScanlineSize64() API. This flaw allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted input with a size smaller than 379 KB.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-52355|2024-04-25T15:16:31.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 20:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46846|2024-05-01T20:21:14.467Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-46846</link>
      <description>SQUID is vulnerable to HTTP request smuggling, caused by chunked decoder lenience, allows a remote attacker to perform Request/Response smuggling past firewall and frontend security systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46846|2024-05-01T20:21:14.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 07:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46847|2024-05-01T20:21:14.811Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206%20extended%20lifecycle%20support
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-46847</link>
      <description>Squid is vulnerable to a Denial of Service,  where a remote attacker can perform buffer overflow attack by writing up to 2 MB of arbitrary data to heap memory when Squid is configured to accept HTTP Digest Authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46847|2024-05-01T20:21:14.811Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 07:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46848|2024-05-01T20:21:15.525Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-46848</link>
      <description>Squid is vulnerable to Denial of Service,  where a remote attacker can perform DoS by sending ftp:// URLs in HTTP Request messages or constructing ftp:// URLs from FTP Native input.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46848|2024-05-01T20:21:15.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 07:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33951|2024-06-04T17:22:07.492Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33951</link>
      <description>A race condition vulnerability was found in the vmwgfx driver in the Linux kernel. The flaw exists within the handling of GEM objects. The issue results from improper locking when performing operations on an object. This flaw allows a local privileged user to disclose information in the context of the kernel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33951|2024-06-04T17:22:07.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33952|2024-05-01T20:20:41.059Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33952</link>
      <description>A double-free vulnerability was found in handling vmw_buffer_object objects in the vmwgfx driver in the Linux kernel. This issue occurs due to the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing further free operations on the object, which may allow a local privileged user to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the kernel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33952|2024-05-01T20:20:41.059Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41175|2024-06-04T17:21:32.785Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41175</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in libtiff due to multiple potential integer overflows in raw2tiff.c. This flaw allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service or possibly execute an arbitrary code via a crafted tiff image, which triggers a heap-based buffer overflow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41175|2024-06-04T17:21:32.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 18:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34968|2024-05-23T23:12:38.765Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34968</link>
      <description>A path disclosure vulnerability was found in Samba. As part of the Spotlight protocol, Samba discloses the server-side absolute path of shares, files, and directories in the results for search queries. This flaw allows a malicious client or an attacker with a targeted RPC request to view the information that is part of the disclosed path.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34968|2024-05-23T23:12:38.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34318|2023-07-10T17:16:59.692Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34318</link>
      <description>A heap buffer overflow vulnerability was found in sox, in the startread function at sox/src/hcom.c:160:41. This flaw can lead to a denial of service, code execution, or information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34318|2023-07-10T17:16:59.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 17:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34966|2024-05-23T23:11:39.953Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34966</link>
      <description>An infinite loop vulnerability was found in Samba's mdssvc RPC service for Spotlight. When parsing Spotlight mdssvc RPC packets sent by the client, the core unmarshalling function sl_unpack_loop() did not validate a field in the network packet that contains the count of elements in an array-like structure. By passing 0 as the count value, the attacked function will run in an endless loop consuming 100% CPU. This flaw allows an attacker to issue a malformed RPC request, triggering an infinite loop, resulting in a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34966|2024-05-23T23:11:39.953Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34967|2024-05-23T23:12:10.750Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34967</link>
      <description>A Type Confusion vulnerability was found in Samba's mdssvc RPC service for Spotlight. When parsing Spotlight mdssvc RPC packets, one encoded data structure is a key-value style dictionary where the keys are character strings, and the values can be any of the supported types in the mdssvc protocol. Due to a lack of type checking in callers of the dalloc_value_for_key() function, which returns the object associated with a key, a caller may trigger a crash in talloc_get_size() when talloc detects that the passed-in pointer is not a valid talloc pointer. With an RPC worker process shared among multiple client connections, a malicious client or attacker can trigger a process crash in a shared RPC mdssvc worker process, affecting all other clients this worker serves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34967|2024-05-23T23:12:10.750Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34432|2023-07-10T20:05:39.681Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34432</link>
      <description>A heap buffer overflow vulnerability was found in sox, in the lsx_readbuf function at sox/src/formats_i.c:98:16. This flaw can lead to a denial of service, code execution, or information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34432|2023-07-10T20:05:39.681Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40547|2024-05-08T08:21:56.201Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40547</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability was found in Shim. The Shim boot support trusts attacker-controlled values when parsing an HTTP response. This flaw allows an attacker to craft a specific malicious HTTP request, leading to a completely controlled out-of-bounds write primitive and complete system compromise. This flaw is only exploitable during the early boot phase, an attacker needs to perform a Man-in-the-Middle or compromise the boot server to be able to exploit this vulnerability successfully.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40547|2024-05-08T08:21:56.201Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 15:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40551|2024-05-01T20:21:00.322Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40551</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the MZ binary format in Shim. An out-of-bounds read may occur, leading to a crash or possible exposure of sensitive data during the system's boot phase.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40551|2024-05-01T20:21:00.322Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40550|2024-05-01T20:20:59.624Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40550</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read flaw was found in Shim when it tried to validate the SBAT information. This issue may expose sensitive data during the system's boot phase.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40550|2024-05-01T20:20:59.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40546|2024-05-01T20:20:57.623Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40546</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Shim when an error happened while creating a new ESL variable. If Shim fails to create the new variable, it tries to print an error message to the user; however, the number of parameters used by the logging function doesn't match the format string used by it, leading to a crash under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40546|2024-05-01T20:20:57.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40660|2024-05-01T20:21:01.533Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40660</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in OpenSC packages that allow a potential PIN bypass. When a token/card is authenticated by one process, it can perform cryptographic operations in other processes when an empty zero-length pin is passed. This issue poses a security risk, particularly for OS logon/screen unlock and for small, permanently connected tokens to computers. Additionally, the token can internally track login status. This flaw allows an attacker to gain unauthorized access, carry out malicious actions, or compromise the system without the user's awareness.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40660|2024-05-01T20:21:01.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 16:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40549|2024-05-01T20:20:59.582Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40549</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read flaw was found in Shim due to the lack of proper boundary verification during the load of a PE binary. This flaw allows an attacker to load a crafted PE binary, triggering the issue and crashing Shim, resulting in a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40549|2024-05-01T20:20:59.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40548|2024-05-08T08:23:58.318Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40548</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow was found in Shim in the 32-bit system. The overflow happens due to an addition operation involving a user-controlled value parsed from the PE binary being used by Shim. This value is further used for memory allocation operations, leading to a heap-based buffer overflow. This flaw causes memory corruption and can lead to a crash or data integrity issues during the boot phase.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40548|2024-05-08T08:23:58.318Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:53:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40661|2024-05-01T20:21:02.210Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40661</link>
      <description>Several memory vulnerabilities were identified within the OpenSC packages, particularly in the card enrollment process using pkcs15-init when a user or administrator enrolls cards. To take advantage of these flaws, an attacker must have physical access to the computer system and employ a custom-crafted USB device or smart card to manipulate responses to APDUs. This manipulation can potentially allow &#13;
compromise key generation, certificate loading, and other card management operations during enrollment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40661|2024-05-01T20:21:02.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 16:58:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40745|2024-05-01T20:21:02.220Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40745</link>
      <description>LibTIFF is vulnerable to an integer overflow. This flaw allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (application crash) or possibly execute an arbitrary code via a crafted tiff image, which triggers a heap-based buffer overflow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40745|2024-05-01T20:21:02.220Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 18:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25586|2023-09-14T20:49:15.468Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-25586</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Binutils. A logic fail in the bfd_init_section_decompress_status function may lead to the use of an uninitialized variable that can cause a crash and local denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25586|2023-09-14T20:49:15.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 20:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25588|2023-09-14T20:47:16.974Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-25588</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Binutils. The field `the_bfd` of `asymbol`struct is uninitialized in the `bfd_mach_o_get_synthetic_symtab` function, which may lead to an application crash and local denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25588|2023-09-14T20:47:16.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 20:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25584|2023-09-14T20:50:58.267Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-25584</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read flaw was found in the parse_module function in bfd/vms-alpha.c in Binutils.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25584|2023-09-14T20:50:58.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 20:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25585|2023-09-14T20:50:09.526Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-25585</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Binutils. The use of an uninitialized field in the struct module *module may lead to application crash and local denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25585|2023-09-14T20:50:09.526Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 20:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50782|2024-04-25T15:12:41.545Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20ansible%20automation%20platform%202
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50782</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the python-cryptography package. This issue may allow a remote attacker to decrypt captured messages in TLS servers that use RSA key exchanges, which may lead to exposure of confidential or sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50782|2024-04-25T15:12:41.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 20:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50781|2024-05-23T22:33:24.337Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50781</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in m2crypto. This issue may allow a remote attacker to decrypt captured messages in TLS servers that use RSA key exchanges, which may lead to exposure of confidential or sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50781|2024-05-23T22:33:24.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 20:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3628|2024-05-01T20:20:46.528Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20data%20grid%208.4.4
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3628</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Infinispan's REST. Bulk read endpoints do not properly evaluate user permissions for the operation. This issue could allow an authenticated user to access information outside of their intended permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3628|2024-05-01T20:20:46.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3106|2024-04-25T11:44:28.571Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3106</link>
      <description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability was found in netlink_dump. This issue can occur when the Netlink socket receives the message(sendmsg) for the XFRM_MSG_GETSA, XFRM_MSG_GETPOLICY type message, and the DUMP flag is set and can cause a denial of service or possibly another unspecified impact. Due to the nature of the flaw, privilege escalation cannot be fully ruled out, although it is unlikely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3106|2024-04-25T11:44:28.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 08:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3223|2024-05-03T15:32:37.244Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20fuse%207.12.1
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3223</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in undertow. Servlets annotated with @MultipartConfig may cause an OutOfMemoryError due to large multipart content. This may allow unauthorized users to cause remote Denial of Service (DoS) attack. If the server uses fileSizeThreshold to limit the file size, it's possible to bypass the limit by setting the file name in the request to null.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3223|2024-05-03T15:32:37.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 13:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3171|2024-05-03T15:32:36.759Z -- red%20hat -- eap%207.4.13
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3171</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in EAP-7 during deserialization of certain classes, which permits instantiation of HashMap and HashTable with no checks on resources consumed. This issue could allow an attacker to submit malicious requests using these classes, which could eventually exhaust the heap and result in a Denial of Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3171|2024-05-03T15:32:36.759Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 15:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3576|2024-05-01T20:20:46.048Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3576</link>
      <description>A memory leak flaw was found in Libtiff's tiffcrop utility. This issue occurs when tiffcrop operates on a TIFF image file, allowing an attacker to pass a crafted TIFF image file to tiffcrop utility, which causes this memory leak issue, resulting an application crash, eventually leading to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3576|2024-05-01T20:20:46.048Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 18:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3961|2024-05-23T22:33:44.493Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3961</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability was identified in Samba when processing client pipe names connecting to Unix domain sockets within a private directory. Samba typically uses this mechanism to connect SMB clients to remote procedure call (RPC) services like SAMR LSA or SPOOLSS, which Samba initiates on demand. However, due to inadequate sanitization of incoming client pipe names, allowing a client to send a pipe name containing Unix directory traversal characters (../). This could result in SMB clients connecting as root to Unix domain sockets outside the private directory. If an attacker or client managed to send a pipe name resolving to an external service using an existing Unix domain socket, it could potentially lead to unauthorized access to the service and consequential adverse events, including compromise or service crashes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3961|2024-05-23T22:33:44.493Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 12:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3019|2024-05-01T20:20:36.175Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3019</link>
      <description>A DMA reentrancy issue leading to a use-after-free error was found in the e1000e NIC emulation code in QEMU. This issue could allow a privileged guest user to crash the QEMU process on the host, resulting in a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3019|2024-05-01T20:20:36.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3347|2024-06-04T17:17:36.560Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3347</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Samba's SMB2 packet signing mechanism. The SMB2 packet signing is not enforced if an admin configured "server signing = required" or for SMB2 connections to Domain Controllers where SMB2 packet signing is mandatory. This flaw allows an attacker to perform attacks, such as a man-in-the-middle attack, by intercepting the network traffic and modifying the SMB2 messages between client and server, affecting the integrity of the data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3347|2024-06-04T17:17:36.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3255|2024-05-29T22:14:09.966Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3255</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the QEMU built-in VNC server while processing ClientCutText messages. A wrong exit condition may lead to an infinite loop when inflating an attacker controlled zlib buffer in the `inflate_buffer` function. This could allow a remote authenticated client who is able to send a clipboard to the VNC server to trigger a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3255|2024-05-29T22:14:09.966Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 16:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3428|2024-04-25T12:18:09.067Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3428</link>
      <description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability was found  in coders/tiff.c in ImageMagick. This issue may allow a local attacker to trick the user into opening a specially crafted file, resulting in an application crash and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3428|2024-04-25T12:18:09.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 18:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3812|2024-05-23T22:48:09.561Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3812</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds memory access flaw was found in the Linux kernel’s TUN/TAP device driver functionality in how a user generates a malicious (too big) networking packet when napi frags is enabled. This flaw allows a local user to crash or potentially escalate their privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3812|2024-05-23T22:48:09.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3384|2024-06-04T17:17:35.326Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20quay%203
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3384</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Quay registry. While the image labels created through Quay undergo validation both in the UI and backend by applying a regex (validation.py), the same validation is&#13;
not performed when the label comes from an image. This flaw allows an attacker to publish a malicious image to a public registry containing a script that can be executed via Cross-site scripting (XSS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3384|2024-06-04T17:17:35.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3629|2024-05-01T20:20:46.805Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20data%20grid%208.4.4
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3629</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Infinispan's REST, Cache retrieval endpoints do not properly evaluate the necessary admin permissions for the operation. This issue could allow an authenticated user to access information outside of their intended permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3629|2024-05-01T20:20:46.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3618|2023-08-08T16:50:48.957Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3618</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in libtiff. A specially crafted tiff file can lead to a segmentation fault due to a buffer overflow in the Fax3Encode function in libtiff/tif_fax3.c, resulting in a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3618|2023-08-08T16:50:48.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 14:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3966|2024-02-22T12:15:53.128Z -- red%20hat -- fast%20datapath%20for%20rhel%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3966</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Open vSwitch where multiple versions are vulnerable to crafted Geneve packets, which may result in a denial of service and invalid memory accesses. Triggering this issue requires that hardware offloading via the netlink path is enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3966|2024-02-22T12:15:53.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 12:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3301|2023-09-13T16:09:36.861Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3301</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in QEMU. The async nature of hot-unplug enables a race scenario where the net device backend is cleared before the virtio-net pci frontend has been unplugged. A malicious guest could use this time window to trigger an assertion and cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3301|2023-09-13T16:09:36.861Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 16:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3603|2024-01-23T00:58:36.996Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3603</link>
      <description>A missing allocation check in sftp server processing read requests may cause a NULL dereference on low-memory conditions. The malicious client can request up to 4GB SFTP reads, causing allocation of up to 4GB buffers, which was not being checked for failure. This will likely crash the authenticated user's sftp server connection (if implemented as forking as recommended). For thread-based servers, this might also cause DoS for legitimate users.&#13;
&#13;
Given this code is not in any released versions, no security releases have been issued.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3603|2024-01-23T00:58:36.996Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 19:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3750|2024-05-01T20:20:48.157Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3750</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in libvirt. The virStoragePoolObjListSearch function does not return a locked pool as expected, resulting in a race condition and denial of service when attempting to lock the same object from another thread. This issue could allow clients connecting to the read-only socket to crash the libvirt daemon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3750|2024-05-01T20:20:48.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3269|2023-07-11T11:45:36.711Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3269</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in the memory management subsystem of the Linux kernel. The lock handling for accessing and updating virtual memory areas (VMAs) is incorrect, leading to use-after-free problems. This issue can be successfully exploited to execute arbitrary kernel code, escalate containers, and gain root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3269|2023-07-11T11:45:36.711Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3863|2023-07-24T14:25:02.287Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3863</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in nfc_llcp_find_local in net/nfc/llcp_core.c in NFC in the Linux kernel. This flaw allows a local user with special privileges to impact a kernel information leak issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3863|2023-07-24T14:25:02.287Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 14:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3971|2024-06-04T17:17:34.925Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20ansible%20automation%20platform%202.3%20for%20rhel%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3971</link>
      <description>An HTML injection flaw was found in Controller in the user interface settings. This flaw allows an attacker to capture credentials by creating a custom login page by injecting HTML, resulting in a complete compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3971|2024-06-04T17:17:34.925Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 14:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3567|2024-05-29T23:02:36.860Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3567</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in vcs_read in drivers/tty/vt/vc_screen.c in vc_screen in the Linux Kernel. This issue may allow an attacker with local user access to cause a system crash or leak internal kernel information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3567|2024-05-29T23:02:36.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3361|2023-10-04T11:34:57.746Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openshift%20data%20science%20%28rhods%29
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3361</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Red Hat OpenShift Data Science. When exporting a pipeline from the Elyra notebook pipeline editor as Python DSL or YAML, it reads S3 credentials from the cluster (ds pipeline server) and saves them in plain text in the generated output instead of an ID for a Kubernetes secret.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3361|2023-10-04T11:34:57.746Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 11:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3674|2024-05-01T20:20:47.491Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3674</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the keylime attestation verifier, which fails to flag a device's submitted TPM quote as faulty when the quote's signature does not validate for some reason. Instead, it will only emit an error in the log without flagging the device as untrusted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3674|2024-05-01T20:20:47.491Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 18:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3899|2024-05-29T23:03:36.878Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3899</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in subscription-manager that allows local privilege escalation due to inadequate authorization. The D-Bus interface com.redhat.RHSM1 exposes a significant number of methods to all users that could change the state of the registration. By using the com.redhat.RHSM1.Config.SetAll() method, a low-privileged local user could tamper with the state of the registration, by unregistering the system or by changing the current entitlements. This flaw allows an attacker to set arbitrary configuration directives for /etc/rhsm/rhsm.conf, which can be abused to cause a local privilege escalation to an unconfined root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3899|2024-05-29T23:03:36.878Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 10:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3972|2024-06-04T17:17:34.485Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3972</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in insights-client. This security issue occurs because of insecure file operations or unsafe handling of temporary files and directories that lead to local privilege escalation. Before the insights-client has been registered on the system by root, an unprivileged local user or attacker could create the /var/tmp/insights-client directory (owning the directory with read, write, and execute permissions) on the system. After the insights-client is registered by root, an attacker could then control the directory content that insights are using by putting malicious scripts into it and executing arbitrary code as root (trivially bypassing SELinux protections because insights processes are allowed to disable SELinux system-wide).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3972|2024-06-04T17:17:34.485Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3773|2024-05-01T20:20:49.531Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3773</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel’s IP framework for transforming packets (XFRM subsystem). This issue may allow a malicious user with CAP_NET_ADMIN privileges to cause a 4 byte out-of-bounds read of XFRMA_MTIMER_THRESH when parsing netlink attributes, leading to potential leakage of sensitive heap data to userspace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3773|2024-05-01T20:20:49.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:47:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3745|2024-06-04T17:17:34.056Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3745</link>
      <description>A heap-based buffer overflow issue was found in ImageMagick's PushCharPixel() function in quantum-private.h. This issue may allow a local attacker to trick the user into opening a specially crafted file, triggering an out-of-bounds read error and allowing an application to crash, resulting in a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3745|2024-06-04T17:17:34.056Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3180|2024-01-23T02:29:25.701Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3180</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the QEMU virtual crypto device while handling data encryption/decryption requests in virtio_crypto_handle_sym_req. There is no check for the value of `src_len` and `dst_len` in virtio_crypto_sym_op_helper, potentially leading to a heap buffer overflow when the two values differ.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3180|2024-01-23T02:29:25.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3354|2023-07-11T16:16:56.294Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3354</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the QEMU built-in VNC server. When a client connects to the VNC server, QEMU checks whether the current number of connections crosses a certain threshold and if so, cleans up the previous connection. If the previous connection happens to be in the handshake phase and fails, QEMU cleans up the connection again, resulting in a NULL pointer dereference issue. This could allow a remote unauthenticated client to cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3354|2023-07-11T16:16:56.294Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 16:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3397|2024-04-25T11:51:42.030Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3397</link>
      <description>A race condition occurred between the functions lmLogClose and txEnd in JFS, in the Linux Kernel, executed in different threads. This flaw allows a local attacker with normal user privileges to crash the system or leak internal kernel information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3397|2024-04-25T11:51:42.030Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3338|2024-01-23T02:34:01.241Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3338</link>
      <description>A null pointer dereference flaw was found in the Linux kernel's DECnet networking protocol. This issue could allow a remote user to crash the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3338|2024-01-23T02:34:01.241Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3355|2024-01-23T02:35:02.994Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3355</link>
      <description>A NULL pointer dereference flaw was found in the Linux kernel's drivers/gpu/drm/msm/msm_gem_submit.c code in the submit_lookup_cmds function, which fails because it lacks a check of the return value of kmalloc(). This issue allows a local user to crash the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3355|2024-01-23T02:35:02.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3640|2024-04-25T12:21:36.635Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3640</link>
      <description>A possible unauthorized memory access flaw was found in the Linux kernel's cpu_entry_area mapping of X86 CPU data to memory, where a user may guess the location of exception stacks or other important data. Based on the previous CVE-2023-0597, the 'Randomize per-cpu entry area' feature was implemented in /arch/x86/mm/cpu_entry_area.c, which works through the init_cea_offsets() function when KASLR is enabled. However, despite this feature, there is still a risk of per-cpu entry area leaks. This issue could allow a local user to gain access to some important data with memory in an expected location and potentially escalate their privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3640|2024-04-25T12:21:36.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3637|2024-06-04T17:17:33.214Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openstack%20platform%2016.2
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3637</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled resource consumption flaw was found in openstack-neutron. This flaw allows a remote authenticated user to query a list of security groups for an invalid project. This issue creates resources that are unconstrained by the user's quota. If a malicious user were to submit a significant number of requests, this could lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3637|2024-06-04T17:17:33.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 12:47:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3772|2024-05-23T22:48:06.400Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3772</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel’s IP framework for transforming packets (XFRM subsystem). This issue may allow a malicious user with CAP_NET_ADMIN privileges to directly dereference a NULL pointer in xfrm_update_ae_params(), leading to a possible kernel crash and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3772|2024-05-23T22:48:06.400Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:47:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3748|2024-01-23T01:05:10.544Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3748</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in FRRouting when parsing certain babeld unicast hello messages that are intended to be ignored. This issue may allow an attacker to send specially crafted hello messages with the unicast flag set, the interval field set to 0, or any TLV that contains a sub-TLV with the Mandatory flag set to enter an infinite loop and cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3748|2024-01-23T01:05:10.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3089|2023-07-05T12:21:03.036Z -- red%20hat -- openshift%20serverless
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3089</link>
      <description>A compliance problem was found in the Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform. Red Hat discovered that, when FIPS mode was enabled, not all of the cryptographic modules in use were FIPS-validated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3089|2023-07-05T12:21:03.036Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3597|2024-06-04T17:17:32.549Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20keycloak%2022
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3597</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Keycloak, where it does not correctly validate its client step-up authentication in org.keycloak.authentication. This flaw allows a remote user authenticated with a password to register a false second authentication factor along with an existing one and bypass authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3597|2024-06-04T17:17:32.549Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 12:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3153|2023-10-04T11:13:40.083Z -- red%20hat -- fast%20datapath%20for%20rhel%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3153</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Open Virtual Network where the service monitor MAC does not properly rate limit. This issue could allow an attacker to cause a denial of service, including on deployments with CoPP enabled and properly configured.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3153|2023-10-04T11:13:40.083Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 11:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3108|2024-04-25T11:44:20.541Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3108</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the subsequent get_user_pages_fast in the Linux kernel’s interface for symmetric key cipher algorithms in the skcipher_recvmsg of crypto/algif_skcipher.c function. This flaw allows a local user to crash the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3108|2024-04-25T11:44:20.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 15:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3164|2023-12-08T11:23:19.581Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3164</link>
      <description>A heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability was found in LibTIFF, in extractImageSection() at tools/tiffcrop.c:7916 and tools/tiffcrop.c:7801. This flaw allows attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted tiff file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3164|2023-12-08T11:23:19.581Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 11:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3758|2024-06-04T17:17:31.274Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3758</link>
      <description>A race condition flaw was found in sssd where the GPO policy is not consistently applied for authenticated users. This may lead to improper authorization issues, granting or denying access to resources inappropriately.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3758|2024-06-04T17:17:31.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 19:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7216|2024-05-13T22:16:12.001Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-7216</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability was found in the CPIO utility. This issue could allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to trick a user into opening a specially crafted archive. During the extraction process, the archiver could follow symlinks outside of the intended directory, which allows files to be written in arbitrary directories through symlinks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7216|2024-05-13T22:16:12.001Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 15:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7250|2024-06-04T11:15:32.414Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-7250</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in iperf, a utility for testing network performance using TCP, UDP, and SCTP. A malicious or malfunctioning client can send less than the expected amount of data to the iperf server, which can cause the server to hang indefinitely waiting for the remainder or until the connection gets closed. This will prevent other connections to the server, leading to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7250|2024-06-04T11:15:32.414Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 12:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7008|2024-05-29T23:09:03.073Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-7008</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in systemd-resolved. This issue may allow systemd-resolved to accept records of DNSSEC-signed domains even when they have no signature, allowing man-in-the-middles (or the upstream DNS resolver) to manipulate records.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7008|2024-05-29T23:09:03.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 13:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7090|2024-03-20T11:05:45.902Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-7090</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in sudo in the handling of ipa_hostname, where ipa_hostname from /etc/sssd/sssd.conf was not propagated in sudo. Therefore, it leads to privilege mismanagement vulnerability in applications, where client hosts retain privileges even after retracting them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7090|2024-03-20T11:05:45.902Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 22:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7192|2024-05-23T23:03:44.339Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208.2%20advanced%20update%20support
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-7192</link>
      <description>A memory leak problem was found in ctnetlink_create_conntrack in net/netfilter/nf_conntrack_netlink.c in the Linux Kernel. This issue may allow a local attacker with CAP_NET_ADMIN privileges to cause a denial of service (DoS) attack due to a refcount overflow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7192|2024-05-23T23:03:44.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 19:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7042|2024-04-25T16:07:48.498Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-7042</link>
      <description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability was found in ath10k_wmi_tlv_op_pull_mgmt_tx_compl_ev() in drivers/net/wireless/ath/ath10k/wmi-tlv.c in the Linux kernel. This issue could be exploited to trigger a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7042|2024-04-25T16:07:48.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6484|2024-05-01T20:21:39.653Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20keycloak%2022
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6484</link>
      <description>A log injection flaw was found in Keycloak. A text string may be injected through the authentication form when using the WebAuthn authentication mode. This issue may have a minor impact to the logs integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6484|2024-05-01T20:21:39.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6596|2024-05-01T20:21:41.604Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openshift%20container%20platform%204.11
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6596</link>
      <description>An incomplete fix was shipped for the Rapid Reset (CVE-2023-44487/CVE-2023-39325) vulnerability for an OpenShift Containers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6596|2024-05-01T20:21:41.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6200|2024-02-02T15:44:56.695Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6200</link>
      <description>A race condition was found in the Linux Kernel. Under certain conditions, an unauthenticated attacker from an adjacent network could send an ICMPv6 router advertisement packet, causing arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6200|2024-02-02T15:44:56.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 12:19:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6693|2024-05-29T23:07:42.729Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6693</link>
      <description>A stack based buffer overflow was found in the virtio-net device of QEMU. This issue occurs when flushing TX in the virtio_net_flush_tx function if guest features VIRTIO_NET_F_HASH_REPORT, VIRTIO_F_VERSION_1 and VIRTIO_NET_F_MRG_RXBUF are enabled. This could allow a malicious user to overwrite local variables allocated on the stack. Specifically, the `out_sg` variable could be used to read a part of process memory and send it to the wire, causing an information leak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6693|2024-05-29T23:07:42.729Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6563|2024-05-08T11:30:55.284Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20single%20sign-on%207.6%20for%20rhel%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6563</link>
      <description>An unconstrained memory consumption vulnerability was discovered in Keycloak. It can be triggered in environments which have millions of offline tokens (&gt; 500,000 users with each having at least 2 saved sessions). If an attacker creates two or more user sessions and then open the "consents" tab of the admin User Interface, the UI attempts to load a huge number of offline client sessions leading to excessive memory and CPU consumption which could potentially crash the entire system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6563|2024-05-08T11:30:55.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 18:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6277|2024-04-25T15:56:01.503Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6277</link>
      <description>An out-of-memory flaw was found in libtiff. Passing a crafted tiff file to TIFFOpen() API may allow a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a craft input with size smaller than 379 KB.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6277|2024-04-25T15:56:01.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 18:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6918|2024-05-22T17:06:45.568Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6918</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the libssh implements abstract layer for message digest (MD) operations implemented by different supported crypto backends. The return values from these were not properly checked, which could cause low-memory situations failures, NULL dereferences, crashes, or usage of the uninitialized memory as an input for the KDF. In this case, non-matching keys will result in decryption/integrity failures, terminating the connection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6918|2024-05-22T17:06:45.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 23:27:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6236|2024-06-04T16:52:38.240Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20jboss%20enterprise%20application%20platform%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6236</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in JBoss EAP. When an OIDC app that serves multiple tenants attempts to access the second tenant, it should prompt the user to log in again since the second tenant is secured with a different OIDC configuration. The underlying issue is in OidcSessionTokenStore when determining if a cached token should be used or not. This logic needs to be updated to take into account the new "provider-url" option in addition to the "realm" option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6236|2024-06-04T16:52:38.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 01:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6535|2024-05-23T22:58:21.052Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6535</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's NVMe driver. This issue may allow an unauthenticated malicious actor to send a set of crafted TCP packages when using NVMe over TCP, leading the NVMe driver to a NULL pointer dereference in the NVMe driver, causing kernel panic and a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6535|2024-05-23T22:58:21.052Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 21:04:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6779|2024-02-15T06:57:30.291Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6779</link>
      <description>An off-by-one heap-based buffer overflow was found in the __vsyslog_internal function of the glibc library. This function is called by the syslog and vsyslog functions. This issue occurs when these functions are called with a message bigger than INT_MAX bytes, leading to an incorrect calculation of the buffer size to store the message, resulting in an application crash. This issue affects glibc 2.37 and newer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6779|2024-02-15T06:57:30.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 14:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6780|2024-03-26T15:30:47.720Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6780</link>
      <description>An integer overflow was found in the __vsyslog_internal function of the glibc library. This function is called by the syslog and vsyslog functions. This issue occurs when these functions are called with a very long message, leading to an incorrect calculation of the buffer size to store the message, resulting in undefined behavior. This issue affects glibc 2.37 and newer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6780|2024-03-26T15:30:47.720Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 14:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6915|2024-05-22T16:38:01.201Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6915</link>
      <description>A Null pointer dereference problem was found in ida_free in lib/idr.c in the Linux Kernel. This issue may allow an attacker using this library to cause a denial of service problem due to a missing check at a function return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6915|2024-05-22T16:38:01.201Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 09:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6606|2024-05-23T23:03:41.449Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6606</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability was found in smbCalcSize in fs/smb/client/netmisc.c in the Linux Kernel. This issue could allow a local attacker to crash the system or leak internal kernel information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6606|2024-05-23T23:03:41.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 16:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6240|2024-06-05T16:35:53.053Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6240</link>
      <description>A Marvin vulnerability side-channel leakage was found in the RSA decryption operation in the Linux Kernel. This issue may allow a network attacker to decrypt ciphertexts or forge signatures, limiting the services that use that private key.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6240|2024-06-05T16:35:53.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 14:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6610|2024-05-23T22:58:30.662Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6610</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability was found in smb2_dump_detail in fs/smb/client/smb2ops.c in the Linux Kernel. This issue could allow a local attacker to crash the system or leak internal kernel information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6610|2024-05-23T22:58:30.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 16:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6725|2024-05-22T21:43:15.360Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openstack%20platform%2017.1%20for%20rhel%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6725</link>
      <description>An access-control flaw was found in the OpenStack Designate component where private configuration information including access keys to BIND were improperly made world readable. A malicious attacker with access to any container could exploit this flaw to access sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6725|2024-05-22T21:43:15.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 12:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6267|2024-05-13T21:00:13.693Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20quarkus%202.13.9.final
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6267</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the json payload. If annotation based security is used to secure a REST resource, the JSON body that the resource may consume is being processed (deserialized) prior to the security constraints being evaluated and applied. This does not happen with configuration based security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6267|2024-05-13T21:00:13.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 18:12:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6787|2024-06-04T17:17:12.505Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20keycloak%2022
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6787</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Keycloak that occurs from an error in the re-authentication mechanism within org.keycloak.authentication. This flaw allows hijacking an active Keycloak session by triggering a new authentication process with the query parameter "prompt=login," prompting the user to re-enter their credentials. If the user cancels this re-authentication by selecting "Restart login," an account takeover may occur, as the new session, with a different SUB, will possess the same SID as the previous session.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6787|2024-06-04T17:17:12.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6816|2024-05-29T23:08:17.179Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6816</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in X.Org server. Both DeviceFocusEvent and the XIQueryPointer reply contain a bit for each logical button currently down. Buttons can be arbitrarily mapped to any value up to 255, but the X.Org Server was only allocating space for the device's particular number of buttons, leading to a heap overflow if a bigger value was used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6816|2024-05-29T23:08:17.179Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 04:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6683|2024-05-29T23:07:29.101Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6683</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the QEMU built-in VNC server while processing ClientCutText messages. The qemu_clipboard_request() function can be reached before vnc_server_cut_text_caps() was called and had the chance to initialize the clipboard peer, leading to a NULL pointer dereference. This could allow a malicious authenticated VNC client to crash QEMU and trigger a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6683|2024-05-29T23:07:29.101Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 19:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6544|2024-06-04T17:17:10.747Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20keycloak%2022
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6544</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Keycloak package. This issue occurs due to a permissive regular expression hardcoded for filtering which allows hosts to register a dynamic client. A malicious user with enough information about the environment could jeopardize an environment with this specific Dynamic Client Registration and TrustedDomain configuration previously unauthorized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6544|2024-06-04T17:17:10.747Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6944|2024-04-25T16:07:03.283Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20developer%20hub
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6944</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Red Hat Developer Hub (RHDH). The catalog-import function leaks GitLab access tokens on the frontend when the base64 encoded GitLab token includes a newline at the end of the string. The sanitized error can display on the frontend, including the raw access token. Upon gaining access to this token and depending on permissions, an attacker could push malicious code to repositories, delete resources in Git, revoke or generate new keys, and sign code illegitimately.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6944|2024-04-25T16:07:03.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 10:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6246|2024-02-15T06:56:44.724Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6246</link>
      <description>A heap-based buffer overflow was found in the __vsyslog_internal function of the glibc library. This function is called by the syslog and vsyslog functions. This issue occurs when the openlog function was not called, or called with the ident argument set to NULL, and the program name (the basename of argv[0]) is bigger than 1024 bytes, resulting in an application crash or local privilege escalation. This issue affects glibc 2.36 and newer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6246|2024-02-15T06:56:44.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 14:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6270|2024-04-25T15:55:52.424Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6270</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the ATA over Ethernet (AoE) driver in the Linux kernel. The aoecmd_cfg_pkts() function improperly updates the refcnt on `struct net_device`, and a use-after-free can be triggered by racing between the free on the struct and the access through the `skbtxq` global queue. This could lead to a denial of service condition or potential code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6270|2024-04-25T15:55:52.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 17:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6476|2024-05-01T20:21:38.273Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openshift%20container%20platform%204.13
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6476</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in CRI-O that involves an experimental annotation leading to a container being unconfined. This may allow a pod to specify and get any amount of memory/cpu, circumventing the kubernetes scheduler and potentially resulting in a denial of service in the node.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6476|2024-05-01T20:21:38.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 21:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6134|2024-05-20T17:11:00.067Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20keycloak%2022
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6134</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Keycloak that prevents certain schemes in redirects, but permits them if a wildcard is appended to the token. This issue could allow an attacker to submit a specially crafted request leading to cross-site scripting (XSS) or further attacks. This flaw is the result of an incomplete fix for CVE-2020-10748.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6134|2024-05-20T17:11:00.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 21:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6377|2024-05-29T23:06:03.044Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6377</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in xorg-server. Querying or changing XKB button actions such as moving from a touchpad to a mouse can result in out-of-bounds memory reads and writes. This may allow local privilege escalation or possible remote code execution in cases where X11 forwarding is involved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6377|2024-05-29T23:06:03.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 06:27:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6121|2024-05-29T23:05:42.965Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6121</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability was found in the NVMe-oF/TCP subsystem in the Linux kernel. This issue may allow a remote attacker to send a crafted TCP packet, triggering a heap-based buffer overflow that results in kmalloc data being printed and potentially leaked to the kernel ring buffer (dmesg).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6121|2024-05-29T23:05:42.965Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6176|2024-05-29T21:03:03.417Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6176</link>
      <description>A null pointer dereference flaw was found in the Linux kernel API for the cryptographic algorithm scatterwalk functionality. This issue occurs when a user constructs a malicious packet with specific socket configuration, which could allow a local user to crash the system or escalate their privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6176|2024-05-29T21:03:03.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 17:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6681|2024-05-29T23:07:17.567Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6681</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in JWCrypto. This flaw allows an attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) attack and possible password brute-force and dictionary attacks to be more resource-intensive. This issue can result in a large amount of computational consumption, causing a denial of service attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6681|2024-05-29T23:07:17.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 14:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6394|2024-05-01T20:21:37.537Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20quarkus%203.2.9.final
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6394</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Quarkus. This issue occurs when receiving a request over websocket with no role-based permission specified on the GraphQL operation, Quarkus processes the request without authentication despite the endpoint being secured. This can allow an attacker to access information and functionality outside of normal granted API permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6394|2024-05-01T20:21:37.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 01:26:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6228|2024-05-01T20:21:35.571Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6228</link>
      <description>An issue was found in the tiffcp utility distributed by the libtiff package where a crafted TIFF file on processing may cause a heap-based buffer overflow leads to an application crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6228|2024-05-01T20:21:35.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6356|2024-06-04T17:17:04.696Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6356</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's NVMe driver. This issue may allow an unauthenticated malicious actor to send a set of crafted TCP packages when using NVMe over TCP, leading the NVMe driver to a NULL pointer dereference in the NVMe driver and causing kernel panic and a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6356|2024-06-04T17:17:04.696Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 21:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6478|2024-05-29T23:06:19.846Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6478</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in xorg-server. A specially crafted request to RRChangeProviderProperty or RRChangeOutputProperty can trigger an integer overflow which may lead to a disclosure of sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6478|2024-05-29T23:06:19.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 06:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6710|2024-05-01T20:21:43.207Z -- red%20hat -- jboss%20core%20services%20for%20rhel%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6710</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the mod_proxy_cluster in the Apache server. This issue may allow a malicious user to add a script in the 'alias' parameter in the URL to trigger the stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. By adding a script on the alias parameter on the URL, it adds a new virtual host and adds the script to the cluster-manager page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6710|2024-05-01T20:21:43.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 22:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6291|2024-05-20T17:11:04.114Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20keycloak%2022
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6291</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the redirect_uri validation logic in Keycloak. This issue may allow a bypass of otherwise explicitly allowed hosts. A successful attack may lead to an access token being stolen, making it possible for the attacker to impersonate other users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6291|2024-05-20T17:11:04.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 14:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6679|2024-05-01T20:21:42.274Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6679</link>
      <description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability was found in dpll_pin_parent_pin_set() in drivers/dpll/dpll_netlink.c in the Digital Phase Locked Loop (DPLL) subsystem in the  Linux kernel. This issue could be exploited to trigger a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6679|2024-05-01T20:21:42.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 18:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6546|2024-05-23T23:08:05.801Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6546</link>
      <description>A race condition was found in the GSM 0710 tty multiplexor in the Linux kernel. This issue occurs when two threads execute the GSMIOC_SETCONF ioctl on the same tty file descriptor with the gsm line discipline enabled, and can lead to a use-after-free problem on a struct gsm_dlci while restarting the gsm mux. This could allow a local unprivileged user to escalate their privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6546|2024-05-23T23:08:05.801Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6395|2024-01-16T15:02:39.645Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6395</link>
      <description>The Mock software contains a vulnerability wherein an attacker could potentially exploit privilege escalation, enabling the execution of arbitrary code with root user privileges. This weakness stems from the absence of proper sandboxing during the expansion and execution of Jinja2 templates, which may be included in certain configuration parameters. While the Mock documentation advises treating users added to the mock group as privileged, certain build systems invoking mock on behalf of users might inadvertently permit less privileged users to define configuration tags. These tags could then be passed as parameters to mock during execution, potentially leading to the utilization of Jinja2 templates for remote privilege escalation and the execution of arbitrary code as the root user on the build server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6395|2024-01-16T15:02:39.645Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 14:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6004|2024-05-22T17:06:28.643Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6004</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in libssh. By utilizing the ProxyCommand or ProxyJump feature, users can exploit unchecked hostname syntax on the client. This issue may allow an attacker to inject malicious code into the command of the features mentioned through the hostname parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6004|2024-05-22T17:06:28.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 17:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6927|2024-05-01T20:21:44.975Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20keycloak%2022
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6927</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. This issue may allow an attacker to steal authorization codes or tokens from clients using a wildcard in the JARM response mode "form_post.jwt" which could be used to bypass the security patch implemented to address CVE-2023-6134.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6927|2024-05-01T20:21:44.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 22:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6531|2024-05-29T23:06:49.051Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6531</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the Linux Kernel due to a race problem in the unix garbage collector's deletion of SKB races with unix_stream_read_generic() on the socket that the SKB is queued on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6531|2024-05-29T23:06:49.051Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 10:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6622|2024-05-29T23:07:12.201Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6622</link>
      <description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability was found in nft_dynset_init() in net/netfilter/nft_dynset.c in nf_tables in the Linux kernel. This issue may allow a local attacker with CAP_NET_ADMIN user privilege to trigger a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6622|2024-05-29T23:07:12.201Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 17:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6238|2024-02-06T23:30:20.019Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6238</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability was found in the NVM Express (NVMe) driver in the Linux kernel. Only privileged user could specify a small meta buffer and let the device perform larger Direct Memory Access (DMA) into the same buffer, overwriting unrelated kernel memory, causing random kernel crashes and memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6238|2024-02-06T23:30:20.019Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 20:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6717|2024-06-08T02:31:53.007Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20keycloak%2022
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6717</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the SAML client registration in Keycloak that could allow an administrator to register malicious JavaScript URIs as Assertion Consumer Service POST Binding URLs (ACS), posing a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) risk. This issue may allow a malicious admin in one realm or a client with registration access to target users in different realms or applications, executing arbitrary JavaScript in their contexts upon form submission. This can enable unauthorized access and harmful actions, compromising the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the complete KC instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6717|2024-06-08T02:31:53.007Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6039|2024-01-23T01:47:14.794Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6039</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in lan78xx_disconnect in drivers/net/usb/lan78xx.c in the network sub-component, net/usb/lan78xx in the Linux Kernel. This flaw allows a local attacker to crash the system when the LAN78XX USB device detaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6039|2024-01-23T01:47:14.794Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 15:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6536|2024-05-23T22:58:30.030Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6536</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's NVMe driver. This issue may allow an unauthenticated malicious actor to send a set of crafted TCP packages when using NVMe over TCP, leading the NVMe driver to a NULL pointer dereference in the NVMe driver, causing kernel panic and a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6536|2024-05-23T22:58:30.030Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 21:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6560|2024-01-23T02:07:14.972Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6560</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds memory access flaw was found in the io_uring SQ/CQ rings functionality in the Linux kernel. This issue could allow a local user to crash the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6560|2024-01-23T02:07:14.972Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 23:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6917|2024-05-01T20:21:44.251Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6917</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in the Performance Co-Pilot (PCP) package, stemming from the mixed privilege levels utilized by systemd services associated with PCP. While certain services operate within the confines of limited PCP user/group privileges, others are granted full root privileges. This disparity in privilege levels poses a risk when privileged root processes interact with directories or directory trees owned by unprivileged PCP users. Specifically, this vulnerability may lead to the compromise of PCP user isolation and facilitate local PCP-to-root exploits, particularly through symlink attacks. These vulnerabilities underscore the importance of maintaining robust privilege separation mechanisms within PCP to mitigate the potential for unauthorized privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6917|2024-05-01T20:21:44.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 14:38:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6393|2024-04-25T15:57:25.820Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20quarkus
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6393</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Quarkus Cache Runtime. When request processing utilizes a Uni cached using @CacheResult and the cached Uni reuses the initial "completion" context, the processing switches to the cached Uni instead of the request context. This is a problem if the cached Uni context contains sensitive information, and could allow a malicious user to benefit from a POST request returning the response that is meant for another user, gaining access to sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6393|2024-04-25T15:57:25.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 16:58:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2422|2024-06-04T17:16:52.606Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20single%20sign-on%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2422</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. A Keycloak server configured to support mTLS authentication for OAuth/OpenID clients does not properly verify the client certificate chain. A client that possesses a proper certificate can authorize itself as any other client, therefore, access data that belongs to other clients.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2422|2024-06-04T17:16:52.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 10:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2680|2023-09-13T16:50:53.532Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2680</link>
      <description>This CVE exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2021-3750. More specifically, the qemu-kvm package as released for Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9.1 via RHSA-2022:7967 included a version of qemu-kvm that was actually missing the fix for CVE-2021-3750.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2680|2023-09-13T16:50:53.532Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 16:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2585|2024-05-03T15:32:35.422Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20single%20sign-on%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2585</link>
      <description>Keycloak's device authorization grant does not correctly validate the device code and client ID. An attacker client could abuse the missing validation to spoof a client consent request and trick an authorization admin into granting consent to a malicious OAuth client or possible unauthorized access to an existing OAuth client.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2585|2024-05-03T15:32:35.422Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2908|2024-01-23T01:44:14.895Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2908</link>
      <description>A null pointer dereference issue was found in Libtiff's tif_dir.c file. This issue may allow an attacker to pass a crafted TIFF image file to the tiffcp utility which triggers a runtime error that causes undefined behavior. This will result in an application crash, eventually leading to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2908|2024-01-23T01:44:14.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2860|2024-01-23T03:20:36.395Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2860</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability was found in the SR-IPv6 implementation in the Linux kernel. The flaw exists within the processing of seg6 attributes. The issue results from the improper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. This flaw allows a privileged local user to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of the Linux kernel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2860|2024-01-23T03:20:36.395Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2974|2024-05-03T15:32:35.950Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20quarkus%202.13.8.final
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2974</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in quarkus-core. This vulnerability occurs because the TLS protocol configured with quarkus.http.ssl.protocols is not enforced, and the client can force the selection of the weaker supported TLS protocol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2974|2024-05-03T15:32:35.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 13:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28835|2024-05-29T23:41:49.131Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28835</link>
      <description>A flaw has been discovered in GnuTLS where an application crash can be induced when attempting to verify a specially crafted .pem bundle using the "certtool --verify-chain" command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28835|2024-05-29T23:41:49.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 06:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28834|2024-05-16T22:17:19.652Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28834</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in GnuTLS. The Minerva attack is a cryptographic vulnerability that exploits deterministic behavior in systems like GnuTLS, leading to side-channel leaks. In specific scenarios, such as when using the GNUTLS_PRIVKEY_FLAG_REPRODUCIBLE flag, it can result in a noticeable step in nonce size from 513 to 512 bits, exposing a potential timing side-channel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28834|2024-05-16T22:17:19.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5037|2024-06-05T18:03:23.194Z -- red%20hat -- logging%20subsystem%20for%20red%20hat%20openshift
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5037</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in OpenShift's Telemeter. If certain conditions are in place, an attacker can use a forged token to bypass the issue ("iss") check during JSON web token (JWT) authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5037|2024-06-05T18:03:23.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5564|2024-06-04T18:02:43.761Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5564</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in libndp. This flaw allows a local malicious user to cause a buffer overflow in NetworkManager, triggered by sending a malformed IPv6 router advertisement packet. This issue occurred as libndp was not correctly validating the route length information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5564|2024-06-04T18:02:43.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 18:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5042|2024-06-04T18:01:39.816Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20advanced%20cluster%20management%20for%20kubernetes%202
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5042</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Submariner project. Due to unnecessary role-based access control permissions, a privileged attacker can run a malicious container on a node that may allow them to steal service account tokens and further compromise other nodes and potentially the entire cluster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5042|2024-06-04T18:01:39.816Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1151|2024-04-18T19:07:37.880Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1151</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was reported in the Open vSwitch sub-component in the Linux Kernel. The flaw occurs when a recursive operation of code push recursively calls into the code block. The OVS module does not validate the stack depth, pushing too many frames and causing a stack overflow. As a result, this can lead to a crash or other related issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1151|2024-04-18T19:07:37.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 14:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1062|2024-05-29T23:26:52.886Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20directory%20server%2011.7%20for%20rhel%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1062</link>
      <description>A heap overflow flaw was found in 389-ds-base. This issue leads to a denial of service when writing a value larger than 256 chars in log_entry_attr.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1062|2024-05-29T23:26:52.886Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 13:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1023|2024-05-31T00:58:27.038Z -- red%20hat -- ceq%203.2
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1023</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Eclipse Vert.x toolkit results in a memory leak due to using Netty FastThreadLocal data structures. Specifically, when the Vert.x HTTP client establishes connections to different hosts, triggering the memory leak. The leak can be accelerated with intimate runtime knowledge, allowing an attacker to exploit this vulnerability. For instance, a server accepting arbitrary internet addresses could serve as an attack vector by connecting to these addresses, thereby accelerating the memory leak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1023|2024-05-31T00:58:27.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 07:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1233|2024-06-04T16:53:51.662Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20jboss%20enterprise%20application%20platform%207.1.0
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1233</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in` JwtValidator.resolvePublicKey` in JBoss EAP, where the validator checks jku and sends a HTTP request. During this process, no whitelisting or other filtering behavior is performed on the destination URL address, which may result in a server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1233|2024-06-04T16:53:51.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 07:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1726|2024-06-05T09:04:22.004Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20quarkus%203.2.11.final
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1726</link>
      <description>A flaw was discovered in the RESTEasy Reactive implementation in Quarkus. Due to security checks for some JAX-RS endpoints being performed after serialization, more processing resources are consumed while the HTTP request is checked. In certain configurations, if an attacker has knowledge of any POST, PUT, or PATCH request paths, they can potentially identify vulnerable endpoints and trigger excessive resource usage as the endpoints process the requests. This can result in a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1726|2024-06-05T09:04:22.004Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:29:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1481|2024-05-29T23:27:57.935Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1481</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in FreeIPA. This issue may allow a remote attacker to craft a HTTP request with parameters that can be interpreted as command arguments to kinit on the FreeIPA server, which can lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1481|2024-05-29T23:27:57.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:39:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1454|2024-02-12T22:29:58.226Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1454</link>
      <description>The use-after-free vulnerability was found in the AuthentIC driver in OpenSC packages, occuring in the card enrolment process using pkcs15-init when a user or administrator enrols or modifies cards. An attacker must have physical access to the computer system and requires a crafted USB device or smart card to present the system with specially crafted responses to the APDUs, which are considered high complexity and low severity. This manipulation can allow for compromised card management operations during enrolment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1454|2024-02-12T22:29:58.226Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 22:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1141|2024-06-04T18:00:46.862Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openstack%20platform%2017.1%20for%20rhel%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1141</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in python-glance-store. The issue occurs when the package logs the access_key for the glance-store when the DEBUG log level is enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1141|2024-06-04T18:00:46.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 14:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1394|2024-06-11T20:17:11.716Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20ansible%20automation%20platform%202.4%20for%20rhel%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1394</link>
      <description>A memory leak flaw was found in Golang in the RSA encrypting/decrypting code, which might lead to a resource exhaustion vulnerability using attacker-controlled inputs​. The memory leak happens in github.com/golang-fips/openssl/openssl/rsa.go#L113. The objects leaked are pkey​ and ctx​. That function uses named return parameters to free pkey​ and ctx​ if there is an error initializing the context or setting the different properties. All return statements related to error cases follow the "return nil, nil, fail(...)" pattern, meaning that pkey​ and ctx​ will be nil inside the deferred function that should free them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1394|2024-06-11T20:17:11.716Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 12:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1013|2024-06-04T18:00:42.304Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1013</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds stack write flaw was found in unixODBC on 64-bit architectures where the caller has 4 bytes and callee writes 8 bytes. This issue may go unnoticed on little-endian architectures, while big-endian architectures can be broken.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1013|2024-06-04T18:00:42.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:53:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1300|2024-06-05T09:03:51.625Z -- red%20hat -- ceq%203.2
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1300</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Eclipse Vert.x toolkit causes a memory leak in TCP servers configured with TLS and SNI support. When processing an unknown SNI server name assigned the default certificate instead of a mapped certificate, the SSL context is erroneously cached in the server name map, leading to memory exhaustion. This flaw allows attackers to send TLS client hello messages with fake server names, triggering a JVM out-of-memory error.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1300|2024-06-05T09:03:51.625Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1459|2024-06-05T16:29:14.611Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20jboss%20enterprise%20application%20platform%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1459</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability was found in Undertow. This issue may allow a remote attacker to append a specially-crafted sequence to an HTTP request for an application deployed to JBoss EAP, which may permit access to privileged or restricted files and directories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1459|2024-06-05T16:29:14.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 20:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1635|2024-06-05T16:29:45.770Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20jboss%20enterprise%20application%20platform%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1635</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Undertow. This vulnerability impacts a server that supports the wildfly-http-client protocol. Whenever a malicious user opens and closes a connection with the HTTP port of the server and then closes the connection immediately, the server will end with both memory and open file limits exhausted at some point, depending on the amount of memory available. &#13;
&#13;
At HTTP upgrade to remoting, the WriteTimeoutStreamSinkConduit leaks connections if RemotingConnection is closed by Remoting ServerConnectionOpenListener. Because the remoting connection originates in Undertow as part of the HTTP upgrade, there is an external layer to the remoting connection. This connection is unaware of the outermost layer when closing the connection during the connection opening procedure. Hence, the Undertow WriteTimeoutStreamSinkConduit is not notified of the closed connection in this scenario. Because WriteTimeoutStreamSinkConduit creates a timeout task, the whole dependency tree leaks via that task, which is added to XNIO WorkerThread. So, the workerThread points to the Undertow conduit, which contains the connections and causes the leak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1635|2024-06-05T16:29:45.770Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 21:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1048|2024-06-04T18:00:34.193Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1048</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the grub2-set-bootflag utility of grub2. After the fix of CVE-2019-14865, grub2-set-bootflag will create a temporary file with the new grubenv content and rename it to the original grubenv file. If the program is killed before the rename operation, the temporary file will not be removed and may fill the filesystem when invoked multiple times, resulting in a filesystem out of free inodes or blocks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1048|2024-06-04T18:00:34.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 17:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1249|2024-06-05T11:41:34.484Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20keycloak%2022
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1249</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Keycloak's OIDC component in the "checkLoginIframe," which allows unvalidated cross-origin messages. This flaw allows attackers to coordinate and send millions of requests in seconds using simple code, significantly impacting the application's availability without proper origin validation for incoming messages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1249|2024-06-05T11:41:34.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 13:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1102|2024-06-04T18:00:15.959Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20jboss%20enterprise%20application%20platform%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1102</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in jberet-core logging. An exception in 'dbProperties' might display user credentials such as the username and password for the database-connection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1102|2024-06-04T18:00:15.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1657|2024-06-04T18:00:13.838Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20ansible%20automation%20platform%202.4%20for%20rhel%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1657</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the ansible automation platform. An insecure WebSocket connection was being used in installation from the Ansible rulebook EDA server. An attacker that has access to any machine in the CIDR block could download all rulebook data from the WebSocket, resulting in loss of confidentiality and integrity of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1657|2024-06-04T18:00:13.838Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1342|2024-06-04T19:34:06.352Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openshift%20container%20platform%204
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1342</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in OpenShift. The existing Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) protections in place do not properly protect GET requests, allowing for the creation of WebSockets via CSRF.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1342|2024-06-04T19:34:06.352Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 15:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1753|2024-06-04T18:00:10.892Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1753</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Buildah (and subsequently Podman Build) which allows containers to mount arbitrary locations on the host filesystem into build containers. A malicious Containerfile can use a dummy image with a symbolic link to the root filesystem as a mount source and cause the mount operation to mount the host root filesystem inside the RUN step. The commands inside the RUN step will then have read-write access to the host filesystem, allowing for full container escape at build time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1753|2024-06-04T18:00:10.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 14:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1139|2024-06-05T11:41:20.434Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openshift%20container%20platform%204.12
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1139</link>
      <description>A credentials leak vulnerability was found in the cluster monitoring operator in OCP.  This issue may allow a remote attacker who has basic login credentials to check the pod manifest to discover a repository pull secret.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1139|2024-06-05T11:41:20.434Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1441|2024-06-04T18:00:02.583Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1441</link>
      <description>An off-by-one error flaw was found in the udevListInterfacesByStatus() function in libvirt when the number of interfaces exceeds the size of the `names` array. This issue can be reproduced by sending specially crafted data to the libvirt daemon, allowing an unprivileged client to perform a denial of service attack by causing the libvirt daemon to crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1441|2024-06-04T18:00:02.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 13:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1725|2024-05-08T01:51:31.044Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openshift%20container%20platform%204.13
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1725</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the kubevirt-csi component of OpenShift Virtualization's Hosted Control Plane (HCP). This issue could allow an authenticated attacker to gain access to the root HCP worker node's volume by creating a custom Persistent Volume that matches the name of a worker node.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1725|2024-05-08T01:51:31.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 20:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1485|2024-04-25T16:27:09.123Z -- red%20hat -- openshift%20developer%20tools%20and%20services
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1485</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the decompression function of registry-support. This issue can be triggered if an unauthenticated remote attacker tricks a user into parsing a devfile which uses the `parent` or `plugin` keywords. This could download a malicious archive and cause the cleanup process to overwrite or delete files outside of the archive, which should not be allowed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1485|2024-04-25T16:27:09.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 23:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1722|2024-04-25T16:28:42.385Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1722</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. In certain conditions, this issue may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to block other accounts from logging in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1722|2024-04-25T16:28:42.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 17:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1132|2024-06-04T17:59:39.871Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20keycloak%2022
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1132</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Keycloak, where it does not properly validate URLs included in a redirect. This issue could allow an attacker to construct a malicious request to bypass validation and access other URLs and sensitive information within the domain or conduct further attacks. This flaw affects any client that utilizes a wildcard in the Valid Redirect URIs field, and requires user interaction within the malicious URL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1132|2024-06-04T17:59:39.871Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 13:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1488|2024-05-29T23:28:18.338Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1488</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Unbound due to incorrect default permissions, allowing any process outside the unbound group to modify the unbound runtime configuration. If a process can connect over localhost to port 8953, it can alter the configuration of unbound.service. This flaw allows an unprivileged attacker to manipulate a running instance, potentially altering forwarders, allowing them to track all queries forwarded by the local resolver, and, in some cases, disrupting resolving altogether.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1488|2024-05-29T23:28:18.338Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1979|2024-06-05T09:04:53.930Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20quarkus%203.2.11.final
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1979</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Quarkus. In certain conditions related to the CI process, git credentials could be inadvertently published, which could put the git repository at risk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1979|2024-06-05T09:04:53.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 09:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1312|2024-02-15T06:56:43.291Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1312</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the Linux kernel's Memory Management subsystem when a user wins two races at the same time with a fail in the mas_prev_slot function. This issue could allow a local user to crash the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1312|2024-02-15T06:56:43.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 12:38:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0193|2024-06-04T17:59:17.378Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0193</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the netfilter subsystem of the Linux kernel. If the catchall element is garbage-collected when the pipapo set is removed, the element can be deactivated twice. This can cause a use-after-free issue on an NFT_CHAIN object or NFT_OBJECT object, allowing a local unprivileged user with CAP_NET_ADMIN capability to escalate their privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0193|2024-06-04T17:59:17.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 18:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0582|2024-04-25T16:18:21.849Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0582</link>
      <description>A memory leak flaw was found in the Linux kernel’s io_uring functionality in how a user registers a buffer ring with IORING_REGISTER_PBUF_RING, mmap() it, and then frees it. This flaw allows a local user to crash or potentially escalate their privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0582|2024-04-25T16:18:21.849Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 14:33:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0408|2024-05-29T23:25:52.111Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0408</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the X.Org server. The GLX PBuffer code does not call the XACE hook when creating the buffer, leaving it unlabeled. When the client issues another request to access that resource (as with a GetGeometry) or when it creates another resource that needs to access that buffer, such as a GC, the XSELINUX code will try to use an object that was never labeled and crash because the SID is NULL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0408|2024-05-29T23:25:52.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 15:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0560|2024-04-25T16:17:37.824Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%203scale%20api%20management%20platform%202
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0560</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in 3Scale, when used with Keycloak 15 (or RHSSO 7.5.0) and superiors. When the auth_type is use_3scale_oidc_issuer_endpoint, the Token Introspection policy discovers the Token Introspection endpoint from the token_introspection_endpoint field, but the field was removed on RH-SSO 7.5. As a result, the policy doesn't inspect tokens, it determines that all tokens are valid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0560|2024-04-25T16:17:37.824Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 16:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0409|2024-05-29T23:26:08.292Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0409</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the X.Org server. The cursor code in both Xephyr and Xwayland uses the wrong type of private at creation. It uses the cursor bits type with the cursor as private, and when initiating the cursor, that overwrites the XSELINUX context.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0409|2024-05-29T23:26:08.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0690|2024-05-29T23:26:36.215Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20ansible%20automation%20platform%202.4%20for%20rhel%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0690</link>
      <description>An information disclosure flaw was found in ansible-core due to a failure to respect the ANSIBLE_NO_LOG configuration in some scenarios. Information is still included in the output in certain tasks, such as loop items. Depending on the task, this issue may include sensitive information, such as decrypted secret values.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0690|2024-05-29T23:26:36.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 12:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0232|2024-04-25T16:16:58.097Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0232</link>
      <description>A heap use-after-free issue has been identified in SQLite in the jsonParseAddNodeArray() function in sqlite3.c. This flaw allows a local attacker to leverage a victim to pass specially crafted malicious input to the application, potentially causing a crash and leading to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0232|2024-04-25T16:16:58.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 14:01:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0822|2024-05-01T20:21:49.552Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20virtualization%20engine%204.4
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0822</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass vulnerability was found in overt-engine. This flaw allows the creation of users in the system without authentication due to a flaw in the CreateUserSession command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0822|2024-05-01T20:21:49.552Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 15:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0567|2024-05-01T20:21:48.190Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0567</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in GnuTLS, where a cockpit (which uses gnuTLS) rejects a certificate chain with distributed trust. This issue occurs when validating a certificate chain with cockpit-certificate-ensure. This flaw allows an unauthenticated, remote client or attacker to initiate a denial of service attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0567|2024-05-01T20:21:48.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 14:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0639|2024-04-25T16:18:58.569Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0639</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability due to a deadlock was found in sctp_auto_asconf_init in net/sctp/socket.c in the Linux kernel’s SCTP subsystem. This flaw allows guests with local user privileges to trigger a deadlock and potentially crash the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0639|2024-04-25T16:18:58.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 15:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0443|2024-05-20T10:22:20.763Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0443</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the blkgs destruction path in block/blk-cgroup.c in the Linux kernel, leading to a cgroup blkio memory leakage problem. When a cgroup is being destroyed, cgroup_rstat_flush() is only called at css_release_work_fn(), which is called when the blkcg reference count reaches 0. This circular dependency will prevent blkcg and some blkgs from being freed after they are made offline. This issue may allow an attacker with a local access to cause system instability, such as an out of memory error.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0443|2024-05-20T10:22:20.763Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 23:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0340|2024-06-05T16:39:12.423Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0340</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in vhost_new_msg in drivers/vhost/vhost.c in the Linux kernel, which does not properly initialize memory in messages passed between virtual guests and the host operating system in the vhost/vhost.c:vhost_new_msg() function. This issue can allow local privileged users to read some kernel memory contents when reading from the /dev/vhost-net device file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0340|2024-06-05T16:39:12.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 17:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0229|2024-05-29T23:25:41.266Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0229</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds memory access flaw was found in the X.Org server. This issue can be triggered when a device frozen by a sync grab is reattached to a different master device. This issue may lead to an application crash, local privilege escalation (if the server runs with extended privileges), or remote code execution in SSH X11 forwarding environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0229|2024-05-29T23:25:41.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 06:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0874|2024-04-25T16:22:44.182Z -- red%20hat -- logging%20subsystem%20for%20red%20hat%20openshift
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0874</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in coredns. This issue could lead to invalid cache entries returning due to incorrectly implemented caching.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0874|2024-04-25T16:22:44.182Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0565|2024-05-23T23:04:22.381Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0565</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds memory read flaw was found in receive_encrypted_standard in fs/smb/client/smb2ops.c in the SMB Client sub-component in the Linux Kernel. This issue occurs due to integer underflow on the memcpy length, leading to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0565|2024-05-23T23:04:22.381Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 20:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0553|2024-05-01T20:21:47.610Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0553</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in GnuTLS. The response times to malformed ciphertexts in RSA-PSK ClientKeyExchange differ from the response times of ciphertexts with correct PKCS#1 v1.5 padding. This issue may allow a remote attacker to perform a timing side-channel attack in the RSA-PSK key exchange, potentially leading to the leakage of sensitive data. CVE-2024-0553 is designated as an incomplete resolution for CVE-2023-5981.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0553|2024-05-01T20:21:47.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 11:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0841|2024-05-22T16:44:15.892Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0841</link>
      <description>A null pointer dereference flaw was found in the hugetlbfs_fill_super function in the Linux kernel hugetlbfs (HugeTLB pages) functionality. This issue may allow a local user to crash the system or potentially escalate their privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0841|2024-05-22T16:44:15.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 11:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0641|2024-05-29T23:26:24.138Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0641</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability was found in tipc_crypto_key_revoke in net/tipc/crypto.c in the Linux kernel’s TIPC subsystem. This flaw allows guests with local user privileges to trigger a deadlock and potentially crash the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0641|2024-05-29T23:26:24.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 15:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0564|2024-04-26T08:16:22.880Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0564</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's memory deduplication mechanism. The max page sharing of Kernel Samepage Merging (KSM), added in Linux kernel version 4.4.0-96.119, can create a side channel. When the attacker and the victim share the same host and the default setting of KSM is "max page sharing=256", it is possible for the attacker to time the unmap to merge with the victim's page. The unmapping time depends on whether it merges with the victim's page and additional physical pages are created beyond the KSM's "max page share". Through these operations, the attacker can leak the victim's page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0564|2024-04-26T08:16:22.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 15:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0646|2024-05-23T23:00:23.283Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0646</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds memory write flaw was found in the Linux kernel’s Transport Layer Security functionality in how a user calls a function splice with a ktls socket as the destination. This flaw allows a local user to crash or potentially escalate their privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0646|2024-05-23T23:00:23.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 15:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0607|2024-04-25T16:18:59.557Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0607</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Netfilter subsystem in the Linux kernel. The issue is in the nft_byteorder_eval() function, where the code iterates through a loop and writes to the `dst` array. On each iteration, 8 bytes are written, but `dst` is an array of u32, so each element only has space for 4 bytes. That means every iteration overwrites part of the previous element corrupting this array of u32. This flaw allows a local user to cause a denial of service or potentially break NetFilter functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0607|2024-04-25T16:18:59.557Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 15:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0914|2024-05-01T20:21:49.596Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0914</link>
      <description>A timing side-channel vulnerability has been discovered in the opencryptoki package while processing RSA PKCS#1 v1.5 padded ciphertexts. This flaw could potentially enable unauthorized RSA ciphertext decryption or signing, even without access to the corresponding private key.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0914|2024-05-01T20:21:49.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 04:53:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0406|2024-04-25T16:17:14.750Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20advanced%20cluster%20security%203
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0406</link>
      <description>A flaw was discovered in the mholt/archiver package. This flaw allows an attacker to create a specially crafted tar file, which, when unpacked, may allow access to restricted files or directories. This issue can allow the creation or overwriting of files with the user's or application's privileges using the library.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0406|2024-04-25T16:17:14.750Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 16:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0775|2024-04-25T16:22:05.159Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0775</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the __ext4_remount in fs/ext4/super.c in ext4 in the Linux kernel. This flaw allows a local user to cause an information leak problem while freeing the old quota file names before a potential failure, leading to a use-after-free.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0775|2024-04-25T16:22:05.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 13:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0562|2024-05-23T22:49:58.281Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208.6%20extended%20update%20support
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0562</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the Linux Kernel. When a disk is removed, bdi_unregister is called to stop further write-back and waits for associated delayed work to complete. However, wb_inode_writeback_end() may schedule bandwidth estimation work after this has completed, which can result in the timer attempting to access the recently freed bdi_writeback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0562|2024-05-23T22:49:58.281Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 19:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0217|2024-04-25T16:16:40.888Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0217</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in PackageKitd. In some conditions, the order of cleanup mechanics for a transaction could be impacted. As a result, some memory access could occur on memory regions that were previously freed. Once freed, a memory region can be reused for other allocations and any previously stored data in this memory region is considered lost.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0217|2024-04-25T16:16:40.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 17:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4693|2024-06-04T17:56:38.174Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4693</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the QEMU Virtio PCI Bindings (hw/virtio/virtio-pci.c). An improper release and use of the irqfd for vector 0 during the boot process leads to a guest triggerable crash via vhost_net_stop(). This flaw allows a malicious guest to crash the QEMU process on the host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4693|2024-06-04T17:56:38.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4369|2024-05-29T20:39:40.421Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openshift%20container%20platform%204
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4369</link>
      <description>An information disclosure flaw was found in OpenShift's internal image registry operator. The AZURE_CLIENT_SECRET can be exposed through an environment variable defined in the pod definition, but is limited to Azure environments. An attacker controlling an account that has high enough permissions to obtain pod information from the openshift-image-registry namespace could use this obtained client secret to perform actions as the registry operator's Azure service account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4369|2024-05-29T20:39:40.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 23:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4871|2024-05-14T14:27:41.323Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20satellite%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4871</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Satellite. When running a remote execution job on a host, the host's SSH key is not being checked. When the key changes, the Satellite still connects it because it uses "-o StrictHostKeyChecking=no". This flaw can lead to a man-in-the-middle attack (MITM), denial of service, leaking of secrets the remote execution job contains, or other issues that may arise from the attacker's ability to forge an SSH key. This issue does not directly allow unauthorized remote execution on the Satellite, although it can leak secrets that may lead to it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4871|2024-05-14T14:27:41.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4436|2024-06-04T17:55:37.472Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openstack%20platform%2016.1
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4436</link>
      <description>The etcd package distributed with the Red Hat OpenStack platform has an incomplete fix for CVE-2022-41723. This issue occurs because the etcd package in the Red Hat OpenStack platform is using http://golang.org/x/net/http2 instead of the one provided by Red Hat Enterprise Linux versions, meaning it should be updated at compile time instead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4436|2024-06-04T17:55:37.472Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 08:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4840|2024-05-30T23:06:12.172Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openstack%20platform%2016.2
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4840</link>
      <description>An flaw was found in the OpenStack Platform (RHOSP) director, a toolset for installing and managing a complete RHOSP environment. Plaintext passwords may be stored in log files, which can expose sensitive information to anyone with access to the logs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4840|2024-05-30T23:06:12.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4437|2024-06-04T17:55:01.138Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openstack%20platform%2016.1
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4437</link>
      <description>The etcd package distributed with the Red Hat OpenStack platform has an incomplete fix for CVE-2021-44716. This issue occurs because the etcd package in the Red Hat OpenStack platform is using http://golang.org/x/net/http2 instead of the one provided by Red Hat Enterprise Linux versions, meaning it should be updated at compile time instead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4437|2024-06-04T17:55:01.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 08:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4418|2024-05-08T03:03:05.135Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4418</link>
      <description>A race condition leading to a stack use-after-free flaw was found in libvirt. Due to a bad assumption in the virNetClientIOEventLoop() method, the `data` pointer to a stack-allocated virNetClientIOEventData structure ended up being used in the virNetClientIOEventFD callback while the data pointer's stack frame was concurrently being "freed" when returning from virNetClientIOEventLoop(). The 'virtproxyd' daemon can be used to trigger requests. If libvirt is configured with fine-grained access control, this issue, in theory, allows a user to escape their otherwise limited access. This flaw allows a local, unprivileged user to access virtproxyd without authenticating. Remote users would need to authenticate before they could access it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4418|2024-05-08T03:03:05.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4438|2024-06-04T17:54:33.071Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openstack%20platform%2016.1
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4438</link>
      <description>The etcd package distributed with the Red Hat OpenStack platform has an incomplete fix for CVE-2023-39325/CVE-2023-44487, known as Rapid Reset. This issue occurs because the etcd package in the Red Hat OpenStack platform is using http://golang.org/x/net/http2 instead of the one provided by Red Hat Enterprise Linux versions, meaning it should be updated at compile time instead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4438|2024-06-04T17:54:33.071Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 08:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4029|2024-05-09T10:40:32.291Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4029</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Wildfly’s management interface. Due to the lack of limitation of sockets for the management interface, it may be possible to cause a denial of service hitting the nofile limit as there is no possibility to configure or set a maximum number of connections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4029|2024-05-09T10:40:32.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 14:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4812|2024-06-05T15:06:13.886Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20satellite%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4812</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Katello plugin for Foreman, where it is possible to store malicious JavaScript code in the "Description" field of a user. This code can be executed when opening certain pages, for example, Host Collections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4812|2024-06-05T15:06:13.886Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4540|2024-06-04T17:53:04.999Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4540</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Keycloak in OAuth 2.0 Pushed Authorization Requests (PAR). Client-provided parameters were found to be included in plain text in the KC_RESTART cookie returned by the authorization server's HTTP response to a `request_uri` authorization request, possibly leading to an information disclosure vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4540|2024-06-04T17:53:04.999Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 15:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21886|2024-06-04T17:37:54.900Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21886</link>
      <description>A heap buffer overflow flaw was found in the DisableDevice function in the X.Org server. This issue may lead to an application crash or, in some circumstances, remote code execution in SSH X11 forwarding environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21886|2024-06-04T17:37:54.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 12:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21885|2024-06-04T17:37:51.149Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21885</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in X.Org server. In the XISendDeviceHierarchyEvent function, it is possible to exceed the allocated array length when certain new device IDs are added to the xXIHierarchyInfo struct. This can trigger a heap buffer overflow condition, which may lead to an application crash or remote code execution in SSH X11 forwarding environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21885|2024-06-04T17:37:51.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 12:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31419|2024-04-25T18:01:22.085Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openshift%20virtualization%204
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31419</link>
      <description>An information disclosure flaw was found in OpenShift Virtualization. The DownwardMetrics feature was introduced to expose host metrics to virtual machine guests and is enabled by default. This issue could expose limited host metrics of a node to any guest in any namespace without being explicitly enabled by an administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31419|2024-04-25T18:01:22.085Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31080|2024-05-29T23:42:50.533Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31080</link>
      <description>A heap-based buffer over-read vulnerability was found in the X.org server's ProcXIGetSelectedEvents() function. This issue occurs when byte-swapped length values are used in replies, potentially leading to memory leakage and segmentation faults, particularly when triggered by a client with a different endianness. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to cause the X server to read heap memory values and then transmit them back to the client until encountering an unmapped page, resulting in a crash. Despite the attacker's inability to control the specific memory copied into the replies, the small length values typically stored in a 32-bit integer can result in significant attempted out-of-bounds reads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31080|2024-05-29T23:42:50.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:47:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31081|2024-05-29T23:43:10.431Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31081</link>
      <description>A heap-based buffer over-read vulnerability was found in the X.org server's ProcXIPassiveGrabDevice() function. This issue occurs when byte-swapped length values are used in replies, potentially leading to memory leakage and segmentation faults, particularly when triggered by a client with a different endianness. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to cause the X server to read heap memory values and then transmit them back to the client until encountering an unmapped page, resulting in a crash. Despite the attacker's inability to control the specific memory copied into the replies, the small length values typically stored in a 32-bit integer can result in significant attempted out-of-bounds reads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31081|2024-05-29T23:43:10.431Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31082|2024-04-04T13:48:34.893Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31082</link>
      <description>A heap-based buffer over-read vulnerability was found in the X.org server's ProcAppleDRICreatePixmap() function. This issue occurs when byte-swapped length values are used in replies, potentially leading to memory leakage and segmentation faults, particularly when triggered by a client with a different endianness. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to cause the X server to read heap memory values and then transmit them back to the client until encountering an unmapped page, resulting in a crash. Despite the attacker's inability to control the specific memory copied into the replies, the small length values typically stored in a 32-bit integer can result in significant attempted out-of-bounds reads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31082|2024-04-04T13:48:34.893Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31083|2024-05-29T23:43:19.237Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31083</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability was found in the ProcRenderAddGlyphs() function of Xorg servers. This issue occurs when AllocateGlyph() is called to store new glyphs sent by the client to the X server, potentially resulting in multiple entries pointing to the same non-refcounted glyphs. Consequently, ProcRenderAddGlyphs() may free a glyph, leading to a use-after-free scenario when the same glyph pointer is subsequently accessed. This flaw allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on the system by sending a specially crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31083|2024-05-29T23:43:19.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31420|2024-06-04T17:35:55.202Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openshift%20virtualization%204
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31420</link>
      <description>A NULL pointer dereference flaw was found in KubeVirt. This flaw allows an attacker who has access to a virtual machine guest on a node with DownwardMetrics enabled to cause a denial of service by issuing a high number of calls to vm-dump-metrics --virtio and then deleting the virtual machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31420|2024-06-04T17:35:55.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 14:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3623|2024-04-25T17:46:47.141Z -- red%20hat -- mirror%20registry%20for%20red%20hat%20openshift
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3623</link>
      <description>A flaw was found when using mirror-registry to install Quay. It uses a default database secret key, which is stored in plain-text format in one of the configuration template files. This issue may lead to all instances of Quay deployed using mirror-registry to have the same database secret key. This flaw allows a malicious actor to access sensitive information from Quay's database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3623|2024-04-25T17:46:47.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3727|2024-06-03T15:06:22.414Z -- red%20hat -- migration%20toolkit%20for%20containers
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3727</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the github.com/containers/image library. This flaw allows attackers to trigger unexpected authenticated registry accesses on behalf of a victim user, causing resource exhaustion, local path traversal, and other attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3727|2024-06-03T15:06:22.414Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3567|2024-06-11T19:37:42.050Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3567</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in QEMU. An assertion failure was present in the update_sctp_checksum() function in hw/net/net_tx_pkt.c when trying to calculate the checksum of a short-sized fragmented packet. This flaw allows a malicious guest to crash QEMU and cause a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3567|2024-06-11T19:37:42.050Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 14:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3049|2024-06-06T10:18:47.685Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3049</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Booth, a cluster ticket manager. If a specially-crafted hash is passed to gcry_md_get_algo_dlen(), it may allow an invalid HMAC to be accepted by the Booth server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3049|2024-06-06T10:18:47.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 05:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3622|2024-04-25T17:46:29.152Z -- red%20hat -- mirror%20registry%20for%20red%20hat%20openshift
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3622</link>
      <description>A flaw was found when using mirror-registry to install Quay. It uses a default secret, which is stored in plain-text format in one of the configuration template files. This issue may lead to all instances of Quay deployed using mirror-registry to have the same secret key. This flaw allows a malicious actor to craft session cookies and as a consequence, it may lead to gaining access to the affected Quay instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3622|2024-04-25T17:46:29.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3625|2024-04-25T17:46:52.179Z -- red%20hat -- mirror%20registry%20for%20red%20hat%20openshift
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3625</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Quay, where Quay's database is stored in plain text in mirror-registry on Jinja's config.yaml file. This issue leaves the possibility of a malicious actor with access to this file to gain access to Quay's Redis instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3625|2024-04-25T17:46:52.179Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3019|2024-06-04T17:32:49.182Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3019</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in PCP. The default pmproxy configuration exposes the Redis server backend to the local network, allowing remote command execution with the privileges of the Redis user. This issue can only be exploited when pmproxy is running. By default, pmproxy is not running and needs to be started manually. The pmproxy service is usually started from the 'Metrics settings' page of the Cockpit web interface. This flaw affects PCP versions 4.3.4 and newer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3019|2024-06-04T17:32:49.182Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 18:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3296|2024-04-05T12:03:59.886Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3296</link>
      <description>A timing-based side-channel flaw exists in the rust-openssl package, which could be sufficient to recover a plaintext across a network in a Bleichenbacher-style attack. To achieve successful decryption, an attacker would have to be able to send a large number of trial messages for decryption. The vulnerability affects the legacy PKCS#1v1.5 RSA encryption padding mode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3296|2024-04-05T12:03:59.886Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3716|2024-06-05T17:22:47.779Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20satellite%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3716</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in foreman-installer when puppet-candlepin is invoked cpdb with the --password parameter. This issue leaks the password in the process list and allows an attacker to take advantage and obtain the password.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3716|2024-06-05T17:22:47.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3624|2024-06-04T17:32:11.306Z -- red%20hat -- mirror%20registry%20for%20red%20hat%20openshift
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3624</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in how Quay's database is stored in plain-text in mirror-registry on the jinja's config.yaml file. This flaw allows a malicious actor with access to this file to gain access to Quay's database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3624|2024-06-04T17:32:11.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3446|2024-04-25T17:46:02.079Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3446</link>
      <description>A double free vulnerability was found in QEMU virtio devices (virtio-gpu, virtio-serial-bus, virtio-crypto), where the mem_reentrancy_guard flag insufficiently protects against DMA reentrancy issues. This issue could allow a malicious privileged guest user to crash the QEMU process on the host, resulting in a denial of service or allow arbitrary code execution within the context of the QEMU process on the host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3446|2024-04-25T17:46:02.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 19:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3094|2024-04-18T17:29:57.790Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3094</link>
      <description>Malicious code was discovered in the upstream tarballs of xz, starting with version 5.6.0. &#13;
Through a series of complex obfuscations, the liblzma build process extracts a prebuilt object file from a disguised test file existing in the source code, which is then used to modify specific functions in the liblzma code. This results in a modified liblzma library that can be used by any software linked against this library, intercepting and modifying the data interaction with this library.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3094|2024-04-18T17:29:57.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 16:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3154|2024-06-05T16:49:15.208Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20openshift%20container%20platform%204.12
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3154</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in cri-o, where an arbitrary systemd property can be injected via a Pod annotation. Any user who can create a pod with an arbitrary annotation may perform an arbitrary action on the host system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3154|2024-06-05T16:49:15.208Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 03:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3508|2024-06-04T17:31:15.887Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20trusted%20profile%20analyzer
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3508</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Bombastic, which allows authenticated users to upload compressed (bzip2 or zstd) SBOMs. The API endpoint verifies the presence of some fields and values in the JSON. To perform this verification, the uploaded file must first be decompressed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3508|2024-06-04T17:31:15.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3657|2024-06-05T20:49:13.347Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20directory%20server%2011
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3657</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in 389-ds-base. A specially-crafted LDAP query can potentially cause a failure on the directory server, leading to a denial of service</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3657|2024-06-05T20:49:13.347Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2182|2024-05-29T21:21:52.184Z -- red%20hat -- fast%20datapath%20for%20red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2182</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Open Virtual Network (OVN). In OVN clusters where BFD is used between hypervisors for high availability, an attacker can inject specially crafted BFD packets from inside unprivileged workloads, including virtual machines or containers, that can trigger a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2182|2024-05-29T21:21:52.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 16:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2419|2024-06-04T17:30:42.025Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20build%20of%20keycloak%2022
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2419</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Keycloak's redirect_uri validation logic. This issue may allow a bypass of otherwise explicitly allowed hosts. A successful attack may lead to the theft of an access token, making it possible for the attacker to impersonate other users. It is very similar to CVE-2023-6291.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2419|2024-06-04T17:30:42.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 13:23:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2199|2024-06-04T17:30:35.441Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20directory%20server%2011
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2199</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability was found in 389-ds-base ldap server. This issue may allow an authenticated user to cause a server crash while modifying `userPassword` using malformed input.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2199|2024-06-04T17:30:35.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2947|2024-06-06T10:18:17.666Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2947</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Cockpit. Deleting a sosreport with a crafted name via the Cockpit web interface can lead to a command injection vulnerability, resulting in privilege escalation. This issue affects Cockpit versions 270 and newer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2947|2024-06-06T10:18:17.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 18:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2496|2024-06-04T17:30:31.872Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2496</link>
      <description>A NULL pointer dereference flaw was found in the udevConnectListAllInterfaces() function in libvirt. This issue can occur when detaching a host interface while at the same time collecting the list of interfaces via virConnectListAllInterfaces API. This flaw could be used to perform a denial of service attack by causing the libvirt daemon to crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2496|2024-06-04T17:30:31.872Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 12:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2700|2024-06-04T17:30:17.872Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20amq%20streams%202.7.0
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2700</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in the quarkus-core component. Quarkus captures local environment variables from the Quarkus namespace during the application's build, therefore, running the resulting application inherits the values captured at build time. Some local environment variables may have been set by the developer or CI environment for testing purposes, such as dropping the database during application startup or trusting all TLS certificates to accept self-signed certificates. If these properties are configured using environment variables or the .env facility, they are captured into the built application, which can lead to dangerous behavior if the application does not override these values. This behavior only happens for configuration properties from the `quarkus.*` namespace. Application-specific properties are not captured.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2700|2024-06-04T17:30:17.872Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2307|2024-05-29T23:28:57.953Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2307</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in osbuild-composer. A condition can be triggered that disables GPG verification for package repositories, which can expose the build phase to a Man-in-the-Middle attack, allowing untrusted code to be installed into an image being built.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2307|2024-05-29T23:28:57.953Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2002|2024-04-25T16:29:54.803Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2002</link>
      <description>A double-free vulnerability was found in libdwarf. In a multiply-corrupted DWARF object, libdwarf may try to dealloc(free) an allocation twice, potentially causing unpredictable and various results.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2002|2024-04-25T16:29:54.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 12:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2467|2024-04-25T16:45:02.948Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2467</link>
      <description>A timing-based side-channel flaw exists in the perl-Crypt-OpenSSL-RSA package, which could be sufficient to recover plaintext across a network in a Bleichenbacher-style attack. To achieve successful decryption, an attacker would have to be able to send a large number of trial messages. The vulnerability affects the legacy PKCS#1v1.5 RSA encryption padding mode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2467|2024-04-25T16:45:02.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2236|2024-04-25T16:44:12.964Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%206
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2236</link>
      <description>A timing-based side-channel flaw was found in libgcrypt's RSA implementation. This issue may allow a remote attacker to initiate a Bleichenbacher-style attack, which can lead to the decryption of RSA ciphertexts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2236|2024-04-25T16:44:12.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 22:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2905|2024-06-04T17:29:28.680Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%209.2%20extended%20update%20support
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2905</link>
      <description>A security vulnerability has been discovered within rpm-ostree, pertaining to the /etc/shadow file in default builds having the world-readable bit enabled. This issue arises from the default permissions being set at a higher level than recommended, potentially exposing sensitive authentication data to unauthorized access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2905|2024-06-04T17:29:28.680Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2494|2024-05-22T17:10:15.731Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2494</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the RPC library APIs of libvirt. The RPC server deserialization code allocates memory for arrays before the non-negative length check is performed by the C API entry points. Passing a negative length to the g_new0 function results in a crash due to the negative length being treated as a huge positive number. This flaw allows a local, unprivileged user to perform a denial of service attack by causing the libvirt daemon to crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2494|2024-05-22T17:10:15.731Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
