<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Red Hat -- ansible</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat/ansible.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat -- ansible</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 14:23:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10684|2024-08-04T11:06:10.659Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10684</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Ansible Engine, all versions 2.7.x, 2.8.x and 2.9.x prior to 2.7.17, 2.8.9 and 2.9.6 respectively, when using ansible_facts as a subkey of itself and promoting it to a variable when inject is enabled, overwriting the ansible_facts after the clean. An attacker could take advantage of this by altering the ansible_facts, such as ansible_hosts, users and any other key data which would lead into privilege escalation or code injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10684|2024-08-04T11:06:10.659Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14332|2024-08-04T12:39:36.318Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14332</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Ansible Engine when using module_args. Tasks executed with check mode (--check-mode) do not properly neutralize sensitive data exposed in the event data. This flaw allows unauthorized users to read this data. The highest threat from this vulnerability is to confidentiality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14332|2024-08-04T12:39:36.318Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10685|2024-08-04T11:06:10.628Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10685</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Ansible Engine affecting Ansible Engine versions 2.7.x before 2.7.17 and 2.8.x before 2.8.11 and 2.9.x before 2.9.7 as well as Ansible Tower before and including versions 3.4.5 and 3.5.5 and 3.6.3 when using modules which decrypts vault files such as assemble, script, unarchive, win_copy, aws_s3 or copy modules. The temporary directory is created in /tmp leaves the s ts unencrypted. On Operating Systems which /tmp is not a tmpfs but part of the root partition, the directory is only cleared on boot and the decryp emains when the host is switched off. The system will be vulnerable when the system is not running. So decrypted data must be cleared as soon as possible and the data which normally is encrypted ble.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10685|2024-08-04T11:06:10.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1736|2024-08-04T06:46:30.890Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1736</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Ansible Engine when a file is moved using atomic_move primitive as the file mode cannot be specified. This sets the destination files world-readable if the destination file does not exist and if the file exists, the file could be changed to have less restrictive permissions before the move. This could lead to the disclosure of sensitive data. All versions in 2.7.x, 2.8.x and 2.9.x branches are believed to be vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1736|2024-08-04T06:46:30.890Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 15:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1735|2024-08-04T06:46:30.837Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1735</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Ansible Engine when the fetch module is used. An attacker could intercept the module, inject a new path, and then choose a new destination path on the controller node. All versions in 2.7.x, 2.8.x and 2.9.x branches are believed to be vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1735|2024-08-04T06:46:30.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 15:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1740|2024-08-04T06:46:30.903Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1740</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Ansible Engine when using Ansible Vault for editing encrypted files. When a user executes "ansible-vault edit", another user on the same computer can read the old and new secret, as it is created in a temporary file with mkstemp and the returned file descriptor is closed and the method write_data is called to write the existing secret in the file. This method will delete the file before recreating it insecurely. All versions in 2.7.x, 2.8.x and 2.9.x branches are believed to be vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1740|2024-08-04T06:46:30.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 15:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14330|2024-08-04T12:39:36.412Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14330</link>
      <description>An Improper Output Neutralization for Logs flaw was found in Ansible when using the uri module, where sensitive data is exposed to content and json output. This flaw allows an attacker to access the logs or outputs of performed tasks to read keys used in playbooks from other users within the uri module. The highest threat from this vulnerability is to data confidentiality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14330|2024-08-04T12:39:36.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10744|2024-08-04T11:14:15.623Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10744</link>
      <description>An incomplete fix was found for the fix of the flaw CVE-2020-1733 ansible: insecure temporary directory when running become_user from become directive. The provided fix is insufficient to prevent the race condition on systems using ACLs and FUSE filesystems. Ansible Engine 2.7.18, 2.8.12, and 2.9.9 as well as previous versions are affected and Ansible Tower 3.4.5, 3.5.6 and 3.6.4 as well as previous versions are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10744|2024-08-04T11:14:15.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 13:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1733|2024-08-04T06:46:30.850Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1733</link>
      <description>A race condition flaw was found in Ansible Engine 2.7.17 and prior, 2.8.9 and prior, 2.9.6 and prior when running a playbook with an unprivileged become user. When Ansible needs to run a module with become user, the temporary directory is created in /var/tmp. This directory is created with "umask 77 &amp;&amp; mkdir -p &lt;dir&gt;"; this operation does not fail if the directory already exists and is owned by another user. An attacker could take advantage to gain control of the become user as the target directory can be retrieved by iterating '/proc/&lt;pid&gt;/cmdline'.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1733|2024-08-04T06:46:30.850Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 18:47:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1753|2024-08-04T06:46:30.868Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1753</link>
      <description>A security flaw was found in Ansible Engine, all Ansible 2.7.x versions prior to 2.7.17, all Ansible 2.8.x versions prior to 2.8.11 and all Ansible 2.9.x versions prior to 2.9.7, when managing kubernetes using the k8s module. Sensitive parameters such as passwords and tokens are passed to kubectl from the command line, not using an environment variable or an input configuration file. This will disclose passwords and tokens from process list and no_log directive from debug module would not have any effect making these secrets being disclosed on stdout and log files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1753|2024-08-04T06:46:30.868Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 14:37:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10691|2024-08-04T11:06:11.130Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10691</link>
      <description>An archive traversal flaw was found in all ansible-engine versions 2.9.x prior to 2.9.7, when running ansible-galaxy collection install. When extracting a collection .tar.gz file, the directory is created without sanitizing the filename. An attacker could take advantage to overwrite any file within the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10691|2024-08-04T11:06:11.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 16:23:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1737|2024-08-04T06:46:30.898Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1737</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Ansible 2.7.17 and prior, 2.8.9 and prior, and 2.9.6 and prior when using the Extract-Zip function from the win_unzip module as the extracted file(s) are not checked if they belong to the destination folder. An attacker could take advantage of this flaw by crafting an archive anywhere in the file system, using a path traversal. This issue is fixed in 2.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1737|2024-08-04T06:46:30.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 15:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1738|2024-08-04T06:46:31.069Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1738</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Ansible Engine when the module package or service is used and the parameter 'use' is not specified. If a previous task is executed with a malicious user, the module sent can be selected by the attacker using the ansible facts file. All versions in 2.7.x, 2.8.x and 2.9.x branches are believed to be vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1738|2024-08-04T06:46:31.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 15:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1734|2024-08-04T06:46:30.815Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1734</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the pipe lookup plugin of ansible. Arbitrary commands can be run, when the pipe lookup plugin uses subprocess.Popen() with shell=True, by overwriting ansible facts and the variable is not escaped by quote plugin. An attacker could take advantage and run arbitrary commands by overwriting the ansible facts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1734|2024-08-04T06:46:30.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 21:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1739|2024-08-04T06:46:30.852Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1739</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Ansible 2.7.16 and prior, 2.8.8 and prior, and 2.9.5 and prior when a password is set with the argument "password" of svn module, it is used on svn command line, disclosing to other users within the same node. An attacker could take advantage by reading the cmdline file from that particular PID on the procfs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1739|2024-08-04T06:46:30.852Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 17:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1746|2024-08-04T06:46:31.070Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1746</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Ansible Engine affecting Ansible Engine versions 2.7.x before 2.7.17 and 2.8.x before 2.8.11 and 2.9.x before 2.9.7 as well as Ansible Tower before and including versions 3.4.5 and 3.5.5 and 3.6.3 when the ldap_attr and ldap_entry community modules are used. The issue discloses the LDAP bind password to stdout or a log file if a playbook task is written using the bind_pw in the parameters field. The highest threat from this vulnerability is data confidentiality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1746|2024-08-04T06:46:31.070Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
