<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Red Hat -- ansible</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat/ansible.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat -- ansible</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:23:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14858|2024-08-05T00:26:39.087Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14858</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Ansible engine 2.x up to 2.8 and Ansible tower 3.x up to 3.5. When a module has an argument_spec with sub parameters marked as no_log, passing an invalid parameter name to the module will cause the task to fail before the no_log options in the sub parameters are processed. As a result, data in the sub parameter fields will not be masked and will be displayed if Ansible is run with increased verbosity and present in the module invocation arguments for the task.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14858|2024-08-05T00:26:39.087Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 14:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14905|2024-08-05T00:34:52.317Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14905</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Ansible Engine versions 2.9.x before 2.9.3, 2.8.x before 2.8.8, 2.7.x before 2.7.16 and earlier, where in Ansible's nxos_file_copy module can be used to copy files to a flash or bootflash on NXOS devices. Malicious code could craft the filename parameter to perform OS command injections. This could result in a loss of confidentiality of the system among other issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14905|2024-08-05T00:34:52.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 16:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14846|2024-08-05T00:26:39.176Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14846</link>
      <description>In Ansible, all Ansible Engine versions up to ansible-engine 2.8.5, ansible-engine 2.7.13, ansible-engine 2.6.19, were logging at the DEBUG level which lead to a disclosure of credentials if a plugin used a library that logged credentials at the DEBUG level. This flaw does not affect Ansible modules, as those are executed in a separate process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14846|2024-08-05T00:26:39.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 18:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14864|2024-08-05T00:26:39.116Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14864</link>
      <description>Ansible, versions 2.9.x before 2.9.1, 2.8.x before 2.8.7 and Ansible versions 2.7.x before 2.7.15, is not respecting the flag no_log set it to True when Sumologic and Splunk callback plugins are used send tasks results events to collectors. This would discloses and collects any sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14864|2024-08-05T00:26:39.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 14:23:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16876|2024-08-05T10:32:54.241Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16876</link>
      <description>ansible before versions 2.5.14, 2.6.11, 2.7.5 is vulnerable to a information disclosure flaw in vvv+ mode with no_log on that can lead to leakage of sensible data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16876|2024-08-05T10:32:54.241Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16859|2024-08-05T10:32:54.246Z -- red%20hat -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16859</link>
      <description>Execution of Ansible playbooks on Windows platforms with PowerShell ScriptBlock logging and Module logging enabled can allow for 'become' passwords to appear in EventLogs in plaintext. A local user with administrator privileges on the machine can view these logs and discover the plaintext password. Ansible Engine 2.8 and older are believed to be vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16859|2024-08-05T10:32:54.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
