<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Red Hat -- Business-central</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat/business-central.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat -- Business-central</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:22:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7463|2024-08-05T16:04:11.697Z -- red%20hat -- business-central
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7463</link>
      <description>JBoss BRMS 6 and BPM Suite 6 before 6.4.3 are vulnerable to a reflected XSS via artifact upload. A malformed XML file, if uploaded, causes an error message to appear that includes part of the bad XML code verbatim without filtering out scripts. Successful exploitation would allow execution of script code within the context of the affected user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7463|2024-08-05T16:04:11.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2674|2024-08-05T14:02:07.305Z -- red%20hat -- business-central
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2674</link>
      <description>JBoss BRMS 6 and BPM Suite 6 before 6.4.3 are vulnerable to a stored XSS via several lists in Business Central. The flaw is due to lack of sanitation of user input when creating new lists. Remote, authenticated attackers that have privileges to create lists can store scripts in them, which are not properly sanitized before showing to other users, including admins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2674|2024-08-05T14:02:07.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14886|2024-08-05T00:26:39.178Z -- red%20hat -- business-central
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14886</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in business-central, as shipped in rhdm-7.5.1 and rhpam-7.5.1, where encoded passwords are stored in errai_security_context. The encoding used for storing the passwords is Base64, not an encryption algorithm, and any recovery of these passwords could lead to user passwords being exposed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14886|2024-08-05T00:26:39.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
