<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Red Hat -- ipa</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat/ipa.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat -- ipa</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 15:23:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14867|2024-08-05T00:26:39.117Z -- red%20hat -- ipa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14867</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in IPA, all 4.6.x versions before 4.6.7, all 4.7.x versions before 4.7.4 and all 4.8.x versions before 4.8.3, in the way the internal function ber_scanf() was used in some components of the IPA server, which parsed kerberos key data. An unauthenticated attacker who could trigger parsing of the krb principal key could cause the IPA server to crash or in some conditions, cause arbitrary code to be executed on the server hosting the IPA server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14867|2024-08-05T00:26:39.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 08:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14826|2024-08-05T00:26:39.109Z -- red%20hat -- ipa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14826</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in FreeIPA versions 4.5.0 and later. Session cookies were retained in the cache after logout. An attacker could abuse this flaw if they obtain previously valid session cookies and can use this to gain access to the session.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14826|2024-08-05T00:26:39.109Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 15:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2590|2024-08-05T14:02:06.518Z -- red%20hat -- ipa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2590</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in ipa before 4.4. IdM's ca-del, ca-disable, and ca-enable commands did not properly check the user's permissions while modifying CAs in Dogtag. An authenticated, unauthorized attacker could use this flaw to delete, disable, or enable CAs causing various denial of service problems with certificate issuance, OCSP signing, and deletion of secret keys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2590|2024-08-05T14:02:06.518Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
