<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Red Hat -- Kernel</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat/kernel.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat -- Kernel</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:24:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14897|2024-08-05T00:26:39.202Z -- red%20hat -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14897</link>
      <description>A stack-based buffer overflow was found in the Linux kernel, version kernel-2.6.32, in Marvell WiFi chip driver. An attacker is able to cause a denial of service (system crash) or, possibly execute arbitrary code, when a STA works in IBSS mode (allows connecting stations together without the use of an AP) and connects to another STA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14897|2024-08-05T00:26:39.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 14:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14896|2024-08-05T00:26:39.112Z -- red%20hat -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14896</link>
      <description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability was found in the Linux kernel, version kernel-2.6.32, in Marvell WiFi chip driver. A remote attacker could cause a denial of service (system crash) or, possibly execute arbitrary code, when the lbs_ibss_join_existing function is called after a STA connects to an AP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14896|2024-08-05T00:26:39.112Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 08:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14901|2024-08-05T00:26:39.139Z -- red%20hat -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14901</link>
      <description>A heap overflow flaw was found in the Linux kernel, all versions 3.x.x and 4.x.x before 4.18.0, in Marvell WiFi chip driver. The vulnerability allows a remote attacker to cause a system crash, resulting in a denial of service, or execute arbitrary code. The highest threat with this vulnerability is with the availability of the system. If code execution occurs, the code will run with the permissions of root. This will affect both confidentiality and integrity of files on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14901|2024-08-05T00:26:39.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 14:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14895|2024-08-05T00:26:39.153Z -- red%20hat -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14895</link>
      <description>A heap-based buffer overflow was discovered in the Linux kernel, all versions 3.x.x and 4.x.x before 4.18.0, in Marvell WiFi chip driver. The flaw could occur when the station attempts a connection negotiation during the handling of the remote devices country settings. This could allow the remote device to cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14895|2024-08-05T00:26:39.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 13:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
