<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Red Hat -- Kernel</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat/kernel.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat -- Kernel</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 21:21:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10690|2024-08-04T11:06:11.142Z -- red%20hat -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10690</link>
      <description>There is a use-after-free in kernel versions before 5.5 due to a race condition between the release of ptp_clock and cdev while resource deallocation. When a (high privileged) process allocates a ptp device file (like /dev/ptpX) and voluntarily goes to sleep. During this time if the underlying device is removed, it can cause an exploitable condition as the process wakes up to terminate and clean all attached files. The system crashes due to the cdev structure being invalid (as already freed) which is pointed to by the inode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10690|2024-08-04T11:06:11.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 13:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10711|2024-08-04T11:14:14.192Z -- red%20hat -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10711</link>
      <description>A NULL pointer dereference flaw was found in the Linux kernel's SELinux subsystem in versions before 5.7. This flaw occurs while importing the Commercial IP Security Option (CIPSO) protocol's category bitmap into the SELinux extensible bitmap via the' ebitmap_netlbl_import' routine. While processing the CIPSO restricted bitmap tag in the 'cipso_v4_parsetag_rbm' routine, it sets the security attribute to indicate that the category bitmap is present, even if it has not been allocated. This issue leads to a NULL pointer dereference issue while importing the same category bitmap into SELinux. This flaw allows a remote network user to crash the system kernel, resulting in a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10711|2024-08-04T11:14:14.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 14:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3900|2024-08-04T19:26:26.695Z -- red%20hat -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3900</link>
      <description>An infinite loop issue was found in the vhost_net kernel module in Linux Kernel up to and including v5.1-rc6, while handling incoming packets in handle_rx(). It could occur if one end sends packets faster than the other end can process them. A guest user, maybe remote one, could use this flaw to stall the vhost_net kernel thread, resulting in a DoS scenario.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3900|2024-08-04T19:26:26.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 14:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-25661|2024-08-04T15:40:36.524Z -- red%20hat -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25661</link>
      <description>A Red Hat only CVE-2020-12351 regression issue was found in the way the Linux kernel's Bluetooth implementation handled L2CAP packets with A2MP CID. This flaw allows a remote attacker in an adjacent range to crash the system, causing a denial of service or potentially executing arbitrary code on the system by sending a specially crafted L2CAP packet. The highest threat from this vulnerability is to confidentiality, integrity, as well as system availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-25661|2024-08-04T15:40:36.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 20:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-25662|2024-08-04T15:40:36.651Z -- red%20hat -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25662</link>
      <description>A Red Hat only CVE-2020-12352 regression issue was found in the way the Linux kernel's Bluetooth stack implementation handled the initialization of stack memory when handling certain AMP packets. This flaw allows a remote attacker in an adjacent range to leak small portions of stack memory on the system by sending specially crafted AMP packets. The highest threat from this vulnerability is to data confidentiality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-25662|2024-08-04T15:40:36.651Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
