<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Red Hat -- keycloak</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat/keycloak.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat -- keycloak</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 15:22:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1758|2024-08-04T06:46:30.910Z -- red%20hat -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1758</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Keycloak in versions before 10.0.0, where it does not perform the TLS hostname verification while sending emails using the SMTP server. This flaw allows an attacker to perform a man-in-the-middle (MITM) attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1758|2024-08-04T06:46:30.910Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 18:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1697|2024-08-04T06:46:30.433Z -- red%20hat -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1697</link>
      <description>It was found in all keycloak versions before 9.0.0 that links to external applications (Application Links) in the admin console are not validated properly and could allow Stored XSS attacks. An authed malicious user could create URLs to trick users in other realms, and possibly conduct further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1697|2024-08-04T06:46:30.433Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 14:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1714|2024-08-04T06:46:30.830Z -- red%20hat -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1714</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Keycloak before version 11.0.0, where the code base contains usages of ObjectInputStream without type checks. This flaw allows an attacker to inject arbitrarily serialized Java Objects, which would then get deserialized in a privileged context and potentially lead to remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1714|2024-08-04T06:46:30.830Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 18:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14366|2024-08-04T12:46:33.307Z -- red%20hat -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14366</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in keycloak, where path traversal using URL-encoded path segments in the request is possible because the resources endpoint applies a transformation of the url path to the file path. Only few specific folder hierarchies can be exposed by this flaw</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14366|2024-08-04T12:46:33.307Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 16:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1718|2024-08-04T06:46:30.307Z -- red%20hat -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1718</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the reset credential flow in all Keycloak versions before 8.0.0. This flaw allows an attacker to gain unauthorized access to the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1718|2024-08-04T06:46:30.307Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 20:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1724|2024-08-04T06:46:30.888Z -- red%20hat -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1724</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Keycloak in versions before 9.0.2. This flaw allows a malicious user that is currently logged in, to see the personal information of a previously logged out user in the account manager section.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1724|2024-08-04T06:46:30.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 20:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1731|2024-08-04T06:46:30.501Z -- red%20hat -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1731</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in all versions of the Keycloak operator, before version 8.0.2,(community only) where the operator generates a random admin password when installing Keycloak, however the password remains the same when deployed to the same OpenShift namespace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1731|2024-08-04T06:46:30.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 16:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1744|2024-08-04T06:46:30.879Z -- red%20hat -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1744</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in keycloak before version 9.0.1. When configuring an Conditional OTP Authentication Flow as a post login flow of an IDP, the failure login events for OTP are not being sent to the brute force protection event queue. So BruteForceProtector does not handle this events.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1744|2024-08-04T06:46:30.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1698|2024-08-04T06:46:29.965Z -- red%20hat -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1698</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in keycloak in versions before 9.0.0. A logged exception in the HttpMethod class may leak the password given as parameter. The highest threat from this vulnerability is to data confidentiality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1698|2024-08-04T06:46:29.965Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 13:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
