<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Red Hat -- mirror registry for Red Hat OpenShift</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat/mirror%20registry%20for%20red%20hat%20openshift.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat -- mirror registry for Red Hat OpenShift</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-3623|2024-04-25T17:46:47.141Z -- Red Hat -- mirror registry for Red Hat OpenShift
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3623</link><description>A flaw was found when using mirror-registry to install Quay. It uses a default database secret key, which is stored in plain-text format in one of the configuration template files. This issue may lead to all instances of Quay deployed using mirror-registry to have the same database secret key. This flaw allows a malicious actor to access sensitive information from Quay's database.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3623|2024-04-25T17:46:47.141Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3622|2024-04-25T17:46:29.152Z -- Red Hat -- mirror registry for Red Hat OpenShift
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3622</link><description>A flaw was found when using mirror-registry to install Quay. It uses a default secret, which is stored in plain-text format in one of the configuration template files. This issue may lead to all instances of Quay deployed using mirror-registry to have the same secret key. This flaw allows a malicious actor to craft session cookies and as a consequence, it may lead to gaining access to the affected Quay instance.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3622|2024-04-25T17:46:29.152Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3625|2024-04-25T17:46:52.179Z -- Red Hat -- mirror registry for Red Hat OpenShift
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3625</link><description>A flaw was found in Quay, where Quay's database is stored in plain text in mirror-registry on Jinja's config.yaml file. This issue leaves the possibility of a malicious actor with access to this file to gain access to Quay's Redis instance.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3625|2024-04-25T17:46:52.179Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3624|2024-04-25T17:46:52.447Z -- Red Hat -- mirror registry for Red Hat OpenShift
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3624</link><description>A flaw was found in how Quay's database is stored in plain-text in mirror-registry on the jinja's config.yaml file. This flaw allows a malicious actor with access to this file to gain access to Quay's database.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3624|2024-04-25T17:46:52.447Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>