<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat/red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 21:20:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1454|2024-02-12T22:29:58.226Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1454</link><description>The use-after-free vulnerability was found in the AuthentIC driver in OpenSC packages, occuring in the card enrolment process using pkcs15-init when a user or administrator enrols or modifies cards. An attacker must have physical access to the computer system and requires a crafted USB device or smart card to present the system with specially crafted responses to the APDUs, which are considered high complexity and low severity. This manipulation can allow for compromised card management operations during enrolment.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1454|2024-02-12T22:29:58.226Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 22:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0408|2024-05-22T16:52:44.549Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0408</link><description>A flaw was found in the X.Org server. The GLX PBuffer code does not call the XACE hook when creating the buffer, leaving it unlabeled. When the client issues another request to access that resource (as with a GetGeometry) or when it creates another resource that needs to access that buffer, such as a GC, the XSELINUX code will try to use an object that was never labeled and crash because the SID is NULL.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0408|2024-05-22T16:52:44.549Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 15:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0409|2024-05-22T16:52:50.313Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0409</link><description>A flaw was found in the X.Org server. The cursor code in both Xephyr and Xwayland uses the wrong type of private at creation. It uses the cursor bits type with the cursor as private, and when initiating the cursor, that overwrites the XSELINUX context.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0409|2024-05-22T16:52:50.313Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0229|2024-05-22T16:52:43.485Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0229</link><description>An out-of-bounds memory access flaw was found in the X.Org server. This issue can be triggered when a device frozen by a sync grab is reattached to a different master device. This issue may lead to an application crash, local privilege escalation (if the server runs with extended privileges), or remote code execution in SSH X11 forwarding environments.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0229|2024-05-22T16:52:43.485Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 06:29:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21886|2024-05-22T16:53:14.665Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21886</link><description>A heap buffer overflow flaw was found in the DisableDevice function in the X.Org server. This issue may lead to an application crash or, in some circumstances, remote code execution in SSH X11 forwarding environments.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21886|2024-05-22T16:53:14.665Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 12:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21885|2024-05-22T16:53:12.711Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21885</link><description>A flaw was found in X.Org server. In the XISendDeviceHierarchyEvent function, it is possible to exceed the allocated array length when certain new device IDs are added to the xXIHierarchyInfo struct. This can trigger a heap buffer overflow condition, which may lead to an application crash or remote code execution in SSH X11 forwarding environments.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21885|2024-05-22T16:53:12.711Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 12:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31080|2024-05-23T23:32:41.998Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31080</link><description>A heap-based buffer over-read vulnerability was found in the X.org server's ProcXIGetSelectedEvents() function. This issue occurs when byte-swapped length values are used in replies, potentially leading to memory leakage and segmentation faults, particularly when triggered by a client with a different endianness. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to cause the X server to read heap memory values and then transmit them back to the client until encountering an unmapped page, resulting in a crash. Despite the attacker's inability to control the specific memory copied into the replies, the small length values typically stored in a 32-bit integer can result in significant attempted out-of-bounds reads.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31080|2024-05-23T23:32:41.998Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31081|2024-05-23T23:33:17.641Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31081</link><description>A heap-based buffer over-read vulnerability was found in the X.org server's ProcXIPassiveGrabDevice() function. This issue occurs when byte-swapped length values are used in replies, potentially leading to memory leakage and segmentation faults, particularly when triggered by a client with a different endianness. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to cause the X server to read heap memory values and then transmit them back to the client until encountering an unmapped page, resulting in a crash. Despite the attacker's inability to control the specific memory copied into the replies, the small length values typically stored in a 32-bit integer can result in significant attempted out-of-bounds reads.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31081|2024-05-23T23:33:17.641Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31083|2024-05-23T23:33:43.621Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31083</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability was found in the ProcRenderAddGlyphs() function of Xorg servers. This issue occurs when AllocateGlyph() is called to store new glyphs sent by the client to the X server, potentially resulting in multiple entries pointing to the same non-refcounted glyphs. Consequently, ProcRenderAddGlyphs() may free a glyph, leading to a use-after-free scenario when the same glyph pointer is subsequently accessed. This flaw allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on the system by sending a specially crafted request.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31083|2024-05-23T23:33:43.621Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:04:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2947|2024-04-25T17:44:26.460Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2947</link><description>A flaw was found in Cockpit. Deleting a sosreport with a crafted name via the Cockpit web interface can lead to a command injection vulnerability, resulting in privilege escalation. This issue affects Cockpit versions 270 and newer.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2947|2024-04-25T17:44:26.460Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 18:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2002|2024-04-25T16:29:54.803Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2002</link><description>A double-free vulnerability was found in libdwarf. In a multiply-corrupted DWARF object, libdwarf may try to dealloc(free) an allocation twice, potentially causing unpredictable and various results.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2002|2024-04-25T16:29:54.803Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 12:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>