<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8.2 Advanced Update Support</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/Red%20Hat/Red%20Hat%20Enterprise%20Linux%208.2%20Advanced%20Update%20Support.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8.2 Advanced Update Support</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 23:21:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2023-3812|2024-05-23T22:48:09.561Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8.2 Advanced Update Support
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3812</link><description>An out-of-bounds memory access flaw was found in the Linux kernel’s TUN/TAP device driver functionality in how a user generates a malicious (too big) networking packet when napi frags is enabled. This flaw allows a local user to crash or potentially escalate their privileges on the system.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3812|2024-05-23T22:48:09.561Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5178|2024-05-23T22:48:10.556Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8.2 Advanced Update Support
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5178</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability was found in drivers/nvme/target/tcp.c` in `nvmet_tcp_free_crypto` due to a logical bug in the NVMe/TCP subsystem in the Linux kernel. This issue may allow a malicious user to cause a use-after-free and double-free problem, which may permit remote code execution or lead to local privilege escalation.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5178|2024-05-23T22:48:10.556Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42753|2024-05-23T21:19:24.462Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8.2 Advanced Update Support
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42753</link><description>An array indexing vulnerability was found in the netfilter subsystem of the Linux kernel. A missing macro could lead to a miscalculation of the `h-&gt;nets` array offset, providing attackers with the primitive to arbitrarily increment/decrement a memory buffer out-of-bound. This issue may allow a local user to crash the system or potentially escalate their privileges on the system.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42753|2024-05-23T21:19:24.462Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 20:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4459|2024-05-23T22:28:24.983Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8.2 Advanced Update Support
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4459</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference flaw was found in vmxnet3_rq_cleanup in drivers/net/vmxnet3/vmxnet3_drv.c in the networking sub-component in vmxnet3 in the Linux Kernel. This issue may allow a local attacker with normal user privilege to cause a denial of service due to a missing sanity check during cleanup.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4459|2024-05-23T22:28:24.983Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 18:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4004|2024-05-23T22:37:33.655Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8.2 Advanced Update Support
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4004</link><description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the Linux kernel's netfilter in the way a user triggers the nft_pipapo_remove function with the element, without a NFT_SET_EXT_KEY_END. This issue could allow a local user to crash the system or potentially escalate their privileges on the system.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4004|2024-05-23T22:37:33.655Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 16:22:18 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>