<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Red Hat -- Red Hat JBoss Enterprise Application Platform 7</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat/red%20hat%20jboss%20enterprise%20application%20platform%207.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat -- Red Hat JBoss Enterprise Application Platform 7</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 13:25:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1459|2024-10-22T01:20:20.001Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20jboss%20enterprise%20application%20platform%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1459</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability was found in Undertow. This issue may allow a remote attacker to append a specially-crafted sequence to an HTTP request for an application deployed to JBoss EAP, which may permit access to privileged or restricted files and directories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1459|2024-10-22T01:20:20.001Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 20:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1635|2024-10-22T01:21:06.023Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20jboss%20enterprise%20application%20platform%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1635</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Undertow. This vulnerability impacts a server that supports the wildfly-http-client protocol. Whenever a malicious user opens and closes a connection with the HTTP port of the server and then closes the connection immediately, the server will end with both memory and open file limits exhausted at some point, depending on the amount of memory available. &#13;
&#13;
At HTTP upgrade to remoting, the WriteTimeoutStreamSinkConduit leaks connections if RemotingConnection is closed by Remoting ServerConnectionOpenListener. Because the remoting connection originates in Undertow as part of the HTTP upgrade, there is an external layer to the remoting connection. This connection is unaware of the outermost layer when closing the connection during the connection opening procedure. Hence, the Undertow WriteTimeoutStreamSinkConduit is not notified of the closed connection in this scenario. Because WriteTimeoutStreamSinkConduit creates a timeout task, the whole dependency tree leaks via that task, which is added to XNIO WorkerThread. So, the workerThread points to the Undertow conduit, which contains the connections and causes the leak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1635|2024-10-22T01:21:06.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 21:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
