<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Red Hat -- Red Hat Single Sign-On 7</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat/red%20hat%20single%20sign-on%207.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat -- Red Hat Single Sign-On 7</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 08:24:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4918|2024-08-02T07:44:52.148Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20single%20sign-on%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4918</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Keycloak package, more specifically org.keycloak.userprofile. When a user registers itself through registration flow, the "password" and "password-confirm" field from the form will occur as regular user attributes. All users and clients with proper rights and roles are able to read users attributes, allowing a malicious user with minimal access to retrieve the users passwords in clear text, jeopardizing their environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4918|2024-08-02T07:44:52.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 19:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2422|2024-08-02T06:19:15.138Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20single%20sign-on%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2422</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. A Keycloak server configured to support mTLS authentication for OAuth/OpenID clients does not properly verify the client certificate chain. A client that possesses a proper certificate can authorize itself as any other client, therefore, access data that belongs to other clients.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2422|2024-08-02T06:19:15.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 10:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2585|2024-08-02T06:26:09.896Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20single%20sign-on%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2585</link>
      <description>Keycloak's device authorization grant does not correctly validate the device code and client ID. An attacker client could abuse the missing validation to spoof a client consent request and trick an authorization admin into granting consent to a malicious OAuth client or possible unauthorized access to an existing OAuth client.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2585|2024-08-02T06:26:09.896Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
