<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat/red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%208.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-28834|2024-05-16T22:17:19.652Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28834</link><description>A flaw was found in GnuTLS. The Minerva attack is a cryptographic vulnerability that exploits deterministic behavior in systems like GnuTLS, leading to side-channel leaks. In specific scenarios, such as when using the GNUTLS_PRIVKEY_FLAG_REPRODUCIBLE flag, it can result in a noticeable step in nonce size from 513 to 512 bits, exposing a potential timing side-channel.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28834|2024-05-16T22:17:19.652Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1481|2024-05-22T17:01:47.262Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1481</link><description>A flaw was found in FreeIPA. This issue may allow a remote attacker to craft a HTTP request with parameters that can be interpreted as command arguments to kinit on the FreeIPA server, which can lead to a denial of service.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1481|2024-05-22T17:01:47.262Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1048|2024-05-22T17:01:17.186Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1048</link><description>A flaw was found in the grub2-set-bootflag utility of grub2. After the fix of CVE-2019-14865, grub2-set-bootflag will create a temporary file with the new grubenv content and rename it to the original grubenv file. If the program is killed before the rename operation, the temporary file will not be removed and may fill the filesystem when invoked multiple times, resulting in a filesystem out of free inodes or blocks.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1048|2024-05-22T17:01:17.186Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 17:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1753|2024-05-23T23:44:08.480Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1753</link><description>A flaw was found in Buildah (and subsequently Podman Build) which allows containers to mount arbitrary locations on the host filesystem into build containers. A malicious Containerfile can use a dummy image with a symbolic link to the root filesystem as a mount source and cause the mount operation to mount the host root filesystem inside the RUN step. The commands inside the RUN step will then have read-write access to the host filesystem, allowing for full container escape at build time.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1753|2024-05-23T23:44:08.480Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 14:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1488|2024-05-21T19:47:24.602Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1488</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Unbound due to incorrect default permissions, allowing any process outside the unbound group to modify the unbound runtime configuration. If a process can connect over localhost to port 8953, it can alter the configuration of unbound.service. This flaw allows an unprivileged attacker to manipulate a running instance, potentially altering forwarders, allowing them to track all queries forwarded by the local resolver, and, in some cases, disrupting resolving altogether.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1488|2024-05-21T19:47:24.602Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:04:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0443|2024-05-20T10:22:20.763Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0443</link><description>A flaw was found in the blkgs destruction path in block/blk-cgroup.c in the Linux kernel, leading to a cgroup blkio memory leakage problem. When a cgroup is being destroyed, cgroup_rstat_flush() is only called at css_release_work_fn(), which is called when the blkcg reference count reaches 0. This circular dependency will prevent blkcg and some blkgs from being freed after they are made offline. This issue may allow an attacker with a local access to cause system instability, such as an out of memory error.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0443|2024-05-20T10:22:20.763Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 23:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0565|2024-05-23T23:04:22.381Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0565</link><description>An out-of-bounds memory read flaw was found in receive_encrypted_standard in fs/smb/client/smb2ops.c in the SMB Client sub-component in the Linux Kernel. This issue occurs due to integer underflow on the memcpy length, leading to a denial of service.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0565|2024-05-23T23:04:22.381Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 20:02:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0553|2024-05-01T20:21:47.610Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0553</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GnuTLS. The response times to malformed ciphertexts in RSA-PSK ClientKeyExchange differ from the response times of ciphertexts with correct PKCS#1 v1.5 padding. This issue may allow a remote attacker to perform a timing side-channel attack in the RSA-PSK key exchange, potentially leading to the leakage of sensitive data. CVE-2024-0553 is designated as an incomplete resolution for CVE-2023-5981.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0553|2024-05-01T20:21:47.610Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 11:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0841|2024-05-22T16:44:15.892Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0841</link><description>A null pointer dereference flaw was found in the hugetlbfs_fill_super function in the Linux kernel hugetlbfs (HugeTLB pages) functionality. This issue may allow a local user to crash the system or potentially escalate their privileges on the system.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0841|2024-05-22T16:44:15.892Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 11:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0646|2024-05-23T23:00:23.283Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0646</link><description>An out-of-bounds memory write flaw was found in the Linux kernel’s Transport Layer Security functionality in how a user calls a function splice with a ktls socket as the destination. This flaw allows a local user to crash or potentially escalate their privileges on the system.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0646|2024-05-23T23:00:23.283Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 15:16:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0914|2024-05-01T20:21:49.596Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0914</link><description>A timing side-channel vulnerability has been discovered in the opencryptoki package while processing RSA PKCS#1 v1.5 padded ciphertexts. This flaw could potentially enable unauthorized RSA ciphertext decryption or signing, even without access to the corresponding private key.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0914|2024-05-01T20:21:49.596Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 04:53:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3019|2024-05-23T16:35:19.453Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3019</link><description>A flaw was found in PCP. The default pmproxy configuration exposes the Redis server backend to the local network, allowing remote command execution with the privileges of the Redis user. This issue can only be exploited when pmproxy is running. By default, pmproxy is not running and needs to be started manually. The pmproxy service is usually started from the 'Metrics settings' page of the Cockpit web interface. This flaw affects PCP versions 4.3.4 and newer.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3019|2024-05-23T16:35:19.453Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 18:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3296|2024-04-05T12:03:59.886Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3296</link><description>A timing-based side-channel flaw exists in the rust-openssl package, which could be sufficient to recover a plaintext across a network in a Bleichenbacher-style attack. To achieve successful decryption, an attacker would have to be able to send a large number of trial messages for decryption. The vulnerability affects the legacy PKCS#1v1.5 RSA encryption padding mode.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3296|2024-04-05T12:03:59.886Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:47:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2307|2024-05-22T16:24:42.043Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2307</link><description>A flaw was found in osbuild-composer. A condition can be triggered that disables GPG verification for package repositories, which can expose the build phase to a Man-in-the-Middle attack, allowing untrusted code to be installed into an image being built.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2307|2024-05-22T16:24:42.043Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2905|2024-04-25T17:44:15.985Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2905</link><description>A security vulnerability has been discovered within rpm-ostree, pertaining to the /etc/shadow file in default builds having the world-readable bit enabled. This issue arises from the default permissions being set at a higher level than recommended, potentially exposing sensitive authentication data to unauthorized access.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2905|2024-04-25T17:44:15.985Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2494|2024-05-22T17:10:15.731Z -- Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2494</link><description>A flaw was found in the RPC library APIs of libvirt. The RPC server deserialization code allocates memory for arrays before the non-negative length check is performed by the C API entry points. Passing a negative length to the g_new0 function results in a crash due to the negative length being treated as a huge positive number. This flaw allows a local, unprivileged user to perform a denial of service attack by causing the libvirt daemon to crash.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2494|2024-05-22T17:10:15.731Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>