<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat/red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:25:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40549|2024-08-02T11:44:06.648Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40549</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read flaw was found in Shim due to the lack of proper boundary verification during the load of a PE binary. This flaw allows an attacker to load a crafted PE binary, triggering the issue and crashing Shim, resulting in a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40549|2024-08-02T11:44:06.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5367|2024-08-02T07:59:43.957Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5367</link>
      <description>A out-of-bounds write flaw was found in the xorg-x11-server. This issue occurs due to an incorrect calculation of a buffer offset when copying data stored in the heap in the XIChangeDeviceProperty function in Xi/xiproperty.c and in RRChangeOutputProperty function in randr/rrproperty.c, allowing for possible escalation of privileges or denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5367|2024-08-02T07:59:43.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3603|2024-08-02T07:01:56.718Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3603</link>
      <description>A missing allocation check in sftp server processing read requests may cause a NULL dereference on low-memory conditions. The malicious client can request up to 4GB SFTP reads, causing allocation of up to 4GB buffers, which was not being checked for failure. This will likely crash the authenticated user's sftp server connection (if implemented as forking as recommended). For thread-based servers, this might also cause DoS for legitimate users.&#13;
&#13;
Given this code is not in any released versions, no security releases have been issued.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3603|2024-08-02T07:01:56.718Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 19:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1672|2024-08-02T05:57:24.884Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1672</link>
      <description>A race condition exists in the Tang server functionality for key generation and key rotation. This flaw results in a small time window where Tang private keys become readable by other processes on the same host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1672|2024-08-02T05:57:24.884Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40550|2024-08-02T11:44:18.703Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40550</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read flaw was found in Shim when it tried to validate the SBAT information. This issue may expose sensitive data during the system's boot phase.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40550|2024-08-02T11:44:18.703Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6478|2024-08-02T08:28:21.864Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6478</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in xorg-server. A specially crafted request to RRChangeProviderProperty or RRChangeOutputProperty can trigger an integer overflow which may lead to a disclosure of sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6478|2024-08-02T08:28:21.864Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 06:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5455|2024-08-02T07:59:44.726Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5455</link>
      <description>A Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in ipa/session/login_password in all supported versions of IPA. This flaw allows an attacker to trick the user into submitting a request that could perform actions as the user, resulting in a loss of confidentiality and system integrity. During community penetration testing it was found that for certain HTTP end-points FreeIPA does not ensure CSRF protection. Due to implementation details one cannot use this flaw for reflection of a cookie representing already logged-in user. An attacker would always have to go through a new authentication attempt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5455|2024-08-02T07:59:44.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 12:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5380|2024-08-02T07:59:44.624Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5380</link>
      <description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the xorg-x11-server. An X server crash may occur in a very specific and legacy configuration (a multi-screen setup with multiple protocol screens, also known as Zaphod mode) if the pointer is warped from within a window on one screen to the root window of the other screen and if the original window is destroyed followed by another window being destroyed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5380|2024-08-02T07:59:44.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3972|2024-08-02T11:25:41.795Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3972</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in insights-client. This security issue occurs because of insecure file operations or unsafe handling of temporary files and directories that lead to local privilege escalation. Before the insights-client has been registered on the system by root, an unprivileged local user or attacker could create the /var/tmp/insights-client directory (owning the directory with read, write, and execute permissions) on the system. After the insights-client is registered by root, an attacker could then control the directory content that insights are using by putting malicious scripts into it and executing arbitrary code as root (trivially bypassing SELinux protections because insights processes are allowed to disable SELinux system-wide).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3972|2024-08-02T11:25:41.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6816|2024-08-02T08:42:07.410Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6816</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in X.Org server. Both DeviceFocusEvent and the XIQueryPointer reply contain a bit for each logical button currently down. Buttons can be arbitrarily mapped to any value up to 255, but the X.Org Server was only allocating space for the device's particular number of buttons, leading to a heap overflow if a bigger value was used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6816|2024-08-02T08:42:07.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 04:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40548|2024-08-02T11:44:02.835Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40548</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow was found in Shim in the 32-bit system. The overflow happens due to an addition operation involving a user-controlled value parsed from the PE binary being used by Shim. This value is further used for memory allocation operations, leading to a heap-based buffer overflow. This flaw causes memory corruption and can lead to a crash or data integrity issues during the boot phase.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40548|2024-08-02T11:44:02.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:53:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6377|2024-08-02T08:28:21.782Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6377</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in xorg-server. Querying or changing XKB button actions such as moving from a touchpad to a mouse can result in out-of-bounds memory reads and writes. This may allow local privilege escalation or possible remote code execution in cases where X11 forwarding is involved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6377|2024-08-02T08:28:21.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 06:27:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40551|2024-08-02T11:44:22.905Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40551</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the MZ binary format in Shim. An out-of-bounds read may occur, leading to a crash or possible exposure of sensitive data during the system's boot phase.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40551|2024-08-02T11:44:22.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40547|2024-08-02T11:44:00.835Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40547</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability was found in Shim. The Shim boot support trusts attacker-controlled values when parsing an HTTP response. This flaw allows an attacker to craft a specific malicious HTTP request, leading to a completely controlled out-of-bounds write primitive and complete system compromise. This flaw is only exploitable during the early boot phase, an attacker needs to perform a Man-in-the-Middle or compromise the boot server to be able to exploit this vulnerability successfully.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40547|2024-08-02T11:44:00.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 15:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40546|2024-08-02T11:43:49.183Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40546</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Shim when an error happened while creating a new ESL variable. If Shim fails to create the new variable, it tries to print an error message to the user; however, the number of parameters used by the logging function doesn't match the format string used by it, leading to a crash under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40546|2024-08-02T11:43:49.183Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3899|2024-08-02T11:24:56.551Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3899</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in subscription-manager that allows local privilege escalation due to inadequate authorization. The D-Bus interface com.redhat.RHSM1 exposes a significant number of methods to all users that could change the state of the registration. By using the com.redhat.RHSM1.Config.SetAll() method, a low-privileged local user could tamper with the state of the registration, by unregistering the system or by changing the current entitlements. This flaw allows an attacker to set arbitrary configuration directives for /etc/rhsm/rhsm.conf, which can be abused to cause a local privilege escalation to an unconfined root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3899|2024-08-02T11:24:56.551Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 10:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21885|2024-08-01T22:35:33.394Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21885</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in X.Org server. In the XISendDeviceHierarchyEvent function, it is possible to exceed the allocated array length when certain new device IDs are added to the xXIHierarchyInfo struct. This can trigger a heap buffer overflow condition, which may lead to an application crash or remote code execution in SSH X11 forwarding environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21885|2024-08-01T22:35:33.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 12:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21886|2024-08-01T22:35:33.404Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21886</link>
      <description>A heap buffer overflow flaw was found in the DisableDevice function in the X.Org server. This issue may lead to an application crash or, in some circumstances, remote code execution in SSH X11 forwarding environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21886|2024-08-01T22:35:33.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 12:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3183|2024-08-01T20:05:07.630Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3183</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in FreeIPA in a way when a Kerberos TGS-REQ is encrypted using the client’s session key. This key is different for each new session, which protects it from brute force attacks. However, the ticket it contains is encrypted using the target principal key directly. For user principals, this key is a hash of a public per-principal randomly-generated salt and the user’s password.

If a principal is compromised it means the attacker would be able to retrieve tickets encrypted to any principal, all of them being encrypted by their own key directly. By taking these tickets and salts offline, the attacker could run brute force attacks to find character strings able to decrypt tickets when combined to a principal salt (i.e. find the principal’s password).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3183|2024-08-01T20:05:07.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 08:18:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2002|2024-08-01T18:56:22.520Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2002</link>
      <description>A double-free vulnerability was found in libdwarf. In a multiply-corrupted DWARF object, libdwarf may try to dealloc(free) an allocation twice, potentially causing unpredictable and various results.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2002|2024-08-01T18:56:22.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 12:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1454|2024-08-01T18:40:20.879Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1454</link>
      <description>The use-after-free vulnerability was found in the AuthentIC driver in OpenSC packages, occuring in the card enrolment process using pkcs15-init when a user or administrator enrols or modifies cards. An attacker must have physical access to the computer system and requires a crafted USB device or smart card to present the system with specially crafted responses to the APDUs, which are considered high complexity and low severity. This manipulation can allow for compromised card management operations during enrolment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1454|2024-08-01T18:40:20.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 22:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5564|2024-07-15T14:42:25.016Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5564</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in libndp. This flaw allows a local malicious user to cause a buffer overflow in NetworkManager, triggered by sending a malformed IPv6 router advertisement packet. This issue occurred as libndp was not correctly validating the route length information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5564|2024-07-15T14:42:25.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 18:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6126|2024-07-08T19:59:25.792Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6126</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the cockpit package. This flaw allows an authenticated user to kill any process when enabling the pam_env's user_readenv option, which leads to a denial of service (DoS) attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6126|2024-07-08T19:59:25.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6126|2024-07-03T14:51:17.880Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6126</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the cockpit package. This flaw allows an authenticated user to kill any process when enabling the pam_env's user_readenv option, which leads to a denial of service (DoS) attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6126|2024-07-03T14:51:17.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31083|2024-06-20T14:32:44.924Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31083</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability was found in the ProcRenderAddGlyphs() function of Xorg servers. This issue occurs when AllocateGlyph() is called to store new glyphs sent by the client to the X server, potentially resulting in multiple entries pointing to the same non-refcounted glyphs. Consequently, ProcRenderAddGlyphs() may free a glyph, leading to a use-after-free scenario when the same glyph pointer is subsequently accessed. This flaw allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on the system by sending a specially crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31083|2024-06-20T14:32:44.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3183|2024-06-12T13:43:10.079Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3183</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in FreeIPA in a way when a Kerberos TGS-REQ is encrypted using the client’s session key. This key is different for each new session, which protects it from brute force attacks. However, the ticket it contains is encrypted using the target principal key directly. For user principals, this key is a hash of a public per-principal randomly-generated salt and the user’s password.

If a principal is compromised it means the attacker would be able to retrieve tickets encrypted to any principal, all of them being encrypted by their own key directly. By taking these tickets and salts offline, the attacker could run brute force attacks to find character strings able to decrypt tickets when combined to a principal salt (i.e. find the principal’s password).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3183|2024-06-12T13:43:10.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 08:18:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7250|2024-06-04T11:15:32.414Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-7250</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in iperf, a utility for testing network performance using TCP, UDP, and SCTP. A malicious or malfunctioning client can send less than the expected amount of data to the iperf server, which can cause the server to hang indefinitely waiting for the remainder or until the connection gets closed. This will prevent other connections to the server, leading to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7250|2024-06-04T11:15:32.414Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 12:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5564|2024-06-04T18:02:43.761Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5564</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in libndp. This flaw allows a local malicious user to cause a buffer overflow in NetworkManager, triggered by sending a malformed IPv6 router advertisement packet. This issue occurred as libndp was not correctly validating the route length information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5564|2024-06-04T18:02:43.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 18:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1454|2024-02-12T22:29:58.226Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1454</link>
      <description>The use-after-free vulnerability was found in the AuthentIC driver in OpenSC packages, occuring in the card enrolment process using pkcs15-init when a user or administrator enrols or modifies cards. An attacker must have physical access to the computer system and requires a crafted USB device or smart card to present the system with specially crafted responses to the APDUs, which are considered high complexity and low severity. This manipulation can allow for compromised card management operations during enrolment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1454|2024-02-12T22:29:58.226Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 22:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0229|2024-05-29T23:25:41.266Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0229</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds memory access flaw was found in the X.Org server. This issue can be triggered when a device frozen by a sync grab is reattached to a different master device. This issue may lead to an application crash, local privilege escalation (if the server runs with extended privileges), or remote code execution in SSH X11 forwarding environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0229|2024-05-29T23:25:41.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 06:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21886|2024-06-04T17:37:54.900Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21886</link>
      <description>A heap buffer overflow flaw was found in the DisableDevice function in the X.Org server. This issue may lead to an application crash or, in some circumstances, remote code execution in SSH X11 forwarding environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21886|2024-06-04T17:37:54.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 12:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21885|2024-06-04T17:37:51.149Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21885</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in X.Org server. In the XISendDeviceHierarchyEvent function, it is possible to exceed the allocated array length when certain new device IDs are added to the xXIHierarchyInfo struct. This can trigger a heap buffer overflow condition, which may lead to an application crash or remote code execution in SSH X11 forwarding environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21885|2024-06-04T17:37:51.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 12:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31080|2024-05-29T23:42:50.533Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31080</link>
      <description>A heap-based buffer over-read vulnerability was found in the X.org server's ProcXIGetSelectedEvents() function. This issue occurs when byte-swapped length values are used in replies, potentially leading to memory leakage and segmentation faults, particularly when triggered by a client with a different endianness. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to cause the X server to read heap memory values and then transmit them back to the client until encountering an unmapped page, resulting in a crash. Despite the attacker's inability to control the specific memory copied into the replies, the small length values typically stored in a 32-bit integer can result in significant attempted out-of-bounds reads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31080|2024-05-29T23:42:50.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:47:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31081|2024-05-29T23:43:10.431Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31081</link>
      <description>A heap-based buffer over-read vulnerability was found in the X.org server's ProcXIPassiveGrabDevice() function. This issue occurs when byte-swapped length values are used in replies, potentially leading to memory leakage and segmentation faults, particularly when triggered by a client with a different endianness. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to cause the X server to read heap memory values and then transmit them back to the client until encountering an unmapped page, resulting in a crash. Despite the attacker's inability to control the specific memory copied into the replies, the small length values typically stored in a 32-bit integer can result in significant attempted out-of-bounds reads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31081|2024-05-29T23:43:10.431Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31083|2024-05-29T23:43:19.237Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31083</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability was found in the ProcRenderAddGlyphs() function of Xorg servers. This issue occurs when AllocateGlyph() is called to store new glyphs sent by the client to the X server, potentially resulting in multiple entries pointing to the same non-refcounted glyphs. Consequently, ProcRenderAddGlyphs() may free a glyph, leading to a use-after-free scenario when the same glyph pointer is subsequently accessed. This flaw allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on the system by sending a specially crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31083|2024-05-29T23:43:19.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2002|2024-04-25T16:29:54.803Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2002</link>
      <description>A double-free vulnerability was found in libdwarf. In a multiply-corrupted DWARF object, libdwarf may try to dealloc(free) an allocation twice, potentially causing unpredictable and various results.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2002|2024-04-25T16:29:54.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 12:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3657|2024-06-12T09:07:42.435Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3657</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in 389-ds-base. A specially-crafted LDAP query can potentially cause a failure on the directory server, leading to a denial of service</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3657|2024-06-12T09:07:42.435Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5564|2024-06-12T08:52:31.589Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5564</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in libndp. This flaw allows a local malicious user to cause a buffer overflow in NetworkManager, triggered by sending a malformed IPv6 router advertisement packet. This issue occurred as libndp was not correctly validating the route length information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5564|2024-06-12T08:52:31.589Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 18:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2199|2024-06-12T09:07:13.798Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2199</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability was found in 389-ds-base ldap server. This issue may allow an authenticated user to cause a server crash while modifying `userPassword` using malformed input.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2199|2024-06-12T09:07:13.798Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3183|2024-06-12T08:18:51.691Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3183</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in FreeIPA in a way when a Kerberos TGS-REQ is encrypted using the client’s session key. This key is different for each new session, which protects it from brute force attacks. However, the ticket it contains is encrypted using the target principal key directly. For user principals, this key is a hash of a public per-principal randomly-generated salt and the user’s password.

If a principal is compromised it means the attacker would be able to retrieve tickets encrypted to any principal, all of them being encrypted by their own key directly. By taking these tickets and salts offline, the attacker could run brute force attacks to find character strings able to decrypt tickets when combined to a principal salt (i.e. find the principal’s password).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3183|2024-06-12T08:18:51.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 08:18:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21885|2024-06-18T18:32:15.149Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21885</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in X.Org server. In the XISendDeviceHierarchyEvent function, it is possible to exceed the allocated array length when certain new device IDs are added to the xXIHierarchyInfo struct. This can trigger a heap buffer overflow condition, which may lead to an application crash or remote code execution in SSH X11 forwarding environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21885|2024-06-18T18:32:15.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 12:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5564|2024-06-28T18:31:08.720Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5564</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in libndp. This flaw allows a local malicious user to cause a buffer overflow in NetworkManager, triggered by sending a malformed IPv6 router advertisement packet. This issue occurred as libndp was not correctly validating the route length information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5564|2024-06-28T18:31:08.720Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 18:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31081|2024-07-05T17:22:25.941Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31081</link>
      <description>A heap-based buffer over-read vulnerability was found in the X.org server's ProcXIPassiveGrabDevice() function. This issue occurs when byte-swapped length values are used in replies, potentially leading to memory leakage and segmentation faults, particularly when triggered by a client with a different endianness. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to cause the X server to read heap memory values and then transmit them back to the client until encountering an unmapped page, resulting in a crash. Despite the attacker's inability to control the specific memory copied into the replies, the small length values typically stored in a 32-bit integer can result in significant attempted out-of-bounds reads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31081|2024-07-05T17:22:25.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5564|2024-07-14T18:15:18.692Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5564</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in libndp. This flaw allows a local malicious user to cause a buffer overflow in NetworkManager, triggered by sending a malformed IPv6 router advertisement packet. This issue occurred as libndp was not correctly validating the route length information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5564|2024-07-14T18:15:18.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 18:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0229|2024-08-01T17:41:16.397Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0229</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds memory access flaw was found in the X.Org server. This issue can be triggered when a device frozen by a sync grab is reattached to a different master device. This issue may lead to an application crash, local privilege escalation (if the server runs with extended privileges), or remote code execution in SSH X11 forwarding environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0229|2024-08-01T17:41:16.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 06:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6126|2024-08-01T21:33:04.382Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6126</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the cockpit package. This flaw allows an authenticated user to kill any process when enabling the pam_env's user_readenv option, which leads to a denial of service (DoS) attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6126|2024-08-01T21:33:04.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31080|2024-08-02T01:46:04.428Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31080</link>
      <description>A heap-based buffer over-read vulnerability was found in the X.org server's ProcXIGetSelectedEvents() function. This issue occurs when byte-swapped length values are used in replies, potentially leading to memory leakage and segmentation faults, particularly when triggered by a client with a different endianness. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to cause the X server to read heap memory values and then transmit them back to the client until encountering an unmapped page, resulting in a crash. Despite the attacker's inability to control the specific memory copied into the replies, the small length values typically stored in a 32-bit integer can result in significant attempted out-of-bounds reads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31080|2024-08-02T01:46:04.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:47:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31083|2024-08-02T01:46:04.596Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31083</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability was found in the ProcRenderAddGlyphs() function of Xorg servers. This issue occurs when AllocateGlyph() is called to store new glyphs sent by the client to the X server, potentially resulting in multiple entries pointing to the same non-refcounted glyphs. Consequently, ProcRenderAddGlyphs() may free a glyph, leading to a use-after-free scenario when the same glyph pointer is subsequently accessed. This flaw allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on the system by sending a specially crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31083|2024-08-02T01:46:04.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31081|2024-08-02T01:46:04.378Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31081</link>
      <description>A heap-based buffer over-read vulnerability was found in the X.org server's ProcXIPassiveGrabDevice() function. This issue occurs when byte-swapped length values are used in replies, potentially leading to memory leakage and segmentation faults, particularly when triggered by a client with a different endianness. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to cause the X server to read heap memory values and then transmit them back to the client until encountering an unmapped page, resulting in a crash. Despite the attacker's inability to control the specific memory copied into the replies, the small length values typically stored in a 32-bit integer can result in significant attempted out-of-bounds reads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31081|2024-08-02T01:46:04.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
