<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7.7 Advanced Update Support</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat/red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207.7%20advanced%20update%20support.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat -- Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7.7 Advanced Update Support</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 14:23:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-9050|2024-10-23T13:12:12.814Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207.7%20advanced%20update%20support
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9050</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the libreswan client plugin for NetworkManager (NetkworkManager-libreswan), where it fails to properly sanitize the VPN configuration from the local unprivileged user. In this configuration, composed by a key-value format, the plugin fails to escape special characters, leading the application to interpret values as keys. One of the most critical parameters that could be abused by a malicious user is the `leftupdown`key. This key takes an executable command as a value and is used to specify what executes as a callback in NetworkManager-libreswan to retrieve configuration settings back to NetworkManager. As NetworkManager uses Polkit to allow an unprivileged user to control the system's network configuration, a malicious actor could achieve local privilege escalation and potential code execution as root in the targeted machine by creating a malicious configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-9050|2024-10-23T13:12:12.814Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 12:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-9050|2024-10-23T11:02:06.460Z -- red%20hat -- red%20hat%20enterprise%20linux%207.7%20advanced%20update%20support</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9050</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the libreswan client plugin for NetworkManager (NetkworkManager-libreswan), where it fails to properly sanitize the VPN configuration from the local unprivileged user. In this configuration, composed by a key-value format, the plugin fails to escape special characters, leading the application to interpret values as keys. One of the most critical parameters that could be abused by a malicious user is the `leftupdown`key. This key takes an executable command as a value and is used to specify what executes as a callback in NetworkManager-libreswan to retrieve configuration settings back to NetworkManager. As NetworkManager uses Polkit to allow an unprivileged user to control the system's network configuration, a malicious actor could achieve local privilege escalation and potential code execution as root in the targeted machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-9050|2024-10-23T11:02:06.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 12:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
