<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Absolute Software -- Secure Access</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/absolute%20software/secure%20access.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Absolute Software -- Secure Access</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 17:21:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37346|2024-06-20T16:51:37.265Z -- absolute%20software -- secure%20access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37346</link>
      <description>There is an insufficient input validation vulnerability in
the Warehouse component of Absolute Secure Access prior to 13.06. Attackers
with system administrator permissions can impair the availability of certain
elements of the Secure Access administrative UI by writing invalid data to the
warehouse over the network. There is no loss of warehouse integrity or
confidentiality, the security scope is unchanged. Loss of availability is high.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37346|2024-06-20T16:51:37.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37345|2024-06-20T16:45:51.929Z -- absolute%20software -- secure%20access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37345</link>
      <description>There is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Secure
Access administrative UI of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.06.
Attackers can pass a limited-length script to the administrative UI which is
then stored where an administrator can access it. The scope is unchanged, there
is no loss of confidentiality. Impact to system availability is none, impact to
system integrity is high</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37345|2024-06-20T16:45:51.929Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37344|2024-06-20T16:38:26.256Z -- absolute%20software -- secure%20access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37344</link>
      <description>There is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Policy
management UI of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.06. Attackers with
system administrator permissions can interfere with another system
administrator’s use of the policy management UI when the administrators are
editing the same policy object. The scope is unchanged, there is no loss of
confidentiality. Impact to system availability is none, impact to system
integrity is high.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37344|2024-06-20T16:38:26.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37347|2024-06-20T16:56:50.468Z -- absolute%20software -- secure%20access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37347</link>
      <description>There is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the pool
configuration component of the management UI of Absolute Secure Access prior to
13.06. Attackers with system administrator permissions can pass a limited
length script to be run by another administrator. The scope is unchanged, there
is no loss of confidentiality. Impact to system integrity is high, impact to
system availability is none.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37347|2024-06-20T16:56:50.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37343|2024-06-20T16:30:21.053Z -- absolute%20software -- secure%20access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37343</link>
      <description>There is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Secure
Access administrative console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.06.
Attackers with valid tunnel credentials can pass a limited-length script to the
administrative console which is then temporarily stored where an administrator
using a non-default configuration could click on it while the attacker has a
valid tunnel session with the server. The scope is unchanged, there is no loss
of confidentiality. Impact to system availability is none, impact to system
integrity is high.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37343|2024-06-20T16:30:21.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
