<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for QSAN -- Storage Manager</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qsan/storage%20manager.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for QSAN -- Storage Manager</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:21:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32518|2024-09-16T18:29:47.617Z -- qsan -- storage%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32518</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in share_link in QSAN Storage Manager allows remote attackers to create a symbolic link then access arbitrary files. The referred vulnerability has been solved with the updated version of QSAN Storage Manager v3.3.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32518|2024-09-16T18:29:47.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 14:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32507|2024-09-16T17:38:03.443Z -- qsan -- storage%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32507</link>
      <description>Absolute Path Traversal vulnerability in FileDownload in QSAN Storage Manager allows remote authenticated attackers download arbitrary files via the Url path parameter. The referred vulnerability has been solved with the updated version of QSAN Storage Manager v3.3.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32507|2024-09-16T17:38:03.443Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 14:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32527|2024-09-16T19:30:57.666Z -- qsan -- storage%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32527</link>
      <description>Path traversal vulnerability in QSAN Storage Manager allows remote unauthenticated attackers to download arbitrary files thru injecting file path in download function. Suggest contacting with QSAN and refer to recommendations in QSAN Document.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32527|2024-09-16T19:30:57.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 14:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32512|2024-09-16T16:48:24.443Z -- qsan -- storage%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32512</link>
      <description>QuickInstall in QSAN Storage Manager does not filter special parameters properly that allows remote unauthenticated attackers to inject and execute arbitrary commands. The referred vulnerability has been solved with the updated version of QSAN Storage Manager v3.3.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32512|2024-09-16T16:48:24.443Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 14:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32508|2024-09-16T18:33:36.254Z -- qsan -- storage%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32508</link>
      <description>Absolute Path Traversal vulnerability in FileStreaming in QSAN Storage Manager allows remote authenticated attackers access arbitrary files by injecting the Symbolic Link following the Url path parameter. The referred vulnerability has been solved with the updated version of QSAN Storage Manager v3.3.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32508|2024-09-16T18:33:36.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 14:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32526|2024-09-16T16:24:00.799Z -- qsan -- storage%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32526</link>
      <description>Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource vulnerability in QSAN Storage Manager allows authenticated remote attackers to access arbitrary password files. Suggest contacting with QSAN and refer to recommendations in QSAN Document.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32526|2024-09-16T16:24:00.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 14:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32510|2024-09-16T21:09:06.325Z -- qsan -- storage%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32510</link>
      <description>QSAN Storage Manager through directory listing vulnerability in antivirus function allows remote authenticated attackers to list arbitrary directories by injecting file path parameter. The referred vulnerability has been solved with the updated version of QSAN Storage Manager v3.3.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32510|2024-09-16T21:09:06.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 14:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32513|2024-09-16T17:23:48.543Z -- qsan -- storage%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32513</link>
      <description>QsanTorture in QSAN Storage Manager does not filter special parameters properly that allows remote unauthenticated attackers to inject and execute arbitrary commands. The referred vulnerability has been solved with the updated version of QSAN Storage Manager v3.3.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32513|2024-09-16T17:23:48.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 14:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32522|2024-09-16T19:14:09.855Z -- qsan -- storage%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32522</link>
      <description>Improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts vulnerability in QSAN Storage Manager, XEVO, SANOS allows remote attackers to discover users’ credentials and obtain access via a brute force attack. Suggest contacting with QSAN and refer to recommendations in QSAN Document.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32522|2024-09-16T19:14:09.855Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 14:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32514|2024-09-16T16:58:14.848Z -- qsan -- storage%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32514</link>
      <description>Improper access control vulnerability in FirmwareUpgrade in QSAN Storage Manager allows remote attackers to reboot and discontinue the device. The referred vulnerability has been solved with the updated version of QSAN Storage Manager v3.3.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32514|2024-09-16T16:58:14.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 14:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32519|2024-09-16T19:11:01.631Z -- qsan -- storage%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32519</link>
      <description>Use of password hash with insufficient computational effort vulnerability in QSAN Storage Manager, XEVO, SANOS allows remote attackers to recover the plain-text password by brute-forcing the MD5 hash. The referred vulnerability has been solved with the updated version of QSAN Storage Manager v3.3.2, QSAN XEVO v2.1.0, and QSAN SANOS v2.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32519|2024-09-16T19:11:01.631Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 14:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32521|2024-09-16T18:04:06.277Z -- qsan -- storage%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32521</link>
      <description>Use of MAC address as an authenticated password in QSAN Storage Manager, XEVO, SANOS allows local attackers to escalate privileges. Suggest contacting with QSAN and refer to recommendations in QSAN Document.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32521|2024-09-16T18:04:06.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 14:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32511|2024-09-16T18:59:24.382Z -- qsan -- storage%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32511</link>
      <description>QSAN Storage Manager through directory listing vulnerability in ViewBroserList allows remote authenticated attackers to list arbitrary directories via the file path parameter. The referred vulnerability has been solved with the updated version of QSAN Storage Manager v3.3.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32511|2024-09-16T18:59:24.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 14:11:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32528|2024-09-16T16:38:38.906Z -- qsan -- storage%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32528</link>
      <description>Observable behavioral discrepancy vulnerability in QSAN Storage Manager allows remote attackers to obtain the system information without permissions. Suggest contacting with QSAN and refer to recommendations in QSAN Document.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32528|2024-09-16T16:38:38.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 14:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32506|2024-09-16T18:03:21.221Z -- qsan -- storage%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32506</link>
      <description>Absolute Path Traversal vulnerability in GetImage in QSAN Storage Manager allows remote authenticated attackers download arbitrary files via the Url path parameter. The referred vulnerability has been solved with the updated version of QSAN Storage Manager v3.3.3 .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32506|2024-09-16T18:03:21.221Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 14:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
