<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Xintian -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/xintian/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Xintian -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:23:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4867|2024-08-02T07:38:00.743Z -- xintian -- smart%20table%20integrated%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4867</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Xintian Smart Table Integrated Management System 5.6.9. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /SysManage/AddUpdateSites.aspx of the component Added Site Page. The manipulation of the argument TbxSiteName leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-239352.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Xintian Smart Table Integrated Management System 5.6.9 ausgemacht. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /SysManage/AddUpdateSites.aspx der Komponente Added Site Page. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments TbxSiteName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4867|2024-08-02T07:38:00.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 00:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4712|2024-08-02T07:38:00.595Z -- xintian -- smart%20table%20integrated%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4712</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Xintian Smart Table Integrated Management System 5.6.9. This affects an unknown part of the file /SysManage/AddUpdateRole.aspx. The manipulation of the argument txtRoleName leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-238575. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Xintian Smart Table Integrated Management System 5.6.9 gefunden. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /SysManage/AddUpdateRole.aspx. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments txtRoleName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4712|2024-08-02T07:38:00.595Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 19:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
