<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for blockmason -- credit-protocol</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/blockmason/credit-protocol.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for blockmason -- credit-protocol</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:24:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-25098|2024-08-05T12:33:47.848Z -- blockmason -- credit-protocol
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25098</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in blockmason credit-protocol. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function executeUcacTx of the file contracts/CreditProtocol.sol of the component UCAC Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The patch is named 082e01f18707ef995e80ebe97fcedb229a55efc5. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252799. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.
In blockmason credit-protocol wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion executeUcacTx der Datei contracts/CreditProtocol.sol der Komponente UCAC Handler. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Dieses Produkt setzt Rolling Releases ein. Aus diesem Grund sind Details zu betroffenen oder zu aktualisierende Versionen nicht verfügbar. Der Patch wird als 082e01f18707ef995e80ebe97fcedb229a55efc5 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-25098|2024-08-05T12:33:47.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 16:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
