<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for nvidia -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nvidia/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for nvidia -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 18:24:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5984|2024-08-04T08:47:40.968Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20vgpu%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5984</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Virtual GPU Manager contains a vulnerability in the vGPU plugin in which it may have the use-after-free vulnerability while freeing some resources, which may lead to denial of service, code execution, and information disclosure. This affects vGPU version 8.x (prior to 8.5), version 10.x (prior to 10.4) and version 11.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5984|2024-08-04T08:47:40.968Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 21:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34380|2024-08-04T00:12:50.375Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20tx1%2C%20tx2%20series%2C%20tx2%20nx%2C%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20xavier%20nx%2C%20nano%20and%20nano%202gb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34380</link>
      <description>Bootloader contains a vulnerability in NVIDIA MB2 where potential heap overflow might cause corruption of the heap metadata, which might lead to arbitrary code execution, denial of service, and information disclosure during secure boot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34380|2024-08-04T00:12:50.375Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34406|2024-08-04T00:12:50.176Z -- nvidia -- shield%20tv
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34406</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Tegra kernel driver contains a vulnerability in NVHost, where a specific race condition can lead to a null pointer dereference, which may lead to a system reboot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34406|2024-08-04T00:12:50.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 18:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5974|2024-08-04T08:47:40.886Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20agx%20xavier%2C%20tx1%2C%20tx2%2C%20and%20nano%20l4t
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5974</link>
      <description>NVIDIA JetPack SDK, version 4.2 and 4.3, contains a vulnerability in its installation scripts in which permissions are incorrectly set on certain directories, which can lead to escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5974|2024-08-04T08:47:40.886Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 22:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34373|2024-08-04T00:12:48.701Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20tx1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34373</link>
      <description>Trusty trusted Linux kernel (TLK) contains a vulnerability in the NVIDIA TLK kernel where a lack of heap hardening could cause heap overflows, which might lead to information disclosure and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34373|2024-08-04T00:12:48.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34396|2024-08-04T00:12:50.016Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20tx2%20series%2C%20tx2%20nx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34396</link>
      <description>Bootloader contains a vulnerability in access permission settings where unauthorized software may be able to overwrite NVIDIA MB2 code, which would result in limited denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34396|2024-08-04T00:12:50.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 21:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5969|2024-08-04T08:47:40.880Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20vgpu%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5969</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Virtual GPU Manager contains a vulnerability in the vGPU plugin, in which it validates a shared resource before using it, creating a race condition which may lead to denial of service or information disclosure. This affects vGPU version 8.x (prior to 8.4), version 9.x (prior to 9.4) and version 10.x (prior to 10.3).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5969|2024-08-04T08:47:40.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 22:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5985|2024-08-04T08:47:41.014Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20vgpu%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5985</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Virtual GPU Manager contains a vulnerability in the vGPU plugin, in which an input data length is not validated, which may lead to tampering or denial of service. This affects vGPU version 8.x (prior to 8.5), version 10.x (prior to 10.4) and version 11.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5985|2024-08-04T08:47:41.014Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 21:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5973|2024-08-04T08:47:41.022Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20vgpu%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5973</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Virtual GPU Manager and the guest drivers contain a vulnerability in vGPU plugin, in which there is the potential to execute privileged operations, which may lead to denial of service. This affects vGPU version 8.x (prior to 8.4), version 9.x (prior to 9.4) and version 10.x (prior to 10.3).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5973|2024-08-04T08:47:41.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 22:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11487|2024-08-04T11:35:11.981Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11487</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX servers, DGX-1 with BMC firmware versions prior to 3.38.30. DGX-2 with BMC firmware versions prior to 1.06.06 and all DGX A100 Servers with all BMC firmware versions, contains a vulnerability in the AMI BMC firmware in which the use of a hard-coded RSA 1024 key with weak ciphers may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11487|2024-08-04T11:35:11.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 03:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34377|2024-08-04T00:12:49.966Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20jetson%20xavier%20nx%2C%20jetson%20tx2%20series%2C%20jetson%20tx2%20nx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34377</link>
      <description>Trusty contains a vulnerability in the HDCP service TA where bounds checking in command 9 is missing. Improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer might lead to escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34377|2024-08-04T00:12:49.966Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34402|2024-08-04T00:12:49.900Z -- nvidia -- shield%20tv
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34402</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Tegra kernel driver contains a vulnerability in NVIDIA NVDEC, where a user with high privileges might be able to read from or write to a memory location that is outside the intended boundary of the buffer, which may lead to denial of service, Information disclosure, loss of Integrity, or possible escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34402|2024-08-04T00:12:49.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 18:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11484|2024-08-04T11:28:13.894Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11484</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX servers, all DGX-1 with BMC firmware versions prior to 3.38.30, contains a vulnerability in the AMI BMC firmware in which an attacker with administrative privileges can obtain the hash of the BMC/IPMI user password, which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11484|2024-08-04T11:28:13.894Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 03:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5981|2024-08-04T08:47:40.951Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5981</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver, all versions, contains a vulnerability in the DirectX11 user mode driver (nvwgf2um/x.dll), in which a specially crafted shader can cause an out of bounds access, which may lead to denial of service or code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5981|2024-08-04T08:47:40.951Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 18:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5992|2024-08-04T08:47:40.917Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20geforce%20now%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5992</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce NOW application software on Windows, all versions prior to 2.0.25.119, contains a vulnerability in its open-source software dependency in which the OpenSSL library is vulnerable to binary planting attacks by a local user, which may lead to code execution or escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5992|2024-08-04T08:47:40.917Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 22:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11488|2024-08-04T11:35:12.447Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11488</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX servers, all DGX-1 with BMC firmware versions prior to 3.38.30 and all DGX-2 with BMC firmware versions prior to 1.06.06, contains a vulnerability in the AMI BMC firmware in which software does not validate the RSA 1024 public key used to verify the firmware signature, which may lead to information disclosure or code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11488|2024-08-04T11:35:12.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 03:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34397|2024-08-04T00:12:49.915Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20tx2%20series%2C%20tx2%20nx%2C%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20xavier%20nx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34397</link>
      <description>Bootloader contains a vulnerability in NVIDIA MB2, which may cause free-the-wrong-heap, which may lead to limited denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34397|2024-08-04T00:12:49.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 21:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34375|2024-08-04T00:12:49.957Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20jetson%20xavier%20nx%2C%20jetson%20tx2%20series%2C%20jetson%20tx2%20nx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34375</link>
      <description>Trusty contains a vulnerability in all trusted applications (TAs) where the stack cookie was not randomized, which might result in stack-based buffer overflow, leading to denial of service, escalation of privileges, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34375|2024-08-04T00:12:49.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5971|2024-08-04T08:47:41.015Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20vgpu%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5971</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Virtual GPU Manager contains a vulnerability in the vGPU plugin, in which the software reads from a buffer by using buffer access mechanisms such as indexes or pointers that reference memory locations after the targeted buffer, which may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, or information disclosure. This affects vGPU version 8.x (prior to 8.4), version 9.x (prior to 9.4) and version 10.x (prior to 10.3).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5971|2024-08-04T08:47:41.015Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 22:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5983|2024-08-04T08:47:40.935Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20vgpu%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5983</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Virtual GPU Manager contains a vulnerability in the vGPU plugin and the host driver kernel module, in which the potential exists to write to a memory location that is outside the intended boundary of the frame buffer memory allocated to guest operating systems, which may lead to denial of service or information disclosure. This affects vGPU version 8.x (prior to 8.5), version 10.x (prior to 10.4) and version 11.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5983|2024-08-04T08:47:40.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 21:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5980|2024-08-04T08:47:40.934Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5980</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver, all versions, contains a vulnerability in multiple components in which a securely loaded system DLL will load its dependencies in an insecure fashion, which may lead to code execution or denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5980|2024-08-04T08:47:40.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 18:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5968|2024-08-04T08:47:40.814Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20vgpu%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5968</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Virtual GPU Manager contains a vulnerability in the vGPU plugin, in which the software does not restrict or incorrectly restricts operations within the boundaries of a resource that is accessed by using an index or pointer, such as memory or files, which may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, or information disclosure. This affects vGPU version 8.x (prior to 8.4), version 9.x (prior to 9.4) and version 10.x (prior to 10.3).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5968|2024-08-04T08:47:40.814Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 22:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34389|2024-08-04T00:12:50.025Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%2C%20tx2%20series%2C%20tx2%20nx%2C%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20xavier%20nx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34389</link>
      <description>Trusty contains a vulnerability in NVIDIA OTE protocol message parsing code, which is present in all the TAs. An incorrect bounds check can allow a local user through a malicious client to access memory from the heap in the TrustZone, which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34389|2024-08-04T00:12:50.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 21:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5975|2024-08-04T08:47:40.915Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20geforce%20now%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5975</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce NOW, versions prior to 2.0.23 on Windows and macOS, contains a vulnerability in the desktop application software that includes sensitive information as part of a URL, which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5975|2024-08-04T08:47:40.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 14:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11489|2024-08-04T11:35:12.442Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11489</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX servers, all DGX-1 with BMC firmware versions prior to 3.38.30 and all DGX-2 with BMC firmware versions prior to 1.06.06, contain a vulnerability in the AMI BMC firmware in which default SNMP community strings are used, which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11489|2024-08-04T11:35:12.442Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 03:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34399|2024-08-04T00:12:49.877Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20and%20tegra%20hardware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34399</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU and Tegra hardware contain a vulnerability in the internal microcontroller which may allow a user with elevated privileges to gain access to information from unscrubbed registers, which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34399|2024-08-04T00:12:49.877Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 14:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11485|2024-08-04T11:35:12.421Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11485</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX servers, all DGX-1 with BMC firmware versions prior to 3.38.30, contains a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the AMI BMC firmware in which the web application does not sufficiently verify whether a well-formed, valid, consistent request was intentionally provided by the user who submitted the request, which can lead to information disclosure or code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11485|2024-08-04T11:35:12.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 03:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11483|2024-08-04T11:28:14.182Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11483</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX servers, all DGX-1 with BMC firmware versions prior to 3.38.30 and all DGX-2 with BMC firmware versions prior to 1.06.06, contains a vulnerability in the AMI BMC firmware in which the firmware includes hard-coded credentials, which may lead to elevation of privileges or information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11483|2024-08-04T11:28:14.182Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 03:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34398|2024-08-04T00:12:50.048Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20data%20center%20gpu%20manager%20%28dcgm%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34398</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DCGM, all versions prior to 2.2.9, contains a vulnerability in the DIAG module where any user can inject shared libraries into the DCGM server, which is usually running as root, which may lead to privilege escalation, total loss of confidentiality and integrity, and complete denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34398|2024-08-04T00:12:50.048Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 15:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34400|2024-08-04T00:12:49.808Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20and%20tegra%20hardware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34400</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU and Tegra hardware contain a vulnerability in the internal microcontroller which may allow a user with elevated privileges to gain access to information from unscrubbed memory, which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34400|2024-08-04T00:12:49.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 14:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5966|2024-08-04T08:47:41.039Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5966</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver, all versions, contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer (nvlddmkm.sys) handler for DxgkDdiEscape, in which a NULL pointer is dereferenced, leading to denial of service or potential escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5966|2024-08-04T08:47:41.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 21:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5961|2024-08-04T08:47:40.909Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5961</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU graphics driver for guest OS contains a vulnerability in which an incorrect resource clean up on a failure path can impact the guest VM, leading to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5961|2024-08-04T08:47:40.909Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 20:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5964|2024-08-04T08:47:40.826Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5964</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver, all versions, contains a vulnerability in the service host component, in which the application resources integrity check may be missed. Such an attack may lead to code execution, denial of service or information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5964|2024-08-04T08:47:40.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34401|2024-08-04T00:12:50.077Z -- nvidia -- shield%20tv
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34401</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Linux kernel distributions contain a vulnerability in nvmap NVGPU_IOCTL_CHANNEL_SET_ERROR_NOTIFIER, where improper access control may lead to code execution, compromised integrity, or denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34401|2024-08-04T00:12:50.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 18:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34394|2024-08-04T00:12:50.176Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20tx2%20series%2C%20tx2%20nx%2C%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20xavier%20nx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34394</link>
      <description>Trusty contains a vulnerability in the NVIDIA OTE protocol that is present in all TAs. An incorrect message stream deserialization allows an attacker to use the malicious CA that is run by the user to cause the buffer overflow, which may lead to information disclosure and data modification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34394|2024-08-04T00:12:50.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 21:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5962|2024-08-04T08:47:40.933Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5962</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver, all versions, contains a vulnerability in the NVIDIA Control Panel component, in which an attacker with local system access can corrupt a system file, which may lead to denial of service or escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5962|2024-08-04T08:47:40.933Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 20:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5976|2024-08-04T08:47:40.938Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20geforce%20now%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5976</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce NOW, versions prior to 2.0.23 (Windows, macOS) and versions prior to 5.31 (Android, Shield TV), contains a vulnerability in the application software where the network test component transmits sensitive information insecurely, which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5976|2024-08-04T08:47:40.938Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 15:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34372|2024-08-04T00:12:49.639Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20tx2%20series%2C%20tx2%20nx%2C%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20xavier%20nx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34372</link>
      <description>Trusty (the trusted OS produced by NVIDIA for Jetson devices) driver contains a vulnerability in the NVIDIA OTE protocol message parsing code where an integer overflow in a malloc() size calculation leads to a buffer overflow on the heap, which might result in information disclosure, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34372|2024-08-04T00:12:49.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 21:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34374|2024-08-04T00:12:48.697Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20jetson%20xavier%20nx%2C%20jetson%20tx2%20series%2C%20jetson%20tx2%20nx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34374</link>
      <description>Trusty contains a vulnerability in command handlers where the length of input buffers is not verified. This vulnerability can cause memory corruption, which may lead to information disclosure, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34374|2024-08-04T00:12:48.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5978|2024-08-04T08:47:41.075Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20geforce%20experience%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5978</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience, all versions prior to 3.20.5.70, contains a vulnerability in its services in which a folder is created by nvcontainer.exe under normal user login with LOCAL_SYSTEM privileges which may lead to a denial of service or escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5978|2024-08-04T08:47:41.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 17:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5960|2024-08-04T08:47:41.025Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5960</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Virtual GPU Manager contains a vulnerability in the kernel module (nvidia.ko), where a null pointer dereference may occur, which may lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5960|2024-08-04T08:47:41.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 20:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11486|2024-08-04T11:35:12.026Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11486</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX servers, all DGX-1 with BMC firmware versions prior to 3.38.30, contain a vulnerability in the AMI BMC firmware in which software allows an attacker to upload or transfer files that can be automatically processed within the product's environment, which may lead to remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11486|2024-08-04T11:35:12.026Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 03:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34381|2024-08-04T00:12:50.078Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20tx1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34381</link>
      <description>Trusty TLK contains a vulnerability in the NVIDIA TLK kernel function where a lack of checks allows the exploitation of an integer overflow on the size parameter of the tz_map_shared_mem function, which might lead to denial of service, information disclosure, or data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34381|2024-08-04T00:12:50.078Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34395|2024-08-04T00:12:50.107Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20tx1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34395</link>
      <description>Trusty TLK contains a vulnerability in its access permission settings where it does not properly restrict access to a resource from a user with local privileges, which might lead to limited information disclosure, a low risk of modifcations to data, and limited denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34395|2024-08-04T00:12:50.107Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 21:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5970|2024-08-04T08:47:40.857Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20vgpu%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5970</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Virtual GPU Manager contains a vulnerability in the vGPU plugin, in which an input data size is not validated, which may lead to tampering or denial of service. This affects vGPU version 8.x (prior to 8.4), version 9.x (prior to 9.4) and version 10.x (prior to 10.3).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5970|2024-08-04T08:47:40.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 22:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34403|2024-08-04T00:12:50.244Z -- nvidia -- shield%20tv
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34403</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Linux distributions contain a vulnerability in nvmap ioctl, which allows any user with a local account to exploit a use-after-free condition, leading to code privilege escalation, loss of confidentiality and integrity, or denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34403|2024-08-04T00:12:50.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 18:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5963|2024-08-04T08:47:40.920Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5963</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver, all versions, contains a vulnerability in the Inter Process Communication APIs, in which improper access control may lead to code execution, denial of service, or information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5963|2024-08-04T08:47:40.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39158|2024-08-04T01:58:18.277Z -- nvidia -- caffe
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39158</link>
      <description>NVCaffe's python required dependencies list used to contain `gfortran`version prior to 0.17.4, entry which does not exist in the repository pypi.org. An attacker could potentially have posted malicious files to pypi.org causing a user to install it within NVCaffe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39158|2024-08-04T01:58:18.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 20:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34382|2024-08-04T00:12:50.365Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20tx1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34382</link>
      <description>Trusty TLK contains a vulnerability in the NVIDIA TLK kernel’s tz_map_shared_mem function where an integer overflow on the size parameter causes the request buffer and the logging buffer to overflow, allowing writes to arbitrary addresses within the kernel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34382|2024-08-04T00:12:50.365Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34378|2024-08-04T00:12:50.370Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20jetson%20xavier%20nx%2C%20jetson%20tx2%20series%2C%20jetson%20tx2%20nx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34378</link>
      <description>Trusty contains a vulnerability in the HDCP service TA where bounds checking in command 11 is missing. Improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer might lead to information disclosure, denial of service, or escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34378|2024-08-04T00:12:50.370Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34405|2024-08-04T00:12:50.082Z -- nvidia -- shield%20tv
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34405</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Linux distributions contain a vulnerability in TrustZone’s TEE_Malloc function, where an unchecked return value causing a null pointer dereference may lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34405|2024-08-04T00:12:50.082Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 18:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34379|2024-08-04T00:12:50.243Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20jetson%20xavier%20nx%2C%20jetson%20tx2%20series%2C%20jetson%20tx2%20nx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34379</link>
      <description>Trusty contains a vulnerability in the HDCP service TA where bounds checking in command 10 is missing. The length of an I/O buffer parameter is not checked, which might lead to memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34379|2024-08-04T00:12:50.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34404|2024-08-04T00:12:50.033Z -- nvidia -- shield%20tv
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34404</link>
      <description>Android images for T210 provided by NVIDIA contain a vulnerability in BROM, where failure to limit access to AHB-DMA when BROM fails may allow an unprivileged attacker with physical access to cause denial of service or impact integrity and confidentiality beyond the security scope of BROM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34404|2024-08-04T00:12:50.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 18:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5958|2024-08-04T08:47:41.028Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5958</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver, all versions, contains a vulnerability in the NVIDIA Control Panel component in which an attacker with local system access can plant a malicious DLL file, which may lead to code execution, denial of service, or information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5958|2024-08-04T08:47:41.028Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 21:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5990|2024-08-04T08:47:40.876Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20geforce%20experience%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5990</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience, all versions prior to 3.20.5.70, contains a vulnerability in the ShadowPlay component which may lead to local privilege escalation, code execution, denial of service or information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5990|2024-08-04T08:47:40.876Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 17:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5987|2024-08-04T08:47:41.015Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20vgpu%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5987</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Virtual GPU Manager contains a vulnerability in the vGPU plugin in which guest-supplied parameters remain writable by the guest after the plugin has validated them, which may lead to the guest being able to pass invalid parameters to plugin handlers, which may lead to denial of service or escalation of privileges. This affects vGPU version 8.x (prior to 8.5), version 10.x (prior to 10.4) and version 11.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5987|2024-08-04T08:47:41.015Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 21:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34386|2024-08-04T00:12:50.004Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20tx1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34386</link>
      <description>Trusty TLK contains a vulnerability in the NVIDIA TLK kernel where an integer overflow in the calloc size calculation can cause the multiplication of count and size can overflow, which might lead to heap overflows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34386|2024-08-04T00:12:50.004Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 21:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34383|2024-08-04T00:12:49.628Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20jetson%20xavier%20nx%2C%20jetson%20tx2%20series%2C%20jetson%20tx2%20nx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34383</link>
      <description>Bootloader contains a vulnerability in NVIDIA MB2 where a potential heap overflow might lead to denial of service or escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34383|2024-08-04T00:12:49.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5986|2024-08-04T08:47:41.068Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20vgpu%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5986</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Virtual GPU Manager contains a vulnerability in the vGPU plugin, in which an input data size is not validated, which may lead to tampering or denial of service. This affects vGPU version 8.x (prior to 8.5), version 10.x (prior to 10.4) and version 11.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5986|2024-08-04T08:47:41.068Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 21:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5977|2024-08-04T08:47:40.918Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20geforce%20experience%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5977</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience, all versions prior to 3.20.5.70, contains a vulnerability in NVIDIA Web Helper NodeJS Web Server in which an uncontrolled search path is used to load a node module, which may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5977|2024-08-04T08:47:40.918Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 17:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5957|2024-08-04T08:47:41.114Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5957</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver, all versions, contains a vulnerability in the NVIDIA Control Panel component in which an attacker with local system access can corrupt a system file, which may lead to denial of service or escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5957|2024-08-04T08:47:41.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 19:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34388|2024-08-04T00:12:49.987Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20tx1%2C%20tx2%20series%2C%20tx2%20nx%2C%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20xavier%20nx%2C%20nano%20and%20nano%202gb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34388</link>
      <description>Bootloader contains a vulnerability in NVIDIA TegraBoot where a potential heap overflow might allow an attacker to control all the RAM after the heap block, leading to denial of service or code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34388|2024-08-04T00:12:49.987Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 21:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5979|2024-08-04T08:47:40.902Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5979</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver, all versions, contains a vulnerability in the NVIDIA Control Panel component in which a user is presented with a dialog box for input by a high-privilege process, which may lead to escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5979|2024-08-04T08:47:40.902Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 18:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34391|2024-08-04T00:12:50.108Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20tx1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34391</link>
      <description>Trusty contains a vulnerability in the NVIDIA TLK kernel function where a lack of checks allows the exploitation of an integer overflow through a specific SMC call that is triggered by the user, which may lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34391|2024-08-04T00:12:50.108Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 21:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34387|2024-08-04T00:12:49.990Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20tx1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34387</link>
      <description>The ARM TrustZone Technology on which Trusty is based on contains a vulnerability in access permission settings where the portion of the DRAM reserved for TrustZone is identity-mapped by TLK with read, write, and execute permissions, which gives write access to kernel code and data that is otherwise mapped read only.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34387|2024-08-04T00:12:49.990Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 21:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34376|2024-08-04T00:12:49.998Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20jetson%20xavier%20nx%2C%20jetson%20tx2%20series%2C%20jetson%20tx2%20nx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34376</link>
      <description>Trusty contains a vulnerability in the HDCP service TA where bounds checking in command 5 is missing. Improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer might lead to denial of service, escalation of privileges, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34376|2024-08-04T00:12:49.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5972|2024-08-04T08:47:41.013Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20vgpu%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5972</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Virtual GPU Manager contains a vulnerability in the vGPU plugin, in which local pointer variables are not initialized and may be freed later, which may lead to tampering or denial of service. This affects vGPU version 8.x (prior to 8.4), version 9.x (prior to 9.4) and version 10.x (prior to 10.3).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5972|2024-08-04T08:47:41.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 22:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34393|2024-08-04T00:12:50.021Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20tx2%20series%2C%20tx2%20nx%2C%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20xavier%20nx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34393</link>
      <description>Trusty contains a vulnerability in TSEC TA which deserializes the incoming messages even though the TSEC TA does not expose any command. This vulnerability might allow an attacker to exploit the deserializer to impact code execution, causing information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34393|2024-08-04T00:12:50.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 21:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5959|2024-08-04T08:47:40.930Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5959</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Virtual GPU Manager, all versions, contains a vulnerability in the vGPU plugin in which an input index value is incorrectly validated which may lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5959|2024-08-04T08:47:40.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 20:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5982|2024-08-04T08:47:40.938Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5982</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver, all versions, contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer (nvlddmkm.sys) scheduler, in which the software does not properly limit the number or frequency of interactions that it has with an actor, such as the number of incoming requests, which may lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5982|2024-08-04T08:47:40.938Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 18:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34385|2024-08-04T00:12:49.860Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20tx1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34385</link>
      <description>Trusty TLK contains a vulnerability in the NVIDIA TLK kernel where an integer overflow in the calculation of a length could lead to a heap overflow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34385|2024-08-04T00:12:49.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5988|2024-08-04T08:47:40.908Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20vgpu%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5988</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Virtual GPU Manager contains a vulnerability in the vGPU plugin, in which allocated memory can be freed twice, which may lead to information disclosure or denial of service. This affects vGPU version 8.x (prior to 8.5), version 10.x (prior to 10.4) and version 11.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5988|2024-08-04T08:47:40.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 21:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34390|2024-08-04T00:12:50.346Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20tx1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34390</link>
      <description>Trusty contains a vulnerability in the NVIDIA TLK kernel function where a lack of checks allows the exploitation of an integer overflow through a specific SMC call that is triggered by the user, which may lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34390|2024-08-04T00:12:50.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 21:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34392|2024-08-04T00:12:49.984Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20tx1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34392</link>
      <description>Trusty TLK contains a vulnerability in the NVIDIA TLK kernel where an integer overflow in the tz_map_shared_mem function can bypass boundary checks, which might lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34392|2024-08-04T00:12:49.984Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 21:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11615|2024-08-04T11:35:13.342Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11615</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX servers, all BMC firmware versions prior to 3.38.30, contain a vulnerability in the AMI BMC firmware in which it uses a hard-coded RC4 cipher key, which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11615|2024-08-04T11:35:13.342Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 03:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5965|2024-08-04T08:47:40.939Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5965</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver, all versions, contains a vulnerability in the DirectX 11 user mode driver (nvwgf2um/x.dll), in which a specially crafted shader can cause an out of bounds access, leading to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5965|2024-08-04T08:47:40.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34384|2024-08-04T00:12:49.913Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20jetson%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20jetson%20xavier%20nx%2C%20jetson%20tx2%20series%2C%20jetson%20tx2%20nx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34384</link>
      <description>Bootloader contains a vulnerability in NVIDIA MB2 where a potential heap overflow could cause memory corruption, which might lead to denial of service or code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34384|2024-08-04T00:12:49.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5991|2024-08-04T08:47:41.040Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20cuda%20toolkit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5991</link>
      <description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit, all versions prior to 11.1.1, contains a vulnerability in the NVJPEG library in which an out-of-bounds read or write operation may lead to code execution, denial of service, or information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5991|2024-08-04T08:47:41.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 20:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11616|2024-08-04T11:35:13.619Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11616</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX servers, all BMC firmware versions prior to 3.38.30, contain a vulnerability in the AMI BMC firmware in which the Pseudo-Random Number Generator (PRNG) algorithm used in the JSOL package that implements the IPMI protocol is not cryptographically strong, which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11616|2024-08-04T11:35:13.619Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 03:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5989|2024-08-04T08:47:40.924Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20vgpu%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5989</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Virtual GPU Manager contains a vulnerability in the vGPU plugin, in which it can dereference a NULL pointer, which may lead to denial of service. This affects vGPU version 8.x (prior to 8.5), version 10.x (prior to 10.4) and version 11.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5989|2024-08-04T08:47:40.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 21:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5967|2024-08-04T08:47:40.974Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5967</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Linux GPU Display Driver, all versions, contains a vulnerability in the UVM driver, in which a race condition may lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5967|2024-08-04T08:47:40.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 21:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31028|2024-08-02T14:45:25.817Z -- nvidia -- nvjpeg2000%20library</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31028</link>
      <description>NVIDIA nvJPEG2000 Library for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where improper input validation might enable an attacker to use a specially crafted input file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31028|2024-08-02T14:45:25.817Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0077|2024-08-01T17:41:15.960Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0077</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Virtual GPU Manager contains a vulnerability in the vGPU plugin, where it allows a guest OS to allocate resources for which the guest OS is not authorized. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0077|2024-08-01T17:41:15.960Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0095|2024-08-01T17:41:15.986Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0095</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux and Windows contains a vulnerability where a user can inject forged logs and executable commands by injecting arbitrary data as a new log entry. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0095|2024-08-01T17:41:15.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0093|2024-08-01T17:41:16.016Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0093</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability where it can expose sensitive information to an actor that is not explicitly authorized to have access to that information. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0093|2024-08-01T17:41:16.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0085|2024-08-01T17:41:15.760Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0085</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where unprivileged users could execute privileged operations on the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0085|2024-08-01T17:41:15.760Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0096|2024-08-01T17:41:15.883Z -- nvidia -- chatrtx</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0096</link>
      <description>NVIDIA ChatRTX for Windows contains a vulnerability in Chat RTX UI, where a user can cause an improper privilege management issue by sending user inputs to change execution flow. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, escalation of privileges, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0096|2024-08-01T17:41:15.883Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 22:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0081|2024-08-01T17:41:15.959Z -- nvidia -- nemo</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0081</link>
      <description>NVIDIA NeMo framework for Ubuntu contains a vulnerability in tools/asr_webapp where an attacker may cause an allocation of resources without limits or throttling. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a server-side denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0081|2024-08-01T17:41:15.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 18:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0091|2024-08-01T17:41:15.985Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0091</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user can cause an untrusted pointer dereference by executing a driver API. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0091|2024-08-01T17:41:15.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0098|2024-08-01T17:41:15.925Z -- nvidia -- chatrtx</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0098</link>
      <description>NVIDIA ChatRTX for Windows contains a vulnerability in the ChatRTX UI and backend, where a user can cause a clear-text transmission of sensitive information issue by data sniffing. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0098|2024-08-01T17:41:15.925Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 22:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0097|2024-08-01T17:41:15.925Z -- nvidia -- chatrtx</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0097</link>
      <description>NVIDIA ChatRTX for Windows contains a vulnerability in ChatRTX UI, where a user can cause an improper privilege management issue by exploiting interprocess communication between different processes. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, escalation of privileges, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0097|2024-08-01T17:41:15.925Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 22:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0074|2024-08-01T17:41:16.440Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0074</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker may access a memory location after the end of the buffer. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0074|2024-08-01T17:41:16.440Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0087|2024-08-01T17:41:15.967Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0087</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux contains a vulnerability where a user can set the logging location to an arbitrary file. If this file exists, logs are appended to the file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0087|2024-08-01T17:41:15.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0073|2024-08-01T17:41:15.913Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0073</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer when the driver is performing an operation at a privilege level that is higher than the minimum level required. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0073|2024-08-01T17:41:15.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0084|2024-08-01T17:41:15.927Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0084</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where the guest OS could execute privileged operations. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0084|2024-08-01T17:41:15.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0089|2024-08-01T17:41:15.971Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0089</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability where the information from a previous client or another process could be disclosed. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, information disclosure, or data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0089|2024-08-01T17:41:15.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0088|2024-08-01T17:41:15.698Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0088</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux contains a vulnerability in shared memory APIs, where a user can cause an improper memory access issue by a network API. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0088|2024-08-01T17:41:15.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0092|2024-08-01T17:41:15.947Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0092</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where an improper check or improper handling of exception conditions might lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0092|2024-08-01T17:41:15.947Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0072|2024-08-01T17:41:15.878Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20cuda%20toolkit</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0072</link>
      <description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump and nvdisasm where an attacker may cause a crash by tricking a user into reading a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a partial denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0072|2024-08-01T17:41:15.878Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0090|2024-08-01T17:41:15.818Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0090</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user can cause an out-of-bounds write. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0090|2024-08-01T17:41:15.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0075|2024-08-01T17:41:16.431Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0075</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user may cause a NULL-pointer dereference by accessing passed parameters the validity of which has not been checked. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service and limited information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0075|2024-08-01T17:41:16.431Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0103|2024-08-01T17:41:15.919Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0103</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux contains a vulnerability where a user may cause an incorrect Initialization of resource by network issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0103|2024-08-01T17:41:15.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0080|2024-08-01T17:41:15.815Z -- nvidia -- nvtiff%20library</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0080</link>
      <description>NVIDIA nvTIFF Library for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where improper input validation might enable an attacker to use a specially crafted input file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0080|2024-08-01T17:41:15.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0071|2024-08-01T17:41:15.919Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0071</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-of-bounds write. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0071|2024-08-01T17:41:15.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0078|2024-08-01T17:41:15.926Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0078</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer, where a user in a guest can cause a NULL-pointer dereference in the host, which may lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0078|2024-08-01T17:41:15.926Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0079|2024-08-01T17:41:15.829Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0079</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer, where a user in a guest VM can cause a NULL-pointer dereference in the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0079|2024-08-01T17:41:15.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0099|2024-08-01T17:41:15.985Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0099</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where the guest OS could cause buffer overrun in the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0099|2024-08-01T17:41:15.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0094|2024-08-01T17:41:16.124Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0094</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where an untrusted guest VM can cause improper control of the interaction frequency in the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0094|2024-08-01T17:41:16.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0100|2024-08-01T17:41:15.921Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0100</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux contains a vulnerability in the tracing API, where a user can corrupt system files. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0100|2024-08-01T17:41:15.921Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0076|2024-08-01T17:41:15.939Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20cuda%20toolkit</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0076</link>
      <description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump and nvdisasm where an attacker may cause a crash by tricking a user into reading a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a partial denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0076|2024-08-01T17:41:15.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0083|2024-08-01T17:41:15.843Z -- nvidia -- chatrtx</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0083</link>
      <description>NVIDIA ChatRTX for Windows contains a vulnerability in the UI, where an attacker can cause a cross-site scripting error by network by running malicious scripts in users' browsers. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0083|2024-08-01T17:41:15.843Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 22:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0086|2024-08-01T17:41:15.913Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0086</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability where the software can dereference a NULL pointer. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service and undefined behavior in the vGPU plugin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0086|2024-08-01T17:41:15.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0082|2024-08-01T17:41:16.012Z -- nvidia -- chatrtx</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0082</link>
      <description>NVIDIA ChatRTX for Windows contains a vulnerability in the UI, where an attacker can cause improper privilege management by sending open file requests to the application. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to local escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0082|2024-08-01T17:41:16.012Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 22:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0100|2024-07-23T18:42:27.513Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0100</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux contains a vulnerability in the tracing API, where a user can corrupt system files. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0100|2024-07-23T18:42:27.513Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0075|2024-07-23T18:28:25.375Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0075</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user may cause a NULL-pointer dereference by accessing passed parameters the validity of which has not been checked. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service and limited information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0075|2024-07-23T18:28:25.375Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31028|2024-07-05T17:22:41.743Z -- nvidia -- nvjpeg2000%20library</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31028</link>
      <description>NVIDIA nvJPEG2000 Library for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where improper input validation might enable an attacker to use a specially crafted input file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31028|2024-07-05T17:22:41.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0072|2024-06-20T16:18:17.569Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20cuda%20toolkit</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0072</link>
      <description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump and nvdisasm where an attacker may cause a crash by tricking a user into reading a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a partial denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0072|2024-06-20T16:18:17.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0099|2024-06-17T13:17:13.597Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0099</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where the guest OS could cause buffer overrun in the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0099|2024-06-17T13:17:13.597Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0091|2024-06-15T03:55:35.767Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0091</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user can cause an untrusted pointer dereference by executing a driver API. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0091|2024-06-15T03:55:35.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0084|2024-06-15T03:55:37.767Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0084</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where the guest OS could execute privileged operations. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0084|2024-06-15T03:55:37.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0090|2024-06-15T03:55:33.792Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0090</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user can cause an out-of-bounds write. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0090|2024-06-15T03:55:33.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0099|2024-06-15T03:55:36.784Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0099</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where the guest OS could cause buffer overrun in the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0099|2024-06-15T03:55:36.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0089|2024-06-15T03:55:34.774Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0089</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability where the information from a previous client or another process could be disclosed. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, information disclosure, or data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0089|2024-06-15T03:55:34.774Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0090|2024-06-14T19:08:11.016Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0090</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user can cause an out-of-bounds write. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0090|2024-06-14T19:08:11.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0084|2024-06-14T17:19:48.609Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0084</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where the guest OS could execute privileged operations. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0084|2024-06-14T17:19:48.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0094|2024-06-13T21:23:31.858Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0094</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where an untrusted guest VM can cause improper control of the interaction frequency in the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0094|2024-06-13T21:23:31.858Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0103|2024-06-13T21:16:51.611Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0103</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux contains a vulnerability where a user may cause an incorrect Initialization of resource by network issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0103|2024-06-13T21:16:51.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0086|2024-06-13T21:23:32.289Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0086</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability where the software can dereference a NULL pointer. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service and undefined behavior in the vGPU plugin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0086|2024-06-13T21:23:32.289Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0095|2024-06-13T21:16:51.975Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0095</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux and Windows contains a vulnerability where a user can inject forged logs and executable commands by injecting arbitrary data as a new log entry. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0095|2024-06-13T21:16:51.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0091|2024-06-13T21:23:29.556Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0091</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user can cause an untrusted pointer dereference by executing a driver API. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0091|2024-06-13T21:23:29.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0084|2024-06-13T21:23:31.105Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0084</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where the guest OS could execute privileged operations. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0084|2024-06-13T21:23:31.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0090|2024-06-13T21:23:28.800Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0090</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user can cause an out-of-bounds write. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0090|2024-06-13T21:23:28.800Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0093|2024-06-13T21:23:29.967Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0093</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability where it can expose sensitive information to an actor that is not explicitly authorized to have access to that information. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0093|2024-06-13T21:23:29.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0099|2024-06-13T21:23:30.685Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0099</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where the guest OS could cause buffer overrun in the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0099|2024-06-13T21:23:30.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0092|2024-06-13T21:23:30.327Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0092</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where an improper check or improper handling of exception conditions might lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0092|2024-06-13T21:23:30.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0089|2024-06-13T21:23:29.198Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0089</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability where the information from a previous client or another process could be disclosed. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, information disclosure, or data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0089|2024-06-13T21:23:29.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0085|2024-06-13T21:23:31.505Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0085</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where unprivileged users could execute privileged operations on the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0085|2024-06-13T21:23:31.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0082|2024-06-06T13:05:04.914Z -- nvidia -- chatrtx</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0082</link>
      <description>NVIDIA ChatRTX for Windows contains a vulnerability in the UI, where an attacker can cause improper privilege management by sending open file requests to the application. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to local escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0082|2024-06-06T13:05:04.914Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 22:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0077|2024-03-27T21:52:27.188Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0077</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Virtual GPU Manager contains a vulnerability in the vGPU plugin, where it allows a guest OS to allocate resources for which the guest OS is not authorized. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0077|2024-03-27T21:52:27.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0098|2024-06-06T13:05:55.509Z -- nvidia -- chatrtx</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0098</link>
      <description>NVIDIA ChatRTX for Windows contains a vulnerability in the ChatRTX UI and backend, where a user can cause a clear-text transmission of sensitive information issue by data sniffing. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0098|2024-06-06T13:05:55.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 22:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0076|2024-04-05T17:50:06.319Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20cuda%20toolkit</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0076</link>
      <description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump and nvdisasm where an attacker may cause a crash by tricking a user into reading a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a partial denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0076|2024-04-05T17:50:06.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0083|2024-04-08T22:10:25.070Z -- nvidia -- chatrtx</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0083</link>
      <description>NVIDIA ChatRTX for Windows contains a vulnerability in the UI, where an attacker can cause a cross-site scripting error by network by running malicious scripts in users' browsers. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0083|2024-04-08T22:10:25.070Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 22:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0071|2024-03-27T21:52:24.951Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0071</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-of-bounds write. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0071|2024-03-27T21:52:24.951Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0088|2024-06-04T17:58:35.426Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0088</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux contains a vulnerability in shared memory APIs, where a user can cause an improper memory access issue by a network API. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0088|2024-06-04T17:58:35.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0073|2024-03-27T21:52:25.390Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0073</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer when the driver is performing an operation at a privilege level that is higher than the minimum level required. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0073|2024-03-27T21:52:25.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0100|2024-05-09T21:51:36.086Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0100</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux contains a vulnerability in the tracing API, where a user can corrupt system files. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0100|2024-05-09T21:51:36.086Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0087|2024-06-04T17:58:57.239Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0087</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux contains a vulnerability where a user can set the logging location to an arbitrary file. If this file exists, logs are appended to the file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0087|2024-06-04T17:58:57.239Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0072|2024-04-05T17:48:13.286Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20cuda%20toolkit</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0072</link>
      <description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump and nvdisasm where an attacker may cause a crash by tricking a user into reading a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a partial denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0072|2024-04-05T17:48:13.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0080|2024-06-04T17:59:06.732Z -- nvidia -- nvtiff%20library</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0080</link>
      <description>NVIDIA nvTIFF Library for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where improper input validation might enable an attacker to use a specially crafted input file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0080|2024-06-04T17:59:06.732Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0096|2024-06-06T13:05:23.260Z -- nvidia -- chatrtx</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0096</link>
      <description>NVIDIA ChatRTX for Windows contains a vulnerability in Chat RTX UI, where a user can cause an improper privilege management issue by sending user inputs to change execution flow. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, escalation of privileges, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0096|2024-06-06T13:05:23.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 22:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0079|2024-03-27T21:52:27.622Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0079</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer, where a user in a guest VM can cause a NULL-pointer dereference in the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0079|2024-03-27T21:52:27.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0075|2024-03-27T21:52:26.716Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0075</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user may cause a NULL-pointer dereference by accessing passed parameters the validity of which has not been checked. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service and limited information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0075|2024-03-27T21:52:26.716Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0074|2024-06-04T17:59:12.509Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0074</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker may access a memory location after the end of the buffer. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0074|2024-06-04T17:59:12.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0097|2024-06-06T13:05:37.589Z -- nvidia -- chatrtx</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0097</link>
      <description>NVIDIA ChatRTX for Windows contains a vulnerability in ChatRTX UI, where a user can cause an improper privilege management issue by exploiting interprocess communication between different processes. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, escalation of privileges, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0097|2024-06-06T13:05:37.589Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 22:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0078|2024-06-04T17:59:16.946Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0078</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer, where a user in a guest can cause a NULL-pointer dereference in the host, which may lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0078|2024-06-04T17:59:16.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0081|2024-06-07T15:31:40.706Z -- nvidia -- nemo</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0081</link>
      <description>NVIDIA NeMo framework for Ubuntu contains a vulnerability in tools/asr_webapp where an attacker may cause an allocation of resources without limits or throttling. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a server-side denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0081|2024-06-07T15:31:40.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 18:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31028|2024-04-05T17:46:49.238Z -- nvidia -- nvjpeg2000%20library</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31028</link>
      <description>NVIDIA nvJPEG2000 Library for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where improper input validation might enable an attacker to use a specially crafted input file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31028|2024-04-05T17:46:49.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0091|2024-06-14T16:21:17.061Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0091</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user can cause an untrusted pointer dereference by executing a driver API. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0091|2024-06-14T16:21:17.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0086|2024-06-14T18:11:21.054Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0086</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability where the software can dereference a NULL pointer. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service and undefined behavior in the vGPU plugin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0086|2024-06-14T18:11:21.054Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0094|2024-06-14T18:11:02.113Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0094</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where an untrusted guest VM can cause improper control of the interaction frequency in the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0094|2024-06-14T18:11:02.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0095|2024-06-14T22:28:33.379Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0095</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux and Windows contains a vulnerability where a user can inject forged logs and executable commands by injecting arbitrary data as a new log entry. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0095|2024-06-14T22:28:33.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0089|2024-06-17T12:53:30.805Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0089</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability where the information from a previous client or another process could be disclosed. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, information disclosure, or data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0089|2024-06-17T12:53:30.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0099|2024-06-17T12:49:44.420Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0099</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where the guest OS could cause buffer overrun in the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0099|2024-06-17T12:49:44.420Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0092|2024-06-17T16:45:23.624Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0092</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where an improper check or improper handling of exception conditions might lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0092|2024-06-17T16:45:23.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0103|2024-06-17T17:00:19.647Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0103</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux contains a vulnerability where a user may cause an incorrect Initialization of resource by network issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0103|2024-06-17T17:00:19.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0071|2024-06-21T17:19:37.192Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0071</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-of-bounds write. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0071|2024-06-21T17:19:37.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0073|2024-06-21T17:25:21.848Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0073</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer when the driver is performing an operation at a privilege level that is higher than the minimum level required. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0073|2024-06-21T17:25:21.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0083|2024-07-12T15:31:06.162Z -- nvidia -- chatrtx</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0083</link>
      <description>NVIDIA ChatRTX for Windows contains a vulnerability in the UI, where an attacker can cause a cross-site scripting error by network by running malicious scripts in users' browsers. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0083|2024-07-12T15:31:06.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 22:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0079|2024-08-01T15:36:12.502Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0079</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer, where a user in a guest VM can cause a NULL-pointer dereference in the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0079|2024-08-01T15:36:12.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
