<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for nvidia -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nvidia/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for nvidia -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 17:21:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0103|2024-06-17T17:00:19.647Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0103</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux contains a vulnerability where a user may cause an incorrect Initialization of resource by network issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0103|2024-06-17T17:00:19.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0092|2024-06-17T16:45:23.624Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0092</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where an improper check or improper handling of exception conditions might lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0092|2024-06-17T16:45:23.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0099|2024-06-17T12:49:44.420Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0099</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where the guest OS could cause buffer overrun in the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0099|2024-06-17T12:49:44.420Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0089|2024-06-17T12:53:30.805Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0089</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability where the information from a previous client or another process could be disclosed. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, information disclosure, or data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0089|2024-06-17T12:53:30.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0095|2024-06-14T22:28:33.379Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0095</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux and Windows contains a vulnerability where a user can inject forged logs and executable commands by injecting arbitrary data as a new log entry. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0095|2024-06-14T22:28:33.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0094|2024-06-14T18:11:02.113Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0094</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where an untrusted guest VM can cause improper control of the interaction frequency in the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0094|2024-06-14T18:11:02.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0086|2024-06-14T18:11:21.054Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0086</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability where the software can dereference a NULL pointer. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service and undefined behavior in the vGPU plugin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0086|2024-06-14T18:11:21.054Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0091|2024-06-14T16:21:17.061Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0091</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user can cause an untrusted pointer dereference by executing a driver API. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0091|2024-06-14T16:21:17.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31035|2024-01-12T18:31:38.411Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20a100</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31035</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 SBIOS contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause an SMI callout vulnerability that could be used to execute arbitrary code at the SMM level. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31035|2024-01-12T18:31:38.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31034|2024-01-12T18:31:41.194Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20a100</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31034</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 SBIOS contains a vulnerability where a local attacker can cause input validation checks to be bypassed by causing an integer overflow. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31034|2024-01-12T18:31:41.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31033|2024-01-12T18:31:39.794Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20a100</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31033</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 BMC contains a vulnerability where a user may cause a missing authentication issue for a critical function by an adjacent network . A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to escalation of privileges, code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31033|2024-01-12T18:31:39.794Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31025|2024-01-12T18:31:42.575Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20a100</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31025</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 BMC contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause an LDAP user injection. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31025|2024-01-12T18:31:42.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31029|2024-01-12T18:31:32.801Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20a100</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31029</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 baseboard management controller (BMC) contains a vulnerability in the host KVM daemon, where an unauthenticated attacker may cause a stack overflow by sending a specially crafted network packet. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31029|2024-01-12T18:31:32.801Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31028|2024-04-05T17:46:49.238Z -- nvidia -- nvjpeg2000%20library</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31028</link>
      <description>NVIDIA nvJPEG2000 Library for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where improper input validation might enable an attacker to use a specially crafted input file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31028|2024-04-05T17:46:49.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31024|2024-01-12T18:31:35.602Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20a100</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31024</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 BMC contains a vulnerability in the host KVM daemon, where an unauthenticated attacker may cause stack memory corruption by sending a specially crafted network packet. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31024|2024-01-12T18:31:35.602Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31032|2024-01-12T18:31:36.994Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20a100</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31032</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 SBIOS contains a vulnerability where a user may cause a dynamic variable evaluation by local access. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31032|2024-01-12T18:31:36.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31031|2024-01-12T18:31:44.171Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20a100</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31031</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 SBIOS contains a vulnerability where a user may cause a heap-based buffer overflow by local access. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31031|2024-01-12T18:31:44.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31030|2024-01-12T18:31:34.210Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20a100</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31030</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 BMC contains a vulnerability in the host KVM daemon, where an unauthenticated attacker may cause a stack overflow by sending a specially crafted network packet. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31030|2024-01-12T18:31:34.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31037|2024-01-24T02:12:30.123Z -- nvidia -- bluefield%202%20dpu%20bmc%2C%20bluefield%203%20dpu%20bmc</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31037</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Bluefield 2 and Bluefield 3 DPU BMC contains a vulnerability in ipmitool, where a root user may cause code injection by a network call. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution on the OS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31037|2024-01-24T02:12:30.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 02:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31036|2024-01-12T17:11:38.579Z -- nvidia -- triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31036</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux and Windows contains a vulnerability where, when it is launched with the non-default command line option --model-control explicit, an attacker may use the model load API to cause a relative path traversal. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31036|2024-01-12T17:11:38.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 17:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0081|2024-06-07T15:31:40.706Z -- nvidia -- nemo</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0081</link>
      <description>NVIDIA NeMo framework for Ubuntu contains a vulnerability in tools/asr_webapp where an attacker may cause an allocation of resources without limits or throttling. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a server-side denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0081|2024-06-07T15:31:40.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 18:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0078|2024-06-04T17:59:16.946Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0078</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer, where a user in a guest can cause a NULL-pointer dereference in the host, which may lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0078|2024-06-04T17:59:16.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0097|2024-06-06T13:05:37.589Z -- nvidia -- chatrtx</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0097</link>
      <description>NVIDIA ChatRTX for Windows contains a vulnerability in ChatRTX UI, where a user can cause an improper privilege management issue by exploiting interprocess communication between different processes. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, escalation of privileges, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0097|2024-06-06T13:05:37.589Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 22:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0074|2024-06-04T17:59:12.509Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0074</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker may access a memory location after the end of the buffer. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0074|2024-06-04T17:59:12.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0075|2024-03-27T21:52:26.716Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0075</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user may cause a NULL-pointer dereference by accessing passed parameters the validity of which has not been checked. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service and limited information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0075|2024-03-27T21:52:26.716Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0079|2024-03-27T21:52:27.622Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0079</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer, where a user in a guest VM can cause a NULL-pointer dereference in the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0079|2024-03-27T21:52:27.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0096|2024-06-06T13:05:23.260Z -- nvidia -- chatrtx</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0096</link>
      <description>NVIDIA ChatRTX for Windows contains a vulnerability in Chat RTX UI, where a user can cause an improper privilege management issue by sending user inputs to change execution flow. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, escalation of privileges, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0096|2024-06-06T13:05:23.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 22:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0080|2024-06-04T17:59:06.732Z -- nvidia -- nvtiff%20library</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0080</link>
      <description>NVIDIA nvTIFF Library for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where improper input validation might enable an attacker to use a specially crafted input file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0080|2024-06-04T17:59:06.732Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0072|2024-04-05T17:48:13.286Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20cuda%20toolkit</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0072</link>
      <description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump and nvdisasm where an attacker may cause a crash by tricking a user into reading a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a partial denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0072|2024-04-05T17:48:13.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0087|2024-06-04T17:58:57.239Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0087</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux contains a vulnerability where a user can set the logging location to an arbitrary file. If this file exists, logs are appended to the file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0087|2024-06-04T17:58:57.239Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0100|2024-05-09T21:51:36.086Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0100</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux contains a vulnerability in the tracing API, where a user can corrupt system files. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0100|2024-05-09T21:51:36.086Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0073|2024-03-27T21:52:25.390Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0073</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer when the driver is performing an operation at a privilege level that is higher than the minimum level required. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0073|2024-03-27T21:52:25.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0088|2024-06-04T17:58:35.426Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0088</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux contains a vulnerability in shared memory APIs, where a user can cause an improper memory access issue by a network API. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0088|2024-06-04T17:58:35.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0071|2024-03-27T21:52:24.951Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0071</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-of-bounds write. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0071|2024-03-27T21:52:24.951Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0083|2024-04-08T22:10:25.070Z -- nvidia -- chatrtx</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0083</link>
      <description>NVIDIA ChatRTX for Windows contains a vulnerability in the UI, where an attacker can cause a cross-site scripting error by network by running malicious scripts in users' browsers. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0083|2024-04-08T22:10:25.070Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 22:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0076|2024-04-05T17:50:06.319Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20cuda%20toolkit</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0076</link>
      <description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in cuobjdump and nvdisasm where an attacker may cause a crash by tricking a user into reading a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a partial denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0076|2024-04-05T17:50:06.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0098|2024-06-06T13:05:55.509Z -- nvidia -- chatrtx</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0098</link>
      <description>NVIDIA ChatRTX for Windows contains a vulnerability in the ChatRTX UI and backend, where a user can cause a clear-text transmission of sensitive information issue by data sniffing. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0098|2024-06-06T13:05:55.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 22:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0077|2024-03-27T21:52:27.188Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20driver%2C%20cloud%20gaming%20driver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0077</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Virtual GPU Manager contains a vulnerability in the vGPU plugin, where it allows a guest OS to allocate resources for which the guest OS is not authorized. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0077|2024-03-27T21:52:27.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0082|2024-06-06T13:05:04.914Z -- nvidia -- chatrtx</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0082</link>
      <description>NVIDIA ChatRTX for Windows contains a vulnerability in the UI, where an attacker can cause improper privilege management by sending open file requests to the application. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to local escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0082|2024-06-06T13:05:04.914Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 22:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0085|2024-06-13T21:23:31.505Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0085</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where unprivileged users could execute privileged operations on the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0085|2024-06-13T21:23:31.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0089|2024-06-13T21:23:29.198Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0089</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability where the information from a previous client or another process could be disclosed. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, information disclosure, or data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0089|2024-06-13T21:23:29.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0092|2024-06-13T21:23:30.327Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0092</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where an improper check or improper handling of exception conditions might lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0092|2024-06-13T21:23:30.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0099|2024-06-13T21:23:30.685Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0099</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where the guest OS could cause buffer overrun in the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0099|2024-06-13T21:23:30.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0093|2024-06-13T21:23:29.967Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0093</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability where it can expose sensitive information to an actor that is not explicitly authorized to have access to that information. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0093|2024-06-13T21:23:29.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0090|2024-06-13T21:23:28.800Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0090</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user can cause an out-of-bounds write. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0090|2024-06-13T21:23:28.800Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0084|2024-06-13T21:23:31.105Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0084</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where the guest OS could execute privileged operations. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0084|2024-06-13T21:23:31.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0091|2024-06-13T21:23:29.556Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0091</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user can cause an untrusted pointer dereference by executing a driver API. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0091|2024-06-13T21:23:29.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0095|2024-06-13T21:16:51.975Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0095</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux and Windows contains a vulnerability where a user can inject forged logs and executable commands by injecting arbitrary data as a new log entry. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0095|2024-06-13T21:16:51.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0086|2024-06-13T21:23:32.289Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0086</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability where the software can dereference a NULL pointer. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service and undefined behavior in the vGPU plugin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0086|2024-06-13T21:23:32.289Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0103|2024-06-13T21:16:51.611Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20triton%20inference%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0103</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux contains a vulnerability where a user may cause an incorrect Initialization of resource by network issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0103|2024-06-13T21:16:51.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0094|2024-06-13T21:23:31.858Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0094</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where an untrusted guest VM can cause improper control of the interaction frequency in the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0094|2024-06-13T21:23:31.858Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0084|2024-06-14T17:19:48.609Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0084</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where the guest OS could execute privileged operations. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0084|2024-06-14T17:19:48.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0090|2024-06-14T19:08:11.016Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0090</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user can cause an out-of-bounds write. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0090|2024-06-14T19:08:11.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0089|2024-06-15T03:55:34.774Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0089</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability where the information from a previous client or another process could be disclosed. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, information disclosure, or data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0089|2024-06-15T03:55:34.774Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0099|2024-06-15T03:55:36.784Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0099</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where the guest OS could cause buffer overrun in the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0099|2024-06-15T03:55:36.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0090|2024-06-15T03:55:33.792Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0090</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user can cause an out-of-bounds write. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0090|2024-06-15T03:55:33.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0084|2024-06-15T03:55:37.767Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0084</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where the guest OS could execute privileged operations. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0084|2024-06-15T03:55:37.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0091|2024-06-15T03:55:35.767Z -- nvidia -- gpu%20display%20driver%2C%20vgpu%20software%2C%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0091</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a user can cause an untrusted pointer dereference by executing a driver API. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0091|2024-06-15T03:55:35.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0099|2024-06-17T13:17:13.597Z -- nvidia -- vgpu%20software%20and%20cloud%20gaming</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0099</link>
      <description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where the guest OS could cause buffer overrun in the host. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, escalation of privileges, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0099|2024-06-17T13:17:13.597Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
