<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for NVIDIA -- DGX H100 BMC</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nvidia/dgx%20h100%20bmc.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for NVIDIA -- DGX H100 BMC</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:21:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31011|2024-08-02T14:45:24.958Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20h100%20bmc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31011</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX H100 BMC contains a vulnerability in the REST service where an attacker may cause improper input validation. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to escalation of privileges and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31011|2024-08-02T14:45:24.958Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 01:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31013|2024-08-02T14:45:24.935Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20h100%20bmc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31013</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX H100 BMC contains a vulnerability in the REST service, where an attacker may cause improper input validation. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to escalation of privileges and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31013|2024-08-02T14:45:24.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 01:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31009|2024-08-02T14:45:24.690Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20h100%20bmc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31009</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX H100 BMC contains a vulnerability in the REST service, where an attacker may cause improper input validation. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31009|2024-08-02T14:45:24.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31015|2024-08-02T14:45:24.882Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20h100%20bmc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31015</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX H100 BMC contains a vulnerability in the REST service where a host user may cause as improper authentication issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to escalation of privileges, information disclosure, code execution, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31015|2024-08-02T14:45:24.882Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 01:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25533|2024-08-02T11:25:19.161Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20h100%20bmc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25533</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX H100 BMC contains a vulnerability in the web UI, where an attacker may cause improper input validation. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to information disclosure, code execution, and escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25533|2024-08-02T11:25:19.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:54:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31008|2024-08-02T14:45:24.707Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20h100%20bmc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31008</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX H100 BMC contains a vulnerability in IPMI, where an attacker may cause improper input validation. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of services, escalation of privileges, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31008|2024-08-02T14:45:24.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25534|2024-08-02T11:25:19.309Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20h100%20bmc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25534</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX H100 BMC contains a vulnerability in IPMI, where an attacker may cause improper input validation. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25534|2024-08-02T11:25:19.309Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25530|2024-08-02T11:25:18.584Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20h100%20bmc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25530</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX H100 BMC contains a vulnerability in the KVM service, where an attacker may cause improper input validation. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25530|2024-08-02T11:25:18.584Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25527|2024-08-02T11:25:18.676Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20h100%20bmc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25527</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX H100 BMC contains a vulnerability in the host KVM daemon, where an authenticated local attacker may cause corruption of kernel memory. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary kernel code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25527|2024-08-02T11:25:18.676Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25531|2024-08-02T11:25:19.070Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20h100%20bmc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25531</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX H100 BMC contains a vulnerability in IPMI, where an attacker may cause insufficient protection of credentials. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25531|2024-08-02T11:25:19.070Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25528|2024-08-02T11:25:19.168Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20h100%20bmc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25528</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX H100 baseboard management controller (BMC) contains a vulnerability in a web server plugin, where an unauthenticated attacker may cause a stack overflow by sending a specially crafted network packet. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25528|2024-08-02T11:25:19.168Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31010|2024-08-02T14:45:24.943Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20h100%20bmc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31010</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX H100 BMC contains a vulnerability in IPMI, where an attacker may cause improper input validation. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31010|2024-08-02T14:45:24.943Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 01:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31012|2024-08-02T14:45:24.689Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20h100%20bmc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31012</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX H100 BMC contains a vulnerability in the REST service where an attacker may cause improper input validation. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to escalation of privileges and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31012|2024-08-02T14:45:24.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 01:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25532|2024-08-02T11:25:19.205Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20h100%20bmc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25532</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX H100 BMC contains a vulnerability in IPMI, where an attacker may cause insufficient protection of credentials. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25532|2024-08-02T11:25:19.205Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25529|2024-08-02T11:25:19.194Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20h100%20bmc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25529</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX H100 BMC and DGX A100 BMC contains a vulnerability in the host KVM daemon, where an unauthenticated attacker may cause a leak of another user’s session token by observing timing discrepancies between server responses. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to information disclosure, escalation of privileges, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25529|2024-08-02T11:25:19.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
