<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for nvidia -- DGX A100</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nvidia/dgx%20a100.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for nvidia -- DGX A100</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 16:24:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31035|2024-08-02T14:45:25.188Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20a100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31035</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 SBIOS contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause an SMI callout vulnerability that could be used to execute arbitrary code at the SMM level. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31035|2024-08-02T14:45:25.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31032|2024-08-02T14:45:24.989Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20a100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31032</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 SBIOS contains a vulnerability where a user may cause a dynamic variable evaluation by local access. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31032|2024-08-02T14:45:24.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31031|2024-08-02T14:45:25.286Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20a100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31031</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 SBIOS contains a vulnerability where a user may cause a heap-based buffer overflow by local access. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31031|2024-08-02T14:45:25.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31029|2024-08-02T14:45:25.582Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20a100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31029</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 baseboard management controller (BMC) contains a vulnerability in the host KVM daemon, where an unauthenticated attacker may cause a stack overflow by sending a specially crafted network packet. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31029|2024-08-02T14:45:25.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31030|2024-08-02T14:45:24.992Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20a100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31030</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 BMC contains a vulnerability in the host KVM daemon, where an unauthenticated attacker may cause a stack overflow by sending a specially crafted network packet. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31030|2024-08-02T14:45:24.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31033|2024-08-02T14:45:25.629Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20a100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31033</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 BMC contains a vulnerability where a user may cause a missing authentication issue for a critical function by an adjacent network . A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to escalation of privileges, code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31033|2024-08-02T14:45:25.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31024|2024-08-02T14:45:25.099Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20a100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31024</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 BMC contains a vulnerability in the host KVM daemon, where an unauthenticated attacker may cause stack memory corruption by sending a specially crafted network packet. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31024|2024-08-02T14:45:25.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31034|2024-08-02T14:45:25.280Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20a100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31034</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 SBIOS contains a vulnerability where a local attacker can cause input validation checks to be bypassed by causing an integer overflow. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31034|2024-08-02T14:45:25.280Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31025|2024-08-02T14:45:24.977Z -- nvidia -- dgx%20a100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31025</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 BMC contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause an LDAP user injection. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31025|2024-08-02T14:45:24.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
