<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for NVIDIA -- Jetson AGX Xavier series, Jetson Xavier NX</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nvidia/jetson%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20jetson%20xavier%20nx.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for NVIDIA -- Jetson AGX Xavier series, Jetson Xavier NX</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 18:24:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28194|2024-08-03T05:48:37.482Z -- nvidia -- jetson%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20jetson%20xavier%20nx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28194</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Jetson Linux Driver Package contains a vulnerability in the Cboot module tegrabl_cbo.c, where, if TFTP is enabled, a local attacker with elevated privileges can cause a memory buffer overflow, which may lead to code execution, loss of Integrity, limited denial of service, and some impact to confidentiality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28194|2024-08-03T05:48:37.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 17:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28197|2024-08-03T05:48:37.465Z -- nvidia -- jetson%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20jetson%20xavier%20nx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28197</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Jetson Linux Driver Package contains a vulnerability in the Cboot ext4_mount function, where Insufficient validation of untrusted data may allow a highly privileged local attacker to cause an integer overflow. This difficult-to-exploit vulnerability may lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, limited denial of service, and some impact to confidentiality and integrity. The scope of impact can extend to other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28197|2024-08-03T05:48:37.465Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 17:57:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28195|2024-08-03T05:48:37.504Z -- nvidia -- jetson%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20jetson%20xavier%20nx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28195</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Jetson Linux Driver Package contains a vulnerability in the Cboot ext4_read_file function, where insufficient validation of untrusted data may allow a highly privileged local attacker to cause a integer overflow, which may lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, limited denial of service, and some impact to confidentiality and integrity. The scope of impact can extend to other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28195|2024-08-03T05:48:37.504Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 17:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28193|2024-08-03T05:48:37.466Z -- nvidia -- jetson%20agx%20xavier%20series%2C%20jetson%20xavier%20nx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28193</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Jetson Linux Driver Package contains a vulnerability in the Cboot module tegrabl_cbo.c, where insufficient validation of untrusted data may allow a local attacker with elevated privileges to cause a memory buffer overflow, which may lead to code execution, loss of integrity, limited denial of service, and some impact to confidentiality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28193|2024-08-03T05:48:37.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 17:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
