<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for NVIDIA -- NVIDIA DGX servers</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nvidia/nvidia%20dgx%20servers.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for NVIDIA -- NVIDIA DGX servers</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:22:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25506|2024-08-02T11:25:18.390Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25506</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX-1 contains a vulnerability in Ofbd in AMI SBIOS, where a preconditioned heap can allow a user with elevated privileges to cause an access beyond the end of a buffer, which may lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, denial of service and information disclosure. The scope of the impact of this vulnerability can extend to other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25506|2024-08-02T11:25:18.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25509|2024-08-02T11:25:19.198Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25509</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX-1 SBIOS contains a vulnerability in Bds, which may lead to code execution, denial of service, and escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25509|2024-08-02T11:25:19.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25505|2024-08-02T11:25:18.402Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25505</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX-1 BMC contains a vulnerability in the IPMI handler of the AMI MegaRAC BMC , where an attacker with the appropriate level of authorization can cause a buffer overflow, which may lead to denial of service, information disclosure, or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25505|2024-08-02T11:25:18.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25507|2024-08-02T11:25:19.060Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25507</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX-1 BMC contains a vulnerability in the SPX REST API, where an attacker with the appropriate level of authorization can inject arbitrary shell commands, which may lead to code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25507|2024-08-02T11:25:19.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25508|2024-08-02T11:25:18.322Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25508</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX-1 BMC contains a vulnerability in the IPMI handler, where an attacker with the appropriate level of authorization can upload and download arbitrary files under certain circumstances, which may lead to denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25508|2024-08-02T11:25:18.322Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0202|2024-08-02T05:02:43.691Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0202</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 SBIOS contains a vulnerability where an attacker may modify arbitrary memory of SMRAM by exploiting the GenericSio and LegacySmmSredir SMM APIs. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service, escalation of privileges, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0202|2024-08-02T05:02:43.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0209|2024-08-02T05:02:44.073Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0209</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX-1 SBIOS contains a vulnerability in the Uncore PEI module, where authentication of the code executed by SSA is missing, which may lead to arbitrary code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges assisted by a firmware implant, information disclosure assisted by a firmware implant, data tampering, and SecureBoot bypass.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0209|2024-08-02T05:02:44.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0207|2024-08-02T05:02:44.102Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0207</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX-2 SBIOS contains a vulnerability where an attacker may modify the ServerSetup NVRAM variable at runtime by executing privileged code. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0207|2024-08-02T05:02:44.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0200|2024-08-02T05:02:43.803Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0200</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX-2 contains a vulnerability in OFBD where a user with high privileges and a pre-conditioned heap can cause an access beyond a buffers end, which may lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, denial of service, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0200|2024-08-02T05:02:43.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0206|2024-08-02T05:02:43.963Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0206</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 SBIOS contains a vulnerability where an attacker may modify arbitrary memory of SMRAM by exploiting the NVME SMM API. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service, escalation of privileges, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0206|2024-08-02T05:02:43.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0201|2024-08-02T05:02:43.844Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0201</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX-2 SBIOS contains a vulnerability in Bds, where a user with high privileges can cause a write beyond the bounds of an indexable resource, which may lead to code execution, denial of service, compromised integrity, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0201|2024-08-02T05:02:43.844Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
