<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for NVIDIA -- NVIDIA GPU and Tegra hardware</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nvidia/nvidia%20gpu%20and%20tegra%20hardware.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for NVIDIA -- NVIDIA GPU and Tegra hardware</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1088|2024-08-03T15:55:18.682Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20and%20tegra%20hardware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1088</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU and Tegra hardware contain a vulnerability in the internal microcontroller which may allow a user with elevated privileges to utilize debug mechanisms with insufficient access control, which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1088|2024-08-03T15:55:18.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 14:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1125|2024-08-03T15:55:18.660Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20and%20tegra%20hardware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1125</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU and Tegra hardware contain a vulnerability in the internal microcontroller which may allow a user with elevated privileges to corrupt program data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1125|2024-08-03T15:55:18.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 14:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23201|2024-08-03T19:05:55.376Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20and%20tegra%20hardware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23201</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU and Tegra hardware contain a vulnerability in an internal microcontroller, which may allow a user with elevated privileges to generate valid microcode by identifying, exploiting, and loading vulnerable microcode. Such an attack could lead to information disclosure, data corruption, or denial of service of the device. The scope may extend to other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23201|2024-08-03T19:05:55.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 14:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23219|2024-08-03T19:05:55.355Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20and%20tegra%20hardware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23219</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU and Tegra hardware contain a vulnerability in the internal microcontroller, which may allow a user with elevated privileges to access protected information by identifying, exploiting, and loading vulnerable microcode. Such an attack may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23219|2024-08-03T19:05:55.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 14:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1105|2024-08-03T15:55:18.491Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20and%20tegra%20hardware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1105</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU and Tegra hardware contain a vulnerability in the internal microcontroller which may allow a user with elevated privileges to access debug registers during runtime, which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1105|2024-08-03T15:55:18.491Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 14:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23217|2024-08-03T19:05:55.701Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20gpu%20and%20tegra%20hardware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23217</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU and Tegra hardware contain a vulnerability in the internal microcontroller, which may allow a user with elevated privileges to instantiate a DMA write operation only within a specific time window timed to corrupt code execution, which may impact confidentiality, integrity, or availability. The scope impact may extend to other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23217|2024-08-03T19:05:55.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 14:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
