<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for NVIDIA -- NVIDIA GeForce Experience Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nvidia/nvidia%20geforce%20experience%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for NVIDIA -- NVIDIA GeForce Experience Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1073|2024-08-03T15:55:18.629Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20geforce%20experience%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1073</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience, all versions prior to 3.23, contains a vulnerability in the login flow when a user tries to log in by using a browser, while, at the same time, any other web page is loaded in other tabs of the same browser. In this situation, the web page can get access to the token of the user login session, leading to the possibility that the user’s account is compromised. This may lead to the targeted user’s data being accessed, altered, or lost.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1073|2024-08-03T15:55:18.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 19:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23175|2024-08-03T19:05:55.554Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20geforce%20experience%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23175</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience contains a vulnerability in user authorization, where GameStream does not correctly apply individual user access controls for users on the same device, which, with user intervention, may lead to escalation of privileges, information disclosure, data tampering, and denial of service, affecting other resources beyond the intended security authority of GameStream.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23175|2024-08-03T19:05:55.554Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 16:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1072|2024-08-03T15:55:18.507Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20geforce%20experience%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1072</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience, all versions prior to 3.21, contains a vulnerability in GameStream (rxdiag.dll) where an arbitrary file deletion due to improper handling of log files may lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1072|2024-08-03T15:55:18.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 19:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-1079|2024-08-03T15:55:18.623Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20geforce%20experience%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-1079</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience, all versions prior to 3.22, contains a vulnerability in GameStream plugins where log files are created using NT/System level permissions, which may lead to code execution, denial of service, or local privilege escalation. The attacker does not have control over the consequence of a modification nor would they be able to leak information as a direct result of the overwrite.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-1079|2024-08-03T15:55:18.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 14:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
