<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for NVIDIA -- NVIDIA DGX servers</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nvidia/nvidia%20dgx%20servers.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for NVIDIA -- NVIDIA DGX servers</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 17:21:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11487|2024-08-04T11:35:11.981Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11487</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX servers, DGX-1 with BMC firmware versions prior to 3.38.30. DGX-2 with BMC firmware versions prior to 1.06.06 and all DGX A100 Servers with all BMC firmware versions, contains a vulnerability in the AMI BMC firmware in which the use of a hard-coded RSA 1024 key with weak ciphers may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11487|2024-08-04T11:35:11.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 03:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11484|2024-08-04T11:28:13.894Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11484</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX servers, all DGX-1 with BMC firmware versions prior to 3.38.30, contains a vulnerability in the AMI BMC firmware in which an attacker with administrative privileges can obtain the hash of the BMC/IPMI user password, which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11484|2024-08-04T11:28:13.894Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 03:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11488|2024-08-04T11:35:12.447Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11488</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX servers, all DGX-1 with BMC firmware versions prior to 3.38.30 and all DGX-2 with BMC firmware versions prior to 1.06.06, contains a vulnerability in the AMI BMC firmware in which software does not validate the RSA 1024 public key used to verify the firmware signature, which may lead to information disclosure or code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11488|2024-08-04T11:35:12.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 03:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11489|2024-08-04T11:35:12.442Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11489</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX servers, all DGX-1 with BMC firmware versions prior to 3.38.30 and all DGX-2 with BMC firmware versions prior to 1.06.06, contain a vulnerability in the AMI BMC firmware in which default SNMP community strings are used, which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11489|2024-08-04T11:35:12.442Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 03:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11485|2024-08-04T11:35:12.421Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11485</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX servers, all DGX-1 with BMC firmware versions prior to 3.38.30, contains a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the AMI BMC firmware in which the web application does not sufficiently verify whether a well-formed, valid, consistent request was intentionally provided by the user who submitted the request, which can lead to information disclosure or code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11485|2024-08-04T11:35:12.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 03:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11483|2024-08-04T11:28:14.182Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11483</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX servers, all DGX-1 with BMC firmware versions prior to 3.38.30 and all DGX-2 with BMC firmware versions prior to 1.06.06, contains a vulnerability in the AMI BMC firmware in which the firmware includes hard-coded credentials, which may lead to elevation of privileges or information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11483|2024-08-04T11:28:14.182Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 03:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11486|2024-08-04T11:35:12.026Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11486</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX servers, all DGX-1 with BMC firmware versions prior to 3.38.30, contain a vulnerability in the AMI BMC firmware in which software allows an attacker to upload or transfer files that can be automatically processed within the product's environment, which may lead to remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11486|2024-08-04T11:35:12.026Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 03:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11615|2024-08-04T11:35:13.342Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11615</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX servers, all BMC firmware versions prior to 3.38.30, contain a vulnerability in the AMI BMC firmware in which it uses a hard-coded RC4 cipher key, which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11615|2024-08-04T11:35:13.342Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 03:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11616|2024-08-04T11:35:13.619Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11616</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX servers, all BMC firmware versions prior to 3.38.30, contain a vulnerability in the AMI BMC firmware in which the Pseudo-Random Number Generator (PRNG) algorithm used in the JSOL package that implements the IPMI protocol is not cryptographically strong, which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11616|2024-08-04T11:35:13.619Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 03:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
