<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for NVIDIA -- NVIDIA GeForce Experience</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nvidia/nvidia%20geforce%20experience.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for NVIDIA -- NVIDIA GeForce Experience</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5701|2024-08-04T20:01:52.147Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20geforce%20experience
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5701</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience, all versions prior to 3.20.0.118, contains a vulnerability when GameStream is enabled in which an attacker with local system access can load the Intel graphics driver DLLs without validating the path or signature (also known as a binary planting or DLL preloading attack), which may lead to denial of service, information disclosure, or escalation of privileges through code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5701|2024-08-04T20:01:52.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 01:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5689|2024-08-04T20:01:52.247Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20geforce%20experience
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5689</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience, all versions prior to 3.20.1, contains a vulnerability in the Downloader component in which a user with local system access can craft input that may allow malicious files to be downloaded and saved. This behavior may lead to code execution, denial of service, or information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5689|2024-08-04T20:01:52.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 01:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5695|2024-08-04T20:01:52.051Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20geforce%20experience
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5695</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience (prior to 3.20.1) and Windows GPU Display Driver (all versions) contains a vulnerability in the local service provider component in which an attacker with local system and privileged access can incorrectly load Windows system DLLs without validating the path or signature (also known as a binary planting or DLL preloading attack), which may lead to denial of service or information disclosure through code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5695|2024-08-04T20:01:52.051Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 20:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5678|2024-08-04T20:01:52.047Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20geforce%20experience
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5678</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience versions prior to 3.19 contains a vulnerability in the Web Helper component, in which an attacker with local system access can craft input that may not be properly validated. Such an attack may lead to code execution, denial of service or information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5678|2024-08-04T20:01:52.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 21:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
