<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for NVIDIA -- NVIDIA DGX A100</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nvidia/nvidia%20dgx%20a100.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for NVIDIA -- NVIDIA DGX A100</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:23:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31601|2024-08-03T07:26:00.904Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20a100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31601</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 contains a vulnerability in SBIOS in the SmbiosPei, which may allow a highly privileged local attacker to cause an out-of-bounds write, which may lead to code execution, denial of service, compromised integrity, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31601|2024-08-03T07:26:00.904Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 18:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31602|2024-08-03T07:25:59.511Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20a100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31602</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 contains a vulnerability in SBIOS in the IpSecDxe, where a user with elevated privileges and a preconditioned heap can exploit an out-of-bounds write vulnerability, which may lead to code execution, denial of service, data integrity impact, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31602|2024-08-03T07:25:59.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 18:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31600|2024-08-03T07:26:01.049Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20a100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31600</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 contains a vulnerability in SBIOS in the SmmCore, where a user with high privileges can chain another vulnerability to this vulnerability, causing an integer overflow, possibly leading to code execution, escalation of privileges, denial of service, compromised integrity, and information disclosure. The scope of impact can extend to other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31600|2024-08-03T07:26:01.049Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 18:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31599|2024-08-03T07:26:00.938Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20a100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31599</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 contains a vulnerability in SBIOS in the Ofbd, where a local user with elevated privileges can cause access to an uninitialized pointer, which may lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, denial of service, and information disclosure. The scope of impact can extend to other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31599|2024-08-03T07:26:00.938Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 18:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31603|2024-08-03T07:26:00.938Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20a100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31603</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 contains a vulnerability in SBIOS in the IpSecDxe, where a user with high privileges and preconditioned IpSecDxe global data can exploit improper validation of an array index to cause code execution, which may lead to denial of service, data integrity impact, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31603|2024-08-03T07:26:00.938Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 18:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28200|2024-08-03T05:48:37.214Z -- nvidia -- nvidia%20dgx%20a100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28200</link>
      <description>NVIDIA DGX A100 contains a vulnerability in SBIOS in the BiosCfgTool, where a local user with elevated privileges can read and write beyond intended bounds in SMRAM, which may lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, denial of service, and information disclosure. The scope of impact can extend to other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28200|2024-08-03T05:48:37.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 00:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
