<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for what3words -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/what3words/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for what3words -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:19:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4428|2024-08-03T17:23:10.776Z -- what3words -- autosuggest%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4428</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in what3words Autosuggest Plugin up to 4.0.0 on WordPress and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function enqueue_scripts of the file w3w-autosuggest/public/class-w3w-autosuggest-public.php of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 4.0.1 is able to address this issue. The patch is named dd59cbac5f86057d6a73b87007c08b8bfa0c32ac. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-234247.
In what3words Autosuggest Plugin bis 4.0.0 für WordPress wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist die Funktion enqueue_scripts der Datei w3w-autosuggest/public/class-w3w-autosuggest-public.php der Komponente Setting Handler. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 4.0.1 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als dd59cbac5f86057d6a73b87007c08b8bfa0c32ac bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4428|2024-08-03T17:23:10.776Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
