<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Iceni -- Argus</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/iceni/argus.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Iceni -- Argus</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 03:23:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8387|2024-08-06T02:20:31.165Z -- iceni -- argus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8387</link>
      <description>An exploitable heap-based buffer overflow exists in Iceni Argus. When it attempts to convert a malformed PDF with an object encoded w/ multiple encoding types terminating with an LZW encoded type, an overflow may occur due to a lack of bounds checking by the LZW decoder. This can lead to code execution under the context of the account of the user running it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8387|2024-08-06T02:20:31.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8385|2024-08-06T02:20:31.184Z -- iceni -- argus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8385</link>
      <description>An exploitable uninitialized variable vulnerability which leads to a stack-based buffer overflow exists in Iceni Argus. When it attempts to convert a malformed PDF to XML a stack variable will be left uninitialized which will later be used to fetch a length that is used in a copy operation. In most cases this will allow an aggressor to write outside the bounds of a stack buffer which is used to contain colors. This can lead to code execution under the context of the account running the tool.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8385|2024-08-06T02:20:31.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8389|2024-08-06T02:20:31.264Z -- iceni -- argus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8389</link>
      <description>An exploitable integer-overflow vulnerability exists within Iceni Argus. When it attempts to convert a malformed PDF to XML, it will attempt to convert each character from a font into a polygon and then attempt to rasterize these shapes. As the application attempts to iterate through the rows and initializing the polygon shape in the buffer, it will write outside of the bounds of said buffer. This can lead to code execution under the context of the account running it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8389|2024-08-06T02:20:31.264Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8386|2024-08-06T02:20:31.075Z -- iceni -- argus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8386</link>
      <description>An exploitable heap-based buffer overflow exists in Iceni Argus. When it attempts to convert a PDF containing a malformed font to XML, the tool will attempt to use a size out of the font to search through a linked list of buffers to return. Due to a signedness issue, a buffer smaller than the requested size will be returned. Later when the tool tries to populate this buffer, the overflow will occur which can lead to code execution under the context of the user running the tool.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8386|2024-08-06T02:20:31.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8388|2024-08-06T02:20:31.172Z -- iceni -- argus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8388</link>
      <description>An exploitable arbitrary heap-overwrite vulnerability exists within Iceni Argus. When it attempts to convert a malformed PDF to XML, it will explicitly trust an index within the specific font object and use it to write the font's name to a single object within an array of objects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8388|2024-08-06T02:20:31.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8715|2024-08-06T02:27:41.248Z -- iceni -- argus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8715</link>
      <description>An exploitable heap corruption vulnerability exists in the loadTrailer functionality of Iceni Argus version 6.6.05. A specially crafted PDF file can cause a heap corruption resulting in arbitrary code execution. An attacker can send/provide a malicious PDF file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8715|2024-08-06T02:27:41.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
