<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Six Apart Ltd. -- Movable Type</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/six%20apart%20ltd./movable%20type.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Six Apart Ltd. -- Movable Type</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 16:24:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-45122|2024-08-03T14:01:31.541Z -- six%20apart%20ltd. -- movable%20type
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45122</link>
      <description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability in Movable Type Movable Type 7 r.5301 and earlier (Movable Type 7 Series), Movable Type Advanced 7 r.5301 and earlier (Movable Type Advanced 7 Series), Movable Type 6.8.7 and earlier (Movable Type 6 Series), Movable Type Advanced 6.8.7 and earlier (Movable Type Advanced 6 Series), Movable Type Premium 1.53 and earlier, and Movable Type Premium Advanced 1.53 and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to inject an arbitrary script.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-45122|2024-08-03T14:01:31.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43660|2024-08-03T13:40:06.233Z -- six%20apart%20ltd. -- movable%20type
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43660</link>
      <description>Improper neutralization of Server-Side Includes (SSW) within a web page in Movable Type series allows a remote authenticated attacker with Privilege of 'Manage of Content Types' may execute an arbitrary Perl script and/or an arbitrary OS command. Affected products/versions are as follows: Movable Type 7 r.5301 and earlier (Movable Type 7 Series), Movable Type Advanced 7 r.5301 and earlier (Movable Type Advanced 7 Series), Movable Type Premium 1.53 and earlier, and Movable Type Premium Advanced 1.53 and earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43660|2024-08-03T13:40:06.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-45113|2024-08-03T14:01:31.530Z -- six%20apart%20ltd. -- movable%20type
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45113</link>
      <description>Improper validation of syntactic correctness of input vulnerability exist in Movable Type series. Having a user to access a specially crafted URL may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to set a specially crafted URL to the Reset Password page and conduct a phishing attack. Affected products/versions are as follows: Movable Type 7 r.5301 and earlier (Movable Type 7 Series), Movable Type Advanced 7 r.5301 and earlier (Movable Type Advanced 7 Series), Movable Type 6.8.7 and earlier (Movable Type 6 Series), Movable Type Advanced 6.8.7 and earlier (Movable Type Advanced 6 Series), Movable Type Premium 1.53 and earlier, and Movable Type Premium Advanced 1.53 and earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-45113|2024-08-03T14:01:31.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
