<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Canon -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/canon/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Canon -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-20877|2024-08-03T17:53:23.123Z -- canon -- canon%20laser%20printers%20and%20small%20office%20multifunctional%20printers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-20877</link>
      <description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability in Canon laser printers and small office multifunctional printers (LBP162L/LBP162, MF4890dw, MF269dw/MF265dw/MF264dw/MF262dw, MF249dw/MF245dw/MF244dw/MF242dw/MF232w, and MF229dw/MF224dw/MF222dw sold in Japan, imageCLASS MF Series (MF113W/MF212W/MF217W/MF227DW/MF229DW, MF232W/MF244DW/MF247DW/MF249DW, MF264DW/MF267DW/MF269DW/MF269DW VP, and MF4570DN/MF4570DW/MF4770N/MF4880DW/MF4890DW) and imageCLASS LBP Series (LBP113W/LBP151DW/LBP162DW ) sold in the US, and iSENSYS (LBP162DW, LBP113W, LBP151DW, MF269dw, MF267dw, MF264dw, MF113w, MF249dw, MF247dw, MF244dw, MF237w, MF232w, MF229dw, MF217w, MF212w, MF4780w, and MF4890dw) and imageRUNNER (2206IF, 2204N, and 2204F) sold in Europe) allows remote attackers to inject an arbitrary script via unspecified vectors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-20877|2024-08-03T17:53:23.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 10:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24672|2024-08-03T04:20:49.127Z -- canon -- imageclass%20mf644cdw
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24672</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Canon imageCLASS MF644Cdw 10.02 printers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the CADM service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-15802.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24672|2024-08-03T04:20:49.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24673|2024-08-03T04:20:49.148Z -- canon -- imageclass%20mf644cdw
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24673</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Canon imageCLASS MF644Cdw 10.02 printers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the SLP protocol. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-15845.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24673|2024-08-03T04:20:49.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24674|2024-08-03T04:20:49.145Z -- canon -- imageclass%20mf644cdw
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24674</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Canon imageCLASS MF644Cdw 10.02 printers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the privet API. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-15834.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24674|2024-08-03T04:20:49.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43608|2024-08-03T13:32:59.829Z -- canon -- imageclass%20mf644cdw
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43608</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Canon imageCLASS MF644Cdw 10.03 printers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the BJNP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an integer overflow before allocating a buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-16032.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43608|2024-08-03T13:32:59.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
