<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for [UNKNOWN] -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/%5Bunknown%5D/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for [UNKNOWN] -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 08:24:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14883|2024-08-05T00:26:39.123Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14883</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Moodle 3.6 before 3.6.7 and 3.7 before 3.7.3, where tokens used to fetch inline atachments in email notifications were not disabled when a user's account was no longer active. Note: to access files, a user would need to know the file path, and their token.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14883|2024-08-05T00:26:39.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 12:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1125|2024-08-05T03:51:48.542Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- procps-ng%2C%20procps
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1125</link>
      <description>procps-ng before version 3.3.15 is vulnerable to a stack buffer overflow in pgrep. This vulnerability is mitigated by FORTIFY, as it involves strncat() to a stack-allocated string. When pgrep is compiled with FORTIFY (as on Red Hat Enterprise Linux and Fedora), the impact is limited to a crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1125|2024-08-05T03:51:48.542Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1073|2024-08-05T03:51:47.320Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ovirt-engine
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1073</link>
      <description>The web console login form in ovirt-engine before version 4.2.3 returned different errors for non-existent users and invalid passwords, allowing an attacker to discover the names of valid user accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1073|2024-08-05T03:51:47.320Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10898|2024-08-05T07:54:34.730Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- openstack-tripleo-heat-templates
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10898</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in openstack-tripleo-heat-templates before version 8.0.2-40. When deployed using Director using default configuration, Opendaylight in RHOSP13 is configured with easily guessable default credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10898|2024-08-05T07:54:34.730Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10859|2024-08-05T07:46:47.345Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- git-annex
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10859</link>
      <description>git-annex is vulnerable to an Information Exposure when decrypting files. A malicious server for a special remote could trick git-annex into decrypting a file that was encrypted to the user's gpg key. This attack could be used to expose encrypted data that was never stored in git-annex</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10859|2024-08-05T07:46:47.345Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14853|2024-08-05T00:26:39.175Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- python-ecdsa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14853</link>
      <description>An error-handling flaw was found in python-ecdsa before version 0.13.3. During signature decoding, malformed DER signatures could raise unexpected exceptions (or no exceptions at all), which could lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14853|2024-08-05T00:26:39.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 12:06:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1060|2024-08-05T03:44:12.002Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- python
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1060</link>
      <description>python before versions 2.7.15, 3.4.9, 3.5.6rc1, 3.6.5rc1 and 3.7.0 is vulnerable to catastrophic backtracking in pop3lib's apop() method. An attacker could use this flaw to cause denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1060|2024-08-05T03:44:12.002Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10901|2024-08-05T07:54:35.810Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10901</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Linux kernel's KVM virtualization subsystem. The VMX code does not restore the GDT.LIMIT to the previous host value, but instead sets it to 64KB. With a corrupted GDT limit a host's userspace code has an ability to place malicious entries in the GDT, particularly to the per-cpu variables. An attacker can use this to escalate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10901|2024-08-05T07:54:35.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10860|2024-08-05T07:46:47.302Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- perl-archive-zip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10860</link>
      <description>perl-archive-zip is vulnerable to a directory traversal in Archive::Zip. It was found that the Archive::Zip module did not properly sanitize paths while extracting zip files. An attacker able to provide a specially crafted archive for processing could use this flaw to write or overwrite arbitrary files in the context of the perl interpreter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10860|2024-08-05T07:46:47.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10880|2024-08-05T07:54:34.830Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10880</link>
      <description>Linux kernel is vulnerable to a stack-out-of-bounds write in the ext4 filesystem code when mounting and writing to a crafted ext4 image in ext4_update_inline_data(). An attacker could use this to cause a system crash and a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10880|2024-08-05T07:54:34.830Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1124|2024-08-05T03:51:48.632Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- procps-ng
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1124</link>
      <description>procps-ng before version 3.3.15 is vulnerable to multiple integer overflows leading to a heap corruption in file2strvec function. This allows a privilege escalation for a local attacker who can create entries in procfs by starting processes, which could result in crashes or arbitrary code execution in proc utilities run by other users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1124|2024-08-05T03:51:48.632Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1090|2024-08-05T03:51:49.104Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- pulp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1090</link>
      <description>In Pulp before version 2.16.2, secrets are passed into override_config when triggering a task and then become readable to all users with read access on the distributor/importer. An attacker with API access can then view these secrets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1090|2024-08-05T03:51:49.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10876|2024-08-05T07:46:47.413Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10876</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Linux kernel in the ext4 filesystem code. A use-after-free is possible in ext4_ext_remove_space() function when mounting and operating a crafted ext4 image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10876|2024-08-05T07:46:47.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14890|2024-08-05T00:26:39.098Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- tower
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14890</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Ansible Tower before 3.6.1 where an attacker with low privilege could retrieve usernames and passwords credentials from the new RHSM saved in plain text into the database at '/api/v2/config' when applying the Ansible Tower license.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14890|2024-08-05T00:26:39.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 06:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10890|2024-08-05T07:54:35.431Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10890</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in moodle before versions 3.5.1, 3.4.4, 3.3.7, 3.1.13. It was possible for the core_course_get_categories web service to return hidden categories, which should be omitted when fetching course categories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10890|2024-08-05T07:54:35.431Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10879|2024-08-05T07:46:46.964Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10879</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ext4 filesystem. A local user can cause a use-after-free in ext4_xattr_set_entry function and a denial of service or unspecified other impact may occur by renaming a file in a crafted ext4 filesystem image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10879|2024-08-05T07:46:46.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10850|2024-08-05T07:46:47.455Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- 389-ds-base
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10850</link>
      <description>389-ds-base before versions 1.4.0.10, 1.3.8.3 is vulnerable to a race condition in the way 389-ds-base handles persistent search, resulting in a crash if the server is under load. An anonymous attacker could use this flaw to trigger a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10850|2024-08-05T07:46:47.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10922|2024-08-05T07:54:35.779Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ttembed
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10922</link>
      <description>An input validation flaw exists in ttembed. With a crafted input file, an attacker may be able to trigger a denial of service condition due to ttembed trusting attacker controlled values.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10922|2024-08-05T07:54:35.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1122|2024-08-05T03:51:48.790Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- procps-ng%2C%20procps
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1122</link>
      <description>procps-ng before version 3.3.15 is vulnerable to a local privilege escalation in top. If a user runs top with HOME unset in an attacker-controlled directory, the attacker could achieve privilege escalation by exploiting one of several vulnerabilities in the config_file() function.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1122|2024-08-05T03:51:48.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10881|2024-08-05T07:54:34.835Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10881</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ext4 filesystem. A local user can cause an out-of-bound access in ext4_get_group_info function, a denial of service, and a system crash by mounting and operating on a crafted ext4 filesystem image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10881|2024-08-05T07:54:34.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14856|2024-08-05T00:26:39.119Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14856</link>
      <description>ansible before versions 2.8.6, 2.7.14, 2.6.20 is vulnerable to a None</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14856|2024-08-05T00:26:39.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 13:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10874|2024-08-05T07:46:47.224Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10874</link>
      <description>In ansible it was found that inventory variables are loaded from current working directory when running ad-hoc command which are under attacker's control, allowing to run arbitrary code as a result.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10874|2024-08-05T07:46:47.224Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1067|2024-08-05T03:51:47.329Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- undertow
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1067</link>
      <description>In Undertow before versions 7.1.2.CR1, 7.1.2.GA it was found that the fix for CVE-2016-4993 was incomplete and Undertow web server is vulnerable to the injection of arbitrary HTTP headers, and also response splitting, due to insufficient sanitization and validation of user input before the input is used as part of an HTTP header value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1067|2024-08-05T03:51:47.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1085|2024-08-05T03:51:48.271Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- openshift-ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1085</link>
      <description>openshift-ansible before versions 3.9.23, 3.7.46 deploys a misconfigured etcd file that causes the SSL client certificate authentication to be disabled. Quotations around the values of ETCD_CLIENT_CERT_AUTH and ETCD_PEER_CLIENT_CERT_AUTH in etcd.conf result in etcd being configured to allow remote users to connect without any authentication if they can access the etcd server bound to the network on the master nodes. An attacker could use this flaw to read and modify all the data about the Openshift cluster in the etcd datastore, potentially adding another compute node, or bringing down the entire cluster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1085|2024-08-05T03:51:48.271Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-19345|2024-08-05T02:16:47.043Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- openshift%2Fmediawiki-apb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-19345</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in all openshift/mediawiki-apb 4.x.x versions prior to 4.3.0, where an insecure modification vulnerability in the /etc/passwd file was found in the container openshift/mediawiki-apb. An attacker with access to the container could use this flaw to modify /etc/passwd and escalate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-19345|2024-08-05T02:16:47.043Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10900|2024-08-05T07:54:36.169Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- networkmanager-vpnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10900</link>
      <description>Network Manager VPNC plugin (aka networkmanager-vpnc) before version 1.2.6 is vulnerable to a privilege escalation attack. A new line character can be used to inject a Password helper parameter into the configuration data passed to VPNC, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10900|2024-08-05T07:54:36.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14824|2024-08-05T00:26:39.128Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- 389-ds-base
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14824</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the 'deref' plugin of 389-ds-base where it could use the 'search' permission to display attribute values. In some configurations, this could allow an authenticated attacker to view private attributes, such as password hashes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14824|2024-08-05T00:26:39.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 14:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10883|2024-08-05T07:54:34.854Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10883</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ext4 filesystem. A local user can cause an out-of-bounds write in jbd2_journal_dirty_metadata(), a denial of service, and a system crash by mounting and operating on a crafted ext4 filesystem image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10883|2024-08-05T07:54:34.854Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10845|2024-08-05T07:46:47.470Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- gnutls
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10845</link>
      <description>It was found that the GnuTLS implementation of HMAC-SHA-384 was vulnerable to a Lucky thirteen style attack. Remote attackers could use this flaw to conduct distinguishing attacks and plain text recovery attacks via statistical analysis of timing data using crafted packets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10845|2024-08-05T07:46:47.470Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14884|2024-08-05T00:26:39.172Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14884</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Moodle 3.7 before 3.73, 3.6 before 3.6.7 and 3.5 before 3.5.9, where a reflected XSS possible from some fatal error messages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14884|2024-08-05T00:26:39.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 12:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10936|2024-08-05T07:54:36.516Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- postgresql
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10936</link>
      <description>A weakness was found in postgresql-jdbc before version 42.2.5. It was possible to provide an SSL Factory and not check the host name if a host name verifier was not provided to the driver. This could lead to a condition where a man-in-the-middle attacker could masquerade as a trusted server by providing a certificate for the wrong host, as long as it was signed by a trusted CA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10936|2024-08-05T07:54:36.516Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10908|2024-08-05T07:54:35.199Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- vdsm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10908</link>
      <description>It was found that vdsm before version 4.20.37 invokes qemu-img on untrusted inputs without limiting resources. By uploading a specially crafted image, an attacker could cause the qemu-img process to consume unbounded amounts of memory of CPU time, causing a denial of service condition that could potentially impact other users of the host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10908|2024-08-05T07:54:35.199Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10933|2024-08-05T07:54:35.801Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- libssh
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10933</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in libssh's server-side state machine before versions 0.7.6 and 0.8.4. A malicious client could create channels without first performing authentication, resulting in unauthorized access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10933|2024-08-05T07:54:35.801Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10921|2024-08-05T07:54:36.317Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ttembed
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10921</link>
      <description>Certain input files may trigger an integer overflow in ttembed input file processing. This overflow could potentially lead to corruption of the input file due to a lack of checking return codes of fgetc/fputc function calls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10921|2024-08-05T07:54:36.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1117|2024-08-05T03:51:48.428Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ovirt-ansible-roles
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1117</link>
      <description>ovirt-ansible-roles before version 1.0.6 has a vulnerability due to a missing no_log directive, resulting in the 'Add oVirt Provider to ManageIQ/CloudForms' playbook inadvertently disclosing admin passwords in the provisioning log. In an environment where logs are shared with other parties, this could lead to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1117|2024-08-05T03:51:48.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1061|2024-08-05T03:51:48.415Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- python
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1061</link>
      <description>python before versions 2.7.15, 3.4.9, 3.5.6rc1, 3.6.5rc1 and 3.7.0 is vulnerable to catastrophic backtracking in the difflib.IS_LINE_JUNK method.  An attacker could use this flaw to cause denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1061|2024-08-05T03:51:48.415Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1120|2024-08-05T03:51:48.863Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1120</link>
      <description>A flaw was found affecting the Linux kernel before version 4.17. By mmap()ing a FUSE-backed file onto a process's memory containing command line arguments (or environment strings), an attacker can cause utilities from psutils or procps (such as ps, w) or any other program which makes a read() call to the /proc/&lt;pid&gt;/cmdline (or /proc/&lt;pid&gt;/environ) files to block indefinitely (denial of service) or for some controlled time (as a synchronization primitive for other attacks).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1120|2024-08-05T03:51:48.863Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10875|2024-08-05T07:46:47.518Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10875</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in ansible. ansible.cfg is read from the current working directory which can be altered to make it point to a plugin or a module path under the control of an attacker, thus allowing the attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10875|2024-08-05T07:46:47.518Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-19338|2024-08-05T02:16:46.895Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- linux%20kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-19338</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the fix for CVE-2019-11135, in the Linux upstream kernel versions before 5.5 where, the way Intel CPUs handle speculative execution of instructions when a TSX Asynchronous Abort (TAA) error occurs. When a guest is running on a host CPU affected by the TAA flaw (TAA_NO=0), but is not affected by the MDS issue (MDS_NO=1), the guest was to clear the affected buffers by using a VERW instruction mechanism. But when the MDS_NO=1 bit was exported to the guests, the guests did not use the VERW mechanism to clear the affected buffers. This issue affects guests running on Cascade Lake CPUs and requires that host has 'TSX' enabled. Confidentiality of data is the highest threat associated with this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-19338|2024-08-05T02:16:46.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10912|2024-08-05T07:54:36.292Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10912</link>
      <description>keycloak before version 4.0.0.final is vulnerable to a infinite loop in session replacement. A Keycloak cluster with multiple nodes could mishandle an expired session replacement and lead to an infinite loop. A malicious authenticated user could use this flaw to achieve Denial of Service on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10912|2024-08-05T07:54:36.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1121|2024-08-05T03:51:48.742Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- procps-ng%2C%20procps
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1121</link>
      <description>procps-ng, procps is vulnerable to a process hiding through race condition. Since the kernel's proc_pid_readdir() returns PID entries in ascending numeric order, a process occupying a high PID can use inotify events to determine when the process list is being scanned, and fork/exec to obtain a lower PID, thus avoiding enumeration. An unprivileged attacker can hide a process from procps-ng's utilities by exploiting a race condition in reading /proc/PID entries. This vulnerability affects procps and procps-ng up to version 3.3.15, newer versions might be affected also.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1121|2024-08-05T03:51:48.742Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10885|2024-08-05T07:54:34.734Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- atomic-openshift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10885</link>
      <description>In atomic-openshift before version 3.10.9 a malicious network-policy configuration can cause Openshift Routing to crash when using ovs-networkpolicy plugin. An attacker can use this flaw to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) attack on an Openshift 3.9, or 3.7 Cluster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10885|2024-08-05T07:54:34.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10906|2024-08-05T07:54:35.543Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- fuse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10906</link>
      <description>In fuse before versions 2.9.8 and 3.x before 3.2.5, fusermount is vulnerable to a restriction bypass when SELinux is active. This allows non-root users to mount a FUSE file system with the 'allow_other' mount option regardless of whether 'user_allow_other' is set in the fuse configuration. An attacker may use this flaw to mount a FUSE file system, accessible by other users, and trick them into accessing files on that file system, possibly causing Denial of Service or other unspecified effects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10906|2024-08-05T07:54:35.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10852|2024-08-05T07:46:47.244Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- sssd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10852</link>
      <description>The UNIX pipe which sudo uses to contact SSSD and read the available sudo rules from SSSD has too wide permissions, which means that anyone who can send a message using the same raw protocol that sudo and SSSD use can read the sudo rules available for any user. This affects versions of SSSD before 1.16.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10852|2024-08-05T07:46:47.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14842|2024-08-05T00:26:39.105Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- libnbd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14842</link>
      <description>Structured reply is a feature of the newstyle NBD protocol allowing the server to send a reply in chunks. A bounds check which was supposed to test for chunk offsets smaller than the beginning of the request did not work because of signed/unsigned confusion. If one of these chunks contains a negative offset then data under control of the server is written to memory before the read buffer supplied by the client. If the read buffer is located on the stack then this allows the stack return address from nbd_pread() to be trivially modified, allowing arbitrary code execution under the control of the server. If the buffer is located on the heap then other memory objects before the buffer can be overwritten, which again would usually lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14842|2024-08-05T00:26:39.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 15:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14882|2024-08-05T00:26:39.160Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14882</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Moodle 3.7 to 3.7.3, 3.6 to 3.6.7, 3.5 to 3.5.9 and earlier where an open redirect existed in the Lesson edit page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14882|2024-08-05T00:26:39.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 12:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10864|2024-08-05T07:46:46.942Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- redhat-certification%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10864</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled resource consumption flaw has been discovered in redhat-certification in the way documents are loaded. A remote attacker may provide an existing but invalid XML file which would be opened and never closed, possibly producing a Denial of Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10864|2024-08-05T07:46:46.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10857|2024-08-05T07:46:47.326Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- git-annex
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10857</link>
      <description>git-annex is vulnerable to a private data exposure and exfiltration attack. It could expose the content of files located outside the git-annex repository, or content from a private web server on localhost or the LAN.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10857|2024-08-05T07:46:47.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14879|2024-08-05T00:26:39.133Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14879</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Moodle versions 3.7.x before 3.7.3, 3.6.x before 3.6.7 and 3.5.x before 3.5.9. When a cohort role assignment was removed, the associated capabilities were not being revoked (where applicable).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14879|2024-08-05T00:26:39.133Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 16:23:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10843|2024-08-05T07:46:46.958Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- source-to-image
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10843</link>
      <description>source-to-image component of Openshift Container Platform before versions atomic-openshift 3.7.53, atomic-openshift 3.9.31 is vulnerable to a privilege escalation which allows the assemble script to run as the root user in a non-privileged container. An attacker can use this flaw to open network connections, and possibly other actions, on the host which are normally only available to a root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10843|2024-08-05T07:46:46.958Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10917|2024-08-05T07:54:35.610Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- pulp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10917</link>
      <description>pulp 2.16.x and possibly older is vulnerable to an improper path parsing. A malicious user or a malicious iso feed repository can write to locations accessible to the 'apache' user. This may lead to overwrite of published content on other iso repositories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10917|2024-08-05T07:54:35.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10873|2024-08-05T07:46:47.325Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- spice%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10873</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was discovered in SPICE before version 0.14.1 where the generated code used for demarshalling messages lacked sufficient bounds checks. A malicious client or server, after authentication, could send specially crafted messages to its peer which would result in a crash or, potentially, other impacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10873|2024-08-05T07:46:47.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10878|2024-08-05T07:46:47.494Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10878</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ext4 filesystem. A local user can cause an out-of-bounds write and a denial of service or unspecified other impact is possible by mounting and operating a crafted ext4 filesystem image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10878|2024-08-05T07:46:47.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14881|2024-08-05T00:26:39.145Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14881</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in moodle 3.7 before 3.7.3, where there is blind XSS reflected in some locations where user email is displayed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14881|2024-08-05T00:26:39.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 12:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10869|2024-08-05T07:46:47.477Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- redhat-certification
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10869</link>
      <description>redhat-certification does not properly restrict files that can be download through the /download page. A remote attacker may download any file accessible by the user running httpd.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10869|2024-08-05T07:46:47.477Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10856|2024-08-05T07:46:47.230Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- podman
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10856</link>
      <description>It has been discovered that podman before version 0.6.1 does not drop capabilities when executing a container as a non-root user. This results in unnecessary privileges being granted to the container.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10856|2024-08-05T07:46:47.230Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14880|2024-08-05T00:26:39.160Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14880</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Moodle versions 3.7 before 3.7.3, 3.6 before 3.6.7, 3.5 before 3.5.9 and earlier. OAuth 2 providers who do not verify users' email address changes require additional verification during sign-up to reduce the risk of account compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14880|2024-08-05T00:26:39.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 15:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1123|2024-08-05T03:51:48.635Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- procps-ng%2C%20procps
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1123</link>
      <description>procps-ng before version 3.3.15 is vulnerable to a denial of service in ps via mmap buffer overflow. Inbuilt protection in ps maps a guard page at the end of the overflowed buffer, ensuring that the impact of this flaw is limited to a crash (temporary denial of service).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1123|2024-08-05T03:51:48.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10903|2024-08-05T07:54:36.330Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- python-cryptography
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10903</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in python-cryptography versions between &gt;=1.9.0 and &lt;2.3. The finalize_with_tag API did not enforce a minimum tag length. If a user did not validate the input length prior to passing it to finalize_with_tag an attacker could craft an invalid payload with a shortened tag (e.g. 1 byte) such that they would have a 1 in 256 chance of passing the MAC check. GCM tag forgeries can cause key leakage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10903|2024-08-05T07:54:36.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14860|2024-08-05T00:26:39.101Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- syndesis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14860</link>
      <description>It was found that the Syndesis configuration for Cross-Origin Resource Sharing was set to allow all origins. An attacker could use this lack of protection to conduct phishing attacks and further access unauthorized information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14860|2024-08-05T00:26:39.101Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 14:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10882|2024-08-05T07:54:34.712Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10882</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ext4 filesystem. A local user can cause an out-of-bound write in in fs/jbd2/transaction.c code, a denial of service, and a system crash by unmounting a crafted ext4 filesystem image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10882|2024-08-05T07:54:34.712Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14857|2024-08-05T00:26:39.151Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- mod_auth_openidc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14857</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in mod_auth_openidc before version 2.4.0.1. An open redirect issue exists in URLs with trailing slashes similar to CVE-2019-3877 in mod_auth_mellon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14857|2024-08-05T00:26:39.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 11:56:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1126|2024-08-05T03:51:48.860Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- procps-ng%2C%20procps
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1126</link>
      <description>procps-ng before version 3.3.15 is vulnerable to an incorrect integer size in proc/alloc.* leading to truncation/integer overflow issues. This flaw is related to CVE-2018-1124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1126|2024-08-05T03:51:48.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14894|2024-08-05T00:26:39.132Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- cloudforms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14894</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the CloudForms management engine version 5.10 and CloudForms management version 5.11, which triggered remote code execution through NFS schedule backup. An attacker logged into the management console could use this flaw to execute arbitrary shell commands on the CloudForms server as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14894|2024-08-05T00:26:39.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 17:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10844|2024-08-05T07:46:46.944Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- gnutls
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10844</link>
      <description>It was found that the GnuTLS implementation of HMAC-SHA-256 was vulnerable to a Lucky thirteen style attack. Remote attackers could use this flaw to conduct distinguishing attacks and plaintext-recovery attacks via statistical analysis of timing data using crafted packets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10844|2024-08-05T07:46:46.944Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10902|2024-08-05T07:54:35.823Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10902</link>
      <description>It was found that the raw midi kernel driver does not protect against concurrent access which leads to a double realloc (double free) in snd_rawmidi_input_params() and snd_rawmidi_output_status() which are part of snd_rawmidi_ioctl() handler in rawmidi.c file. A malicious local attacker could possibly use this for privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10902|2024-08-05T07:54:35.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10855|2024-08-05T07:46:47.397Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10855</link>
      <description>Ansible 2.5 prior to 2.5.5, and 2.4 prior to 2.4.5, do not honor the no_log task flag for failed tasks. When the no_log flag has been used to protect sensitive data passed to a task from being logged, and that task does not run successfully, Ansible will expose sensitive data in log files and on the terminal of the user running Ansible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10855|2024-08-05T07:46:47.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1075|2024-08-05T03:51:48.553Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ovirt-engine
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1075</link>
      <description>ovirt-engine up to version 4.2.3 is vulnerable to an unfiltered password when choosing manual db provisioning. When engine-setup was run and one chooses to provision the database manually or connect to a remote database, the password input was logged in cleartext during the verification step. Sharing the provisioning log might inadvertently leak database passwords.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1075|2024-08-05T03:51:48.553Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10877|2024-08-05T07:46:47.469Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10877</link>
      <description>Linux kernel ext4 filesystem is vulnerable to an out-of-bound access in the ext4_ext_drop_refs() function when operating on a crafted ext4 filesystem image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10877|2024-08-05T07:46:47.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10905|2024-08-05T07:54:36.246Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- cfme
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10905</link>
      <description>CloudForms Management Engine (cfme) is vulnerable to an improper security setting in the dRuby component of CloudForms. An attacker with access to an unprivileged local shell could use this flaw to execute commands as a high privileged user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10905|2024-08-05T07:54:36.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10916|2024-08-05T07:54:35.215Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- lftp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10916</link>
      <description>It has been discovered that lftp up to and including version 4.8.3 does not properly sanitize remote file names, leading to a loss of integrity on the local system when reverse mirroring is used. A remote attacker may trick a user to use reverse mirroring on an attacker controlled FTP server, resulting in the removal of all files in the current working directory of the victim's system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10916|2024-08-05T07:54:35.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1132|2024-08-05T03:51:48.839Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- opendaylight
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1132</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Opendaylight's SDNInterfaceapp (SDNI). Attackers can SQL inject the component's database (SQLite) without authenticating to the controller or SDNInterfaceapp. SDNInterface has been deprecated in OpenDayLight since it was last used in the final Carbon series release. In addition to the component not being included in OpenDayLight in newer releases, the SDNInterface component is not packaged in the opendaylight package included in RHEL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1132|2024-08-05T03:51:48.839Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10891|2024-08-05T07:54:34.734Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10891</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in moodle before versions 3.5.1, 3.4.4, 3.3.7, 3.1.13. When a quiz question bank is imported, it was possible for the question preview that is displayed to execute JavaScript that is written into the question bank.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10891|2024-08-05T07:54:34.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10889|2024-08-05T07:54:34.784Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10889</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in moodle before versions 3.5.1, 3.4.4, 3.3.7. No option existed to omit logs from data privacy exports, which may contain details of other users who interacted with the requester.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10889|2024-08-05T07:54:34.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10847|2024-08-05T07:46:47.419Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- prosody
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10847</link>
      <description>prosody before versions 0.10.2, 0.9.14 is vulnerable to an Authentication Bypass. Prosody did not verify that the virtual host associated with a user session remained the same across stream restarts. A user may authenticate to XMPP host A and migrate their authenticated session to XMPP host B of the same Prosody instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10847|2024-08-05T07:46:47.419Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14902|2024-08-05T00:26:39.142Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- samba
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14902</link>
      <description>There is an issue in all samba 4.11.x versions before 4.11.5, all samba 4.10.x versions before 4.10.12 and all samba 4.9.x versions before 4.9.18, where the removal of the right to create or modify a subtree would not automatically be taken away on all domain controllers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14902|2024-08-05T00:26:39.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1046|2024-08-05T03:44:11.842Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- pdns
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1046</link>
      <description>pdns before version 4.1.2 is vulnerable to a buffer overflow in dnsreplay. In the dnsreplay tool provided with PowerDNS Authoritative, replaying a specially crafted PCAP file can trigger a stack-based buffer overflow, leading to a crash and potentially arbitrary code execution. This buffer overflow only occurs when the -ecs-stamp option of dnsreplay is used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1046|2024-08-05T03:44:11.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1070|2024-08-05T03:51:47.334Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- routing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1070</link>
      <description>routing before version 3.10 is vulnerable to an improper input validation of the Openshift Routing configuration which can cause an entire shard to be brought down. A malicious user can use this vulnerability to cause a Denial of Service attack for other users of the router shard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1070|2024-08-05T03:51:47.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1116|2024-08-05T03:51:48.873Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- polkit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1116</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in polkit before version 0.116. The implementation of the polkit_backend_interactive_authority_check_authorization function in polkitd allows to test for authentication and trigger authentication of unrelated processes owned by other users. This may result in a local DoS and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1116|2024-08-05T03:51:48.873Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10846|2024-08-05T07:46:47.512Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- gnutls
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10846</link>
      <description>A cache-based side channel in GnuTLS implementation that leads to plain text recovery in cross-VM attack setting was found. An attacker could use a combination of "Just in Time" Prime+probe attack in combination with Lucky-13 attack to recover plain text using crafted packets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10846|2024-08-05T07:46:47.512Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1113|2024-08-05T03:51:48.931Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- setup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1113</link>
      <description>setup before version 2.11.4-1.fc28 in Fedora and Red Hat Enterprise Linux added /sbin/nologin and /usr/sbin/nologin to /etc/shells. This violates security assumptions made by pam_shells and some daemons which allow access based on a user's shell being listed in /etc/shells. Under some circumstances, users which had their shell changed to /sbin/nologin could still access the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1113|2024-08-05T03:51:48.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1072|2024-08-05T03:51:48.552Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ovirt-engine-setup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1072</link>
      <description>ovirt-engine before version ovirt 4.2.2 is vulnerable to an information exposure through log files. When engine-backup was run with one of the options "--provision*db", the database username and password were logged in cleartext. Sharing the provisioning log might inadvertently leak database passwords.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1072|2024-08-05T03:51:48.552Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14865|2024-08-05T00:26:39.094Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- grub2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14865</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the grub2-set-bootflag utility of grub2. A local attacker could run this utility under resource pressure (for example by setting RLIMIT), causing grub2 configuration files to be truncated and leaving the system unbootable on subsequent reboots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14865|2024-08-05T00:26:39.094Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 09:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10892|2024-08-05T07:54:34.913Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- docker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10892</link>
      <description>The default OCI linux spec in oci/defaults{_linux}.go in Docker/Moby from 1.11 to current does not block /proc/acpi pathnames. The flaw allows an attacker to modify host's hardware like enabling/disabling bluetooth or turning up/down keyboard brightness.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10892|2024-08-05T07:54:34.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10871|2024-08-05T07:46:47.376Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- 389-ds-base
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10871</link>
      <description>389-ds-base before versions 1.3.8.5, 1.4.0.12 is vulnerable to a Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information. By default, when the Replica and/or retroChangeLog plugins are enabled, 389-ds-base stores passwords in plaintext format in their respective changelog files. An attacker with sufficiently high privileges, such as root or Directory Manager, can query these files in order to retrieve plaintext passwords.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10871|2024-08-05T07:46:47.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1080|2024-08-05T03:51:48.562Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- pki-core
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1080</link>
      <description>Dogtag PKI, through version 10.6.1, has a vulnerability in AAclAuthz.java that, under certain configurations, causes the application of ACL allow and deny rules to be reversed. If a server is configured to process allow rules before deny rules (authz.evaluateOrder=allow,deny), then allow rules will deny access and deny rules will grant access. This may result in an escalation of privileges or have other unintended consequences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1080|2024-08-05T03:51:48.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
