<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for [UNKNOWN] -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/%5Bunknown%5D/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for [UNKNOWN] -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:23:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7497|2024-08-05T16:04:11.900Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- cfme
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7497</link>
      <description>The dialog for creating cloud volumes (cinder provider) in CloudForms does not filter cloud tenants by user. An attacker with the ability to create storage volumes could use this to create storage volumes for any other tenant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7497|2024-08-05T16:04:11.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2669|2024-08-05T14:02:06.877Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- dovecot
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2669</link>
      <description>Dovecot before version 2.2.29 is vulnerable to a denial of service. When 'dict' passdb and userdb were used for user authentication, the username sent by the IMAP/POP3 client was sent through var_expand() to perform %variable expansion. Sending specially crafted %variable fields could result in excessive memory usage causing the process to crash (and restart), or excessive CPU usage causing all authentications to hang.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2669|2024-08-05T14:02:06.877Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2672|2024-08-05T14:02:07.221Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- foreman
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2672</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in foreman before version 1.15 in the logging of adding and registering images. An attacker with access to the foreman log file would be able to view passwords for provisioned systems in the log file, allowing them to access those systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2672|2024-08-05T14:02:07.221Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2665|2024-08-05T14:02:07.257Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- rhscon-core
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2665</link>
      <description>The skyring-setup command creates random password for mongodb skyring database but it writes password in plain text to /etc/skyring/skyring.conf file which is owned by root but read by local user. Any local user who has access to system running skyring service will be able to get password in plain text.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2665|2024-08-05T14:02:07.257Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16851|2024-08-05T10:32:53.988Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- samba
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16851</link>
      <description>Samba from version 4.0.0 and before versions 4.7.12, 4.8.7, 4.9.3 is vulnerable to a denial of service. During the processing of an LDAP search before Samba's AD DC returns the LDAP entries to the client, the entries are cached in a single memory object with a maximum size of 256MB. When this size is reached, the Samba process providing the LDAP service will follow the NULL pointer, terminating the process. There is no further vulnerability associated with this issue, merely a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16851|2024-08-05T10:32:53.988Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16853|2024-08-05T10:32:54.157Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- samba
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16853</link>
      <description>Samba from version 4.7.0 has a vulnerability that allows a user in a Samba AD domain to crash the KDC when Samba is built in the non-default MIT Kerberos configuration. With this advisory the Samba Team clarify that the MIT Kerberos build of the Samba AD DC is considered experimental. Therefore the Samba Team will not issue security patches for this configuration. Additionally, Samba 4.7.12, 4.8.7 and 4.9.3 have been issued as security releases to prevent building of the AD DC with MIT Kerberos unless --with-experimental-mit-ad-dc is specified to the configure command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16853|2024-08-05T10:32:54.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2670|2024-08-05T14:02:06.996Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- undertow
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2670</link>
      <description>It was found in Undertow before 1.3.28 that with non-clean TCP close, the Websocket server gets into infinite loop on every IO thread, effectively causing DoS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2670|2024-08-05T14:02:06.996Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14883|2024-08-05T00:26:39.123Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14883</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Moodle 3.6 before 3.6.7 and 3.7 before 3.7.3, where tokens used to fetch inline atachments in email notifications were not disabled when a user's account was no longer active. Note: to access files, a user would need to know the file path, and their token.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14883|2024-08-05T00:26:39.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 12:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1125|2024-08-05T03:51:48.542Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- procps-ng%2C%20procps
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1125</link>
      <description>procps-ng before version 3.3.15 is vulnerable to a stack buffer overflow in pgrep. This vulnerability is mitigated by FORTIFY, as it involves strncat() to a stack-allocated string. When pgrep is compiled with FORTIFY (as on Red Hat Enterprise Linux and Fedora), the impact is limited to a crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1125|2024-08-05T03:51:48.542Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2600|2024-08-05T14:02:06.499Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2600</link>
      <description>In jenkins before versions 2.44, 2.32.2 node monitor data could be viewed by low privilege users via the remote API. These included system configuration and runtime information of these nodes (SECURITY-343).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2600|2024-08-05T14:02:06.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16849|2024-08-05T10:32:54.175Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- openstack-mistral
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16849</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in openstack-mistral. By manipulating the SSH private key filename, the std.ssh action can be used to disclose the presence of arbitrary files within the filesystem of the executor running the action. Since std.ssh private_key_filename can take an absolute path, it can be used to assess whether or not a file exists on the executor's filesystem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16849|2024-08-05T10:32:54.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1073|2024-08-05T03:51:47.320Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ovirt-engine
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1073</link>
      <description>The web console login form in ovirt-engine before version 4.2.3 returned different errors for non-existent users and invalid passwords, allowing an attacker to discover the names of valid user accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1073|2024-08-05T03:51:47.320Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14645|2024-08-05T09:38:12.812Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- haproxy
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14645</link>
      <description>A flaw was discovered in the HPACK decoder of HAProxy, before 1.8.14, that is used for HTTP/2. An out-of-bounds read access in hpack_valid_idx() resulted in a remote crash and denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14645|2024-08-05T09:38:12.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10898|2024-08-05T07:54:34.730Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- openstack-tripleo-heat-templates
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10898</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in openstack-tripleo-heat-templates before version 8.0.2-40. When deployed using Director using default configuration, Opendaylight in RHOSP13 is configured with easily guessable default credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10898|2024-08-05T07:54:34.730Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16867|2024-08-05T10:32:54.050Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- qemu%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16867</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in qemu Media Transfer Protocol (MTP) before version 3.1.0. A path traversal in the in usb_mtp_write_data function in hw/usb/dev-mtp.c due to an improper filename sanitization. When the guest device is mounted in read-write mode, this allows to read/write arbitrary files which may lead do DoS scenario OR possibly lead to code execution on the host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16867|2024-08-05T10:32:54.050Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14646|2024-08-05T09:38:13.102Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14646</link>
      <description>The Linux kernel before 4.15-rc8 was found to be vulnerable to a NULL pointer dereference bug in the __netlink_ns_capable() function in the net/netlink/af_netlink.c file. A local attacker could exploit this when a net namespace with a netnsid is assigned to cause a kernel panic and a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14646|2024-08-05T09:38:13.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2613|2024-08-05T14:02:07.012Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2613</link>
      <description>jenkins before versions 2.44, 2.32.2 is vulnerable to a user creation CSRF using GET by admins. While this user record was only retained until restart in most cases, administrators' web browsers could be manipulated to create a large number of user records (SECURITY-406).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2613|2024-08-05T14:02:07.012Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2668|2024-08-05T14:02:07.340Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- 389-ds-base
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2668</link>
      <description>389-ds-base before versions 1.3.5.17 and 1.3.6.10 is vulnerable to an invalid pointer dereference in the way LDAP bind requests are handled. A remote unauthenticated attacker could use this flaw to make ns-slapd crash via a specially crafted LDAP bind request, resulting in denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2668|2024-08-05T14:02:07.340Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16838|2024-08-05T10:32:54.014Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- sssd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16838</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in sssd Group Policy Objects implementation. When the GPO is not readable by SSSD due to a too strict permission settings on the server side, SSSD will allow all authenticated users to login instead of denying access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16838|2024-08-05T10:32:54.014Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 17:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10859|2024-08-05T07:46:47.345Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- git-annex
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10859</link>
      <description>git-annex is vulnerable to an Information Exposure when decrypting files. A malicious server for a special remote could trick git-annex into decrypting a file that was encrypted to the user's gpg key. This attack could be used to expose encrypted data that was never stored in git-annex</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10859|2024-08-05T07:46:47.345Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2599|2024-08-05T14:02:06.971Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2599</link>
      <description>Jenkins before versions 2.44 and 2.32.2 is vulnerable to an insufficient permission check. This allows users with permissions to create new items (e.g. jobs) to overwrite existing items they don't have access to (SECURITY-321).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2599|2024-08-05T14:02:06.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14853|2024-08-05T00:26:39.175Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- python-ecdsa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14853</link>
      <description>An error-handling flaw was found in python-ecdsa before version 0.13.3. During signature decoding, malformed DER signatures could raise unexpected exceptions (or no exceptions at all), which could lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14853|2024-08-05T00:26:39.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 12:06:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1060|2024-08-05T03:44:12.002Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- python
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1060</link>
      <description>python before versions 2.7.15, 3.4.9, 3.5.6rc1, 3.6.5rc1 and 3.7.0 is vulnerable to catastrophic backtracking in pop3lib's apop() method. An attacker could use this flaw to cause denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1060|2024-08-05T03:44:12.002Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10901|2024-08-05T07:54:35.810Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10901</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Linux kernel's KVM virtualization subsystem. The VMX code does not restore the GDT.LIMIT to the previous host value, but instead sets it to 64KB. With a corrupted GDT limit a host's userspace code has an ability to place malicious entries in the GDT, particularly to the per-cpu variables. An attacker can use this to escalate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10901|2024-08-05T07:54:35.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10860|2024-08-05T07:46:47.302Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- perl-archive-zip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10860</link>
      <description>perl-archive-zip is vulnerable to a directory traversal in Archive::Zip. It was found that the Archive::Zip module did not properly sanitize paths while extracting zip files. An attacker able to provide a specially crafted archive for processing could use this flaw to write or overwrite arbitrary files in the context of the perl interpreter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10860|2024-08-05T07:46:47.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10880|2024-08-05T07:54:34.830Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10880</link>
      <description>Linux kernel is vulnerable to a stack-out-of-bounds write in the ext4 filesystem code when mounting and writing to a crafted ext4 image in ext4_update_inline_data(). An attacker could use this to cause a system crash and a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10880|2024-08-05T07:54:34.830Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7464|2024-08-05T16:04:11.737Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- jboss
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7464</link>
      <description>It was found that the JAXP implementation used in JBoss EAP 7.0 for SAX and DOM parsing is vulnerable to certain XXE flaws. An attacker could use this flaw to cause DoS, SSRF, or information disclosure if they are able to provide XML content for parsing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7464|2024-08-05T16:04:11.737Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1124|2024-08-05T03:51:48.632Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- procps-ng
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1124</link>
      <description>procps-ng before version 3.3.15 is vulnerable to multiple integer overflows leading to a heap corruption in file2strvec function. This allows a privilege escalation for a local attacker who can create entries in procfs by starting processes, which could result in crashes or arbitrary code execution in proc utilities run by other users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1124|2024-08-05T03:51:48.632Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1090|2024-08-05T03:51:49.104Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- pulp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1090</link>
      <description>In Pulp before version 2.16.2, secrets are passed into override_config when triggering a task and then become readable to all users with read access on the distributor/importer. An attacker with API access can then view these secrets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1090|2024-08-05T03:51:49.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10876|2024-08-05T07:46:47.413Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10876</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Linux kernel in the ext4 filesystem code. A use-after-free is possible in ext4_ext_remove_space() function when mounting and operating a crafted ext4 image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10876|2024-08-05T07:46:47.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14890|2024-08-05T00:26:39.098Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- tower
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14890</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Ansible Tower before 3.6.1 where an attacker with low privilege could retrieve usernames and passwords credentials from the new RHSM saved in plain text into the database at '/api/v2/config' when applying the Ansible Tower license.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14890|2024-08-05T00:26:39.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 06:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15137|2024-08-05T19:50:16.136Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- atomic-openshift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15137</link>
      <description>The OpenShift image import whitelist failed to enforce restrictions correctly when running commands such as "oc tag", for example. This could allow a user with access to OpenShift to run images from registries that should not be allowed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15137|2024-08-05T19:50:16.136Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14622|2024-08-05T09:29:51.941Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- libtirpc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14622</link>
      <description>A null-pointer dereference vulnerability was found in libtirpc before version 0.3.3-rc3. The return value of makefd_xprt() was not checked in all instances, which could lead to a crash when the server exhausted the maximum number of available file descriptors. A remote attacker could cause an rpc-based application to crash by flooding it with new connections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14622|2024-08-05T09:29:51.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7500|2024-08-05T16:04:11.858Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- rpm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7500</link>
      <description>It was found that rpm did not properly handle RPM installations when a destination path was a symbolic link to a directory, possibly changing ownership and permissions of an arbitrary directory, and RPM files being placed in an arbitrary destination. An attacker, with write access to a directory in which a subdirectory will be installed, could redirect that directory to an arbitrary location and gain root privilege.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7500|2024-08-05T16:04:11.858Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14644|2024-08-05T09:38:12.991Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- pdns
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14644</link>
      <description>An issue has been found in PowerDNS Recursor from 4.0.0 up to and including 4.1.4. A remote attacker sending a DNS query for a meta-type like OPT can lead to a zone being wrongly cached as failing DNSSEC validation. It only arises if the parent zone is signed, and all the authoritative servers for that parent zone answer with FORMERR to a query for at least one of the meta-types. As a result, subsequent queries from clients requesting DNSSEC validation will be answered with a ServFail.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14644|2024-08-05T09:38:12.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16846|2024-08-05T10:32:53.997Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16846</link>
      <description>It was found in Ceph versions before 13.2.4 that authenticated ceph RGW users can cause a denial of service against OMAPs holding bucket indices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16846|2024-08-05T10:32:53.997Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14667|2024-08-05T09:38:12.990Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- richfaces
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14667</link>
      <description>The RichFaces Framework 3.X through 3.3.4 is vulnerable to Expression Language (EL) injection via the UserResource resource. A remote, unauthenticated attacker could exploit this to execute arbitrary code using a chain of java serialized objects via org.ajax4jsf.resource.UserResource$UriData.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14667|2024-08-05T09:38:12.990Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2602|2024-08-05T14:02:06.917Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2602</link>
      <description>jenkins before versions 2.44, 2.32.2 is vulnerable to an improper blacklisting of the Pipeline metadata files in the agent-to-master security subsystem. This could allow metadata files to be written to by malicious agents (SECURITY-358).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2602|2024-08-05T14:02:06.917Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16855|2024-08-05T10:32:54.074Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- pdns-recursor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16855</link>
      <description>An issue has been found in PowerDNS Recursor before version 4.1.8 where a remote attacker sending a DNS query can trigger an out-of-bounds memory read while computing the hash of the query for a packet cache lookup, possibly leading to a crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16855|2024-08-05T10:32:54.074Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16857|2024-08-05T10:32:54.067Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- samba
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16857</link>
      <description>Samba from version 4.9.0 and before version 4.9.3 that have AD DC configurations watching for bad passwords (to restrict brute forcing of passwords) in a window of more than 3 minutes may not watch for bad passwords at all. The primary risk from this issue is with regards to domains that have been upgraded from Samba 4.8 and earlier. In these cases the manual testing done to confirm an organisation's password policies apply as expected may not have been re-done after the upgrade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16857|2024-08-05T10:32:54.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16872|2024-08-05T10:32:54.018Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- qemu%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16872</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in qemu Media Transfer Protocol (MTP). The code opening files in usb_mtp_get_object and usb_mtp_get_partial_object and directories in usb_mtp_object_readdir doesn't consider that the underlying filesystem may have changed since the time lstat(2) was called in usb_mtp_object_alloc, a classical TOCTTOU problem. An attacker with write access to the host filesystem shared with a guest can use this property to navigate the host filesystem in the context of the QEMU process and read any file the QEMU process has access to. Access to the filesystem may be local or via a network share protocol such as CIFS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16872|2024-08-05T10:32:54.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10890|2024-08-05T07:54:35.431Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10890</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in moodle before versions 3.5.1, 3.4.4, 3.3.7, 3.1.13. It was possible for the core_course_get_categories web service to return hidden categories, which should be omitted when fetching course categories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10890|2024-08-05T07:54:35.431Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16856|2024-08-05T10:32:54.143Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- openstack-octavia
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16856</link>
      <description>In a default Red Hat Openstack Platform Director installation, openstack-octavia before versions openstack-octavia 2.0.2-5 and openstack-octavia-3.0.1-0.20181009115732 creates log files that are readable by all users. Sensitive information such as private keys can appear in these log files allowing for information exposure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16856|2024-08-05T10:32:54.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 17:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14660|2024-08-05T09:38:12.616Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- glusterfs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14660</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in glusterfs server through versions 4.1.4 and 3.1.2 which allowed repeated usage of GF_META_LOCK_KEY xattr. A remote, authenticated attacker could use this flaw to create multiple locks for single inode by using setxattr repetitively resulting in memory exhaustion of glusterfs server node.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14660|2024-08-05T09:38:12.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2612|2024-08-05T14:02:06.508Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2612</link>
      <description>In Jenkins before versions 2.44, 2.32.2 low privilege users were able to override JDK download credentials (SECURITY-392), resulting in future builds possibly failing to download a JDK.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2612|2024-08-05T14:02:06.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10879|2024-08-05T07:46:46.964Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10879</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ext4 filesystem. A local user can cause a use-after-free in ext4_xattr_set_entry function and a denial of service or unspecified other impact may occur by renaming a file in a crafted ext4 filesystem image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10879|2024-08-05T07:46:46.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15138|2024-08-05T19:50:16.307Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- atomic-openshift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15138</link>
      <description>The OpenShift Enterprise cluster-read can access webhook tokens which would allow an attacker with sufficient privileges to view confidential webhook tokens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15138|2024-08-05T19:50:16.307Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14650|2024-08-05T09:38:12.593Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- sos-collector
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14650</link>
      <description>It was discovered that sos-collector does not properly set the default permissions of newly created files, making all files created by the tool readable by any local user. A local attacker may use this flaw by waiting for a legit user to run sos-collector and steal the collected data in the /var/tmp directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14650|2024-08-05T09:38:12.593Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16868|2024-08-05T10:32:54.146Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- gnutls
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16868</link>
      <description>A Bleichenbacher type side-channel based padding oracle attack was found in the way gnutls handles verification of RSA decrypted PKCS#1 v1.5 data. An attacker who is able to run process on the same physical core as the victim process, could use this to extract plaintext or in some cases downgrade any TLS connections to a vulnerable server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16868|2024-08-05T10:32:54.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10850|2024-08-05T07:46:47.455Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- 389-ds-base
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10850</link>
      <description>389-ds-base before versions 1.4.0.10, 1.3.8.3 is vulnerable to a race condition in the way 389-ds-base handles persistent search, resulting in a crash if the server is under load. An anonymous attacker could use this flaw to trigger a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10850|2024-08-05T07:46:47.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10922|2024-08-05T07:54:35.779Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ttembed
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10922</link>
      <description>An input validation flaw exists in ttembed. With a crafted input file, an attacker may be able to trigger a denial of service condition due to ttembed trusting attacker controlled values.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10922|2024-08-05T07:54:35.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14662|2024-08-05T09:38:12.959Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14662</link>
      <description>It was found Ceph versions before 13.2.4 that authenticated ceph users with read only permissions could steal dm-crypt encryption keys used in ceph disk encryption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14662|2024-08-05T09:38:12.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16847|2024-08-05T10:32:54.125Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- qemu%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16847</link>
      <description>An OOB heap buffer r/w access issue was found in the NVM Express Controller emulation in QEMU. It could occur in nvme_cmb_ops routines in nvme device. A guest user/process could use this flaw to crash the QEMU process resulting in DoS or potentially run arbitrary code with privileges of the QEMU process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16847|2024-08-05T10:32:54.125Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1122|2024-08-05T03:51:48.790Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- procps-ng%2C%20procps
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1122</link>
      <description>procps-ng before version 3.3.15 is vulnerable to a local privilege escalation in top. If a user runs top with HOME unset in an attacker-controlled directory, the attacker could achieve privilege escalation by exploiting one of several vulnerabilities in the config_file() function.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1122|2024-08-05T03:51:48.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7470|2024-08-05T16:04:11.576Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- spacewalk-backend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7470</link>
      <description>It was found that spacewalk-channel can be used by a non-admin user or disabled users to perform administrative tasks due to an incorrect authorization check in backend/server/rhnChannel.py.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7470|2024-08-05T16:04:11.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7482|2024-08-05T16:04:11.726Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7482</link>
      <description>In the Linux kernel before version 4.12, Kerberos 5 tickets decoded when using the RXRPC keys incorrectly assumes the size of a field. This could lead to the size-remaining variable wrapping and the data pointer going over the end of the buffer. This could possibly lead to memory corruption and possible privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7482|2024-08-05T16:04:11.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16837|2024-08-05T10:32:54.010Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16837</link>
      <description>Ansible "User" module leaks any data which is passed on as a parameter to ssh-keygen. This could lean in undesirable situations such as passphrases credentials passed as a parameter for the ssh-keygen executable. Showing those credentials in clear text form for every user which have access just to the process list.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16837|2024-08-05T10:32:54.010Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14631|2024-08-05T09:29:51.898Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14631</link>
      <description>moodle before versions 3.5.2, 3.4.5, 3.3.8 is vulnerable to a boost theme - blog search GET parameter insufficiently filtered. The breadcrumb navigation provided by Boost theme when displaying search results of a blog were insufficiently filtered, which could result in reflected XSS if a user followed a malicious link containing JavaScript in the search parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14631|2024-08-05T09:29:51.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7466|2024-08-05T16:04:11.382Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7466</link>
      <description>Ansible before version 2.3 has an input validation vulnerability in the handling of data sent from client systems. An attacker with control over a client system being managed by Ansible, and the ability to send facts back to the Ansible server, could use this flaw to execute arbitrary code on the Ansible server using the Ansible server privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7466|2024-08-05T16:04:11.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7518|2024-08-05T16:04:11.892Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7518</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel before version 4.12 in the way the KVM module processed the trap flag(TF) bit in EFLAGS during emulation of the syscall instruction, which leads to a debug exception(#DB) being raised in the guest stack. A user/process inside a guest could use this flaw to potentially escalate their privileges inside the guest. Linux guests are not affected by this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7518|2024-08-05T16:04:11.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10881|2024-08-05T07:54:34.835Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10881</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ext4 filesystem. A local user can cause an out-of-bound access in ext4_get_group_info function, a denial of service, and a system crash by mounting and operating on a crafted ext4 filesystem image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10881|2024-08-05T07:54:34.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16884|2024-08-05T10:32:54.149Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16884</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's NFS41+ subsystem. NFS41+ shares mounted in different network namespaces at the same time can make bc_svc_process() use wrong back-channel IDs and cause a use-after-free vulnerability. Thus a malicious container user can cause a host kernel memory corruption and a system panic. Due to the nature of the flaw, privilege escalation cannot be fully ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16884|2024-08-05T10:32:54.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14856|2024-08-05T00:26:39.119Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14856</link>
      <description>ansible before versions 2.8.6, 2.7.14, 2.6.20 is vulnerable to a None</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14856|2024-08-05T00:26:39.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 13:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14664|2024-08-05T09:38:12.688Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- foreman
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14664</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in foreman from versions 1.18. A stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists due to an improperly escaped HTML code in the breadcrumbs bar. This allows a user with permissions to edit which attribute is used in the breadcrumbs bar to store code that will be executed on the client side.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14664|2024-08-05T09:38:12.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2666|2024-08-05T14:02:07.176Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- undertow
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2666</link>
      <description>It was discovered in Undertow that the code that parsed the HTTP request line permitted invalid characters. This could be exploited, in conjunction with a proxy that also permitted the invalid characters but with a different interpretation, to inject data into the HTTP response. By manipulating the HTTP response the attacker could poison a web-cache, perform an XSS attack, or obtain sensitive information from requests other than their own.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2666|2024-08-05T14:02:07.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10874|2024-08-05T07:46:47.224Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10874</link>
      <description>In ansible it was found that inventory variables are loaded from current working directory when running ad-hoc command which are under attacker's control, allowing to run arbitrary code as a result.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10874|2024-08-05T07:46:47.224Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1067|2024-08-05T03:51:47.329Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- undertow
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1067</link>
      <description>In Undertow before versions 7.1.2.CR1, 7.1.2.GA it was found that the fix for CVE-2016-4993 was incomplete and Undertow web server is vulnerable to the injection of arbitrary HTTP headers, and also response splitting, due to insufficient sanitization and validation of user input before the input is used as part of an HTTP header value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1067|2024-08-05T03:51:47.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2608|2024-08-05T14:02:06.498Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2608</link>
      <description>Jenkins before versions 2.44, 2.32.2 is vulnerable to a remote code execution vulnerability involving the deserialization of various types in javax.imageio in XStream-based APIs (SECURITY-383).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2608|2024-08-05T14:02:06.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1085|2024-08-05T03:51:48.271Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- openshift-ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1085</link>
      <description>openshift-ansible before versions 3.9.23, 3.7.46 deploys a misconfigured etcd file that causes the SSL client certificate authentication to be disabled. Quotations around the values of ETCD_CLIENT_CERT_AUTH and ETCD_PEER_CLIENT_CERT_AUTH in etcd.conf result in etcd being configured to allow remote users to connect without any authentication if they can access the etcd server bound to the network on the master nodes. An attacker could use this flaw to read and modify all the data about the Openshift cluster in the etcd datastore, potentially adding another compute node, or bringing down the entire cluster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1085|2024-08-05T03:51:48.271Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14663|2024-08-05T09:38:12.940Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- dnsdist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14663</link>
      <description>An issue has been found in PowerDNS DNSDist before 1.3.3 allowing a remote attacker to craft a DNS query with trailing data such that the addition of a record by dnsdist, for example an OPT record when adding EDNS Client Subnet, might result in the trailing data being smuggled to the backend as a valid record while not seen by dnsdist. This is an issue when dnsdist is deployed as a DNS Firewall and used to filter some records that should not be received by the backend. This issue occurs only when either the 'useClientSubnet' or the experimental 'addXPF' parameters are used when declaring a new backend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14663|2024-08-05T09:38:12.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-19345|2024-08-05T02:16:47.043Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- openshift%2Fmediawiki-apb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-19345</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in all openshift/mediawiki-apb 4.x.x versions prior to 4.3.0, where an insecure modification vulnerability in the /etc/passwd file was found in the container openshift/mediawiki-apb. An attacker with access to the container could use this flaw to modify /etc/passwd and escalate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-19345|2024-08-05T02:16:47.043Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16852|2024-08-05T10:32:54.124Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- samba
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16852</link>
      <description>Samba from version 4.9.0 and before version 4.9.3 is vulnerable to a NULL pointer de-reference. During the processing of an DNS zone in the DNS management DCE/RPC server, the internal DNS server or the Samba DLZ plugin for BIND9, if the DSPROPERTY_ZONE_MASTER_SERVERS property or DSPROPERTY_ZONE_SCAVENGING_SERVERS property is set, the server will follow a NULL pointer and terminate. There is no further vulnerability associated with this issue, merely a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16852|2024-08-05T10:32:54.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10900|2024-08-05T07:54:36.169Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- networkmanager-vpnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10900</link>
      <description>Network Manager VPNC plugin (aka networkmanager-vpnc) before version 1.2.6 is vulnerable to a privilege escalation attack. A new line character can be used to inject a Password helper parameter into the configuration data passed to VPNC, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10900|2024-08-05T07:54:36.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14630|2024-08-05T09:29:51.675Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14630</link>
      <description>moodle before versions 3.5.2, 3.4.5, 3.3.8, 3.1.14 is vulnerable to an XML import of ddwtos could lead to intentional remote code execution. When importing legacy 'drag and drop into text' (ddwtos) type quiz questions, it was possible to inject and execute PHP code from within the imported questions, either intentionally or by importing questions from an untrusted source.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14630|2024-08-05T09:29:51.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16845|2024-08-05T10:32:54.012Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- nginx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16845</link>
      <description>nginx before versions 1.15.6, 1.14.1 has a vulnerability in the ngx_http_mp4_module, which might allow an attacker to cause infinite loop in a worker process, cause a worker process crash, or might result in worker process memory disclosure by using a specially crafted mp4 file. The issue only affects nginx if it is built with the ngx_http_mp4_module (the module is not built by default) and the .mp4. directive is used in the configuration file. Further, the attack is only possible if an attacker is able to trigger processing of a specially crafted mp4 file with the ngx_http_mp4_module.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16845|2024-08-05T10:32:54.012Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16869|2024-08-05T10:32:54.115Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- nettle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16869</link>
      <description>A Bleichenbacher type side-channel based padding oracle attack was found in the way nettle handles endian conversion of RSA decrypted PKCS#1 v1.5 data. An attacker who is able to run a process on the same physical core as the victim process, could use this flaw extract plaintext or in some cases downgrade any TLS connections to a vulnerable server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16869|2024-08-05T10:32:54.115Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2617|2024-08-05T14:02:06.951Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- hawtio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2617</link>
      <description>hawtio before version 1.5.5 is vulnerable to remote code execution via file upload. An attacker could use this vulnerability to upload a crafted file which could be executed on a target machine where hawtio is deployed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2617|2024-08-05T14:02:06.951Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16844|2024-08-05T10:32:54.086Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- nginx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16844</link>
      <description>nginx before versions 1.15.6 and 1.14.1 has a vulnerability in the implementation of HTTP/2 that can allow for excessive CPU usage. This issue affects nginx compiled with the ngx_http_v2_module (not compiled by default) if the 'http2' option of the 'listen' directive is used in a configuration file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16844|2024-08-05T10:32:54.086Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14824|2024-08-05T00:26:39.128Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- 389-ds-base
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14824</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the 'deref' plugin of 389-ds-base where it could use the 'search' permission to display attribute values. In some configurations, this could allow an authenticated attacker to view private attributes, such as password hashes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14824|2024-08-05T00:26:39.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 14:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10883|2024-08-05T07:54:34.854Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10883</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ext4 filesystem. A local user can cause an out-of-bounds write in jbd2_journal_dirty_metadata(), a denial of service, and a system crash by mounting and operating on a crafted ext4 filesystem image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10883|2024-08-05T07:54:34.854Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10845|2024-08-05T07:46:47.470Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- gnutls
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10845</link>
      <description>It was found that the GnuTLS implementation of HMAC-SHA-384 was vulnerable to a Lucky thirteen style attack. Remote attackers could use this flaw to conduct distinguishing attacks and plain text recovery attacks via statistical analysis of timing data using crafted packets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10845|2024-08-05T07:46:47.470Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16858|2024-08-05T10:32:54.146Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- libreoffice
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16858</link>
      <description>It was found that libreoffice before versions 6.0.7 and 6.1.3 was vulnerable to a directory traversal attack which could be used to execute arbitrary macros bundled with a document. An attacker could craft a document, which when opened by LibreOffice, would execute a Python method from a script in any arbitrary file system location, specified relative to the LibreOffice install location.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16858|2024-08-05T10:32:54.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 17:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16883|2024-08-05T10:32:54.202Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- sssd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16883</link>
      <description>sssd versions from 1.13.0 to before 2.0.0 did not properly restrict access to the infopipe according to the "allowed_uids" configuration parameter. If sensitive information were stored in the user directory, this could be inadvertently disclosed to local attackers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16883|2024-08-05T10:32:54.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14884|2024-08-05T00:26:39.172Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14884</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Moodle 3.7 before 3.73, 3.6 before 3.6.7 and 3.5 before 3.5.9, where a reflected XSS possible from some fatal error messages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14884|2024-08-05T00:26:39.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 12:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7510|2024-08-05T16:04:11.915Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- rhv
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7510</link>
      <description>In ovirt-engine 4.1, if a host was provisioned with cloud-init, the root password could be revealed through the REST interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7510|2024-08-05T16:04:11.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 17:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10936|2024-08-05T07:54:36.516Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- postgresql
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10936</link>
      <description>A weakness was found in postgresql-jdbc before version 42.2.5. It was possible to provide an SSL Factory and not check the host name if a host name verifier was not provided to the driver. This could lead to a condition where a man-in-the-middle attacker could masquerade as a trusted server by providing a certificate for the wrong host, as long as it was signed by a trusted CA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10936|2024-08-05T07:54:36.516Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2609|2024-08-05T14:02:07.010Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2609</link>
      <description>jenkins before versions 2.44, 2.32.2 is vulnerable to an information disclosure vulnerability in search suggestions (SECURITY-385). The autocomplete feature on the search box discloses the names of the views in its suggestions, including the ones for which the current user does not have access to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2609|2024-08-05T14:02:07.010Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10908|2024-08-05T07:54:35.199Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- vdsm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10908</link>
      <description>It was found that vdsm before version 4.20.37 invokes qemu-img on untrusted inputs without limiting resources. By uploading a specially crafted image, an attacker could cause the qemu-img process to consume unbounded amounts of memory of CPU time, causing a denial of service condition that could potentially impact other users of the host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10908|2024-08-05T07:54:35.199Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2603|2024-08-05T14:02:06.483Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2603</link>
      <description>Jenkins before versions 2.44, 2.32.2 is vulnerable to a user data leak in disconnected agents' config.xml API. This could leak sensitive data such as API tokens (SECURITY-362).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2603|2024-08-05T14:02:06.483Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10933|2024-08-05T07:54:35.801Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- libssh
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10933</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in libssh's server-side state machine before versions 0.7.6 and 0.8.4. A malicious client could create channels without first performing authentication, resulting in unauthorized access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10933|2024-08-05T07:54:35.801Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14649|2024-08-05T09:38:13.114Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ceph-iscsi-cli
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14649</link>
      <description>It was found that ceph-isci-cli package as shipped by Red Hat Ceph Storage 2 and 3 is using python-werkzeug in debug shell mode. This is done by setting debug=True in file /usr/bin/rbd-target-api provided by ceph-isci-cli package. This allows unauthenticated attackers to access this debug shell and escalate privileges. Once an attacker has successfully connected to this debug shell they will be able to execute arbitrary commands remotely. These commands will run with the same privileges as of user executing the application which is using python-werkzeug with debug shell mode enabled. In - Red Hat Ceph Storage 2 and 3, ceph-isci-cli package runs python-werkzeug library with root level permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14649|2024-08-05T09:38:13.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14656|2024-08-05T09:38:12.828Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14656</link>
      <description>A missing address check in the callers of the show_opcodes() in the Linux kernel allows an attacker to dump the kernel memory at an arbitrary kernel address into the dmesg log.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14656|2024-08-05T09:38:12.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10921|2024-08-05T07:54:36.317Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ttembed
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10921</link>
      <description>Certain input files may trigger an integer overflow in ttembed input file processing. This overflow could potentially lead to corruption of the input file due to a lack of checking return codes of fgetc/fputc function calls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10921|2024-08-05T07:54:36.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1117|2024-08-05T03:51:48.428Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ovirt-ansible-roles
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1117</link>
      <description>ovirt-ansible-roles before version 1.0.6 has a vulnerability due to a missing no_log directive, resulting in the 'Add oVirt Provider to ManageIQ/CloudForms' playbook inadvertently disclosing admin passwords in the provisioning log. In an environment where logs are shared with other parties, this could lead to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1117|2024-08-05T03:51:48.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1061|2024-08-05T03:51:48.415Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- python
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1061</link>
      <description>python before versions 2.7.15, 3.4.9, 3.5.6rc1, 3.6.5rc1 and 3.7.0 is vulnerable to catastrophic backtracking in the difflib.IS_LINE_JUNK method.  An attacker could use this flaw to cause denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1061|2024-08-05T03:51:48.415Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1120|2024-08-05T03:51:48.863Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1120</link>
      <description>A flaw was found affecting the Linux kernel before version 4.17. By mmap()ing a FUSE-backed file onto a process's memory containing command line arguments (or environment strings), an attacker can cause utilities from psutils or procps (such as ps, w) or any other program which makes a read() call to the /proc/&lt;pid&gt;/cmdline (or /proc/&lt;pid&gt;/environ) files to block indefinitely (denial of service) or for some controlled time (as a synchronization primitive for other attacks).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1120|2024-08-05T03:51:48.863Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10875|2024-08-05T07:46:47.518Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10875</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in ansible. ansible.cfg is read from the current working directory which can be altered to make it point to a plugin or a module path under the control of an attacker, thus allowing the attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10875|2024-08-05T07:46:47.518Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14619|2024-08-05T09:29:51.723Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14619</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the crypto subsystem of the Linux kernel before version kernel-4.15-rc4. The "null skcipher" was being dropped when each af_alg_ctx was freed instead of when the aead_tfm was freed. This can cause the null skcipher to be freed while it is still in use leading to a local user being able to crash the system or possibly escalate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14619|2024-08-05T09:29:51.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-19338|2024-08-05T02:16:46.895Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- linux%20kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-19338</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the fix for CVE-2019-11135, in the Linux upstream kernel versions before 5.5 where, the way Intel CPUs handle speculative execution of instructions when a TSX Asynchronous Abort (TAA) error occurs. When a guest is running on a host CPU affected by the TAA flaw (TAA_NO=0), but is not affected by the MDS issue (MDS_NO=1), the guest was to clear the affected buffers by using a VERW instruction mechanism. But when the MDS_NO=1 bit was exported to the guests, the guests did not use the VERW mechanism to clear the affected buffers. This issue affects guests running on Cascade Lake CPUs and requires that host has 'TSX' enabled. Confidentiality of data is the highest threat associated with this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-19338|2024-08-05T02:16:46.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14637|2024-08-05T09:38:12.558Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14637</link>
      <description>The SAML broker consumer endpoint in Keycloak before version 4.6.0.Final ignores expiration conditions on SAML assertions. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability to perform a replay attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14637|2024-08-05T09:38:12.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10912|2024-08-05T07:54:36.292Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10912</link>
      <description>keycloak before version 4.0.0.final is vulnerable to a infinite loop in session replacement. A Keycloak cluster with multiple nodes could mishandle an expired session replacement and lead to an infinite loop. A malicious authenticated user could use this flaw to achieve Denial of Service on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10912|2024-08-05T07:54:36.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2595|2024-08-05T14:02:06.518Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- wildfly
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2595</link>
      <description>It was found that the log file viewer in Red Hat JBoss Enterprise Application 6 and 7 allows arbitrary file read to authenticated user via path traversal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2595|2024-08-05T14:02:06.518Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1121|2024-08-05T03:51:48.742Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- procps-ng%2C%20procps
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1121</link>
      <description>procps-ng, procps is vulnerable to a process hiding through race condition. Since the kernel's proc_pid_readdir() returns PID entries in ascending numeric order, a process occupying a high PID can use inotify events to determine when the process list is being scanned, and fork/exec to obtain a lower PID, thus avoiding enumeration. An unprivileged attacker can hide a process from procps-ng's utilities by exploiting a race condition in reading /proc/PID entries. This vulnerability affects procps and procps-ng up to version 3.3.15, newer versions might be affected also.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1121|2024-08-05T03:51:48.742Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10885|2024-08-05T07:54:34.734Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- atomic-openshift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10885</link>
      <description>In atomic-openshift before version 3.10.9 a malicious network-policy configuration can cause Openshift Routing to crash when using ovs-networkpolicy plugin. An attacker can use this flaw to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) attack on an Openshift 3.9, or 3.7 Cluster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10885|2024-08-05T07:54:34.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10906|2024-08-05T07:54:35.543Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- fuse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10906</link>
      <description>In fuse before versions 2.9.8 and 3.x before 3.2.5, fusermount is vulnerable to a restriction bypass when SELinux is active. This allows non-root users to mount a FUSE file system with the 'allow_other' mount option regardless of whether 'user_allow_other' is set in the fuse configuration. An attacker may use this flaw to mount a FUSE file system, accessible by other users, and trick them into accessing files on that file system, possibly causing Denial of Service or other unspecified effects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10906|2024-08-05T07:54:35.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14625|2024-08-05T09:29:51.690Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14625</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux Kernel where an attacker may be able to have an uncontrolled read to kernel-memory from within a vm guest. A race condition between connect() and close() function may allow an attacker using the AF_VSOCK protocol to gather a 4 byte information leak or possibly intercept or corrupt AF_VSOCK messages destined to other clients.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14625|2024-08-05T09:29:51.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14629|2024-08-05T09:29:51.868Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- samba
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14629</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability was discovered in Samba's LDAP server before versions 4.7.12, 4.8.7, and 4.9.3. A CNAME loop could lead to infinite recursion in the server. An unprivileged local attacker could create such an entry, leading to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14629|2024-08-05T09:29:51.868Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2639|2024-08-05T14:02:06.927Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- cloudforms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2639</link>
      <description>It was found that CloudForms does not verify that the server hostname matches the domain name in the certificate when using a custom CA and communicating with Red Hat Virtualization (RHEV) and OpenShift. This would allow an attacker to spoof RHEV or OpenShift systems and potentially harvest sensitive information from CloudForms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2639|2024-08-05T14:02:06.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10852|2024-08-05T07:46:47.244Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- sssd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10852</link>
      <description>The UNIX pipe which sudo uses to contact SSSD and read the available sudo rules from SSSD has too wide permissions, which means that anyone who can send a message using the same raw protocol that sudo and SSSD use can read the sudo rules available for any user. This affects versions of SSSD before 1.16.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10852|2024-08-05T07:46:47.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14842|2024-08-05T00:26:39.105Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- libnbd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14842</link>
      <description>Structured reply is a feature of the newstyle NBD protocol allowing the server to send a reply in chunks. A bounds check which was supposed to test for chunk offsets smaller than the beginning of the request did not work because of signed/unsigned confusion. If one of these chunks contains a negative offset then data under control of the server is written to memory before the read buffer supplied by the client. If the read buffer is located on the stack then this allows the stack return address from nbd_pread() to be trivially modified, allowing arbitrary code execution under the control of the server. If the buffer is located on the heap then other memory objects before the buffer can be overwritten, which again would usually lead to arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14842|2024-08-05T00:26:39.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 15:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14882|2024-08-05T00:26:39.160Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14882</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Moodle 3.7 to 3.7.3, 3.6 to 3.6.7, 3.5 to 3.5.9 and earlier where an open redirect existed in the Lesson edit page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14882|2024-08-05T00:26:39.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 12:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2637|2024-08-05T14:02:06.920Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- rhosp-director
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2637</link>
      <description>A design flaw issue was found in the Red Hat OpenStack Platform director use of TripleO to enable libvirtd based live-migration. Libvirtd is deployed by default (by director) listening on 0.0.0.0 (all interfaces) with no-authentication or encryption. Anyone able to make a TCP connection to any compute host IP address, including 127.0.0.1, other loopback interface addresses, or in some cases possibly addresses that have been exposed beyond the management interface, could use this to open a virsh session to the libvirtd instance and gain control of virtual machine instances or possibly take over the host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2637|2024-08-05T14:02:06.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10864|2024-08-05T07:46:46.942Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- redhat-certification%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10864</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled resource consumption flaw has been discovered in redhat-certification in the way documents are loaded. A remote attacker may provide an existing but invalid XML file which would be opened and never closed, possibly producing a Denial of Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10864|2024-08-05T07:46:46.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2673|2024-08-05T14:02:07.120Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- openstack-keystone
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2673</link>
      <description>An authorization-check flaw was discovered in federation configurations of the OpenStack Identity service (keystone). An authenticated federated user could request permissions to a project and unintentionally be granted all related roles including administrative roles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2673|2024-08-05T14:02:07.120Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10857|2024-08-05T07:46:47.326Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- git-annex
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10857</link>
      <description>git-annex is vulnerable to a private data exposure and exfiltration attack. It could expose the content of files located outside the git-annex repository, or content from a private web server on localhost or the LAN.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10857|2024-08-05T07:46:47.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14879|2024-08-05T00:26:39.133Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14879</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Moodle versions 3.7.x before 3.7.3, 3.6.x before 3.6.7 and 3.5.x before 3.5.9. When a cohort role assignment was removed, the associated capabilities were not being revoked (where applicable).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14879|2024-08-05T00:26:39.133Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 16:23:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10843|2024-08-05T07:46:46.958Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- source-to-image
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10843</link>
      <description>source-to-image component of Openshift Container Platform before versions atomic-openshift 3.7.53, atomic-openshift 3.9.31 is vulnerable to a privilege escalation which allows the assemble script to run as the root user in a non-privileged container. An attacker can use this flaw to open network connections, and possibly other actions, on the host which are normally only available to a root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10843|2024-08-05T07:46:46.958Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10917|2024-08-05T07:54:35.610Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- pulp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10917</link>
      <description>pulp 2.16.x and possibly older is vulnerable to an improper path parsing. A malicious user or a malicious iso feed repository can write to locations accessible to the 'apache' user. This may lead to overwrite of published content on other iso repositories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10917|2024-08-05T07:54:35.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10873|2024-08-05T07:46:47.325Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- spice%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10873</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was discovered in SPICE before version 0.14.1 where the generated code used for demarshalling messages lacked sufficient bounds checks. A malicious client or server, after authentication, could send specially crafted messages to its peer which would result in a crash or, potentially, other impacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10873|2024-08-05T07:46:47.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10878|2024-08-05T07:46:47.494Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10878</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ext4 filesystem. A local user can cause an out-of-bounds write and a denial of service or unspecified other impact is possible by mounting and operating a crafted ext4 filesystem image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10878|2024-08-05T07:46:47.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14881|2024-08-05T00:26:39.145Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14881</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in moodle 3.7 before 3.7.3, where there is blind XSS reflected in some locations where user email is displayed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14881|2024-08-05T00:26:39.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 12:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16873|2024-08-05T10:32:54.055Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- golang
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16873</link>
      <description>In Go before 1.10.6 and 1.11.x before 1.11.3, the "go get" command is vulnerable to remote code execution when executed with the -u flag and the import path of a malicious Go package, or a package that imports it directly or indirectly. Specifically, it is only vulnerable in GOPATH mode, but not in module mode (the distinction is documented at https://golang.org/cmd/go/#hdr-Module_aware_go_get). Using custom domains, it's possible to arrange things so that a Git repository is cloned to a folder named ".git" by using a vanity import path that ends with "/.git". If the Git repository root contains a "HEAD" file, a "config" file, an "objects" directory, a "refs" directory, with some work to ensure the proper ordering of operations, "go get -u" can be tricked into considering the parent directory as a repository root, and running Git commands on it. That will use the "config" file in the original Git repository root for its configuration, and if that config file contains malicious commands, they will execute on the system running "go get -u".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16873|2024-08-05T10:32:54.055Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10869|2024-08-05T07:46:47.477Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- redhat-certification
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10869</link>
      <description>redhat-certification does not properly restrict files that can be download through the /download page. A remote attacker may download any file accessible by the user running httpd.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10869|2024-08-05T07:46:47.477Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2654|2024-08-05T14:02:06.940Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- jenkins-email-ext
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2654</link>
      <description>jenkins-email-ext before version 2.57.1 is vulnerable to an Information Exposure. The Email Extension Plugins is able to send emails to a dynamically created list of users based on the changelogs, like authors of SCM changes since the last successful build. This could in some cases result in emails being sent to people who have no user account in Jenkins, and in rare cases even people who were not involved in whatever project was being built, due to some mapping based on the local-part of email addresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2654|2024-08-05T14:02:06.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10856|2024-08-05T07:46:47.230Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- podman
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10856</link>
      <description>It has been discovered that podman before version 0.6.1 does not drop capabilities when executing a container as a non-root user. This results in unnecessary privileges being granted to the container.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10856|2024-08-05T07:46:47.230Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14648|2024-08-05T09:38:12.905Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- 389-ds-base%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14648</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in 389 Directory Server. A specially crafted search query could lead to excessive CPU consumption in the do_search() function. An unauthenticated attacker could use this flaw to provoke a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14648|2024-08-05T09:38:12.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14624|2024-08-05T09:29:51.694Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- 389-ds-base
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14624</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was discovered in 389-ds-base through versions 1.3.7.10, 1.3.8.8 and 1.4.0.16. The lock controlling the error log was not correctly used when re-opening the log file in log__error_emergency(). An attacker could send a flood of modifications to a very large DN, which would cause slapd to crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14624|2024-08-05T09:29:51.694Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14880|2024-08-05T00:26:39.160Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14880</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Moodle versions 3.7 before 3.7.3, 3.6 before 3.6.7, 3.5 before 3.5.9 and earlier. OAuth 2 providers who do not verify users' email address changes require additional verification during sign-up to reduce the risk of account compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14880|2024-08-05T00:26:39.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 15:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1123|2024-08-05T03:51:48.635Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- procps-ng%2C%20procps
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1123</link>
      <description>procps-ng before version 3.3.15 is vulnerable to a denial of service in ps via mmap buffer overflow. Inbuilt protection in ps maps a guard page at the end of the overflowed buffer, ensuring that the impact of this flaw is limited to a crash (temporary denial of service).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1123|2024-08-05T03:51:48.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10903|2024-08-05T07:54:36.330Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- python-cryptography
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10903</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in python-cryptography versions between &gt;=1.9.0 and &lt;2.3. The finalize_with_tag API did not enforce a minimum tag length. If a user did not validate the input length prior to passing it to finalize_with_tag an attacker could craft an invalid payload with a shortened tag (e.g. 1 byte) such that they would have a 1 in 256 chance of passing the MAC check. GCM tag forgeries can cause key leakage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10903|2024-08-05T07:54:36.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14621|2024-08-05T09:29:51.860Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- libtirpc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14621</link>
      <description>An infinite loop vulnerability was found in libtirpc before version 1.0.2-rc2. With the port to using poll rather than select, exhaustion of file descriptors would cause the server to enter an infinite loop, consuming a large amount of CPU time and denying service to other clients until restarted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14621|2024-08-05T09:29:51.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7468|2024-08-05T16:04:11.554Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- curl
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7468</link>
      <description>In curl and libcurl 7.52.0 to and including 7.53.1, libcurl would attempt to resume a TLS session even if the client certificate had changed. That is unacceptable since a server by specification is allowed to skip the client certificate check on resume, and may instead use the old identity which was established by the previous certificate (or no certificate). libcurl supports by default the use of TLS session id/ticket to resume previous TLS sessions to speed up subsequent TLS handshakes. They are used when for any reason an existing TLS connection couldn't be kept alive to make the next handshake faster. This flaw is a regression and identical to CVE-2016-5419 reported on August 3rd 2016, but affecting a different version range.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7468|2024-08-05T16:04:11.554Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14860|2024-08-05T00:26:39.101Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- syndesis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14860</link>
      <description>It was found that the Syndesis configuration for Cross-Origin Resource Sharing was set to allow all origins. An attacker could use this lack of protection to conduct phishing attacks and further access unauthorized information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14860|2024-08-05T00:26:39.101Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 14:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10882|2024-08-05T07:54:34.712Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10882</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ext4 filesystem. A local user can cause an out-of-bound write in in fs/jbd2/transaction.c code, a denial of service, and a system crash by unmounting a crafted ext4 filesystem image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10882|2024-08-05T07:54:34.712Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2610|2024-08-05T14:02:06.521Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2610</link>
      <description>jenkins before versions 2.44, 2.32.2 is vulnerable to a persisted cross-site scripting in search suggestions due to improperly escaping users with less-than and greater-than characters in their names (SECURITY-388).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2610|2024-08-05T14:02:06.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14857|2024-08-05T00:26:39.151Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- mod_auth_openidc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14857</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in mod_auth_openidc before version 2.4.0.1. An open redirect issue exists in URLs with trailing slashes similar to CVE-2019-3877 in mod_auth_mellon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14857|2024-08-05T00:26:39.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 11:56:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1126|2024-08-05T03:51:48.860Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- procps-ng%2C%20procps
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1126</link>
      <description>procps-ng before version 3.3.15 is vulnerable to an incorrect integer size in proc/alloc.* leading to truncation/integer overflow issues. This flaw is related to CVE-2018-1124.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1126|2024-08-05T03:51:48.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14894|2024-08-05T00:26:39.132Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- cloudforms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14894</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the CloudForms management engine version 5.10 and CloudForms management version 5.11, which triggered remote code execution through NFS schedule backup. An attacker logged into the management console could use this flaw to execute arbitrary shell commands on the CloudForms server as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14894|2024-08-05T00:26:39.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 17:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2622|2024-08-05T14:02:06.918Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- openstack-mistral
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2622</link>
      <description>An accessibility flaw was found in the OpenStack Workflow (mistral) service where a service log directory was improperly made world readable. A malicious system user could exploit this flaw to access sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2622|2024-08-05T14:02:06.918Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10844|2024-08-05T07:46:46.944Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- gnutls
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10844</link>
      <description>It was found that the GnuTLS implementation of HMAC-SHA-256 was vulnerable to a Lucky thirteen style attack. Remote attackers could use this flaw to conduct distinguishing attacks and plaintext-recovery attacks via statistical analysis of timing data using crafted packets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10844|2024-08-05T07:46:46.944Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10902|2024-08-05T07:54:35.823Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10902</link>
      <description>It was found that the raw midi kernel driver does not protect against concurrent access which leads to a double realloc (double free) in snd_rawmidi_input_params() and snd_rawmidi_output_status() which are part of snd_rawmidi_ioctl() handler in rawmidi.c file. A malicious local attacker could possibly use this for privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10902|2024-08-05T07:54:35.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10855|2024-08-05T07:46:47.397Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10855</link>
      <description>Ansible 2.5 prior to 2.5.5, and 2.4 prior to 2.4.5, do not honor the no_log task flag for failed tasks. When the no_log flag has been used to protect sensitive data passed to a task from being logged, and that task does not run successfully, Ansible will expose sensitive data in log files and on the terminal of the user running Ansible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10855|2024-08-05T07:46:47.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1075|2024-08-05T03:51:48.553Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ovirt-engine
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1075</link>
      <description>ovirt-engine up to version 4.2.3 is vulnerable to an unfiltered password when choosing manual db provisioning. When engine-setup was run and one chooses to provision the database manually or connect to a remote database, the password input was logged in cleartext during the verification step. Sharing the provisioning log might inadvertently leak database passwords.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1075|2024-08-05T03:51:48.553Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10877|2024-08-05T07:46:47.469Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10877</link>
      <description>Linux kernel ext4 filesystem is vulnerable to an out-of-bound access in the ext4_ext_drop_refs() function when operating on a crafted ext4 filesystem image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10877|2024-08-05T07:46:47.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14643|2024-08-05T09:38:12.833Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- smart_proxy_dynflow
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14643</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass flaw was found in the smart_proxy_dynflow component used by Foreman. A malicious attacker can use this flaw to remotely execute arbitrary commands on machines managed by vulnerable Foreman instances, in a highly privileged context.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14643|2024-08-05T09:38:12.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2659|2024-08-05T14:02:07.018Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- dropbear
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2659</link>
      <description>It was found that dropbear before version 2013.59 with GSSAPI leaks whether given username is valid or invalid. When an invalid username is given, the GSSAPI authentication failure was incorrectly counted towards the maximum allowed number of password attempts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2659|2024-08-05T14:02:07.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 20:44:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10905|2024-08-05T07:54:36.246Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- cfme
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10905</link>
      <description>CloudForms Management Engine (cfme) is vulnerable to an improper security setting in the dRuby component of CloudForms. An attacker with access to an unprivileged local shell could use this flaw to execute commands as a high privileged user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10905|2024-08-05T07:54:36.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10916|2024-08-05T07:54:35.215Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- lftp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10916</link>
      <description>It has been discovered that lftp up to and including version 4.8.3 does not properly sanitize remote file names, leading to a loss of integrity on the local system when reverse mirroring is used. A remote attacker may trick a user to use reverse mirroring on an attacker controlled FTP server, resulting in the removal of all files in the current working directory of the victim's system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10916|2024-08-05T07:54:35.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16862|2024-08-05T10:32:54.234Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16862</link>
      <description>A security flaw was found in the Linux kernel in a way that the cleancache subsystem clears an inode after the final file truncation (removal). The new file created with the same inode may contain leftover pages from cleancache and the old file data instead of the new one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16862|2024-08-05T10:32:54.234Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1132|2024-08-05T03:51:48.839Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- opendaylight
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1132</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Opendaylight's SDNInterfaceapp (SDNI). Attackers can SQL inject the component's database (SQLite) without authenticating to the controller or SDNInterfaceapp. SDNInterface has been deprecated in OpenDayLight since it was last used in the final Carbon series release. In addition to the component not being included in OpenDayLight in newer releases, the SDNInterface component is not packaged in the opendaylight package included in RHEL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1132|2024-08-05T03:51:48.839Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2638|2024-08-05T14:02:06.903Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- infinispan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2638</link>
      <description>It was found that the REST API in Infinispan before version 9.0.0 did not properly enforce auth constraints. An attacker could use this vulnerability to read or modify data in the default cache or a known cache name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2638|2024-08-05T14:02:06.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16843|2024-08-05T10:32:54.156Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- nginx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16843</link>
      <description>nginx before versions 1.15.6 and 1.14.1 has a vulnerability in the implementation of HTTP/2 that can allow for excessive memory consumption. This issue affects nginx compiled with the ngx_http_v2_module (not compiled by default) if the 'http2' option of the 'listen' directive is used in a configuration file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16843|2024-08-05T10:32:54.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2604|2024-08-05T14:02:06.918Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2604</link>
      <description>In Jenkins before versions 2.44, 2.32.2 low privilege users were able to act on administrative monitors due to them not being consistently protected by permission checks (SECURITY-371).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2604|2024-08-05T14:02:06.918Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7467|2024-08-05T16:04:11.557Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- minicom
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7467</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow flaw was found in the way minicom before version 2.7.1 handled VT100 escape sequences. A malicious terminal device could potentially use this flaw to crash minicom, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the minicom process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7467|2024-08-05T16:04:11.557Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16841|2024-08-05T10:32:54.002Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- samba
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16841</link>
      <description>Samba from version 4.3.0 and before versions 4.7.12, 4.8.7 and 4.9.3 are vulnerable to a denial of service. When configured to accept smart-card authentication, Samba's KDC will call talloc_free() twice on the same memory if the principal in a validly signed certificate does not match the principal in the AS-REQ. This is only possible after authentication with a trusted certificate. talloc is robust against further corruption from a double-free with talloc_free() and directly calls abort(), terminating the KDC process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16841|2024-08-05T10:32:54.002Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10891|2024-08-05T07:54:34.734Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10891</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in moodle before versions 3.5.1, 3.4.4, 3.3.7, 3.1.13. When a quiz question bank is imported, it was possible for the question preview that is displayed to execute JavaScript that is written into the question bank.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10891|2024-08-05T07:54:34.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14618|2024-08-05T09:29:51.906Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- curl
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14618</link>
      <description>curl before version 7.61.1 is vulnerable to a buffer overrun in the NTLM authentication code. The internal function Curl_ntlm_core_mk_nt_hash multiplies the length of the password by two (SUM) to figure out how large temporary storage area to allocate from the heap. The length value is then subsequently used to iterate over the password and generate output into the allocated storage buffer. On systems with a 32 bit size_t, the math to calculate SUM triggers an integer overflow when the password length exceeds 2GB (2^31 bytes). This integer overflow usually causes a very small buffer to actually get allocated instead of the intended very huge one, making the use of that buffer end up in a heap buffer overflow. (This bug is almost identical to CVE-2017-8816.)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14618|2024-08-05T09:29:51.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10889|2024-08-05T07:54:34.784Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10889</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in moodle before versions 3.5.1, 3.4.4, 3.3.7. No option existed to omit logs from data privacy exports, which may contain details of other users who interacted with the requester.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10889|2024-08-05T07:54:34.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10847|2024-08-05T07:46:47.419Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- prosody
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10847</link>
      <description>prosody before versions 0.10.2, 0.9.14 is vulnerable to an Authentication Bypass. Prosody did not verify that the virtual host associated with a user session remained the same across stream restarts. A user may authenticate to XMPP host A and migrate their authenticated session to XMPP host B of the same Prosody instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10847|2024-08-05T07:46:47.419Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16879|2024-08-05T10:32:54.171Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- tower
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16879</link>
      <description>Ansible Tower before version 3.3.3 does not set a secure channel as it is using the default insecure configuration channel settings for messaging celery workers from RabbitMQ. This could lead in data leak of sensitive information such as passwords as well as denial of service attacks by deleting projects or inventory files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16879|2024-08-05T10:32:54.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14902|2024-08-05T00:26:39.142Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- samba
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14902</link>
      <description>There is an issue in all samba 4.11.x versions before 4.11.5, all samba 4.10.x versions before 4.10.12 and all samba 4.9.x versions before 4.9.18, where the removal of the right to create or modify a subtree would not automatically be taken away on all domain controllers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14902|2024-08-05T00:26:39.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7465|2024-08-05T16:04:11.524Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- jboss
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7465</link>
      <description>It was found that the JAXP implementation used in JBoss EAP 7.0 for XSLT processing is vulnerable to code injection. An attacker could use this flaw to cause remote code execution if they are able to provide XSLT content for parsing. Doing a transform in JAXP requires the use of a 'javax.xml.transform.TransformerFactory'. If the FEATURE_SECURE_PROCESSING feature is set to 'true', it mitigates this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7465|2024-08-05T16:04:11.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1046|2024-08-05T03:44:11.842Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- pdns
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1046</link>
      <description>pdns before version 4.1.2 is vulnerable to a buffer overflow in dnsreplay. In the dnsreplay tool provided with PowerDNS Authoritative, replaying a specially crafted PCAP file can trigger a stack-based buffer overflow, leading to a crash and potentially arbitrary code execution. This buffer overflow only occurs when the -ecs-stamp option of dnsreplay is used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1046|2024-08-05T03:44:11.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7519|2024-08-05T16:04:11.820Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7519</link>
      <description>In Ceph, a format string flaw was found in the way libradosstriper parses input from user. A user could crash an application or service using the libradosstriper library.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7519|2024-08-05T16:04:11.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1070|2024-08-05T03:51:47.334Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- routing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1070</link>
      <description>routing before version 3.10 is vulnerable to an improper input validation of the Openshift Routing configuration which can cause an entire shard to be brought down. A malicious user can use this vulnerability to cause a Denial of Service attack for other users of the router shard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1070|2024-08-05T03:51:47.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1116|2024-08-05T03:51:48.873Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- polkit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1116</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in polkit before version 0.116. The implementation of the polkit_backend_interactive_authority_check_authorization function in polkitd allows to test for authentication and trigger authentication of unrelated processes owned by other users. This may result in a local DoS and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1116|2024-08-05T03:51:48.873Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14651|2024-08-05T09:38:12.621Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- glusterfs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14651</link>
      <description>It was found that the fix for CVE-2018-10927, CVE-2018-10928, CVE-2018-10929, CVE-2018-10930, and CVE-2018-10926 was incomplete. A remote, authenticated attacker could use one of these flaws to execute arbitrary code, create arbitrary files, or cause denial of service on glusterfs server nodes via symlinks to relative paths.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14651|2024-08-05T09:38:12.621Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2607|2024-08-05T14:02:06.917Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2607</link>
      <description>jenkins before versions 2.44, 2.32.2 is vulnerable to a persisted cross-site scripting vulnerability in console notes (SECURITY-382). Jenkins allows plugins to annotate build logs, adding new content or changing the presentation of existing content while the build is running. Malicious Jenkins users, or users with SCM access, could configure jobs or modify build scripts such that they print serialized console notes that perform cross-site scripting attacks on Jenkins users viewing the build logs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2607|2024-08-05T14:02:06.917Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10846|2024-08-05T07:46:47.512Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- gnutls
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10846</link>
      <description>A cache-based side channel in GnuTLS implementation that leads to plain text recovery in cross-VM attack setting was found. An attacker could use a combination of "Just in Time" Prime+probe attack in combination with Lucky-13 attack to recover plain text using crafted packets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10846|2024-08-05T07:46:47.512Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7481|2024-08-05T16:04:11.540Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7481</link>
      <description>Ansible before versions 2.3.1.0 and 2.4.0.0 fails to properly mark lookup-plugin results as unsafe. If an attacker could control the results of lookup() calls, they could inject Unicode strings to be parsed by the jinja2 templating system, resulting in code execution. By default, the jinja2 templating language is now marked as 'unsafe' and is not evaluated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7481|2024-08-05T16:04:11.540Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1113|2024-08-05T03:51:48.931Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- setup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1113</link>
      <description>setup before version 2.11.4-1.fc28 in Fedora and Red Hat Enterprise Linux added /sbin/nologin and /usr/sbin/nologin to /etc/shells. This violates security assumptions made by pam_shells and some daemons which allow access based on a user's shell being listed in /etc/shells. Under some circumstances, users which had their shell changed to /sbin/nologin could still access the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1113|2024-08-05T03:51:48.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16854|2024-08-05T10:32:54.258Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16854</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in moodle versions 3.5 to 3.5.2, 3.4 to 3.4.5, 3.3 to 3.3.8, 3.1 to 3.1.14 and earlier. The login form is not protected by a token to prevent login cross-site request forgery. Fixed versions include 3.6, 3.5.3, 3.4.6, 3.3.9 and 3.1.15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16854|2024-08-05T10:32:54.258Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1072|2024-08-05T03:51:48.552Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ovirt-engine-setup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1072</link>
      <description>ovirt-engine before version ovirt 4.2.2 is vulnerable to an information exposure through log files. When engine-backup was run with one of the options "--provision*db", the database username and password were logged in cleartext. Sharing the provisioning log might inadvertently leak database passwords.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1072|2024-08-05T03:51:48.552Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16875|2024-08-05T10:32:54.282Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- golang
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16875</link>
      <description>The crypto/x509 package of Go before 1.10.6 and 1.11.x before 1.11.3 does not limit the amount of work performed for each chain verification, which might allow attackers to craft pathological inputs leading to a CPU denial of service. Go TLS servers accepting client certificates and TLS clients are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16875|2024-08-05T10:32:54.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14666|2024-08-05T09:38:13.123Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- satellite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14666</link>
      <description>An improper authorization flaw was found in the Smart Class feature of Foreman. An attacker can use it to change configuration of any host registered in Red Hat Satellite, independent of the organization the host belongs to. This flaw affects all Red Hat Satellite 6 versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14666|2024-08-05T09:38:13.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14627|2024-08-05T09:29:51.696Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- jboss%2Fwildfly
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14627</link>
      <description>The IIOP OpenJDK Subsystem in WildFly before version 14.0.0 does not honour configuration when SSL transport is required. Servers before this version that are configured with the following setting allow clients to create plaintext connections: &lt;transport-config confidentiality="required" trust-in-target="supported"/&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14627|2024-08-05T09:29:51.696Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2598|2024-08-05T14:02:06.933Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2598</link>
      <description>Jenkins before versions 2.44, 2.32.2 uses AES ECB block cipher mode without IV for encrypting secrets which makes Jenkins and the stored secrets vulnerable to unnecessary risks (SECURITY-304).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2598|2024-08-05T14:02:06.933Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14865|2024-08-05T00:26:39.094Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- grub2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14865</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the grub2-set-bootflag utility of grub2. A local attacker could run this utility under resource pressure (for example by setting RLIMIT), causing grub2 configuration files to be truncated and leaving the system unbootable on subsequent reboots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14865|2024-08-05T00:26:39.094Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 09:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10892|2024-08-05T07:54:34.913Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- docker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10892</link>
      <description>The default OCI linux spec in oci/defaults{_linux}.go in Docker/Moby from 1.11 to current does not block /proc/acpi pathnames. The flaw allows an attacker to modify host's hardware like enabling/disabling bluetooth or turning up/down keyboard brightness.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10892|2024-08-05T07:54:34.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16874|2024-08-05T10:32:54.222Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- golang
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16874</link>
      <description>In Go before 1.10.6 and 1.11.x before 1.11.3, the "go get" command is vulnerable to directory traversal when executed with the import path of a malicious Go package which contains curly braces (both '{' and '}' characters). Specifically, it is only vulnerable in GOPATH mode, but not in module mode (the distinction is documented at https://golang.org/cmd/go/#hdr-Module_aware_go_get). The attacker can cause an arbitrary filesystem write, which can lead to code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16874|2024-08-05T10:32:54.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10871|2024-08-05T07:46:47.376Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- 389-ds-base
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10871</link>
      <description>389-ds-base before versions 1.3.8.5, 1.4.0.12 is vulnerable to a Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information. By default, when the Replica and/or retroChangeLog plugins are enabled, 389-ds-base stores passwords in plaintext format in their respective changelog files. An attacker with sufficiently high privileges, such as root or Directory Manager, can query these files in order to retrieve plaintext passwords.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10871|2024-08-05T07:46:47.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1080|2024-08-05T03:51:48.562Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- pki-core
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1080</link>
      <description>Dogtag PKI, through version 10.6.1, has a vulnerability in AAclAuthz.java that, under certain configurations, causes the application of ACL allow and deny rules to be reversed. If a server is configured to process allow rules before deny rules (authz.evaluateOrder=allow,deny), then allow rules will deny access and deny rules will grant access. This may result in an escalation of privileges or have other unintended consequences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1080|2024-08-05T03:51:48.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
