<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for [UNKNOWN] -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/%5Bunknown%5D/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for [UNKNOWN] -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 14:22:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10723|2024-08-04T11:14:14.697Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- dpdk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10723</link>
      <description>A memory corruption issue was found in DPDK versions 17.05 and above. This flaw is caused by an integer truncation on the index of a payload. Under certain circumstances, the index (a UInt) is copied and truncated into a uint16, which can lead to out of bound indexing and possible memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10723|2024-08-04T11:14:14.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 18:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10706|2024-08-04T11:06:11.155Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- openshift%2Fopenshift-apiserver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10706</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in OpenShift Container Platform where OAuth tokens are not encrypted when the encryption of data at rest is enabled. This flaw allows an attacker with access to a backup to obtain OAuth tokens and then use them to log into the cluster as any user who logged into the cluster via the WebUI or via the command line in the last 24 hours. Once the backup is older than 24 hours the OAuth tokens are no longer valid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10706|2024-08-04T11:06:11.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 13:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1728|2024-08-04T06:46:30.949Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1728</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in all versions of Keycloak where, the pages on the Admin Console area of the application are completely missing general HTTP security headers in HTTP-responses. This does not directly lead to a security issue, yet it might aid attackers in their efforts to exploit other problems. The flaws unnecessarily make the servers more prone to Clickjacking, channel downgrade attacks and other similar client-based attack vectors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1728|2024-08-04T06:46:30.949Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 13:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10725|2024-08-04T11:14:14.236Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- dpdk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10725</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in DPDK version 19.11 and above that allows a malicious guest to cause a segmentation fault of the vhost-user backend application running on the host, which could result in a loss of connectivity for the other guests running on that host. This is caused by a missing validity check of the descriptor address in the function `virtio_dev_rx_batch_packed()`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10725|2024-08-04T11:14:14.236Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 13:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1727|2024-08-04T06:46:30.851Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1727</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Keycloak before 9.0.2, where every Authorization URL that points to an IDP server lacks proper input validation as it allows a wide range of characters. This flaw allows a malicious to craft deep links that introduce further attack scenarios on affected clients.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1727|2024-08-04T06:46:30.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 17:46:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10738|2024-08-04T11:14:14.722Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10738</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Moodle versions 3.8 before 3.8.3, 3.7 before 3.7.6, 3.6 before 3.6.10, 3.5 before 3.5.12 and earlier unsupported versions. It was possible to create a SCORM package in such a way that when added to a course, it could be interacted with via web services in order to achieve remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10738|2024-08-04T11:14:14.722Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 15:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1700|2024-08-04T06:46:30.305Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1700</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the way the Ceph RGW Beast front-end handles unexpected disconnects. An authenticated attacker can abuse this flaw by making multiple disconnect attempts resulting in a permanent leak of a socket connection by radosgw. This flaw could lead to a denial of service condition by pile up of CLOSE_WAIT sockets, eventually leading to the exhaustion of available resources, preventing legitimate users from connecting to the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1700|2024-08-04T06:46:30.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1696|2024-08-04T06:46:30.878Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- pki-core
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1696</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the all pki-core 10.x.x versions, where Token Processing Service (TPS) where it did not properly sanitize Profile IDs, enabling a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability when the profile ID is printed. An attacker with sufficient permissions could trick an authenticated victim into executing a specially crafted Javascript code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1696|2024-08-04T06:46:30.878Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 13:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10736|2024-08-04T11:14:14.781Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10736</link>
      <description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was found in Ceph versions 15.2.0 before 15.2.2, where the ceph-mon and ceph-mgr daemons do not properly restrict access, resulting in gaining access to unauthorized resources. This flaw allows an authenticated client to modify the configuration and possibly conduct further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10736|2024-08-04T11:14:14.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 17:49:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1760|2024-08-04T06:46:30.894Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1760</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Ceph Object Gateway, where it supports request sent by an anonymous user in Amazon S3. This flaw could lead to potential XSS attacks due to the lack of proper neutralization of untrusted input.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1760|2024-08-04T06:46:30.894Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10773|2024-08-04T11:14:14.957Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10773</link>
      <description>A stack information leak flaw was found in s390/s390x in the Linux kernel’s memory manager functionality, where it incorrectly writes to the /proc/sys/vm/cmm_timeout file. This flaw allows a local user to see the kernel data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10773|2024-08-04T11:14:14.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 16:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10722|2024-08-04T11:14:14.909Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- dpdk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10722</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in DPDK versions 18.05 and above. A missing check for an integer overflow in vhost_user_set_log_base() could result in a smaller memory map than requested, possibly allowing memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10722|2024-08-04T11:14:14.909Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 18:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1712|2024-08-04T06:46:30.849Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- systemd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1712</link>
      <description>A heap use-after-free vulnerability was found in systemd before version v245-rc1, where asynchronous Polkit queries are performed while handling dbus messages. A local unprivileged attacker can abuse this flaw to crash systemd services or potentially execute code and elevate their privileges, by sending specially crafted dbus messages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1712|2024-08-04T06:46:30.849Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 16:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10740|2024-08-04T11:14:14.944Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- wildfly
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10740</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Wildfly in versions before 20.0.0.Final, where a remote deserialization attack is possible in the Enterprise Application Beans(EJB) due to lack of validation/filtering capabilities in wildfly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10740|2024-08-04T11:14:14.944Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 17:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1707|2024-08-04T06:46:30.234Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- openshift%2Fpostgresql-apb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1707</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in all openshift/postgresql-apb 4.x.x versions prior to 4.3.0, where an insecure modification vulnerability in the /etc/passwd file was found in the container openshift/postgresql-apb. An attacker with access to the container could use this flaw to modify /etc/passwd and escalate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1707|2024-08-04T06:46:30.234Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10724|2024-08-04T11:14:15.210Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- dpdk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10724</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in DPDK versions 18.11 and above. The vhost-crypto library code is missing validations for user-supplied values, potentially allowing an information leak through an out-of-bounds memory read.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10724|2024-08-04T11:14:15.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 17:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10726|2024-08-04T11:14:15.435Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- dpdk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10726</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in DPDK versions 19.11 and above. A malicious container that has direct access to the vhost-user socket can keep sending VHOST_USER_GET_INFLIGHT_FD messages, causing a resource leak (file descriptors and virtual memory), which may result in a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10726|2024-08-04T11:14:15.435Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 13:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1709|2024-08-04T06:46:30.193Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- openshift%2Fmediawiki
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1709</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in all openshift/mediawiki 4.x.x versions prior to 4.3.0, where an insecure modification vulnerability in the /etc/passwd file was found in the openshift/mediawiki. An attacker with access to the container could use this flaw to modify /etc/passwd and escalate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1709|2024-08-04T06:46:30.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
