<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for [UNKNOWN] -- ceph</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/%5Bunknown%5D/ceph.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for [UNKNOWN] -- ceph</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1700|2024-08-04T06:46:30.305Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1700</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the way the Ceph RGW Beast front-end handles unexpected disconnects. An authenticated attacker can abuse this flaw by making multiple disconnect attempts resulting in a permanent leak of a socket connection by radosgw. This flaw could lead to a denial of service condition by pile up of CLOSE_WAIT sockets, eventually leading to the exhaustion of available resources, preventing legitimate users from connecting to the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1700|2024-08-04T06:46:30.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10736|2024-08-04T11:14:14.781Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10736</link>
      <description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was found in Ceph versions 15.2.0 before 15.2.2, where the ceph-mon and ceph-mgr daemons do not properly restrict access, resulting in gaining access to unauthorized resources. This flaw allows an authenticated client to modify the configuration and possibly conduct further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10736|2024-08-04T11:14:14.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 17:49:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1760|2024-08-04T06:46:30.894Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1760</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Ceph Object Gateway, where it supports request sent by an anonymous user in Amazon S3. This flaw could lead to potential XSS attacks due to the lack of proper neutralization of untrusted input.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1760|2024-08-04T06:46:30.894Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3821|2024-08-04T19:19:18.564Z -- %5Bunknown%5D -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3821</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the way civetweb frontend was handling requests for ceph RGW server with SSL enabled. An unauthenticated attacker could create multiple connections to ceph RADOS gateway to exhaust file descriptors for ceph-radosgw service resulting in a remote denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3821|2024-08-04T19:19:18.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
