<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cobham plc -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cobham%20plc/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cobham plc -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-9530|2024-08-04T21:54:44.562Z -- cobham%20plc -- explorer%20710
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-9530</link>
      <description>The web root directory of the Cobham EXPLORER 710, firmware version 1.07, has no access restrictions on downloading and reading all files. This could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker connected to the device to access and download any file found in the web root directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-9530|2024-08-04T21:54:44.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-9531|2024-08-04T21:54:44.584Z -- cobham%20plc -- explorer%20710
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-9531</link>
      <description>The web application portal of the Cobham EXPLORER 710, firmware version 1.07, allows unauthenticated access to port 5454. This could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to connect to this port via Telnet and execute 86 Attention (AT) commands, including some that provide unauthenticated, shell-like access to the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-9531|2024-08-04T21:54:44.584Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-9534|2024-08-04T21:54:44.413Z -- cobham%20plc -- explorer%20710
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-9534</link>
      <description>The Cobham EXPLORER 710, firmware version 1.07, does not validate its firmware image. Development scripts left in the firmware can be used to upload a custom firmware image that the device runs. This could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker to upload their own firmware that could be used to intercept or modify traffic, spoof or intercept GPS traffic, exfiltrate private data, hide a backdoor, or cause a denial-of-service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-9534|2024-08-04T21:54:44.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-9529|2024-08-04T21:54:44.511Z -- cobham%20plc -- explorer%20710
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-9529</link>
      <description>The web application portal of the Cobham EXPLORER 710, firmware version 1.07, has no authentication by default. This could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker connected to the device to access the portal and to make any change to the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-9529|2024-08-04T21:54:44.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-9532|2024-08-04T21:54:44.525Z -- cobham%20plc -- explorer%20710
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-9532</link>
      <description>The web application portal of the Cobham EXPLORER 710, firmware version 1.07, sends the login password in cleartext. This could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker to intercept the password and gain access to the portal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-9532|2024-08-04T21:54:44.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-9533|2024-08-04T21:54:44.145Z -- cobham%20plc -- explorer%20710
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-9533</link>
      <description>The root password of the Cobham EXPLORER 710 is the same for all versions of firmware up to and including v1.08. This could allow an attacker to reverse-engineer the password from available versions to gain authenticated access to the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-9533|2024-08-04T21:54:44.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
