<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Zabbix -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/zabbix/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Zabbix -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:19:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24918|2024-08-03T04:29:01.739Z -- zabbix -- frontend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24918</link>
      <description>An authenticated user can create a link with reflected Javascript code inside it for items’ page and send it to other users. The payload can be executed only with a known CSRF token value of the victim, which is changed periodically and is difficult to predict. Malicious code has access to all the same objects as the rest of the web page and can make arbitrary modifications to the contents of the page being displayed to a victim during social engineering attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24918|2024-08-03T04:29:01.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24919|2024-08-03T04:29:01.858Z -- zabbix -- frontend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24919</link>
      <description>An authenticated user can create a link with reflected Javascript code inside it for graphs’ page and send it to other users. The payload can be executed only with a known CSRF token value of the victim, which is changed periodically and is difficult to predict. Malicious code has access to all the same objects as the rest of the web page and can make arbitrary modifications to the contents of the page being displayed to a victim during social engineering attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24919|2024-08-03T04:29:01.858Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23132|2024-08-03T03:36:20.009Z -- zabbix -- proxy%2C%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23132</link>
      <description>During Zabbix installation from RPM, DAC_OVERRIDE SELinux capability is in use to access PID files in [/var/run/zabbix] folder. In this case, Zabbix Proxy or Server processes can bypass file read, write and execute permissions check on the file system level</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23132|2024-08-03T03:36:20.009Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-46768|2024-08-03T14:39:38.708Z -- zabbix -- web%20service%20report%20generation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46768</link>
      <description>Arbitrary file read vulnerability exists in Zabbix Web Service Report Generation, which listens on the port 10053. The service does not have proper validation for URL parameters before reading the files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-46768|2024-08-03T14:39:38.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43515|2024-08-03T13:32:59.684Z -- zabbix -- frontend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43515</link>
      <description>Zabbix Frontend provides a feature that allows admins to maintain the installation and ensure that only certain IP addresses can access it. In this way, any user will not be able to access the Zabbix Frontend while it is being maintained and possible sensitive data will be prevented from being disclosed. An attacker can bypass this protection and access the instance using IP address not listed in the defined range.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43515|2024-08-03T13:32:59.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43516|2024-08-03T13:32:59.496Z -- zabbix -- zabbix%20agent%20%28msi%20packages%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43516</link>
      <description>A Firewall Rule which allows all incoming TCP connections to all programs from any source and to all ports is created in Windows Firewall after Zabbix agent installation (MSI)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43516|2024-08-03T13:32:59.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24349|2024-08-03T04:07:02.563Z -- zabbix -- frontend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24349</link>
      <description>An authenticated user can create a link with reflected XSS payload for actions’ pages, and send it to other users. Malicious code has access to all the same objects as the rest of the web page and can make arbitrary modifications to the contents of the page being displayed to a victim. This attack can be implemented with the help of social engineering and expiration of a number of factors - an attacker should have authorized access to the Zabbix Frontend and allowed network connection between a malicious server and victim’s computer, understand attacked infrastructure, be recognized by the victim as a trustee and use trusted communication channel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24349|2024-08-03T04:07:02.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40626|2024-08-03T12:21:46.555Z -- zabbix -- frontend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40626</link>
      <description>An unauthenticated user can create a link with reflected Javascript code inside the backurl parameter and send it to other authenticated users in order to create a fake account with predefined login, password and role in Zabbix Frontend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40626|2024-08-03T12:21:46.555Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24917|2024-08-03T04:29:01.621Z -- zabbix -- frontend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24917</link>
      <description>An authenticated user can create a link with reflected Javascript code inside it for services’ page and send it to other users. The payload can be executed only with a known CSRF token value of the victim, which is changed periodically and is difficult to predict. Malicious code has access to all the same objects as the rest of the web page and can make arbitrary modifications to the contents of the page being displayed to a victim during social engineering attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24917|2024-08-03T04:29:01.621Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23133|2024-08-03T03:36:19.878Z -- zabbix -- frontend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23133</link>
      <description>An authenticated user can create a hosts group from the configuration with XSS payload, which will be available for other users. When XSS is stored by an authenticated malicious actor and other users try to search for groups during new host creation, the XSS payload will fire and the actor can steal session cookies and perform session hijacking to impersonate users or take over their accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23133|2024-08-03T03:36:19.878Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35230|2024-08-03T09:29:17.473Z -- zabbix -- frontend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35230</link>
      <description>An authenticated user can create a link with reflected Javascript code inside it for the graphs page and send it to other users. The payload can be executed only with a known CSRF token value of the victim, which is changed periodically and is difficult to predict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35230|2024-08-03T09:29:17.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35229|2024-08-03T09:29:17.467Z -- zabbix -- frontend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35229</link>
      <description>An authenticated user can create a link with reflected Javascript code inside it for the discovery page and send it to other users. The payload can be executed only with a known CSRF token value of the victim, which is changed periodically and is difficult to predict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35229|2024-08-03T09:29:17.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23134|2024-08-03T03:36:20.017Z -- zabbix -- frontend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23134</link>
      <description>After the initial setup process, some steps of setup.php file are reachable not only by super-administrators, but by unauthenticated users as well. Malicious actor can pass step checks and potentially change the configuration of Zabbix Frontend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23134|2024-08-03T03:36:20.017Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23131|2024-08-03T03:36:20.024Z -- zabbix -- frontend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23131</link>
      <description>In the case of instances where the SAML SSO authentication is enabled (non-default), session data can be modified by a malicious actor, because a user login stored in the session was not verified. Malicious unauthenticated actor may exploit this issue to escalate privileges and gain admin access to Zabbix Frontend. To perform the attack, SAML authentication is required to be enabled and the actor has to know the username of Zabbix user (or use the guest account, which is disabled by default).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23131|2024-08-03T03:36:20.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22120|2024-06-04T17:52:44.718Z -- zabbix -- zabbix</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22120</link>
      <description>Zabbix server can perform command execution for configured scripts. After command is executed, audit entry is added to "Audit Log". Due to "clientip" field is not sanitized, it is possible to injection SQL into "clientip" and exploit time based blind SQL injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22120|2024-06-04T17:52:44.718Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 09:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22119|2024-02-09T08:26:20.006Z -- zabbix -- zabbix</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22119</link>
      <description>The cause of vulnerability is improper validation of form input field “Name” on Graph page in Items section.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22119|2024-02-09T08:26:20.006Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 08:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22120|2024-08-01T22:35:34.820Z -- zabbix -- zabbix</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22120</link>
      <description>Zabbix server can perform command execution for configured scripts. After command is executed, audit entry is added to "Audit Log". Due to "clientip" field is not sanitized, it is possible to injection SQL into "clientip" and exploit time based blind SQL injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22120|2024-08-01T22:35:34.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 09:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22119|2024-08-01T22:35:34.822Z -- zabbix -- zabbix</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22119</link>
      <description>The cause of vulnerability is improper validation of form input field “Name” on Graph page in Items section.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22119|2024-08-01T22:35:34.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 08:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
