<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Zabbix -- Frontend</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/zabbix/frontend.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Zabbix -- Frontend</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:23:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23131|2024-09-16T16:52:43.145Z -- zabbix -- frontend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23131</link>
      <description>In the case of instances where the SAML SSO authentication is enabled (non-default), session data can be modified by a malicious actor, because a user login stored in the session was not verified. Malicious unauthenticated actor may exploit this issue to escalate privileges and gain admin access to Zabbix Frontend. To perform the attack, SAML authentication is required to be enabled and the actor has to know the username of Zabbix user (or use the guest account, which is disabled by default).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23131|2024-09-16T16:52:43.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 15:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24918|2024-09-16T18:44:15.093Z -- zabbix -- frontend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24918</link>
      <description>An authenticated user can create a link with reflected Javascript code inside it for items’ page and send it to other users. The payload can be executed only with a known CSRF token value of the victim, which is changed periodically and is difficult to predict. Malicious code has access to all the same objects as the rest of the web page and can make arbitrary modifications to the contents of the page being displayed to a victim during social engineering attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24918|2024-09-16T18:44:15.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 19:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40626|2024-09-16T19:19:37.577Z -- zabbix -- frontend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40626</link>
      <description>An unauthenticated user can create a link with reflected Javascript code inside the backurl parameter and send it to other authenticated users in order to create a fake account with predefined login, password and role in Zabbix Frontend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40626|2024-09-16T19:19:37.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 06:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24349|2024-09-16T18:45:12.504Z -- zabbix -- frontend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24349</link>
      <description>An authenticated user can create a link with reflected XSS payload for actions’ pages, and send it to other users. Malicious code has access to all the same objects as the rest of the web page and can make arbitrary modifications to the contents of the page being displayed to a victim. This attack can be implemented with the help of social engineering and expiration of a number of factors - an attacker should have authorized access to the Zabbix Frontend and allowed network connection between a malicious server and victim’s computer, understand attacked infrastructure, be recognized by the victim as a trustee and use trusted communication channel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24349|2024-09-16T18:45:12.504Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 19:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43515|2024-09-16T17:54:03.501Z -- zabbix -- frontend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43515</link>
      <description>Zabbix Frontend provides a feature that allows admins to maintain the installation and ensure that only certain IP addresses can access it. In this way, any user will not be able to access the Zabbix Frontend while it is being maintained and possible sensitive data will be prevented from being disclosed. An attacker can bypass this protection and access the instance using IP address not listed in the defined range.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43515|2024-09-16T17:54:03.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 01:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
