<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Rocket Software -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/rocket%20software/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Rocket Software -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:22:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28502|2024-08-02T13:43:22.500Z -- rocket%20software -- unidata
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28502</link>
      <description>Rocket Software UniData versions prior to 8.2.4 build 3003 and UniVerse versions prior to 11.3.5 build 1001 or 12.2.1 build 2002 suffer from a stack-based buffer overflow in the "udadmin" service that can lead to remote code execution as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28502|2024-08-02T13:43:22.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 20:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28501|2024-08-02T12:38:25.404Z -- rocket%20software -- unidata
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28501</link>
      <description>Rocket Software UniData versions prior to 8.2.4 build 3003 and UniVerse versions prior to 11.3.5 build 1001 or 12.2.1 build 2002 suffer from a heap-based buffer overflow in the unirpcd daemon that, if successfully exploited, can lead to remote code execution as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28501|2024-08-02T12:38:25.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 19:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28503|2024-08-02T13:43:22.599Z -- rocket%20software -- unidata
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28503</link>
      <description>Rocket Software UniData versions prior to 8.2.4 build 3003 and UniVerse versions prior to 11.3.5 build 1001 or 12.2.1 build 2002 suffer from an authentication bypass vulnerability, where a special username with a deterministic password can be leveraged to bypass authentication checks and execute OS commands as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28503|2024-08-02T13:43:22.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 20:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28506|2024-08-02T13:43:22.423Z -- rocket%20software -- unidata
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28506</link>
      <description>Rocket Software UniData versions prior to 8.2.4 build 3003 and UniVerse versions prior to 11.3.5 build 1001 or 12.2.1 build 2002 suffer from a stack-based buffer overflow, where a string is copied into a buffer using a memcpy-like function and a user-provided length. This requires a valid login to exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28506|2024-08-02T13:43:22.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 20:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28509|2024-08-02T13:43:22.434Z -- rocket%20software -- unidata
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28509</link>
      <description>Rocket Software UniData versions prior to 8.2.4 build 3003 and UniVerse versions prior to 11.3.5 build 1001 or 12.2.1 build 2002 use weak encryption for packet-level security and passwords transferred on the wire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28509|2024-08-02T13:43:22.434Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 20:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28508|2024-08-02T13:43:22.463Z -- rocket%20software -- unidata
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28508</link>
      <description>Rocket Software UniData versions prior to 8.2.4 build 3003 and UniVerse versions prior to 11.3.5 build 1001 or 12.2.1 build 2002 suffer from a heap-based overflow vulnerability, where certain input can corrupt the heap and crash the forked process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28508|2024-08-02T13:43:22.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 20:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28504|2024-08-02T13:43:22.470Z -- rocket%20software -- unidata
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28504</link>
      <description>Rocket Software UniData versions prior to 8.2.4 build 3003 and UniVerse versions prior to 11.3.5 build 1001 or 12.2.1 build 2002 suffer from a stack-based buffer overflow that can lead to remote code execution as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28504|2024-08-02T13:43:22.470Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 20:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28505|2024-08-02T13:43:22.519Z -- rocket%20software -- unidata
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28505</link>
      <description>Rocket Software UniData versions prior to 8.2.4 build 3003 and UniVerse versions prior to 11.3.5 build 1001 or 12.2.1 build 2002 suffer from a buffer overflow in an API function, where a string is copied into a caller-provided buffer without checking the length. This requires a valid login to exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28505|2024-08-02T13:43:22.519Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 20:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28507|2024-08-02T13:43:22.295Z -- rocket%20software -- unidata
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28507</link>
      <description>Rocket Software UniData versions prior to 8.2.4 build 3003 and UniVerse versions prior to 11.3.5 build 1001 or 12.2.1 build 2002 suffer from a memory-exhaustion issue, where a decompression routine will allocate increasing amounts of memory until all system memory is exhausted and the forked process crashes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28507|2024-08-02T13:43:22.295Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 20:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
