<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for spinnaker -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/spinnaker/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for spinnaker -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 17:22:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43832|2024-08-04T04:10:15.747Z -- spinnaker -- spinnaker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43832</link>
      <description>Spinnaker is an open source, multi-cloud continuous delivery platform. Spinnaker has improper permissions allowing pipeline creation &amp; execution. This lets an arbitrary user with access to the gate endpoint to create a pipeline and execute it without authentication. If users haven't setup Role-based access control (RBAC) with-in spinnaker, this enables remote execution and access to deploy almost any resources on any account. Patches are available on the latest releases of the supported branches and users are advised to upgrade as soon as possible. Users unable to upgrade should enable RBAC on ALL accounts and applications. This mitigates the ability of a pipeline to affect any accounts. Block application access unless permission are enabled. Users should make sure ALL application creation is restricted via appropriate wildcards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43832|2024-08-04T04:10:15.747Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 19:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39143|2024-08-04T01:58:18.142Z -- spinnaker -- spinnaker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39143</link>
      <description>Spinnaker is an open source, multi-cloud continuous delivery platform. A path traversal vulnerability was discovered in uses of TAR files by AppEngine for deployments. This uses a utility to extract files locally for deployment without validating the paths in that deployment don't override system files. This would allow an attacker to override files on the container, POTENTIALLY introducing a MITM type attack vector by replacing libraries or injecting wrapper files. Users are advised to update as soon as possible. For users unable to update disable Google AppEngine deployments and/or disable artifacts that provide TARs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39143|2024-08-04T01:58:18.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 17:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
