<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for GitLab -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/gitlab/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for GitLab -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 04:24:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39930|2024-08-04T02:20:34.134Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39930</link>
      <description>Missing authorization in GitLab EE versions between 12.4 and 14.3.6, between 14.4.0 and 14.4.4, and between 14.5.0 and 14.5.2 allowed an attacker to access a user's custom project and group templates</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39930|2024-08-04T02:20:34.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39885|2024-08-04T02:20:33.578Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39885</link>
      <description>A Stored XSS in merge request creation page in all versions of Gitlab EE starting from 13.7 before 14.1.7, all versions starting from 14.2 before 14.2.5, and all versions starting from 14.3 before 14.3.1 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code on the victim's behalf via malicious approval rule names</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39885|2024-08-04T02:20:33.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 16:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39871|2024-08-04T02:20:33.665Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39871</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 13.0, an instance that has the setting to disable Bitbucket Server import enabled is bypassed by an attacker making a crafted API call.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39871|2024-08-04T02:20:33.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 16:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39880|2024-08-04T02:20:33.608Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39880</link>
      <description>A Denial Of Service vulnerability in the apollo_upload_server Ruby gem in GitLab CE/EE all versions starting from 11.9 before 14.0.9, all versions starting from 14.1 before 14.1.4, and all versions starting from 14.2 before 14.2.2 allows an attacker to deny access to all users via specially crafted requests to the apollo_upload_server middleware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39880|2024-08-04T02:20:33.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 14:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39894|2024-08-04T02:20:33.670Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39894</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 8.0, a DNS rebinding vulnerability exists in Fogbugz importer which may be used by attackers to exploit Server Side Request Forgery attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39894|2024-08-04T02:20:33.670Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 12:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39916|2024-08-04T02:20:33.776Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39916</link>
      <description>Lack of an access control check in the External Status Check feature allowed any authenticated user to retrieve the configuration of any External Status Check in GitLab EE starting from 14.1 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39916|2024-08-04T02:20:33.776Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39947|2024-08-04T02:20:34.198Z -- gitlab -- gitlab%20runner
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39947</link>
      <description>In specific circumstances, trace file buffers in GitLab Runner versions up to 14.3.4, 14.4 to 14.4.2, and 14.5 to 14.5.2 would re-use the file descriptor 0 for multiple traces and mix the output of several jobs</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39947|2024-08-04T02:20:34.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 16:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39881|2024-08-04T02:20:33.652Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39881</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 7.7, the application may let a malicious user create an OAuth client application with arbitrary scope names which may allow the malicious user to trick unsuspecting users to authorize the malicious client application using the spoofed scope name and description.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39881|2024-08-04T02:20:33.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 13:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39918|2024-08-04T02:20:34.144Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39918</link>
      <description>Incorrect Authorization in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 11.1 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2, allows a user to add comments to a vulnerability which cannot be accessed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39918|2024-08-04T02:20:34.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39902|2024-08-04T02:20:33.778Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39902</link>
      <description>Incorrect Authorization in GitLab CE/EE 13.4 or above allows a user with guest membership in a project to modify the severity of an incident.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39902|2024-08-04T02:20:33.778Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 22:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39945|2024-08-04T02:20:34.109Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39945</link>
      <description>Improper access control in the GitLab CE/EE API affecting all versions starting from 9.4 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2, allows an author of a Merge Request to approve the Merge Request even after having their project access revoked</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39945|2024-08-04T02:20:34.109Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:47:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39942|2024-08-04T02:20:34.141Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39942</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2, allows low-privileged users to bypass file size limits in the NPM package repository to potentially cause denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39942|2024-08-04T02:20:34.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 16:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39917|2024-08-04T02:20:34.188Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39917</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.9 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2. A regular expression related to quick actions features was susceptible to catastrophic backtracking that could cause a DOS attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39917|2024-08-04T02:20:34.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:47:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39906|2024-08-04T02:20:33.690Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39906</link>
      <description>Improper validation of ipynb files in GitLab CE/EE version 13.5 and above allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code on the victim's behalf.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39906|2024-08-04T02:20:33.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 23:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39869|2024-08-04T02:20:33.663Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39869</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 8.9, project exports may expose trigger tokens configured on that project.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39869|2024-08-04T02:20:33.663Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 12:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39868|2024-08-04T02:20:33.614Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39868</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 8.12, an authenticated low-privileged malicious user may create a project with unlimited repository size by modifying values in a project export.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39868|2024-08-04T02:20:33.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 16:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39911|2024-08-04T02:20:33.804Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39911</link>
      <description>An improper access control flaw in all versions of GitLab CE/EE starting from 13.9 before 14.2.6, all versions starting from 14.3 before 14.3.4, and all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.1 exposes private email address of Issue and Merge Requests assignee to Webhook data consumers</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39911|2024-08-04T02:20:33.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 23:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39933|2024-08-04T02:20:34.065Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39933</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.10 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2. A regular expression used for handling user input (notes, comments, etc) was susceptible to catastrophic backtracking that could cause a DOS attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39933|2024-08-04T02:20:34.065Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:47:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39899|2024-08-04T02:20:33.678Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39899</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE, an attacker with physical access to a user’s machine may brute force the user’s password via the change password function. There is a rate limit in place, but the attack may still be conducted by stealing the session id from the physical compromise of the account and splitting the attack over several IP addresses and passing in the compromised session value from these various locations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39899|2024-08-04T02:20:33.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 16:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39936|2024-08-04T02:20:34.197Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39936</link>
      <description>Improper access control in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 10.7 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2, allows an attacker in possession of a deploy token to access a project's disabled wiki.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39936|2024-08-04T02:20:34.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39872|2024-08-04T02:20:33.624Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39872</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 14.1, an improper access control vulnerability allows users with expired password to still access GitLab through git and API through access tokens acquired before password expiration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39872|2024-08-04T02:20:33.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 12:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39887|2024-08-04T02:20:33.689Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39887</link>
      <description>A stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in the GitLab Flavored Markdown in GitLab CE/EE version 8.4 and above allowed an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code on the victim's behalf.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39887|2024-08-04T02:20:33.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 11:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39909|2024-08-04T02:20:33.725Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39909</link>
      <description>Lack of email address ownership verification in the CODEOWNERS feature in all versions of GitLab EE starting from 11.3 before 14.2.6, all versions starting from 14.3 before 14.3.4, and all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.1 allows an attacker to bypass CODEOWNERS Merge Request approval requirement under rare circumstances</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39909|2024-08-04T02:20:33.725Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 23:03:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39907|2024-08-04T02:20:33.681Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39907</link>
      <description>A potential DOS vulnerability was discovered in GitLab CE/EE starting with version 13.7. The stripping of EXIF data from certain images resulted in high CPU usage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39907|2024-08-04T02:20:33.681Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 23:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39927|2024-08-04T02:20:34.234Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39927</link>
      <description>Server side request forgery protections in GitLab CE/EE versions between 8.4 and 14.4.4, between 14.5.0 and 14.5.2, and between 14.6.0 and 14.6.1 would fail to protect against attacks sending requests to localhost on port 80 or 443 if GitLab was configured to run on a port other than 80 or 443</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39927|2024-08-04T02:20:34.234Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 16:51:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39900|2024-08-04T02:20:33.699Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39900</link>
      <description>Information disclosure from SendEntry in GitLab starting with 10.8 allowed exposure of full URL of artifacts stored in object-storage with a temporary availability via Rails logs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39900|2024-08-04T02:20:33.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 16:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39893|2024-08-04T02:20:33.763Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39893</link>
      <description>A potential DOS vulnerability was discovered in GitLab starting with version 9.1 that allowed parsing files without authorisation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39893|2024-08-04T02:20:33.763Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 12:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39938|2024-08-04T02:20:34.129Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39938</link>
      <description>A vulnerable regular expression pattern in GitLab CE/EE since version 8.15 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2, allows an attacker to cause uncontrolled resource consumption leading to Denial of Service via specially crafted deploy Slash commands</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39938|2024-08-04T02:20:34.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39910|2024-08-04T02:20:33.691Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39910</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.6 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2. GitLab was vulnerable to HTML Injection through the Swagger UI feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39910|2024-08-04T02:20:33.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39903|2024-08-04T02:20:33.686Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39903</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 13.0, a privileged user, through an API call, can change the visibility level of a group or a project to a restricted option even after the instance administrator sets that visibility option as restricted in settings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39903|2024-08-04T02:20:33.686Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 22:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39875|2024-08-04T02:20:33.568Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39875</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 13.6, it is possible to see pending invitations of any public group or public project by visiting an API endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39875|2024-08-04T02:20:33.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 12:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39882|2024-08-04T02:20:33.633Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39882</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE, provided a user ID, anonymous users can use a few endpoints to retrieve information about any GitLab user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39882|2024-08-04T02:20:33.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 12:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39883|2024-08-04T02:20:33.672Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39883</link>
      <description>Improper authorization checks in all versions of GitLab EE starting from 13.11 before 14.1.7, all versions starting from 14.2 before 14.2.5, and all versions starting from 14.3 before 14.3.1 allows subgroup members to see epics from all parent subgroups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39883|2024-08-04T02:20:33.672Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 16:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39892|2024-08-04T02:20:33.593Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39892</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 12.0, a lower privileged user can import users from projects that they don't have a maintainer role on and disclose email addresses of those users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39892|2024-08-04T02:20:33.593Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 16:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39890|2024-08-04T02:20:33.754Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39890</link>
      <description>It was possible to bypass 2FA for LDAP users and access some specific pages with Basic Authentication in GitLab 14.1.1 and above.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39890|2024-08-04T02:20:33.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 17:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39884|2024-08-04T02:20:33.652Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39884</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab EE since version 8.13, an endpoint discloses names of private groups that have access to a project to low privileged users that are part of that project.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39884|2024-08-04T02:20:33.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 12:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39889|2024-08-04T02:20:33.622Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39889</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab EE since version 14.1, due to an insecure direct object reference vulnerability, an endpoint may reveal the protected branch name to a malicious user who makes a crafted API call with the ID of the protected branch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39889|2024-08-04T02:20:33.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 13:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39897|2024-08-04T02:20:33.759Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39897</link>
      <description>Improper access control in GitLab CE/EE version 10.5 and above allowed subgroup members with inherited access to a project from a parent group to still have access even after the subgroup is transferred</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39897|2024-08-04T02:20:33.759Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 23:07:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39941|2024-08-04T02:20:34.131Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39941</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE versions 12.0 to 14.3.6, 14.4 to 14.4.4, and 14.5 to 14.5.2 allowed non-project members to see the default branch name for projects that restrict access to the repository to project members</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39941|2024-08-04T02:20:34.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39939|2024-08-04T02:20:34.025Z -- gitlab -- gitlab%20runner
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39939</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in GitLab Runner affecting all versions starting from 13.7 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2, allows an attacker triggering a job with a specially crafted docker image to exhaust resources on runner manager</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39939|2024-08-04T02:20:34.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39896|2024-08-04T02:20:33.774Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39896</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 8.0, when an admin uses the impersonate feature twice and stops impersonating, the admin may be logged in as the second user they impersonated, which may lead to repudiation issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39896|2024-08-04T02:20:33.774Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 16:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39937|2024-08-04T02:20:34.096Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39937</link>
      <description>A collision in access memoization logic in all versions of GitLab CE/EE before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2, leads to potential elevated privileges in groups and projects under rare circumstances</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39937|2024-08-04T02:20:34.096Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39944|2024-08-04T02:20:34.148Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39944</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 11.0 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2. A permissions validation flaw allowed group members with a developer role to elevate their privilege to a maintainer on projects they import</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39944|2024-08-04T02:20:34.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39934|2024-08-04T02:20:34.187Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39934</link>
      <description>Improper access control allows any project member to retrieve the service desk email address in GitLab CE/EE versions starting 12.10 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39934|2024-08-04T02:20:34.187Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39876|2024-08-04T02:20:33.669Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39876</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 11.3, the endpoint for auto-completing Assignee discloses the members of private groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39876|2024-08-04T02:20:33.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 18:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39877|2024-08-04T02:20:33.679Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39877</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was discovered in GitLab starting with version 12.2 that allows an attacker to cause uncontrolled resource consumption with a specially crafted file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39877|2024-08-04T02:20:33.679Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 16:41:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39895|2024-08-04T02:20:33.884Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39895</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 8.0, an attacker can set the pipeline schedules to be active in a project export so when an unsuspecting owner imports that project, pipelines are active by default on that project. Under specialized conditions, this may lead to information disclosure if the project is imported from an untrusted source.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39895|2024-08-04T02:20:33.884Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 23:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39870|2024-08-04T02:20:33.659Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39870</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 11.11, an instance that has the setting to disable Repo by URL import enabled is bypassed by an attacker making a crafted API call.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39870|2024-08-04T02:20:33.659Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 13:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39912|2024-08-04T02:20:33.680Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39912</link>
      <description>A potential DoS vulnerability was discovered in GitLab CE/EE starting with version 13.7. Using a malformed TIFF images was possible to trigger memory exhaustion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39912|2024-08-04T02:20:33.680Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 23:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39946|2024-08-04T02:20:34.213Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39946</link>
      <description>Improper neutralization of user input in GitLab CE/EE versions 14.3 to 14.3.6, 14.4 to 14.4.4, and 14.5 to 14.5.2 allowed an attacker to exploit XSS by abusing the generation of the HTML code related to emojis</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39946|2024-08-04T02:20:34.213Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 16:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39915|2024-08-04T02:20:33.854Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39915</link>
      <description>Improper access control in the GraphQL API in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 13.0 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2, allows an attacker to see the names of project access tokens on arbitrary projects</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39915|2024-08-04T02:20:33.854Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39891|2024-08-04T02:20:33.670Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39891</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 8.0, access tokens created as part of admin's impersonation of a user are not cleared at the end of impersonation which may lead to unnecessary sensitive info disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39891|2024-08-04T02:20:33.670Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 13:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39879|2024-08-04T02:20:33.644Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39879</link>
      <description>Missing authentication in all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 7.11.0 allows an attacker with access to a victim's session to disable two-factor authentication</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39879|2024-08-04T02:20:33.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 16:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39940|2024-08-04T02:20:34.190Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39940</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 13.2 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2. GitLab Maven Package registry is vulnerable to a regular expression denial of service when a specifically crafted string is sent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39940|2024-08-04T02:20:34.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39914|2024-08-04T02:20:33.786Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39914</link>
      <description>A regular expression denial of service issue in GitLab versions 8.13 to 14.2.5, 14.3.0 to 14.3.3 and 14.4.0 could cause excessive usage of resources when a specially crafted username was used when provisioning a new user</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39914|2024-08-04T02:20:33.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 22:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39898|2024-08-04T02:20:33.663Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39898</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 10.6, a project export leaks the external webhook token value which may allow access to the project which it was exported from.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39898|2024-08-04T02:20:33.663Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 23:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39867|2024-08-04T02:20:33.672Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39867</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 8.15, a DNS rebinding vulnerability in Gitea Importer may be exploited by an attacker to trigger Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39867|2024-08-04T02:20:33.672Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 12:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39935|2024-08-04T02:20:34.211Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39935</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 10.5 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2. Unauthorized external users could perform Server Side Requests via the CI Lint API</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39935|2024-08-04T02:20:34.211Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:47:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39888|2024-08-04T02:20:33.655Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39888</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab EE starting from 13.10 before 14.1.7, all versions starting from 14.2 before 14.2.5, and all versions starting from 14.3 before 14.3.1 a specific API endpoint may reveal details about a private group and other sensitive info inside issue and merge request templates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39888|2024-08-04T02:20:33.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 12:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39886|2024-08-04T02:20:33.642Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39886</link>
      <description>Permissions rules were not applied while issues were moved between projects of the same group in GitLab versions starting with 10.6 and up to 14.1.7 allowing users to read confidential Epic references.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39886|2024-08-04T02:20:33.642Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 13:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39866|2024-08-04T02:20:33.617Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39866</link>
      <description>A business logic error in the project deletion process in GitLab 13.6 and later allows persistent access via project access tokens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39866|2024-08-04T02:20:33.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 12:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39931|2024-08-04T02:20:34.167Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39931</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 8.11 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2. Under specific condition an unauthorised project member was allowed to delete a protected branches due to a business logic error.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39931|2024-08-04T02:20:34.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39932|2024-08-04T02:20:34.203Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39932</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 11.0 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2. Using large payloads, the diff feature could be used to trigger high load time for users reviewing code changes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39932|2024-08-04T02:20:34.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:47:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39901|2024-08-04T02:20:33.701Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39901</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 11.10, an admin of a group can see the SCIM token of that group by visiting a specific endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39901|2024-08-04T02:20:33.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 23:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39873|2024-08-04T02:20:33.651Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39873</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE, there exists a content spoofing vulnerability which may be leveraged by attackers to trick users into visiting a malicious website by spoofing the content in an error response.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39873|2024-08-04T02:20:33.651Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 16:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39913|2024-08-04T02:20:33.764Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39913</link>
      <description>Accidental logging of system root password in the migration log in all versions of GitLab CE/EE before 14.2.6, all versions starting from 14.3 before 14.3.4, and all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.1 allows an attacker with local file system access to obtain system root-level privileges</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39913|2024-08-04T02:20:33.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 23:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39878|2024-08-04T02:20:33.708Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39878</link>
      <description>A stored Reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in the Jira integration in GitLab version 13.0 up to 14.3.1 allowed an attacker to execute arbitrary javascript code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39878|2024-08-04T02:20:33.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 12:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39874|2024-08-04T02:20:33.620Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39874</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE since version 11.0, the requirement to enforce 2FA is not honored when using git commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39874|2024-08-04T02:20:33.620Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 16:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39908|2024-08-04T02:20:33.693Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39908</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE starting from 0.8.0 before 14.2.6, all versions starting from 14.3 before 14.3.4, and all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.1 certain Unicode characters can be abused to commit malicious code into projects without being noticed in merge request or source code viewer UI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39908|2024-08-04T02:20:33.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 22:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39905|2024-08-04T02:20:33.677Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39905</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in the GitLab CE/EE API since version 8.9.6 allows a user to see basic information on private groups that a public project has been shared with</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39905|2024-08-04T02:20:33.677Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 23:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39943|2024-08-04T02:20:34.212Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39943</link>
      <description>An authorization logic error in the External Status Check API in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 14.1 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2, allowed a user to update the status of the check via an API call</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39943|2024-08-04T02:20:34.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 22:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39904|2024-08-04T02:20:33.680Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39904</link>
      <description>An Improper Access Control vulnerability in the GraphQL API in all versions of GitLab CE/EE starting from 13.1 before 14.2.6, all versions starting from 14.3 before 14.3.4, and all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.1 allows a Merge Request creator to resolve discussions and apply suggestions after a project owner has locked the Merge Request</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39904|2024-08-04T02:20:33.680Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 23:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39919|2024-08-04T02:20:34.231Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39919</link>
      <description>In all versions of GitLab CE/EE starting version 14.0 before 14.3.6, all versions starting from 14.4 before 14.4.4, all versions starting from 14.5 before 14.5.2, the reset password token and new user email token are accidentally logged which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39919|2024-08-04T02:20:34.231Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 15:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6371|2024-08-02T08:28:21.792Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6371</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.8.5, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.3, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.1. A wiki page with a crafted payload may lead to a Stored XSS, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6371|2024-08-02T08:28:21.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 07:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6477|2024-08-02T08:28:21.814Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6477</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. When a user is assigned a custom role with admin_group_member permission, they may be able to make a group, other members or themselves Owners of that group, which may lead to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6477|2024-08-02T08:28:21.814Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6678|2024-08-02T08:35:14.893Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6678</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions before 16.8.6, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a  denial of service using malicious crafted content in a junit test report file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6678|2024-08-02T08:35:14.893Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6564|2024-08-02T08:35:14.927Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6564</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE Premium and Ultimate affecting versions 16.4.3, 16.5.3, and 16.6.1. In projects using subgroups to define who can push and/or merge to protected branches, there may have been instances in which subgroup members with the Developer role were able to push or merge to protected branches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6564|2024-08-02T08:35:14.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6736|2024-08-02T08:35:15.057Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6736</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 11.3 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for an attacker to cause a client-side denial of service using malicious crafted content in the CODEOWNERS file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6736|2024-08-02T08:35:15.057Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6688|2024-08-02T08:35:14.844Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6688</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. A problem with the processing logic for Google Chat Messages integration may lead to a regular expression DoS attack on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6688|2024-08-02T08:35:14.844Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6840|2024-08-02T08:42:08.148Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6840</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.4 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows a maintainer to change the name of a protected branch that bypasses the security policy added to block MR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6840|2024-08-02T08:42:08.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6682|2024-08-02T08:35:14.911Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6682</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. A problem with the processing logic for Discord Integrations Chat Messages can lead to a regular expression DoS attack on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6682|2024-08-02T08:35:14.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:42:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7045|2024-08-02T08:50:07.755Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7045</link>
      <description>A CSRF vulnerability exists within GitLab CE/EE from versions 13.11 before 16.10.6, from 16.11 before 16.11.3, from 17.0 before 17.0.1. By leveraging this vulnerability, an attacker could exfiltrate anti-CSRF tokens via the Kubernetes Agent Server (KAS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7045|2024-08-02T08:50:07.755Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6502|2024-08-02T08:35:13.273Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6502</link>
      <description>A Denial of Service (DoS) condition has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.10.6, version 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1. It is possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using a crafted wiki page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6502|2024-08-02T08:35:13.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6489|2024-08-02T08:28:21.821Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6489</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability was identified in GitLab CE/EE, versions 16.7.7 prior to 16.8.6, 16.9 prior to 16.9.4 and 16.10 prior to 16.10.2 which allows an attacker to spike the GitLab instance resources usage resulting in service degradation via chat integration feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6489|2024-08-02T08:28:21.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3509|2024-08-02T06:55:03.388Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3509</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for group members with sub-maintainer role to change the title of privately accessible deploy keys associated with projects in the group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3509|2024-08-02T06:55:03.388Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6323|2024-08-01T21:33:05.449Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6323</link>
      <description>Improper authorization in global search in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.11 prior to 16.11.5 and 17.0 prior to 17.0.3 and 17.1 prior to 17.1.1 allows an attacker leak content of a private repository in a public project.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6323|2024-08-01T21:33:05.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7057|2024-08-01T21:45:38.455Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7057</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where job artifacts can be inappropriately exposed to users lacking the proper authorization level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7057|2024-08-01T21:45:38.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5318|2024-08-01T21:11:12.380Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5318</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 11.11 prior to 16.10.6, starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.3, and starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.1. A Guest user can view dependency lists of private projects through job artifacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5318|2024-08-01T21:11:12.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5430|2024-08-01T21:11:12.743Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5430</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.10 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows a project maintainer can delete the merge request approval policy via graphQL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5430|2024-08-01T21:11:12.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5258|2024-08-01T21:03:11.132Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5258</link>
      <description>An authorization vulnerability exists within GitLab from versions 16.10 before 16.10.6, 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1 where an authenticated attacker could utilize a crafted naming convention to bypass pipeline authorization logic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5258|2024-08-01T21:03:11.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5067|2024-08-01T21:03:10.510Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5067</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.11 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where certain project-level analytics settings could be leaked in DOM to group members with Developer or higher roles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5067|2024-08-01T21:03:10.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5470|2024-08-01T21:11:12.792Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5470</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4 and from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 where a Guest user with `admin_push_rules` permission may have been able to create project-level deploy tokens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5470|2024-08-01T21:11:12.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5257|2024-08-01T21:03:11.049Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5257</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4 and from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 where a Developer user with `admin_compliance_framework` custom role may have been able to modify the URL for a group namespace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5257|2024-08-01T21:03:11.049Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7047|2024-08-01T21:45:38.425Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7047</link>
      <description>A cross site scripting vulnerability exists in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.6 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary scripts under the context of the current logged in user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7047|2024-08-01T21:45:38.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6385|2024-08-01T21:41:03.228Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6385</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6385|2024-08-01T21:41:03.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7060|2024-08-01T21:52:30.379Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7060</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE in project/group exports affecting all versions from 15.4 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allows unauthorized users to view the resultant export.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7060|2024-08-01T21:52:30.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5655|2024-08-01T21:18:06.633Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5655</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5655|2024-08-01T21:18:06.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6595|2024-08-01T21:41:03.899Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6595</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 11.8 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 where it was possible to upload an NPM package with conflicting package data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6595|2024-08-01T21:41:03.899Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 01:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7091|2024-08-01T21:52:30.873Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7091</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.6 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where it was possible to disclose limited information of an exported group or project to another user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7091|2024-08-01T21:52:30.873Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5469|2024-08-01T21:11:12.757Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5469</link>
      <description>DoS in KAS in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.10.0 prior to 16.10.6 and 16.11.0 prior to 16.11.3 allows an attacker to crash KAS via crafted gRPC requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5469|2024-08-01T21:11:12.757Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2880|2024-08-01T19:25:42.152Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2880</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.5 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 in which a user with `admin_group_member` custom role permission could ban group members.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2880|2024-08-01T19:25:42.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2434|2024-08-01T19:11:53.542Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2434</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions of GitLab CE/EE  16.9 prior to 16.9.6, 16.10 prior to 16.10.4, and 16.11 prior to 16.11.1 where path traversal could lead to DoS and restricted file read.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2434|2024-08-01T19:11:53.542Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2177|2024-08-01T19:03:39.319Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2177</link>
      <description>A Cross Window Forgery vulnerability exists within GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.3 prior to 16.11.5, 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and 17.1 prior to 17.1.1. This condition allows for an attacker to abuse the OAuth authentication flow via a crafted payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2177|2024-08-01T19:03:39.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 13:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3115|2024-08-01T19:32:42.612Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3115</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.0 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows an attacker to access issues and epics without having an SSO session using Duo Chat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3115|2024-08-01T19:32:42.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2651|2024-08-01T19:18:48.247Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2651</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.9.7, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.5, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using maliciously crafted markdown content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2651|2024-08-01T19:18:48.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3092|2024-08-01T19:32:42.686Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3092</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. A payload may lead to a Stored XSS while using the diff viewer, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3092|2024-08-01T19:32:42.686Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2279|2024-08-01T19:11:52.092Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2279</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 to 16.8.6 all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. Using the autocomplete for issues references feature a crafted payload may lead to a stored XSS, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2279|2024-08-01T19:11:52.092Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2818|2024-08-01T19:25:41.894Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2818</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.8.5, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.3, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.1. It was possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using malicious crafted description parameter for labels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2818|2024-08-01T19:25:41.894Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 07:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2874|2024-08-01T19:25:42.188Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2874</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.10.6, version 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1. A runner registered with a crafted description has the potential to disrupt the loading of targeted GitLab web resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2874|2024-08-01T19:25:42.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 07:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2191|2024-08-01T19:03:39.103Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2191</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows merge request title to be visible publicly despite being set as project members only.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2191|2024-08-01T19:03:39.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2454|2024-08-01T19:11:53.493Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2454</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.11 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. The pins endpoint is susceptible to DoS through a crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2454|2024-08-01T19:11:53.493Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2829|2024-08-01T19:25:41.746Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2829</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.5 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. A crafted wildcard filter in FileFinder may lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2829|2024-08-01T19:25:41.746Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0199|2024-08-01T17:41:16.006Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0199</link>
      <description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 11.3 prior to 16.7.7, 16.7.6 prior to 16.8.4, and 16.8.3 prior to 16.9.2. An attacker could bypass CODEOWNERS by utilizing a crafted payload in an old feature branch to perform malicious actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0199|2024-08-01T17:41:16.006Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0231|2024-08-01T17:41:16.067Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0231</link>
      <description>A resource misdirection vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE versions 12.0 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allows an attacker to craft a repository import in such a way as to misdirect commits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0231|2024-08-01T17:41:16.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1299|2024-07-30T15:26:03.018Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1299</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 16.8 prior to 16.8.4 and 16.9 prior to 16.9.2. It was possible for a user with custom role of `manage_group_access_tokens` to rotate group access tokens with owner privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1299|2024-07-30T15:26:03.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:39:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7047|2024-07-26T19:21:17.148Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7047</link>
      <description>A cross site scripting vulnerability exists in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.6 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary scripts under the context of the current logged in user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7047|2024-07-26T19:21:17.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6371|2024-07-25T04:08:51.479Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6371</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.8.5, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.3, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.1. A wiki page with a crafted payload may lead to a Stored XSS, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6371|2024-07-25T04:08:51.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 07:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6477|2024-07-25T04:08:56.492Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6477</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. When a user is assigned a custom role with admin_group_member permission, they may be able to make a group, other members or themselves Owners of that group, which may lead to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6477|2024-07-25T04:08:56.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2434|2024-07-25T04:09:51.497Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2434</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions of GitLab CE/EE  16.9 prior to 16.9.6, 16.10 prior to 16.10.4, and 16.11 prior to 16.11.1 where path traversal could lead to DoS and restricted file read.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2434|2024-07-25T04:09:51.497Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6678|2024-07-25T04:09:06.484Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6678</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions before 16.8.6, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a  denial of service using malicious crafted content in a junit test report file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6678|2024-07-25T04:09:06.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1347|2024-07-25T04:09:36.499Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1347</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker through a crafted email address may be able to bypass domain based restrictions on an instance or a group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1347|2024-07-25T04:09:36.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6736|2024-07-25T04:09:11.484Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6736</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 11.3 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for an attacker to cause a client-side denial of service using malicious crafted content in the CODEOWNERS file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6736|2024-07-25T04:09:11.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6840|2024-07-25T04:09:16.492Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6840</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.4 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows a maintainer to change the name of a protected branch that bypasses the security policy added to block MR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6840|2024-07-25T04:09:16.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3092|2024-07-25T04:10:01.503Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3092</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. A payload may lead to a Stored XSS while using the diff viewer, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3092|2024-07-25T04:10:01.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2279|2024-07-25T04:09:46.504Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2279</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 to 16.8.6 all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. Using the autocomplete for issues references feature a crafted payload may lead to a stored XSS, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2279|2024-07-25T04:09:46.504Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1451|2024-07-25T04:09:41.499Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1451</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. A crafted payload  added to the user profile page could lead to a stored XSS on the client side, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1451|2024-07-25T04:09:41.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0410|2024-07-25T04:09:26.496Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0410</link>
      <description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 15.1 prior to 16.7.6, 16.8 prior to 16.8.3, and 16.9 prior to 16.9.1. A developer could bypass CODEOWNERS approvals by creating a merge conflict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0410|2024-07-25T04:09:26.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4895|2024-07-25T04:07:31.588Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4895</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 to 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. This vulnerability allows for bypassing the 'group ip restriction' settings to access environment details of projects</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4895|2024-07-25T04:07:31.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0861|2024-07-25T04:09:31.507Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0861</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. Users with the `Guest` role can change `Custom dashboard projects` settings contrary to permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0861|2024-07-25T04:09:31.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3509|2024-07-25T04:05:21.486Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3509</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for group members with sub-maintainer role to change the title of privately accessible deploy keys associated with projects in the group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3509|2024-07-25T04:05:21.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6489|2024-07-25T04:09:01.484Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6489</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability was identified in GitLab CE/EE, versions 16.7.7 prior to 16.8.6, 16.9 prior to 16.9.4 and 16.10 prior to 16.10.2 which allows an attacker to spike the GitLab instance resources usage resulting in service degradation via chat integration feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6489|2024-07-25T04:09:01.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2829|2024-07-25T04:09:56.499Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2829</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.5 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. A crafted wildcard filter in FileFinder may lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2829|2024-07-25T04:09:56.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2191|2024-07-24T15:05:28.063Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2191</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows merge request title to be visible publicly despite being set as project members only.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2191|2024-07-24T15:05:28.063Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5257|2024-07-23T18:30:27.972Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5257</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4 and from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 where a Developer user with `admin_compliance_framework` custom role may have been able to modify the URL for a group namespace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5257|2024-07-23T18:30:27.972Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4895|2024-07-19T21:11:58.103Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4895</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 to 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. This vulnerability allows for bypassing the 'group ip restriction' settings to access environment details of projects</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4895|2024-07-19T21:11:58.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3115|2024-07-15T18:33:50.330Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3115</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.0 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows an attacker to access issues and epics without having an SSO session using Duo Chat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3115|2024-07-15T18:33:50.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6385|2024-07-12T03:55:20.246Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6385</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6385|2024-07-12T03:55:20.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5470|2024-07-11T15:08:22.150Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5470</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4 and from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 where a Guest user with `admin_push_rules` permission may have been able to create project-level deploy tokens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5470|2024-07-11T15:08:22.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2880|2024-07-11T06:57:24.360Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2880</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.5 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 in which a user with `admin_group_member` custom role permission could ban group members.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2880|2024-07-11T06:57:24.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6385|2024-07-11T06:56:54.515Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6385</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6385|2024-07-11T06:56:54.515Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5470|2024-07-11T06:57:04.361Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5470</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4 and from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 where a Guest user with `admin_push_rules` permission may have been able to create project-level deploy tokens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5470|2024-07-11T06:57:04.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5257|2024-07-11T06:57:09.372Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5257</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4 and from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 where a Developer user with `admin_compliance_framework` custom role may have been able to modify the URL for a group namespace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5257|2024-07-11T06:57:09.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1963|2024-07-10T15:06:54.954Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1963</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 8.4 prior to 16.10.7, starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.4, and starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.2. A vulnerability in GitLab's Asana integration allowed an attacker to potentially cause a regular expression denial of service by sending specially crafted requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1963|2024-07-10T15:06:54.954Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6489|2024-07-08T20:13:28.175Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6489</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability was identified in GitLab CE/EE, versions 16.7.7 prior to 16.8.6, 16.9 prior to 16.9.4 and 16.10 prior to 16.10.2 which allows an attacker to spike the GitLab instance resources usage resulting in service degradation via chat integration feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6489|2024-07-08T20:13:28.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1525|2024-07-05T17:21:54.930Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1525</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. Under some specialized conditions, an LDAP user may be able to reset their password using their verified secondary email address and sign-in using direct authentication with the reset password, bypassing LDAP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1525|2024-07-05T17:21:54.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6736|2024-07-05T17:20:46.176Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6736</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 11.3 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for an attacker to cause a client-side denial of service using malicious crafted content in the CODEOWNERS file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6736|2024-07-05T17:20:46.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6564|2024-07-05T17:21:52.048Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6564</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE Premium and Ultimate affecting versions 16.4.3, 16.5.3, and 16.6.1. In projects using subgroups to define who can push and/or merge to protected branches, there may have been instances in which subgroup members with the Developer role were able to push or merge to protected branches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6564|2024-07-05T17:21:52.048Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1451|2024-07-05T17:21:54.204Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1451</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. A crafted payload  added to the user profile page could lead to a stored XSS on the client side, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1451|2024-07-05T17:21:54.204Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1066|2024-07-05T17:20:47.183Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1066</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 13.3.0 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows an attacker to do a resource exhaustion using GraphQL `vulnerabilitiesCountByDay`</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1066|2024-07-05T17:20:47.183Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1816|2024-07-05T17:22:42.726Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1816</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows for an attacker to cause a denial of service using a crafted OpenAPI file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1816|2024-07-05T17:22:42.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6840|2024-07-05T17:20:46.439Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6840</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.4 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows a maintainer to change the name of a protected branch that bypasses the security policy added to block MR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6840|2024-07-05T17:20:46.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3509|2024-07-05T17:21:53.932Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3509</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for group members with sub-maintainer role to change the title of privately accessible deploy keys associated with projects in the group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3509|2024-07-05T17:21:53.932Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5655|2024-06-28T13:09:22.469Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5655</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5655|2024-06-28T13:09:22.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4901|2024-06-28T13:08:59.344Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4901</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, where a stored XSS vulnerability could be imported from a project with malicious commit notes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4901|2024-06-28T13:08:59.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5655|2024-06-27T19:55:33.371Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5655</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5655|2024-06-27T19:55:33.371Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5430|2024-06-27T19:05:34.915Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5430</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.10 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows a project maintainer can delete the merge request approval policy via graphQL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5430|2024-06-27T19:05:34.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4011|2024-06-27T17:41:04.644Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4011</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.1 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows non-project member to promote key results to objectives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4011|2024-06-27T17:41:04.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4557|2024-06-27T17:26:27.963Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4557</link>
      <description>Multiple Denial of Service (DoS) conditions has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 1.0 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1 which allowed an attacker to cause resource exhaustion via banzai pipeline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4557|2024-06-27T17:26:27.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3959|2024-06-27T17:37:19.509Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3959</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows private job artifacts can be accessed by any user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3959|2024-06-27T17:37:19.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1347|2024-06-20T13:52:43.570Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1347</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker through a crafted email address may be able to bypass domain based restrictions on an instance or a group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1347|2024-06-20T13:52:43.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4597|2024-06-17T19:47:03.571Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4597</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.7 before 16.9.7, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.5, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.2. An attacker could force a user with an active SAML session to approve an MR via CSRF.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4597|2024-06-17T19:47:03.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4835|2024-06-14T22:45:45.358Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4835</link>
      <description>A XSS condition exists within GitLab in versions 15.11 before 16.10.6, 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1. By leveraging this condition, an attacker can craft a malicious page to exfiltrate sensitive user information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4835|2024-06-14T22:45:45.358Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 06:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5469|2024-06-14T04:04:49.726Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5469</link>
      <description>DoS in KAS in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.10.0 prior to 16.10.6 and 16.11.0 prior to 16.11.3 allows an attacker to crash KAS via crafted gRPC requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5469|2024-06-14T04:04:49.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1495|2024-06-13T17:17:40.855Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1495</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 13.1 prior to 16.10.7, starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.4, and starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using maliciously crafted file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1495|2024-06-13T17:17:40.855Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2651|2024-06-04T17:29:46.148Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2651</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.9.7, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.5, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using maliciously crafted markdown content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2651|2024-06-04T17:29:46.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2279|2024-06-04T17:30:10.331Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2279</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 to 16.8.6 all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. Using the autocomplete for issues references feature a crafted payload may lead to a stored XSS, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2279|2024-06-04T17:30:10.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2829|2024-06-04T17:30:18.728Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2829</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.5 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. A crafted wildcard filter in FileFinder may lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2829|2024-06-04T17:30:18.728Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2434|2024-06-04T17:30:36.312Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2434</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions of GitLab CE/EE  16.9 prior to 16.9.6, 16.10 prior to 16.10.4, and 16.11 prior to 16.11.1 where path traversal could lead to DoS and restricted file read.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2434|2024-06-04T17:30:36.312Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2818|2024-06-04T17:30:38.952Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2818</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.8.5, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.3, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.1. It was possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using malicious crafted description parameter for labels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2818|2024-06-04T17:30:38.952Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 07:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2874|2024-06-04T17:30:47.399Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2874</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.10.6, version 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1. A runner registered with a crafted description has the potential to disrupt the loading of targeted GitLab web resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2874|2024-06-04T17:30:47.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 07:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2454|2024-06-04T17:30:51.249Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2454</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.11 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. The pins endpoint is susceptible to DoS through a crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2454|2024-06-04T17:30:51.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3092|2024-04-12T04:04:57.767Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3092</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. A payload may lead to a Stored XSS while using the diff viewer, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3092|2024-04-12T04:04:57.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4835|2024-05-23T06:30:50.384Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4835</link>
      <description>A XSS condition exists within GitLab in versions 15.11 before 16.10.6, 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1. By leveraging this condition, an attacker can craft a malicious page to exfiltrate sensitive user information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4835|2024-05-23T06:30:50.384Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 06:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4024|2024-06-04T17:54:01.085Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4024</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 7.8 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker with their Bitbucket account credentials may be able to take over a GitLab account linked to another user's Bitbucket account, if Bitbucket is used as an OAuth 2.0 provider on GitLab.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4024|2024-06-04T17:54:01.085Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4006|2024-06-04T17:55:08.568Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4006</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1 where personal access scopes were not honored by GraphQL subscriptions</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4006|2024-06-04T17:55:08.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4539|2024-06-04T17:55:55.247Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4539</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.4 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2 where abusing the API to filter branch and tags could lead to Denial of Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4539|2024-06-04T17:55:55.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4597|2024-05-09T01:38:11.850Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4597</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.7 before 16.9.7, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.5, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.2. An attacker could force a user with an active SAML session to approve an MR via CSRF.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4597|2024-05-09T01:38:11.850Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0410|2024-02-22T04:04:41.024Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0410</link>
      <description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 15.1 prior to 16.7.6, 16.8 prior to 16.8.3, and 16.9 prior to 16.9.1. A developer could bypass CODEOWNERS approvals by creating a merge conflict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0410|2024-02-22T04:04:41.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0861|2024-02-22T04:04:46.027Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0861</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. Users with the `Guest` role can change `Custom dashboard projects` settings contrary to permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0861|2024-02-22T04:04:46.027Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0199|2024-03-07T00:39:50.159Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0199</link>
      <description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 11.3 prior to 16.7.7, 16.7.6 prior to 16.8.4, and 16.8.3 prior to 16.9.2. An attacker could bypass CODEOWNERS by utilizing a crafted payload in an old feature branch to perform malicious actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0199|2024-03-07T00:39:50.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1451|2024-02-22T04:04:51.022Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1451</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. A crafted payload  added to the user profile page could lead to a stored XSS on the client side, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1451|2024-02-22T04:04:51.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1299|2024-03-07T00:39:45.501Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1299</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 16.8 prior to 16.8.4 and 16.9 prior to 16.9.2. It was possible for a user with custom role of `manage_group_access_tokens` to rotate group access tokens with owner privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1299|2024-03-07T00:39:45.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:39:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1066|2024-03-23T04:04:24.274Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1066</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 13.3.0 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows an attacker to do a resource exhaustion using GraphQL `vulnerabilitiesCountByDay`</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1066|2024-03-23T04:04:24.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1250|2024-03-13T04:04:49.939Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1250</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.2. When a user is assigned a custom role with manage_group_access_tokens permission, they may be able to create group access tokens with Owner privileges, which may lead to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1250|2024-03-13T04:04:49.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 20:47:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1525|2024-03-23T04:04:29.177Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1525</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. Under some specialized conditions, an LDAP user may be able to reset their password using their verified secondary email address and sign-in using direct authentication with the reset password, bypassing LDAP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1525|2024-03-23T04:04:29.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1947|2024-06-04T18:00:40.082Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1947</link>
      <description>A denial of service (DoS) condition was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 13.2.4 before 16.10.6, 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1. By leveraging this vulnerability an attacker could create a DoS condition by sending crafted API calls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1947|2024-06-04T18:00:40.082Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1347|2024-06-04T18:01:05.241Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1347</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker through a crafted email address may be able to bypass domain based restrictions on an instance or a group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1347|2024-06-04T18:01:05.241Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5258|2024-06-04T18:01:51.492Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5258</link>
      <description>An authorization vulnerability exists within GitLab from versions 16.10 before 16.10.6, 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1 where an authenticated attacker could utilize a crafted naming convention to bypass pipeline authorization logic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5258|2024-06-04T18:01:51.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5318|2024-06-04T18:02:21.999Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5318</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 11.11 prior to 16.10.6, starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.3, and starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.1. A Guest user can view dependency lists of private projects through job artifacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5318|2024-06-04T18:02:21.999Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6736|2024-02-26T20:32:17.214Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6736</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 11.3 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for an attacker to cause a client-side denial of service using malicious crafted content in the CODEOWNERS file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6736|2024-02-26T20:32:17.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6371|2024-06-04T17:16:57.971Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6371</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.8.5, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.3, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.1. A wiki page with a crafted payload may lead to a Stored XSS, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6371|2024-06-04T17:16:57.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 07:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6678|2024-04-12T04:04:42.942Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6678</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions before 16.8.6, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a  denial of service using malicious crafted content in a junit test report file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6678|2024-04-12T04:04:42.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6564|2024-02-09T18:47:22.622Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6564</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE Premium and Ultimate affecting versions 16.4.3, 16.5.3, and 16.6.1. In projects using subgroups to define who can push and/or merge to protected branches, there may have been instances in which subgroup members with the Developer role were able to push or merge to protected branches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6564|2024-02-09T18:47:22.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6682|2024-06-04T17:17:11.196Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6682</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. A problem with the processing logic for Discord Integrations Chat Messages can lead to a regular expression DoS attack on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6682|2024-06-04T17:17:11.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:42:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6840|2024-02-07T22:02:20.934Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6840</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.4 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows a maintainer to change the name of a protected branch that bypasses the security policy added to block MR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6840|2024-02-07T22:02:20.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6477|2024-02-22T04:04:35.685Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6477</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. When a user is assigned a custom role with admin_group_member permission, they may be able to make a group, other members or themselves Owners of that group, which may lead to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6477|2024-02-22T04:04:35.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6489|2024-04-12T04:04:38.091Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6489</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability was identified in GitLab CE/EE, versions 16.7.7 prior to 16.8.6, 16.9 prior to 16.9.4 and 16.10 prior to 16.10.2 which allows an attacker to spike the GitLab instance resources usage resulting in service degradation via chat integration feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6489|2024-04-12T04:04:38.091Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6688|2024-05-09T01:38:46.718Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6688</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. A problem with the processing logic for Google Chat Messages integration may lead to a regular expression DoS attack on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6688|2024-05-09T01:38:46.718Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6502|2024-06-04T17:17:20.207Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6502</link>
      <description>A Denial of Service (DoS) condition has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.10.6, version 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1. It is possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using a crafted wiki page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6502|2024-06-04T17:17:20.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7045|2024-06-04T17:17:24.088Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-7045</link>
      <description>A CSRF vulnerability exists within GitLab CE/EE from versions 13.11 before 16.10.6, from 16.11 before 16.11.3, from 17.0 before 17.0.1. By leveraging this vulnerability, an attacker could exfiltrate anti-CSRF tokens via the Kubernetes Agent Server (KAS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7045|2024-06-04T17:17:24.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3509|2024-05-07T06:29:39.757Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3509</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for group members with sub-maintainer role to change the title of privately accessible deploy keys associated with projects in the group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3509|2024-05-07T06:29:39.757Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4895|2024-02-22T04:04:21.576Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4895</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 to 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. This vulnerability allows for bypassing the 'group ip restriction' settings to access environment details of projects</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4895|2024-02-22T04:04:21.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1736|2024-06-13T18:17:49.907Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1736</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions prior to 16.10.7, starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.4, and starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.2. A vulnerability in GitLab's CI/CD pipeline editor could allow for denial of service attacks through maliciously crafted configuration files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1736|2024-06-13T18:17:49.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4201|2024-06-14T19:18:50.469Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4201</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 5.1 before 16.10.7, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.111.4, all versions starting from 17.0 before 17.0.2. When viewing an XML file in a repository in raw mode, it can be made to render as HTML if viewed under specific circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4201|2024-06-14T19:18:50.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5469|2024-06-15T20:49:28.558Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5469</link>
      <description>DoS in KAS in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.10.0 prior to 16.10.6 and 16.11.0 prior to 16.11.3 allows an attacker to crash KAS via crafted gRPC requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5469|2024-06-15T20:49:28.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3092|2024-06-18T19:34:28.995Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3092</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. A payload may lead to a Stored XSS while using the diff viewer, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3092|2024-06-18T19:34:28.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4006|2024-06-20T19:31:15.040Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4006</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1 where personal access scopes were not honored by GraphQL subscriptions</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4006|2024-06-20T19:31:15.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2434|2024-06-20T19:35:46.975Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2434</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions of GitLab CE/EE  16.9 prior to 16.9.6, 16.10 prior to 16.10.4, and 16.11 prior to 16.11.1 where path traversal could lead to DoS and restricted file read.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2434|2024-06-20T19:35:46.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4024|2024-06-20T19:40:36.439Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4024</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 7.8 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker with their Bitbucket account credentials may be able to take over a GitLab account linked to another user's Bitbucket account, if Bitbucket is used as an OAuth 2.0 provider on GitLab.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4024|2024-06-20T19:40:36.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2829|2024-06-20T19:38:32.265Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2829</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.5 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. A crafted wildcard filter in FileFinder may lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2829|2024-06-20T19:38:32.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1493|2024-06-27T18:20:35.300Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1493</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 9.2 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, with the processing logic for generating link in dependency files can lead to a regular  expression DoS attack on the server</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1493|2024-06-27T18:20:35.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4901|2024-06-28T03:55:14.993Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4901</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, where a stored XSS vulnerability could be imported from a project with malicious commit notes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4901|2024-06-28T03:55:14.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5655|2024-06-28T03:55:13.887Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5655</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5655|2024-06-28T03:55:13.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6323|2024-07-02T15:58:28.186Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6323</link>
      <description>Improper authorization in global search in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.11 prior to 16.11.5 and 17.0 prior to 17.0.3 and 17.1 prior to 17.1.1 allows an attacker leak content of a private repository in a public project.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6323|2024-07-02T15:58:28.186Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2191|2024-07-05T20:17:35.161Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2191</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows merge request title to be visible publicly despite being set as project members only.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2191|2024-07-05T20:17:35.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2177|2024-07-09T13:30:57.825Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2177</link>
      <description>A Cross Window Forgery vulnerability exists within GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.3 prior to 16.11.5, 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and 17.1 prior to 17.1.1. This condition allows for an attacker to abuse the OAuth authentication flow via a crafted payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2177|2024-07-09T13:30:57.825Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 13:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2177|2024-07-10T16:31:47.937Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2177</link>
      <description>A Cross Window Forgery vulnerability exists within GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.3 prior to 16.11.5, 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and 17.1 prior to 17.1.1. This condition allows for an attacker to abuse the OAuth authentication flow via a crafted payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2177|2024-07-10T16:31:47.937Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 13:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2880|2024-07-11T13:57:10.477Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2880</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.5 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 in which a user with `admin_group_member` custom role permission could ban group members.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2880|2024-07-11T13:57:10.477Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6385|2024-07-11T18:29:36.592Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6385</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6385|2024-07-11T18:29:36.592Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6385|2024-07-12T10:36:50.276Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6385</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6385|2024-07-12T10:36:50.276Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6595|2024-07-17T19:48:11.724Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6595</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 11.8 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 where it was possible to upload an NPM package with conflicting package data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6595|2024-07-17T19:48:11.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 01:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6688|2024-07-23T17:47:37.023Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6688</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. A problem with the processing logic for Google Chat Messages integration may lead to a regular expression DoS attack on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6688|2024-07-23T17:47:37.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6840|2024-07-24T04:09:49.152Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6840</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.4 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows a maintainer to change the name of a protected branch that bypasses the security policy added to block MR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6840|2024-07-24T04:09:49.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2434|2024-07-24T04:10:34.320Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2434</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions of GitLab CE/EE  16.9 prior to 16.9.6, 16.10 prior to 16.10.4, and 16.11 prior to 16.11.1 where path traversal could lead to DoS and restricted file read.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2434|2024-07-24T04:10:34.320Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6371|2024-07-24T04:09:24.158Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6371</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.8.5, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.3, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.1. A wiki page with a crafted payload may lead to a Stored XSS, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6371|2024-07-24T04:09:24.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 07:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6678|2024-07-24T04:09:39.155Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6678</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions before 16.8.6, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a  denial of service using malicious crafted content in a junit test report file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6678|2024-07-24T04:09:39.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0410|2024-07-24T04:10:05.499Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0410</link>
      <description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 15.1 prior to 16.7.6, 16.8 prior to 16.8.3, and 16.9 prior to 16.9.1. A developer could bypass CODEOWNERS approvals by creating a merge conflict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0410|2024-07-24T04:10:05.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3509|2024-07-24T04:05:52.646Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3509</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for group members with sub-maintainer role to change the title of privately accessible deploy keys associated with projects in the group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3509|2024-07-24T04:05:52.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1347|2024-07-24T04:10:19.323Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1347</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker through a crafted email address may be able to bypass domain based restrictions on an instance or a group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1347|2024-07-24T04:10:19.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3092|2024-07-24T04:10:44.319Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3092</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. A payload may lead to a Stored XSS while using the diff viewer, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3092|2024-07-24T04:10:44.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1451|2024-07-24T04:10:24.317Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1451</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. A crafted payload  added to the user profile page could lead to a stored XSS on the client side, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1451|2024-07-24T04:10:24.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6489|2024-07-24T04:09:34.159Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6489</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability was identified in GitLab CE/EE, versions 16.7.7 prior to 16.8.6, 16.9 prior to 16.9.4 and 16.10 prior to 16.10.2 which allows an attacker to spike the GitLab instance resources usage resulting in service degradation via chat integration feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6489|2024-07-24T04:09:34.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2279|2024-07-24T04:10:29.316Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2279</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 to 16.8.6 all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. Using the autocomplete for issues references feature a crafted payload may lead to a stored XSS, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2279|2024-07-24T04:10:29.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4895|2024-07-24T04:08:04.067Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4895</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 to 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. This vulnerability allows for bypassing the 'group ip restriction' settings to access environment details of projects</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4895|2024-07-24T04:08:04.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6477|2024-07-24T04:09:29.153Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6477</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. When a user is assigned a custom role with admin_group_member permission, they may be able to make a group, other members or themselves Owners of that group, which may lead to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6477|2024-07-24T04:09:29.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2829|2024-07-24T04:10:39.344Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2829</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.5 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. A crafted wildcard filter in FileFinder may lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2829|2024-07-24T04:10:39.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6736|2024-07-24T04:09:44.153Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6736</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 11.3 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for an attacker to cause a client-side denial of service using malicious crafted content in the CODEOWNERS file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6736|2024-07-24T04:09:44.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0861|2024-07-24T04:10:10.463Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0861</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. Users with the `Guest` role can change `Custom dashboard projects` settings contrary to permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0861|2024-07-24T04:10:10.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0199|2024-07-24T14:03:21.689Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0199</link>
      <description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 11.3 prior to 16.7.7, 16.7.6 prior to 16.8.4, and 16.8.3 prior to 16.9.2. An attacker could bypass CODEOWNERS by utilizing a crafted payload in an old feature branch to perform malicious actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0199|2024-07-24T14:03:21.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2177|2024-07-24T14:58:58.843Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2177</link>
      <description>A Cross Window Forgery vulnerability exists within GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.3 prior to 16.11.5, 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and 17.1 prior to 17.1.1. This condition allows for an attacker to abuse the OAuth authentication flow via a crafted payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2177|2024-07-24T14:58:58.843Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 13:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7091|2024-07-24T22:07:45.260Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7091</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.6 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where it was possible to disclose limited information of an exported group or project to another user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7091|2024-07-24T22:07:45.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0231|2024-07-24T22:08:20.025Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0231</link>
      <description>A resource misdirection vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE versions 12.0 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allows an attacker to craft a repository import in such a way as to misdirect commits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0231|2024-07-24T22:08:20.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7060|2024-07-24T22:07:50.018Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7060</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE in project/group exports affecting all versions from 15.4 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allows unauthorized users to view the resultant export.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7060|2024-07-24T22:07:50.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5067|2024-07-24T22:08:05.034Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5067</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.11 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where certain project-level analytics settings could be leaked in DOM to group members with Developer or higher roles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5067|2024-07-24T22:08:05.034Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0231|2024-07-25T13:39:35.927Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0231</link>
      <description>A resource misdirection vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE versions 12.0 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allows an attacker to craft a repository import in such a way as to misdirect commits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0231|2024-07-25T13:39:35.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7060|2024-07-25T13:43:31.196Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7060</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE in project/group exports affecting all versions from 15.4 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allows unauthorized users to view the resultant export.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7060|2024-07-25T13:43:31.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7091|2024-07-25T15:03:32.800Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7091</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.6 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where it was possible to disclose limited information of an exported group or project to another user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7091|2024-07-25T15:03:32.800Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5067|2024-07-26T15:33:01.159Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5067</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.11 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where certain project-level analytics settings could be leaked in DOM to group members with Developer or higher roles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5067|2024-07-26T15:33:01.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7057|2024-07-26T15:55:10.800Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7057</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where job artifacts can be inappropriately exposed to users lacking the proper authorization level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7057|2024-07-26T15:55:10.800Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6678|2024-07-31T15:49:40.510Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6678</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions before 16.8.6, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a  denial of service using malicious crafted content in a junit test report file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6678|2024-07-31T15:49:40.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1525|2024-08-01T18:40:21.306Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1525</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. Under some specialized conditions, an LDAP user may be able to reset their password using their verified secondary email address and sign-in using direct authentication with the reset password, bypassing LDAP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1525|2024-08-01T18:40:21.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0861|2024-08-01T18:18:18.806Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0861</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. Users with the `Guest` role can change `Custom dashboard projects` settings contrary to permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0861|2024-08-01T18:18:18.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1947|2024-08-01T18:56:22.407Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1947</link>
      <description>A denial of service (DoS) condition was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 13.2.4 before 16.10.6, 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1. By leveraging this vulnerability an attacker could create a DoS condition by sending crafted API calls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1947|2024-08-01T18:56:22.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1493|2024-08-01T18:40:21.333Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1493</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 9.2 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, with the processing logic for generating link in dependency files can lead to a regular  expression DoS attack on the server</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1493|2024-08-01T18:40:21.333Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1963|2024-08-01T18:56:22.389Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1963</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 8.4 prior to 16.10.7, starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.4, and starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.2. A vulnerability in GitLab's Asana integration allowed an attacker to potentially cause a regular expression denial of service by sending specially crafted requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1963|2024-08-01T18:56:22.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0410|2024-08-01T18:04:49.660Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0410</link>
      <description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 15.1 prior to 16.7.6, 16.8 prior to 16.8.3, and 16.9 prior to 16.9.1. A developer could bypass CODEOWNERS approvals by creating a merge conflict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0410|2024-08-01T18:04:49.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1451|2024-08-01T18:40:21.118Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1451</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. A crafted payload  added to the user profile page could lead to a stored XSS on the client side, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1451|2024-08-01T18:40:21.118Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1736|2024-08-01T18:48:21.821Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1736</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions prior to 16.10.7, starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.4, and starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.2. A vulnerability in GitLab's CI/CD pipeline editor could allow for denial of service attacks through maliciously crafted configuration files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1736|2024-08-01T18:48:21.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1299|2024-08-01T18:33:25.390Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1299</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 16.8 prior to 16.8.4 and 16.9 prior to 16.9.2. It was possible for a user with custom role of `manage_group_access_tokens` to rotate group access tokens with owner privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1299|2024-08-01T18:33:25.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:39:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1347|2024-08-01T18:33:25.387Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1347</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker through a crafted email address may be able to bypass domain based restrictions on an instance or a group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1347|2024-08-01T18:33:25.387Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1495|2024-08-01T18:40:21.205Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1495</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 13.1 prior to 16.10.7, starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.4, and starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using maliciously crafted file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1495|2024-08-01T18:40:21.205Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1816|2024-08-01T18:48:21.985Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1816</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows for an attacker to cause a denial of service using a crafted OpenAPI file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1816|2024-08-01T18:48:21.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1250|2024-08-01T18:33:25.356Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1250</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.2. When a user is assigned a custom role with manage_group_access_tokens permission, they may be able to create group access tokens with Owner privileges, which may lead to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1250|2024-08-01T18:33:25.356Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 20:47:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1066|2024-08-01T18:26:30.545Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1066</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 13.3.0 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows an attacker to do a resource exhaustion using GraphQL `vulnerabilitiesCountByDay`</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1066|2024-08-01T18:26:30.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4024|2024-08-01T20:26:57.255Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4024</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 7.8 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker with their Bitbucket account credentials may be able to take over a GitLab account linked to another user's Bitbucket account, if Bitbucket is used as an OAuth 2.0 provider on GitLab.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4024|2024-08-01T20:26:57.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4835|2024-08-01T20:55:10.129Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4835</link>
      <description>A XSS condition exists within GitLab in versions 15.11 before 16.10.6, 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1. By leveraging this condition, an attacker can craft a malicious page to exfiltrate sensitive user information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4835|2024-08-01T20:55:10.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 06:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4539|2024-08-01T20:40:47.531Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4539</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.4 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2 where abusing the API to filter branch and tags could lead to Denial of Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4539|2024-08-01T20:40:47.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4597|2024-08-01T20:47:41.257Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4597</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.7 before 16.9.7, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.5, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.2. An attacker could force a user with an active SAML session to approve an MR via CSRF.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4597|2024-08-01T20:47:41.257Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4901|2024-08-01T20:55:10.235Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4901</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, where a stored XSS vulnerability could be imported from a project with malicious commit notes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4901|2024-08-01T20:55:10.235Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4006|2024-08-01T20:26:57.281Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4006</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1 where personal access scopes were not honored by GraphQL subscriptions</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4006|2024-08-01T20:26:57.281Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4557|2024-08-01T20:47:41.409Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4557</link>
      <description>Multiple Denial of Service (DoS) conditions has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 1.0 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1 which allowed an attacker to cause resource exhaustion via banzai pipeline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4557|2024-08-01T20:47:41.409Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4201|2024-08-01T20:33:52.911Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4201</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 5.1 before 16.10.7, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.111.4, all versions starting from 17.0 before 17.0.2. When viewing an XML file in a repository in raw mode, it can be made to render as HTML if viewed under specific circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4201|2024-08-01T20:33:52.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3959|2024-08-01T20:26:57.148Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3959</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows private job artifacts can be accessed by any user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3959|2024-08-01T20:26:57.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4011|2024-08-01T20:26:57.321Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4011</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.1 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows non-project member to promote key results to objectives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4011|2024-08-01T20:26:57.321Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4895|2024-08-02T07:38:01.031Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4895</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 to 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. This vulnerability allows for bypassing the 'group ip restriction' settings to access environment details of projects</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4895|2024-08-02T07:38:01.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
