<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for GitLab -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/gitlab/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for GitLab -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:24:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1071|2024-08-02T05:32:46.336Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1071</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions from 15.5 before 15.8.5, all versions starting from 15.9 before 15.9.4, all versions starting from 15.10 before 15.10.1. Due to improper permissions checks it was possible for an unauthorised user to remove an issue from an epic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1071|2024-08-02T05:32:46.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4379|2024-08-02T07:24:04.500Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4379</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 15.3 prior to 16.2.8, 16.3 prior to 16.3.5, and 16.4 prior to 16.4.1. Code owner approval was not removed from merge requests when the target branch was updated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4379|2024-08-02T07:24:04.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 21:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3363|2024-08-02T06:55:02.594Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3363</link>
      <description>An information disclosure issue in Gitlab CE/EE affecting all versions from 13.6 prior to 15.11.10, all versions from 16.0 prior to 16.0.6, all versions from 16.1 prior to 16.1.1, resulted in the Sidekiq log including webhook tokens when the log format was set to `default`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3363|2024-08-02T06:55:02.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 02:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0989|2024-08-02T05:32:46.144Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0989</link>
      <description>An information disclosure issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 13.11 prior to 16.2.8, 16.3 prior to 16.3.5, and 16.4 prior to 16.4.1 allows an attacker to extract non-protected CI/CD variables by tricking a user to visit a fork with a malicious CI/CD configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0989|2024-08-02T05:32:46.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 06:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0756|2024-08-02T05:24:34.193Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0756</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 15.9.6, all versions starting from 15.10 before 15.10.5, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.1. The main branch of a repository with a specially crafted name allows an attacker to create repositories with malicious code, victims who clone or download these repositories will execute arbitrary code on their systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0756|2024-08-02T05:24:34.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0042|2024-08-02T04:54:32.610Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0042</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 11.4 prior to 15.5.7, 15.6 prior to 15.6.4, and 15.7 prior to 15.7.2. GitLab Pages allows redirection to arbitrary protocols.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0042|2024-08-02T04:54:32.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6033|2024-08-02T08:21:17.132Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6033</link>
      <description>Improper neutralization of input in Jira integration configuration in GitLab CE/EE, affecting all versions from 15.10 prior to 16.6.1, 16.5 prior to 16.5.3, and 16.4 prior to 16.4.3 allows attacker to execute javascript in victim's browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6033|2024-08-02T08:21:17.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3399|2024-08-02T06:55:03.360Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3399</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 11.6 before 16.3.6, all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.4.2, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.1. It was possible for an unauthorised project or group member to read the CI/CD variables using the custom project templates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3399|2024-08-02T06:55:03.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3993|2024-08-02T07:08:50.764Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3993</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 14.3 before 16.0.8, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.3, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.2. Access tokens may have been logged when a query was made to a specific endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3993|2024-08-02T07:08:50.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4002|2024-08-02T07:17:11.377Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4002</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 14.1 before 16.0.8, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.3, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.2. It was possible for EE-licensed users to link any security policy project by its ID to projects or groups the user has access to, potentially revealing the security projects's configured security policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4002|2024-08-02T07:17:11.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1167|2024-08-02T05:40:58.086Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1167</link>
      <description>Improper authorization in Gitlab EE affecting all versions from 12.3.0 before 15.8.5, all versions starting from 15.9 before 15.9.4, all versions starting from 15.10 before 15.10.1 allows an unauthorized access to security reports in MR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1167|2024-08-02T05:40:58.086Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2232|2024-08-02T06:19:13.591Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2232</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 15.10 before 16.1, leading to a ReDoS vulnerability in the Jira prefix</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2232|2024-08-02T06:19:13.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0155|2024-08-02T05:02:43.635Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0155</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 15.8.5, 15.9.4, 15.10.1. Open redirects was possible due to framing arbitrary content on any page allowing user controlled markdown</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0155|2024-08-02T05:02:43.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0326|2024-08-02T05:10:55.157Z -- gitlab -- gitlab%20dast%20api%20scanner
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0326</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab DAST API scanner affecting all versions starting from 1.6.50 before 2.11.0, where Authorization headers was leaked in vulnerability report evidence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0326|2024-08-02T05:10:55.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0805|2024-08-02T05:24:34.345Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0805</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 15.2 before 15.9.6, all versions starting from 15.10 before 15.10.5, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.1. A malicious group member may continue to have access to the public projects of a public group even after being banned from the public group by the owner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0805|2024-08-02T05:24:34.345Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4011|2024-08-02T07:17:11.267Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4011</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 15.11 prior to 16.2.2 which allows an attacker to spike the resource consumption resulting in DoS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4011|2024-08-02T07:17:11.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 05:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3949|2024-08-02T07:08:50.845Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3949</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 11.3 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for unauthorized users to view a public projects' release descriptions via an atom endpoint when release access on the public was set to only project members.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3949|2024-08-02T07:08:50.845Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0483|2024-08-02T05:10:56.329Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0483</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 12.1 before 15.7.8, all versions starting from 15.8 before 15.8.4, all versions starting from 15.9 before 15.9.2. It was possible for a project maintainer to extract a Datadog integration API key by modifying the site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0483|2024-08-02T05:10:56.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0508|2024-08-02T05:17:48.970Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0508</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.4 before 15.10.8, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.7, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.2. Open redirection was possible via HTTP response splitting in the NPM package API.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0508|2024-08-02T05:17:48.970Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0223|2024-08-02T05:02:43.859Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0223</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 15.5 before 15.7.8, all versions starting from 15.8 before 15.8.4, all versions starting from 15.9 before 15.9.2. Non-project members could retrieve release descriptions via the API, even if the release visibility is restricted to project members only in the project settings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0223|2024-08-02T05:02:43.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2022|2024-08-02T06:12:19.529Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2022</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting before 16.0.8, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.3, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.2, which leads to developers being able to create pipeline schedules on protected branches even if they don't have access to merge</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2022|2024-08-02T06:12:19.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 08:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1936|2024-08-02T06:05:26.764Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1936</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 13.7 before 15.11.10, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.6, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.1, which allows an attacker to leak the email address of a user who created a service desk issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1936|2024-08-02T06:05:26.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 07:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5963|2024-08-02T08:14:25.152Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5963</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE with Advanced Search affecting all versions from 13.9 to 16.3.6, 16.4 prior to 16.4.2 and 16.5 prior to 16.5.1 that could allow a denial of service in the Advanced Search function by chaining too many syntax operators.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5963|2024-08-02T08:14:25.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:18:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1204|2024-08-02T05:40:58.360Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1204</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 10.1 before 15.10.8, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.7, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.2. A user could use an unverified email as a public email and commit email by sending a specifically crafted request on user update settings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1204|2024-08-02T05:40:58.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5933|2024-08-02T08:14:25.134Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5933</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions after 13.7 before 16.6.6, 16.7 prior to 16.7.4, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.1. Improper input sanitization of user name allows arbitrary API PUT requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5933|2024-08-02T08:14:25.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 01:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1787|2024-08-02T05:57:25.239Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1787</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 15.9 before 15.9.4, all versions starting from 15.10 before 15.10.1. A search timeout could be triggered if a specific HTML payload was used in the issue description.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1787|2024-08-02T05:57:25.239Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1708|2024-08-02T05:57:24.793Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1708</link>
      <description>An issue was identified in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 1.0 prior to 15.8.5, 15.9 prior to 15.9.4, and 15.10 prior to 15.10.1 where non-printable characters gets copied from clipboard, allowing unexpected commands to be executed on victim machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1708|2024-08-02T05:57:24.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1265|2024-08-02T05:40:59.892Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1265</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 11.9 before 15.9.6, all versions starting from 15.10 before 15.10.5, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.1. The condition allows for a privileged attacker, under certain conditions, to obtain session tokens from all users of a GitLab instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1265|2024-08-02T05:40:59.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3907|2024-08-02T07:08:50.859Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3907</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.0 prior to 16.4.4, 16.5 prior to 16.5.4, and 16.6 prior to 16.6.2 allows a project Maintainer to use a Project Access Token to escalate their role to Owner</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3907|2024-08-02T07:08:50.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 23:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5512|2024-08-02T07:59:44.782Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5512</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.3 before 16.4.4, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.4, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.2. File integrity may be compromised when specific HTML encoding is used for file names leading for incorrect representation in the UI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5512|2024-08-02T07:59:44.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3102|2024-08-02T06:48:07.147Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3102</link>
      <description>A sensitive information leak issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.6, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.1, which allows access to titles of private issue and MR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3102|2024-08-02T06:48:07.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 15:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5198|2024-08-02T07:52:07.928Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5198</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions prior to 16.2.7, all versions starting from 16.3 before 16.3.5, and all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.4.1. It was possible for a removed project member to write to protected branches using deploy keys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5198|2024-08-02T07:52:07.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 07:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3443|2024-08-02T06:55:03.511Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3443</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 12.1 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for a Guest user to add an emoji on confidential work items.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3443|2024-08-02T06:55:03.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1836|2024-08-02T06:05:26.777Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1836</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 5.1 before 15.9.6, all versions starting from 15.10 before 15.10.5, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.1. When viewing an XML file in a repository in "raw" mode, it can be made to render as HTML if viewed under specific circumstances</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1836|2024-08-02T06:05:26.777Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2576|2024-08-02T06:26:09.897Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2576</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 13.7 before 15.11.10, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.6, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.1. This allowed a developer to remove the CODEOWNERS rules and merge to a protected branch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2576|2024-08-02T06:26:09.897Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 02:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3909|2024-08-02T07:08:50.675Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3909</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.3 before 16.3.6, all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.4.2, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.1. A Regular Expression Denial of Service was possible by adding a large string in timeout input in gitlab-ci.yml file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3909|2024-08-02T07:08:50.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1084|2024-08-02T05:32:46.382Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1084</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 15.7.8, all versions starting from 15.8 before 15.8.4, all versions starting from 15.9 before 15.9.2. A malicious project Maintainer may create a Project Access Token with Owner level privileges using a crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1084|2024-08-02T05:32:46.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2620|2024-08-02T06:26:09.822Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2620</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.1 prior to 15.11.10, all versions from 16.0 prior to 16.0.6, all versions from 16.1 prior to 16.1.1. A maintainer could modify a webhook URL to leak masked webhook secrets by manipulating other masked portions. This addresses an incomplete fix for CVE-2023-0838.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2620|2024-08-02T06:26:09.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 02:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3205|2024-08-02T06:48:08.280Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3205</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 15.11 before 16.1.5, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.5, all versions starting from 16.3 before 16.3.1. An authenticated user could trigger a denial of service when importing or cloning malicious content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3205|2024-08-02T06:48:08.280Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 10:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3964|2024-08-02T07:08:50.762Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3964</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 13.2 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for users to access composer packages on public projects that have package registry disabled in the project settings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3964|2024-08-02T07:08:50.762Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:02:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3950|2024-08-02T07:08:50.670Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3950</link>
      <description>An information disclosure issue in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.2 prior to 16.2.5, and 16.3 prior to 16.3.1 allowed other Group Owners to see the Public Key for a Google Cloud Logging audit event streaming destination, if configured. Owners can now only write the key, not read it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3950|2024-08-02T07:08:50.670Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 10:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2198|2024-08-02T06:12:20.673Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2198</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 8.7 before 15.10.8, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.7, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.2. A Regular Expression Denial of Service was possible via sending crafted payloads to the preview_markdown endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2198|2024-08-02T06:12:20.673Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1710|2024-08-02T05:57:25.060Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1710</link>
      <description>A sensitive information disclosure vulnerability in GitLab affecting all versions from 15.0 prior to 15.8.5, 15.9 prior to 15.9.4 and 15.10 prior to 15.10.1 allows an attacker to view the count of internal notes for a given issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1710|2024-08-02T05:57:25.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2190|2024-08-02T06:12:20.660Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2190</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 13.10 before 15.11.10, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.6, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.1. It may be possible for users to view new commits to private projects in a fork created while the project was public.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2190|2024-08-02T06:12:20.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 02:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3484|2024-08-02T06:55:03.354Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3484</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 12.8 before 15.11.11, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.7, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.2. An attacker could change the name or path of a public top-level group in certain situations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3484|2024-08-02T06:55:03.354Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 13:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5009|2024-08-02T07:44:53.779Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5009</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 13.12 before 16.2.7, all versions starting from 16.3 before 16.3.4. It was possible for an attacker to run pipeline jobs as an arbitrary user via scheduled security scan policies. This was a bypass of [CVE-2023-3932](https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3932) showing additional impact.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5009|2024-08-02T07:44:53.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 07:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4378|2024-08-02T07:24:04.549Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4378</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 11.8 before 16.1.5, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.5, all versions starting from 16.3 before 16.3.1. A malicious Maintainer can, under specific circumstances, leak the sentry token by changing the configured URL in the Sentry error tracking settings page. This was as a result of an incomplete fix for CVE-2022-4365.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4378|2024-08-02T07:24:04.549Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 10:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1098|2024-08-02T05:32:46.366Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1098</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability has been discovered in GitLab EE/CE affecting all versions starting from 11.5 before 15.8.5, all versions starting from 15.9 before 15.9.4, all versions starting from 15.10 before 15.10.1 will allow an admin to leak password from repository mirror configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1098|2024-08-02T05:32:46.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0632|2024-08-02T05:17:50.249Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0632</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 15.2 before 16.0.8, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.3, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.2. A Regular Expression Denial of Service was possible by using crafted payloads to search Harbor Registry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0632|2024-08-02T05:17:50.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 23:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5332|2024-08-02T07:52:08.548Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5332</link>
      <description>Patch in third party library Consul requires 'enable-script-checks' to be set to False. This was required to enable a patch by the vendor. Without this setting the patch could be bypassed. This only affects GitLab-EE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5332|2024-08-02T07:52:08.548Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 06:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1417|2024-08-02T05:49:11.429Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1417</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 15.9 before 15.9.4, all versions starting from 15.10 before 15.10.1. It was possible for an unauthorised user to add child epics linked to victim's epic in an unrelated group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1417|2024-08-02T05:49:11.429Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2485|2024-08-02T06:26:08.924Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2485</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 14.1 before 15.10.8, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.7, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.2. A malicious maintainer in a project can escalate other users to Owners in that project if they import members from another project that those other users are Owners of.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2485|2024-08-02T06:26:08.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1733|2024-08-02T05:57:25.240Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1733</link>
      <description>A denial of service condition exists in the Prometheus server bundled with GitLab affecting all versions from 11.10 to 15.8.5, 15.9 to 15.9.4 and 15.10 to 15.10.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1733|2024-08-02T05:57:25.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5226|2024-08-02T07:52:08.425Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5226</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. Under certain circumstances, a malicious actor bypass prohibited branch checks using a specially crafted branch name to manipulate repository content in the UI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5226|2024-08-02T07:52:08.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6680|2024-08-02T08:35:14.879Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6680</link>
      <description>An improper certificate validation issue in Smartcard authentication in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 11.6 prior to 16.4.4, 16.5 prior to 16.5.4, and 16.6 prior to 16.6.2 allows an attacker to authenticate as another user given their public key if they use Smartcard authentication. Smartcard authentication is an experimental feature and has to be manually enabled by an administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6680|2024-08-02T08:35:14.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 16:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3444|2024-08-02T06:55:03.538Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3444</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.3 before 15.11.10, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.6, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.1, which allows an attacker to merge arbitrary code into protected branches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3444|2024-08-02T06:55:03.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 02:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5356|2024-08-02T07:59:43.251Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5356</link>
      <description>Incorrect authorization checks in GitLab CE/EE from all versions starting from 8.13 before 16.5.6, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.4, all versions starting from 16.7 before 16.7.2, allows a user to abuse slack/mattermost integrations to execute slash commands as another user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5356|2024-08-02T07:59:43.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 13:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2164|2024-08-02T06:12:20.617Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2164</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 15.9 before 16.0.8, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.3, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.2. It was possible for an attacker to trigger a stored XSS vulnerability via user interaction with a crafted URL in the WebIDE beta.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2164|2024-08-02T06:12:20.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 23:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4630|2024-08-02T07:31:06.683Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4630</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 10.6 before 16.1.5, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.5, all versions starting from 16.3 before 16.3.1 in which any user can read limited information about any project's imports.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4630|2024-08-02T07:31:06.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 13:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1621|2024-08-02T05:57:24.643Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1621</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 before 15.10.5, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.1. A malicious group member may continue to commit to projects even from a restricted IP address.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1621|2024-08-02T05:57:24.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2182|2024-08-02T06:12:20.652Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2182</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 15.10 before 15.10.5, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.1. Under certain conditions when OpenID Connect is enabled on an instance, it may allow users who are marked as 'external' to become 'regular' users thus leading to privilege escalation for those users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2182|2024-08-02T06:12:20.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3364|2024-08-02T06:55:02.657Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3364</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 8.14 before 16.0.8, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.3, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.2. A Regular Expression Denial of Service was possible via sending crafted payloads which use AutolinkFilter to the preview_markdown endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3364|2024-08-02T06:55:02.657Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 23:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0120|2024-08-02T05:02:43.687Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0120</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 10.0 before 16.1.5, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.5, all versions starting from 16.3 before 16.3.1. Due to improper permission validation it was possible to edit labels description by an unauthorised user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0120|2024-08-02T05:02:43.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 10:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3424|2024-08-02T06:55:03.222Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3424</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 10.3 before 15.11.10, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.6, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.1. A Regular Expression Denial of Service was possible via sending crafted payloads to the preview_markdown endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3424|2024-08-02T06:55:03.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 02:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1210|2024-08-02T05:40:59.650Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1210</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 12.9 before 16.0.8, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.3, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.2. It was possible to leak a user's email via an error message for groups that restrict membership by email domain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1210|2024-08-02T05:40:59.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 23:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2200|2024-08-02T06:12:20.653Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2200</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 7.14 before 15.11.10, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.6, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.1, which allows an attacker to inject HTML in an email address field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2200|2024-08-02T06:12:20.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 02:02:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1401|2024-08-02T05:49:11.372Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1401</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab DAST scanner affecting all versions starting from 3.0.29 before 4.0.5, in which the DAST scanner leak cross site cookies on redirect during authorization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1401|2024-08-02T05:49:11.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 06:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5995|2024-08-02T08:14:25.158Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5995</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for an attacker to abuse the policy bot to gain access to internal projects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5995|2024-08-02T08:14:25.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5612|2024-08-02T08:07:32.101Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5612</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 16.6.6, 16.7 prior to 16.7.4, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.1. It was possible to read the user email address via tags feed although the visibility in the user profile has been disabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5612|2024-08-02T08:07:32.101Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 02:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4008|2024-08-02T07:17:10.997Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4008</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.9 before 16.0.8, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.3, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.2. It was possible to takeover GitLab Pages with unique domain URLs if the random string added was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4008|2024-08-02T07:17:10.997Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 06:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2199|2024-08-02T06:12:20.665Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2199</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 before 15.10.8, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.7, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.2. A Regular Expression Denial of Service was possible via sending crafted payloads to the preview_markdown endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2199|2024-08-02T06:12:20.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4018|2024-08-02T07:17:11.580Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4018</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.5, all versions starting from 16.3 before 16.3.1. Due to improper permission validation it was possible to create model experiments in public projects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4018|2024-08-02T07:17:11.580Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 10:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3210|2024-08-02T06:48:08.043Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3210</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 15.11 before 16.1.5, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.5, all versions starting from 16.3 before 16.3.1. An authenticated user could trigger a denial of service when importing or cloning malicious content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3210|2024-08-02T06:48:08.043Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 10:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2069|2024-08-02T06:12:20.196Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2069</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 10.0 before 12.9.8, all versions starting from 12.10 before 12.10.7, all versions starting from 13.0 before 13.0.1. A user with the role of developer could use the import project feature to leak CI/CD variables.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2069|2024-08-02T06:12:20.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5106|2024-08-02T07:44:53.795Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5106</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in Ultimate-licensed GitLab EE affecting all versions starting 13.12 prior to 16.2.8, 16.3.0 prior to 16.3.5, and 16.4.0 prior to 16.4.1 that could allow an attacker to impersonate users in CI pipelines through direct transfer group imports.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5106|2024-08-02T07:44:53.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 11:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3385|2024-08-02T06:55:03.047Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3385</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 8.10 before 16.0.8, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.3, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.2. Under specific circumstances, a user importing a project 'from export' could access and read unrelated files via uploading a specially crafted file. This was due to a bug in `tar`, fixed in [`tar-1.35`](https://lists.gnu.org/archive/html/info-gnu/2023-07/msg00005.html).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3385|2024-08-02T06:55:03.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 23:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3979|2024-08-02T07:08:50.787Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3979</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 10.6 before 16.2.8, all versions starting from 16.3 before 16.3.5, all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.4.1. It was possible that upstream members to collaborate with you on your branch get permission to write to the merge request’s source branch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3979|2024-08-02T07:08:50.787Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 06:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4812|2024-08-02T07:38:00.651Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4812</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 15.3 before 16.5.6, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.4, all versions starting from 16.7 before 16.7.2. The required CODEOWNERS approval could be bypassed by adding changes to a previously approved merge request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4812|2024-08-02T07:38:00.651Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 13:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3511|2024-08-02T06:55:03.372Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3511</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 8.17 before 16.4.4, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.4, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.2. It was possible for auditor users to fork and submit merge requests to private projects they're not a member of.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3511|2024-08-02T06:55:03.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1072|2024-08-02T05:32:46.375Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1072</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 9.0 before 15.7.8, all versions starting from 15.8 before 15.8.4, all versions starting from 15.9 before 15.9.2. It was possible to trigger a resource depletion attack due to improper filtering for number of requests to read commits details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1072|2024-08-02T05:32:46.375Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3401|2024-08-02T06:55:03.501Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3401</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 16.0.8, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.3, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.2. The main branch of a repository with a specially designed name allows an attacker to create repositories with malicious code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3401|2024-08-02T06:55:03.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 08:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3917|2024-08-02T07:08:50.793Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3917</link>
      <description>Denial of Service in pipelines affecting all versions of Gitlab EE and CE prior to 16.2.8, 16.3 prior to 16.3.5, and 16.4 prior to 16.4.1 allows attacker to cause pipelines to fail.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3917|2024-08-02T07:08:50.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 06:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3922|2024-08-02T07:08:50.765Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3922</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 8.15 before 16.2.8, all versions starting from 16.3 before 16.3.5, all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.4.1. It was possible to hijack some links and buttons on the GitLab UI to a malicious page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3922|2024-08-02T07:08:50.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 07:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7028|2024-08-02T08:50:07.648Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7028</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.1 prior to 16.1.6, 16.2 prior to 16.2.9, 16.3 prior to 16.3.7, 16.4 prior to 16.4.5, 16.5 prior to 16.5.6, 16.6 prior to 16.6.4, and 16.7 prior to 16.7.2 in which user account password reset emails could be delivered to an unverified email address.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7028|2024-08-02T08:50:07.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 13:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0518|2024-08-02T05:17:49.377Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0518</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 14.0 before 15.6.7, all versions starting from 15.7 before 15.7.6, all versions starting from 15.8 before 15.8.1. It was possible to trigger a DoS attack by uploading a malicious Helm chart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0518|2024-08-02T05:17:49.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5061|2024-08-02T07:44:53.785Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5061</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 9.3 before 16.4.4, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.4, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.2. In certain situations, it may have been possible for developers to override predefined CI variables via the REST API.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5061|2024-08-02T07:44:53.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 16:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3914|2024-08-02T07:08:50.677Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3914</link>
      <description>A business logic error in GitLab EE affecting all versions prior to 16.2.8, 16.3 prior to 16.3.5, and 16.4 prior to 16.4.1 allows access to internal projects. A service account is not deleted when a namespace is deleted, allowing access to internal projects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3914|2024-08-02T07:08:50.677Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 06:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4647|2024-08-02T07:31:06.690Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4647</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 15.2 before 16.1.5, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.5, all versions starting from 16.3 before 16.3.1 in which the projects API pagination can be skipped, potentially leading to DoS on certain instances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4647|2024-08-02T07:31:06.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 10:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2013|2024-08-02T06:12:19.526Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2013</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 1.2 before 15.10.8, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.7, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.2. An issue was found that allows someone to abuse a discrepancy between the Web application display and the git command line interface to social engineer victims into cloning non-trusted code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2013|2024-08-02T06:12:19.526Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3413|2024-08-02T06:55:03.412Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3413</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.8, all versions starting from 16.3 before 16.3.5, all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.4.1. It was possible to read the source code of a project through a fork created before changing visibility to only project members.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3413|2024-08-02T06:55:03.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 08:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6159|2024-08-02T08:21:17.706Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6159</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 12.7 prior to 16.6.6, 16.7 prior to 16.7.4, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.1 It was possible for an attacker to trigger a Regular Expression Denial of Service via a `Cargo.toml` containing maliciously crafted input.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6159|2024-08-02T08:21:17.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 02:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1825|2024-08-02T06:05:26.652Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1825</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 15.7 before 15.10.8, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.7, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.2. It was possible to disclose issue notes to an unauthorized user at project export.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1825|2024-08-02T06:05:26.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4317|2024-08-02T07:24:03.786Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4317</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 9.2 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for a user with the Developer role to update a pipeline schedule from an unprotected branch to a protected branch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4317|2024-08-02T07:24:03.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3362|2024-08-02T06:55:02.661Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3362</link>
      <description>An information disclosure issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.0 prior to 16.0.6, and version 16.1.0 allows unauthenticated actors to access the import error information if a project was imported from GitHub.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3362|2024-08-02T06:55:02.661Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 02:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2589|2024-08-02T06:26:09.698Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2589</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 before 15.10.8, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.7, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.2. An attacker can clone a repository from a public project, from a disallowed IP, even after the top-level group has enabled IP restrictions on the group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2589|2024-08-02T06:26:09.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3932|2024-08-02T07:08:50.781Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3932</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 13.12 before 16.0.8, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.3, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.2. It was possible for an attacker to run pipeline jobs as an arbitrary user via scheduled security scan policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3932|2024-08-02T07:08:50.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 04:01:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3900|2024-08-02T07:08:50.790Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3900</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.3, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.2. An invalid 'start_sha' value on merge requests page may lead to Denial of Service as Changes tab would not load.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3900|2024-08-02T07:08:50.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2442|2024-08-02T06:19:15.149Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2442</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.7, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.2. A specially crafted merge request could lead to a stored XSS on the client side which allows attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2442|2024-08-02T06:19:15.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2478|2024-08-02T06:26:08.974Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2478</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.4 before 15.9.7, all versions starting from 15.10 before 15.10.6, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.2. Under certain conditions, a malicious unauthorized GitLab user may use a GraphQL endpoint to attach a malicious runner to any project.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2478|2024-08-02T06:26:08.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0485|2024-08-02T05:10:56.451Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0485</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 13.11 before 15.8.5, all versions starting from 15.9 before 15.9.4, all versions starting from 15.10 before 15.10.1. It was possible that a project member demoted to a user role to read project updates by doing a diff with a pre-existing fork.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0485|2024-08-02T05:10:56.451Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3920|2024-08-02T07:08:50.695Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3920</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 11.2 before 16.2.8, all versions starting from 16.3 before 16.3.5, all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.4.1. It was possible that a maintainer to create a fork relationship between existing projects contrary to the documentation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3920|2024-08-02T07:08:50.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 06:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1555|2024-08-02T05:49:11.671Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1555</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 15.2 before 16.1.5, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.5, all versions starting from 16.3 before 16.3.1. A namespace-level banned user can access the API.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1555|2024-08-02T05:49:11.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 10:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0523|2024-08-02T05:17:49.250Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0523</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 15.6 before 15.8.5, 15.9 before 15.9.4, and 15.10 before 15.10.1. An XSS was possible via a malicious email address for certain instances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0523|2024-08-02T05:17:49.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4658|2024-08-02T07:31:06.624Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4658</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 8.13 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for an attacker to abuse the `Allowed to merge` permission as a guest user, when granted the permission through a group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4658|2024-08-02T07:31:06.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:01:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3915|2024-08-02T07:08:50.788Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3915</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.5, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.5, all versions starting from 16.3 before 16.3.1. If an external user is given an owner role on any group, that external user may escalate their privileges on the instance by creating a service account in that group. This service account is not classified as external and may be used to access internal projects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3915|2024-08-02T07:08:50.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 10:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0450|2024-08-02T05:10:56.334Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0450</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 8.1 to 15.8.5, and from 15.9 to 15.9.4, and from 15.10 to 15.10.1. It was possible to add a branch with an ambiguous name that could be used to social engineer users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0450|2024-08-02T05:10:56.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3115|2024-08-02T06:48:07.189Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3115</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions affecting all versions from 11.11 prior to 16.2.8, 16.3 prior to 16.3.5, and 16.4 prior to 16.4.1. Single Sign On restrictions were not correctly enforced for indirect project members accessing public members-only project repositories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3115|2024-08-02T06:48:07.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 06:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0838|2024-08-02T05:24:34.393Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0838</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting versions starting from 15.1 before 15.8.5, 15.9 before 15.9.4, and 15.10 before 15.10.1. A maintainer could modify a webhook URL to leak masked webhook secrets by adding a new parameter to the url. This addresses an incomplete fix for CVE-2022-4342.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0838|2024-08-02T05:24:34.393Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5207|2024-08-02T07:52:07.762Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5207</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was discovered in GitLab CE and EE affecting all versions starting 16.0 prior to 16.2.8, 16.3 prior to 16.3.5, and 16.4 prior to 16.4.1. An authenticated attacker could perform arbitrary pipeline execution under the context of another user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5207|2024-08-02T07:52:07.762Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 08:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2030|2024-08-02T06:12:19.983Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2030</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 12.2 prior to 16.5.6, 16.6 prior to 16.6.4, and 16.7 prior to 16.7.2 in which an attacker could potentially modify the metadata of signed commits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2030|2024-08-02T06:12:19.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 13:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4522|2024-08-02T07:31:06.112Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4522</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 16.2.0. Committing directories containing LF character results in 500 errors when viewing the commit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4522|2024-08-02T07:31:06.112Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 07:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3904|2024-08-02T07:08:50.867Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3904</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting before 16.4.4, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.4, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.2. It was possible to overflow the time spent on an issue that altered the details shown in the issue boards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3904|2024-08-02T07:08:50.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 16:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3500|2024-08-02T06:55:03.361Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3500</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 10.0 before 16.0.8, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.3, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.2. A reflected XSS was possible when creating specific PlantUML diagrams that allowed the attacker to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3500|2024-08-02T06:55:03.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2015|2024-08-02T06:12:19.501Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2015</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 before 15.10.8, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.7, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.2. A reflected XSS was possible when creating new abuse reports which allows attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2015|2024-08-02T06:12:19.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4912|2024-08-02T07:44:52.047Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4912</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 10.5 before 16.4.3, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.3, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.1. It was possible for an attacker to cause a client-side denial of service using malicious crafted mermaid diagram input.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4912|2024-08-02T07:44:52.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3906|2024-08-02T07:08:50.669Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3906</link>
      <description>An input validation issue in the asset proxy in GitLab EE, affecting all versions from 12.3 prior to 16.2.8, 16.3 prior to 16.3.5, and 16.4 prior to 16.4.1, allowed an authenticated attacker to craft image urls which bypass the asset proxy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3906|2024-08-02T07:08:50.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 06:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2001|2024-08-02T06:05:27.137Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2001</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 15.10.8, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.7, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.2. An attacker was able to spoof protected tags, which could potentially lead a victim to download malicious code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2001|2024-08-02T06:05:27.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2181|2024-08-02T06:12:20.627Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2181</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 15.9.8, 15.10.0 before 15.10.7, and 15.11.0 before 15.11.3. A malicious developer could use a git feature called refs/replace to smuggle content into a merge request which would not be visible during review in the UI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2181|2024-08-02T06:12:20.627Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1965|2024-08-02T06:05:27.087Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1965</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 14.2 before 15.9.6, all versions starting from 15.10 before 15.10.5, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.1. Lack of verification on RelayState parameter allowed a maliciously crafted URL to obtain access tokens granted for 3rd party Group SAML SSO logins. This feature isn't enabled by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1965|2024-08-02T06:05:27.087Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1279|2024-08-02T05:40:59.806Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1279</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 4.1 before 16.1.5, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.5, all versions starting from 16.3 before 16.3.1 where it was possible to create a URL that would redirect to a different project.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1279|2024-08-02T05:40:59.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 10:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2132|2024-08-02T06:12:20.575Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2132</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.4 before 15.10.8, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.7, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.2. A DollarMathPostFilter Regular Expression Denial of Service in was possible by sending crafted payloads to the preview_markdown endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2132|2024-08-02T06:12:20.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3246|2024-08-02T06:48:08.258Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3246</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE/CE affecting all versions starting before 16.3.6, all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.4.2, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.1 which allows an attackers to block Sidekiq job processor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3246|2024-08-02T06:48:08.258Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5825|2024-08-02T08:14:24.604Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5825</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.3.6, all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.4.2, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.1. A low-privileged attacker can point a CI/CD Component to an incorrect path and cause the server to exhaust all available memory through an infinite loop and cause Denial of Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5825|2024-08-02T08:14:24.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 10:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2825|2024-08-02T06:33:05.812Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2825</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting only version 16.0.0. An unauthenticated malicious user can use a path traversal vulnerability to read arbitrary files on the server when an attachment exists in a public project nested within at least five groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2825|2024-08-02T06:33:05.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6955|2024-08-02T08:42:08.572Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6955</link>
      <description>An improper access control vulnerability exists in GitLab Remote Development affecting all versions prior to 16.5.6, 16.6 prior to 16.6.4 and 16.7 prior to 16.7.2. This condition allows an attacker to create a workspace in one group that is associated with an agent from another group. </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6955|2024-08-02T08:42:08.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 13:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1178|2024-08-02T05:40:58.154Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1178</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 8.6 before 15.9.6, all versions starting from 15.10 before 15.10.5, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.1. File integrity may be compromised when source code or installation packages are pulled from a tag or from a release containing a ref to another commit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1178|2024-08-02T05:40:58.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6051|2024-08-02T08:21:17.188Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6051</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.4.4, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.4, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.2. File integrity may be compromised when source code or installation packages are pulled from a specific tag.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6051|2024-08-02T08:21:17.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 16:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5831|2024-08-02T08:14:24.606Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5831</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.3.6, all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.4.2, and all versions starting from 16.5.0 before 16.5.1 which have the `super_sidebar_logged_out` feature flag enabled. Affected versions with this default-disabled feature flag enabled may unintentionally disclose GitLab version metadata to unauthorized actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5831|2024-08-02T08:14:24.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 10:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2233|2024-08-02T06:19:13.579Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2233</link>
      <description>An improper authorization issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 11.8 before 16.2.8, all versions starting from 16.3 before 16.3.5 and all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.4.1. It allows a project reporter to leak the owner's Sentry instance projects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2233|2024-08-02T06:19:13.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 06:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0921|2024-08-02T05:24:34.643Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0921</link>
      <description>A lack of length validation in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 8.3 before 15.10.8, 15.11 before 15.11.7, and 16.0 before 16.0.2 allows an authenticated attacker to create a large Issue description via GraphQL which, when repeatedly requested, saturates CPU usage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0921|2024-08-02T05:24:34.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4532|2024-08-02T07:31:06.033Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4532</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.8, all versions starting from 16.3 before 16.3.5, all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.4.1. Users were capable of linking CI/CD jobs of private projects which they are not a member of.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4532|2024-08-02T07:31:06.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 06:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0121|2024-08-02T05:02:43.992Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0121</link>
      <description>A denial of service issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 13.2.4 before 15.10.8, all versions starting from 15.11 before 15.11.7, all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.0.2 which allows an attacker to cause high resource consumption using malicious test report artifacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0121|2024-08-02T05:02:43.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4700|2024-08-02T07:37:59.401Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4700</link>
      <description>An authorization issue affecting GitLab EE affecting all versions from 14.7 prior to 16.3.6, 16.4 prior to 16.4.2, and 16.5 prior to 16.5.1, allowed a user to run jobs in protected environments, bypassing any required approvals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4700|2024-08-02T07:37:59.401Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 17:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3994|2024-08-02T07:08:50.873Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3994</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 9.3 before 16.0.8, all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.1.3, all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.2.2. A Regular Expression Denial of Service was possible via sending crafted payloads which use ProjectReferenceFilter to the preview_markdown endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3994|2024-08-02T07:08:50.873Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0050|2024-08-02T04:54:32.609Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0050</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 13.7 before 15.7.8, all versions starting from 15.8 before 15.8.4, all versions starting from 15.9 before 15.9.2. A specially crafted Kroki diagram could lead to a stored XSS on the client side which allows attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0050|2024-08-02T04:54:32.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0319|2024-08-02T05:10:55.061Z -- gitlab -- gitlab
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0319</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 13.6 before 15.8.5, all versions starting from 15.9 before 15.9.4, all versions starting from 15.10 before 15.10.1, allowing to read environment names supposed to be restricted to project memebers only.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0319|2024-08-02T05:10:55.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4895|2024-08-02T07:38:01.031Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4895</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 to 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. This vulnerability allows for bypassing the 'group ip restriction' settings to access environment details of projects</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4895|2024-08-02T07:38:01.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4011|2024-08-01T20:26:57.321Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4011</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.1 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows non-project member to promote key results to objectives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4011|2024-08-01T20:26:57.321Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3959|2024-08-01T20:26:57.148Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3959</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows private job artifacts can be accessed by any user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3959|2024-08-01T20:26:57.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4201|2024-08-01T20:33:52.911Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4201</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 5.1 before 16.10.7, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.111.4, all versions starting from 17.0 before 17.0.2. When viewing an XML file in a repository in raw mode, it can be made to render as HTML if viewed under specific circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4201|2024-08-01T20:33:52.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4557|2024-08-01T20:47:41.409Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4557</link>
      <description>Multiple Denial of Service (DoS) conditions has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 1.0 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1 which allowed an attacker to cause resource exhaustion via banzai pipeline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4557|2024-08-01T20:47:41.409Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4006|2024-08-01T20:26:57.281Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4006</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1 where personal access scopes were not honored by GraphQL subscriptions</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4006|2024-08-01T20:26:57.281Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4901|2024-08-01T20:55:10.235Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4901</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, where a stored XSS vulnerability could be imported from a project with malicious commit notes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4901|2024-08-01T20:55:10.235Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4597|2024-08-01T20:47:41.257Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4597</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.7 before 16.9.7, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.5, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.2. An attacker could force a user with an active SAML session to approve an MR via CSRF.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4597|2024-08-01T20:47:41.257Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4539|2024-08-01T20:40:47.531Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4539</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.4 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2 where abusing the API to filter branch and tags could lead to Denial of Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4539|2024-08-01T20:40:47.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4835|2024-08-01T20:55:10.129Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4835</link>
      <description>A XSS condition exists within GitLab in versions 15.11 before 16.10.6, 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1. By leveraging this condition, an attacker can craft a malicious page to exfiltrate sensitive user information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4835|2024-08-01T20:55:10.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 06:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4024|2024-08-01T20:26:57.255Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4024</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 7.8 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker with their Bitbucket account credentials may be able to take over a GitLab account linked to another user's Bitbucket account, if Bitbucket is used as an OAuth 2.0 provider on GitLab.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4024|2024-08-01T20:26:57.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1066|2024-08-01T18:26:30.545Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1066</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 13.3.0 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows an attacker to do a resource exhaustion using GraphQL `vulnerabilitiesCountByDay`</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1066|2024-08-01T18:26:30.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1250|2024-08-01T18:33:25.356Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1250</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.2. When a user is assigned a custom role with manage_group_access_tokens permission, they may be able to create group access tokens with Owner privileges, which may lead to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1250|2024-08-01T18:33:25.356Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 20:47:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1816|2024-08-01T18:48:21.985Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1816</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows for an attacker to cause a denial of service using a crafted OpenAPI file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1816|2024-08-01T18:48:21.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1495|2024-08-01T18:40:21.205Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1495</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 13.1 prior to 16.10.7, starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.4, and starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using maliciously crafted file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1495|2024-08-01T18:40:21.205Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1347|2024-08-01T18:33:25.387Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1347</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker through a crafted email address may be able to bypass domain based restrictions on an instance or a group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1347|2024-08-01T18:33:25.387Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1299|2024-08-01T18:33:25.390Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1299</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 16.8 prior to 16.8.4 and 16.9 prior to 16.9.2. It was possible for a user with custom role of `manage_group_access_tokens` to rotate group access tokens with owner privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1299|2024-08-01T18:33:25.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:39:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1736|2024-08-01T18:48:21.821Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1736</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions prior to 16.10.7, starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.4, and starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.2. A vulnerability in GitLab's CI/CD pipeline editor could allow for denial of service attacks through maliciously crafted configuration files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1736|2024-08-01T18:48:21.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1451|2024-08-01T18:40:21.118Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1451</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. A crafted payload  added to the user profile page could lead to a stored XSS on the client side, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1451|2024-08-01T18:40:21.118Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0410|2024-08-01T18:04:49.660Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0410</link>
      <description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 15.1 prior to 16.7.6, 16.8 prior to 16.8.3, and 16.9 prior to 16.9.1. A developer could bypass CODEOWNERS approvals by creating a merge conflict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0410|2024-08-01T18:04:49.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1963|2024-08-01T18:56:22.389Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1963</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 8.4 prior to 16.10.7, starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.4, and starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.2. A vulnerability in GitLab's Asana integration allowed an attacker to potentially cause a regular expression denial of service by sending specially crafted requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1963|2024-08-01T18:56:22.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1493|2024-08-01T18:40:21.333Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1493</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 9.2 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, with the processing logic for generating link in dependency files can lead to a regular  expression DoS attack on the server</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1493|2024-08-01T18:40:21.333Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1947|2024-08-01T18:56:22.407Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1947</link>
      <description>A denial of service (DoS) condition was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 13.2.4 before 16.10.6, 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1. By leveraging this vulnerability an attacker could create a DoS condition by sending crafted API calls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1947|2024-08-01T18:56:22.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0861|2024-08-01T18:18:18.806Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0861</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. Users with the `Guest` role can change `Custom dashboard projects` settings contrary to permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0861|2024-08-01T18:18:18.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1525|2024-08-01T18:40:21.306Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1525</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. Under some specialized conditions, an LDAP user may be able to reset their password using their verified secondary email address and sign-in using direct authentication with the reset password, bypassing LDAP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1525|2024-08-01T18:40:21.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6678|2024-07-31T15:49:40.510Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6678</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions before 16.8.6, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a  denial of service using malicious crafted content in a junit test report file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6678|2024-07-31T15:49:40.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7057|2024-07-26T15:55:10.800Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7057</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where job artifacts can be inappropriately exposed to users lacking the proper authorization level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7057|2024-07-26T15:55:10.800Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5067|2024-07-26T15:33:01.159Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5067</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.11 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where certain project-level analytics settings could be leaked in DOM to group members with Developer or higher roles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5067|2024-07-26T15:33:01.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7091|2024-07-25T15:03:32.800Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7091</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.6 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where it was possible to disclose limited information of an exported group or project to another user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7091|2024-07-25T15:03:32.800Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7060|2024-07-25T13:43:31.196Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7060</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE in project/group exports affecting all versions from 15.4 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allows unauthorized users to view the resultant export.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7060|2024-07-25T13:43:31.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0231|2024-07-25T13:39:35.927Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0231</link>
      <description>A resource misdirection vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE versions 12.0 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allows an attacker to craft a repository import in such a way as to misdirect commits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0231|2024-07-25T13:39:35.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5067|2024-07-24T22:08:05.034Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5067</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.11 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where certain project-level analytics settings could be leaked in DOM to group members with Developer or higher roles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5067|2024-07-24T22:08:05.034Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7060|2024-07-24T22:07:50.018Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7060</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE in project/group exports affecting all versions from 15.4 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allows unauthorized users to view the resultant export.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7060|2024-07-24T22:07:50.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0231|2024-07-24T22:08:20.025Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0231</link>
      <description>A resource misdirection vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE versions 12.0 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allows an attacker to craft a repository import in such a way as to misdirect commits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0231|2024-07-24T22:08:20.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7091|2024-07-24T22:07:45.260Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7091</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.6 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where it was possible to disclose limited information of an exported group or project to another user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7091|2024-07-24T22:07:45.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2177|2024-07-24T14:58:58.843Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2177</link>
      <description>A Cross Window Forgery vulnerability exists within GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.3 prior to 16.11.5, 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and 17.1 prior to 17.1.1. This condition allows for an attacker to abuse the OAuth authentication flow via a crafted payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2177|2024-07-24T14:58:58.843Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 13:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0199|2024-07-24T14:03:21.689Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0199</link>
      <description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 11.3 prior to 16.7.7, 16.7.6 prior to 16.8.4, and 16.8.3 prior to 16.9.2. An attacker could bypass CODEOWNERS by utilizing a crafted payload in an old feature branch to perform malicious actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0199|2024-07-24T14:03:21.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0861|2024-07-24T04:10:10.463Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0861</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. Users with the `Guest` role can change `Custom dashboard projects` settings contrary to permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0861|2024-07-24T04:10:10.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6736|2024-07-24T04:09:44.153Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6736</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 11.3 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for an attacker to cause a client-side denial of service using malicious crafted content in the CODEOWNERS file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6736|2024-07-24T04:09:44.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2829|2024-07-24T04:10:39.344Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2829</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.5 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. A crafted wildcard filter in FileFinder may lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2829|2024-07-24T04:10:39.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6477|2024-07-24T04:09:29.153Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6477</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. When a user is assigned a custom role with admin_group_member permission, they may be able to make a group, other members or themselves Owners of that group, which may lead to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6477|2024-07-24T04:09:29.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4895|2024-07-24T04:08:04.067Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4895</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 to 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. This vulnerability allows for bypassing the 'group ip restriction' settings to access environment details of projects</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4895|2024-07-24T04:08:04.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2279|2024-07-24T04:10:29.316Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2279</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 to 16.8.6 all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. Using the autocomplete for issues references feature a crafted payload may lead to a stored XSS, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2279|2024-07-24T04:10:29.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6489|2024-07-24T04:09:34.159Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6489</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability was identified in GitLab CE/EE, versions 16.7.7 prior to 16.8.6, 16.9 prior to 16.9.4 and 16.10 prior to 16.10.2 which allows an attacker to spike the GitLab instance resources usage resulting in service degradation via chat integration feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6489|2024-07-24T04:09:34.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1451|2024-07-24T04:10:24.317Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1451</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. A crafted payload  added to the user profile page could lead to a stored XSS on the client side, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1451|2024-07-24T04:10:24.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3092|2024-07-24T04:10:44.319Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3092</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. A payload may lead to a Stored XSS while using the diff viewer, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3092|2024-07-24T04:10:44.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1347|2024-07-24T04:10:19.323Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1347</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker through a crafted email address may be able to bypass domain based restrictions on an instance or a group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1347|2024-07-24T04:10:19.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3509|2024-07-24T04:05:52.646Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3509</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for group members with sub-maintainer role to change the title of privately accessible deploy keys associated with projects in the group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3509|2024-07-24T04:05:52.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0410|2024-07-24T04:10:05.499Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0410</link>
      <description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 15.1 prior to 16.7.6, 16.8 prior to 16.8.3, and 16.9 prior to 16.9.1. A developer could bypass CODEOWNERS approvals by creating a merge conflict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0410|2024-07-24T04:10:05.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6678|2024-07-24T04:09:39.155Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6678</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions before 16.8.6, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a  denial of service using malicious crafted content in a junit test report file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6678|2024-07-24T04:09:39.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6371|2024-07-24T04:09:24.158Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6371</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.8.5, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.3, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.1. A wiki page with a crafted payload may lead to a Stored XSS, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6371|2024-07-24T04:09:24.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 07:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2434|2024-07-24T04:10:34.320Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2434</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions of GitLab CE/EE  16.9 prior to 16.9.6, 16.10 prior to 16.10.4, and 16.11 prior to 16.11.1 where path traversal could lead to DoS and restricted file read.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2434|2024-07-24T04:10:34.320Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6840|2024-07-24T04:09:49.152Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6840</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.4 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows a maintainer to change the name of a protected branch that bypasses the security policy added to block MR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6840|2024-07-24T04:09:49.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6688|2024-07-23T17:47:37.023Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6688</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. A problem with the processing logic for Google Chat Messages integration may lead to a regular expression DoS attack on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6688|2024-07-23T17:47:37.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6595|2024-07-17T19:48:11.724Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6595</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 11.8 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 where it was possible to upload an NPM package with conflicting package data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6595|2024-07-17T19:48:11.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 01:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6385|2024-07-12T10:36:50.276Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6385</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6385|2024-07-12T10:36:50.276Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6385|2024-07-11T18:29:36.592Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6385</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6385|2024-07-11T18:29:36.592Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2880|2024-07-11T13:57:10.477Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2880</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.5 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 in which a user with `admin_group_member` custom role permission could ban group members.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2880|2024-07-11T13:57:10.477Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2177|2024-07-10T16:31:47.937Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2177</link>
      <description>A Cross Window Forgery vulnerability exists within GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.3 prior to 16.11.5, 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and 17.1 prior to 17.1.1. This condition allows for an attacker to abuse the OAuth authentication flow via a crafted payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2177|2024-07-10T16:31:47.937Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 13:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2177|2024-07-09T13:30:57.825Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2177</link>
      <description>A Cross Window Forgery vulnerability exists within GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.3 prior to 16.11.5, 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and 17.1 prior to 17.1.1. This condition allows for an attacker to abuse the OAuth authentication flow via a crafted payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2177|2024-07-09T13:30:57.825Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 13:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2191|2024-07-05T20:17:35.161Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2191</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows merge request title to be visible publicly despite being set as project members only.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2191|2024-07-05T20:17:35.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6323|2024-07-02T15:58:28.186Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6323</link>
      <description>Improper authorization in global search in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.11 prior to 16.11.5 and 17.0 prior to 17.0.3 and 17.1 prior to 17.1.1 allows an attacker leak content of a private repository in a public project.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6323|2024-07-02T15:58:28.186Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5655|2024-06-28T03:55:13.887Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5655</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5655|2024-06-28T03:55:13.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4901|2024-06-28T03:55:14.993Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4901</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, where a stored XSS vulnerability could be imported from a project with malicious commit notes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4901|2024-06-28T03:55:14.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1493|2024-06-27T18:20:35.300Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1493</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 9.2 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, with the processing logic for generating link in dependency files can lead to a regular  expression DoS attack on the server</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1493|2024-06-27T18:20:35.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2829|2024-06-20T19:38:32.265Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2829</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.5 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. A crafted wildcard filter in FileFinder may lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2829|2024-06-20T19:38:32.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4024|2024-06-20T19:40:36.439Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4024</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 7.8 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker with their Bitbucket account credentials may be able to take over a GitLab account linked to another user's Bitbucket account, if Bitbucket is used as an OAuth 2.0 provider on GitLab.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4024|2024-06-20T19:40:36.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2434|2024-06-20T19:35:46.975Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2434</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions of GitLab CE/EE  16.9 prior to 16.9.6, 16.10 prior to 16.10.4, and 16.11 prior to 16.11.1 where path traversal could lead to DoS and restricted file read.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2434|2024-06-20T19:35:46.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4006|2024-06-20T19:31:15.040Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4006</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1 where personal access scopes were not honored by GraphQL subscriptions</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4006|2024-06-20T19:31:15.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3092|2024-06-18T19:34:28.995Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3092</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. A payload may lead to a Stored XSS while using the diff viewer, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3092|2024-06-18T19:34:28.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5469|2024-06-15T20:49:28.558Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5469</link>
      <description>DoS in KAS in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.10.0 prior to 16.10.6 and 16.11.0 prior to 16.11.3 allows an attacker to crash KAS via crafted gRPC requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5469|2024-06-15T20:49:28.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4201|2024-06-14T19:18:50.469Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4201</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 5.1 before 16.10.7, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.111.4, all versions starting from 17.0 before 17.0.2. When viewing an XML file in a repository in raw mode, it can be made to render as HTML if viewed under specific circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4201|2024-06-14T19:18:50.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1736|2024-06-13T18:17:49.907Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1736</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions prior to 16.10.7, starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.4, and starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.2. A vulnerability in GitLab's CI/CD pipeline editor could allow for denial of service attacks through maliciously crafted configuration files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1736|2024-06-13T18:17:49.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4895|2024-02-22T04:04:21.576Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4895</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 to 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. This vulnerability allows for bypassing the 'group ip restriction' settings to access environment details of projects</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4895|2024-02-22T04:04:21.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3509|2024-05-07T06:29:39.757Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3509</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for group members with sub-maintainer role to change the title of privately accessible deploy keys associated with projects in the group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3509|2024-05-07T06:29:39.757Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7045|2024-06-04T17:17:24.088Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-7045</link>
      <description>A CSRF vulnerability exists within GitLab CE/EE from versions 13.11 before 16.10.6, from 16.11 before 16.11.3, from 17.0 before 17.0.1. By leveraging this vulnerability, an attacker could exfiltrate anti-CSRF tokens via the Kubernetes Agent Server (KAS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7045|2024-06-04T17:17:24.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6502|2024-06-04T17:17:20.207Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6502</link>
      <description>A Denial of Service (DoS) condition has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.10.6, version 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1. It is possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using a crafted wiki page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6502|2024-06-04T17:17:20.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6688|2024-05-09T01:38:46.718Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6688</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. A problem with the processing logic for Google Chat Messages integration may lead to a regular expression DoS attack on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6688|2024-05-09T01:38:46.718Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6489|2024-04-12T04:04:38.091Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6489</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability was identified in GitLab CE/EE, versions 16.7.7 prior to 16.8.6, 16.9 prior to 16.9.4 and 16.10 prior to 16.10.2 which allows an attacker to spike the GitLab instance resources usage resulting in service degradation via chat integration feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6489|2024-04-12T04:04:38.091Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6477|2024-02-22T04:04:35.685Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6477</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. When a user is assigned a custom role with admin_group_member permission, they may be able to make a group, other members or themselves Owners of that group, which may lead to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6477|2024-02-22T04:04:35.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6840|2024-02-07T22:02:20.934Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6840</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.4 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows a maintainer to change the name of a protected branch that bypasses the security policy added to block MR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6840|2024-02-07T22:02:20.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6682|2024-06-04T17:17:11.196Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6682</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. A problem with the processing logic for Discord Integrations Chat Messages can lead to a regular expression DoS attack on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6682|2024-06-04T17:17:11.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:42:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6564|2024-02-09T18:47:22.622Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6564</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE Premium and Ultimate affecting versions 16.4.3, 16.5.3, and 16.6.1. In projects using subgroups to define who can push and/or merge to protected branches, there may have been instances in which subgroup members with the Developer role were able to push or merge to protected branches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6564|2024-02-09T18:47:22.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6678|2024-04-12T04:04:42.942Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6678</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions before 16.8.6, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a  denial of service using malicious crafted content in a junit test report file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6678|2024-04-12T04:04:42.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6371|2024-06-04T17:16:57.971Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6371</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.8.5, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.3, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.1. A wiki page with a crafted payload may lead to a Stored XSS, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6371|2024-06-04T17:16:57.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 07:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6736|2024-02-26T20:32:17.214Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6736</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 11.3 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for an attacker to cause a client-side denial of service using malicious crafted content in the CODEOWNERS file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6736|2024-02-26T20:32:17.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5318|2024-06-04T18:02:21.999Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5318</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 11.11 prior to 16.10.6, starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.3, and starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.1. A Guest user can view dependency lists of private projects through job artifacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5318|2024-06-04T18:02:21.999Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5258|2024-06-04T18:01:51.492Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5258</link>
      <description>An authorization vulnerability exists within GitLab from versions 16.10 before 16.10.6, 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1 where an authenticated attacker could utilize a crafted naming convention to bypass pipeline authorization logic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5258|2024-06-04T18:01:51.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1347|2024-06-04T18:01:05.241Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1347</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker through a crafted email address may be able to bypass domain based restrictions on an instance or a group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1347|2024-06-04T18:01:05.241Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1947|2024-06-04T18:00:40.082Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1947</link>
      <description>A denial of service (DoS) condition was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 13.2.4 before 16.10.6, 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1. By leveraging this vulnerability an attacker could create a DoS condition by sending crafted API calls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1947|2024-06-04T18:00:40.082Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1525|2024-03-23T04:04:29.177Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1525</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. Under some specialized conditions, an LDAP user may be able to reset their password using their verified secondary email address and sign-in using direct authentication with the reset password, bypassing LDAP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1525|2024-03-23T04:04:29.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1250|2024-03-13T04:04:49.939Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1250</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.2. When a user is assigned a custom role with manage_group_access_tokens permission, they may be able to create group access tokens with Owner privileges, which may lead to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1250|2024-03-13T04:04:49.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 20:47:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1066|2024-03-23T04:04:24.274Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1066</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 13.3.0 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows an attacker to do a resource exhaustion using GraphQL `vulnerabilitiesCountByDay`</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1066|2024-03-23T04:04:24.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1299|2024-03-07T00:39:45.501Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1299</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 16.8 prior to 16.8.4 and 16.9 prior to 16.9.2. It was possible for a user with custom role of `manage_group_access_tokens` to rotate group access tokens with owner privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1299|2024-03-07T00:39:45.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:39:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1451|2024-02-22T04:04:51.022Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1451</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. A crafted payload  added to the user profile page could lead to a stored XSS on the client side, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1451|2024-02-22T04:04:51.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0199|2024-03-07T00:39:50.159Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0199</link>
      <description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 11.3 prior to 16.7.7, 16.7.6 prior to 16.8.4, and 16.8.3 prior to 16.9.2. An attacker could bypass CODEOWNERS by utilizing a crafted payload in an old feature branch to perform malicious actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0199|2024-03-07T00:39:50.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0861|2024-02-22T04:04:46.027Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0861</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. Users with the `Guest` role can change `Custom dashboard projects` settings contrary to permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0861|2024-02-22T04:04:46.027Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0410|2024-02-22T04:04:41.024Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0410</link>
      <description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 15.1 prior to 16.7.6, 16.8 prior to 16.8.3, and 16.9 prior to 16.9.1. A developer could bypass CODEOWNERS approvals by creating a merge conflict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0410|2024-02-22T04:04:41.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4597|2024-05-09T01:38:11.850Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4597</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.7 before 16.9.7, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.5, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.2. An attacker could force a user with an active SAML session to approve an MR via CSRF.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4597|2024-05-09T01:38:11.850Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4539|2024-06-04T17:55:55.247Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4539</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.4 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2 where abusing the API to filter branch and tags could lead to Denial of Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4539|2024-06-04T17:55:55.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4006|2024-06-04T17:55:08.568Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4006</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1 where personal access scopes were not honored by GraphQL subscriptions</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4006|2024-06-04T17:55:08.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4024|2024-06-04T17:54:01.085Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4024</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 7.8 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker with their Bitbucket account credentials may be able to take over a GitLab account linked to another user's Bitbucket account, if Bitbucket is used as an OAuth 2.0 provider on GitLab.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4024|2024-06-04T17:54:01.085Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4835|2024-05-23T06:30:50.384Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4835</link>
      <description>A XSS condition exists within GitLab in versions 15.11 before 16.10.6, 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1. By leveraging this condition, an attacker can craft a malicious page to exfiltrate sensitive user information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4835|2024-05-23T06:30:50.384Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 06:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3092|2024-04-12T04:04:57.767Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3092</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. A payload may lead to a Stored XSS while using the diff viewer, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3092|2024-04-12T04:04:57.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2454|2024-06-04T17:30:51.249Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2454</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.11 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. The pins endpoint is susceptible to DoS through a crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2454|2024-06-04T17:30:51.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2874|2024-06-04T17:30:47.399Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2874</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.10.6, version 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1. A runner registered with a crafted description has the potential to disrupt the loading of targeted GitLab web resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2874|2024-06-04T17:30:47.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 07:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2818|2024-06-04T17:30:38.952Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2818</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.8.5, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.3, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.1. It was possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using malicious crafted description parameter for labels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2818|2024-06-04T17:30:38.952Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 07:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2434|2024-06-04T17:30:36.312Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2434</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions of GitLab CE/EE  16.9 prior to 16.9.6, 16.10 prior to 16.10.4, and 16.11 prior to 16.11.1 where path traversal could lead to DoS and restricted file read.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2434|2024-06-04T17:30:36.312Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2829|2024-06-04T17:30:18.728Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2829</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.5 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. A crafted wildcard filter in FileFinder may lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2829|2024-06-04T17:30:18.728Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2279|2024-06-04T17:30:10.331Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2279</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 to 16.8.6 all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. Using the autocomplete for issues references feature a crafted payload may lead to a stored XSS, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2279|2024-06-04T17:30:10.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2651|2024-06-04T17:29:46.148Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2651</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.9.7, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.5, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using maliciously crafted markdown content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2651|2024-06-04T17:29:46.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1495|2024-06-13T17:17:40.855Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1495</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 13.1 prior to 16.10.7, starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.4, and starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using maliciously crafted file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1495|2024-06-13T17:17:40.855Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5469|2024-06-14T04:04:49.726Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5469</link>
      <description>DoS in KAS in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.10.0 prior to 16.10.6 and 16.11.0 prior to 16.11.3 allows an attacker to crash KAS via crafted gRPC requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5469|2024-06-14T04:04:49.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4835|2024-06-14T22:45:45.358Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4835</link>
      <description>A XSS condition exists within GitLab in versions 15.11 before 16.10.6, 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1. By leveraging this condition, an attacker can craft a malicious page to exfiltrate sensitive user information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4835|2024-06-14T22:45:45.358Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 06:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4597|2024-06-17T19:47:03.571Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4597</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.7 before 16.9.7, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.5, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.2. An attacker could force a user with an active SAML session to approve an MR via CSRF.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4597|2024-06-17T19:47:03.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1347|2024-06-20T13:52:43.570Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1347</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker through a crafted email address may be able to bypass domain based restrictions on an instance or a group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1347|2024-06-20T13:52:43.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3959|2024-06-27T17:37:19.509Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3959</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows private job artifacts can be accessed by any user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3959|2024-06-27T17:37:19.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4557|2024-06-27T17:26:27.963Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4557</link>
      <description>Multiple Denial of Service (DoS) conditions has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 1.0 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1 which allowed an attacker to cause resource exhaustion via banzai pipeline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4557|2024-06-27T17:26:27.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4011|2024-06-27T17:41:04.644Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4011</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.1 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows non-project member to promote key results to objectives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4011|2024-06-27T17:41:04.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5430|2024-06-27T19:05:34.915Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5430</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.10 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows a project maintainer can delete the merge request approval policy via graphQL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5430|2024-06-27T19:05:34.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5655|2024-06-27T19:55:33.371Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5655</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5655|2024-06-27T19:55:33.371Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4901|2024-06-28T13:08:59.344Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4901</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, where a stored XSS vulnerability could be imported from a project with malicious commit notes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4901|2024-06-28T13:08:59.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5655|2024-06-28T13:09:22.469Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5655</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5655|2024-06-28T13:09:22.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3509|2024-07-05T17:21:53.932Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3509</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for group members with sub-maintainer role to change the title of privately accessible deploy keys associated with projects in the group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3509|2024-07-05T17:21:53.932Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6840|2024-07-05T17:20:46.439Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6840</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.4 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows a maintainer to change the name of a protected branch that bypasses the security policy added to block MR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6840|2024-07-05T17:20:46.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1816|2024-07-05T17:22:42.726Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1816</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows for an attacker to cause a denial of service using a crafted OpenAPI file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1816|2024-07-05T17:22:42.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1066|2024-07-05T17:20:47.183Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1066</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 13.3.0 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows an attacker to do a resource exhaustion using GraphQL `vulnerabilitiesCountByDay`</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1066|2024-07-05T17:20:47.183Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1451|2024-07-05T17:21:54.204Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1451</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. A crafted payload  added to the user profile page could lead to a stored XSS on the client side, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1451|2024-07-05T17:21:54.204Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6564|2024-07-05T17:21:52.048Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6564</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE Premium and Ultimate affecting versions 16.4.3, 16.5.3, and 16.6.1. In projects using subgroups to define who can push and/or merge to protected branches, there may have been instances in which subgroup members with the Developer role were able to push or merge to protected branches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6564|2024-07-05T17:21:52.048Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6736|2024-07-05T17:20:46.176Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6736</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 11.3 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for an attacker to cause a client-side denial of service using malicious crafted content in the CODEOWNERS file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6736|2024-07-05T17:20:46.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1525|2024-07-05T17:21:54.930Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1525</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.1 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. Under some specialized conditions, an LDAP user may be able to reset their password using their verified secondary email address and sign-in using direct authentication with the reset password, bypassing LDAP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1525|2024-07-05T17:21:54.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6489|2024-07-08T20:13:28.175Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6489</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability was identified in GitLab CE/EE, versions 16.7.7 prior to 16.8.6, 16.9 prior to 16.9.4 and 16.10 prior to 16.10.2 which allows an attacker to spike the GitLab instance resources usage resulting in service degradation via chat integration feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6489|2024-07-08T20:13:28.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1963|2024-07-10T15:06:54.954Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1963</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 8.4 prior to 16.10.7, starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.4, and starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.2. A vulnerability in GitLab's Asana integration allowed an attacker to potentially cause a regular expression denial of service by sending specially crafted requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1963|2024-07-10T15:06:54.954Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5257|2024-07-11T06:57:09.372Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5257</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4 and from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 where a Developer user with `admin_compliance_framework` custom role may have been able to modify the URL for a group namespace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5257|2024-07-11T06:57:09.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5470|2024-07-11T06:57:04.361Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5470</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4 and from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 where a Guest user with `admin_push_rules` permission may have been able to create project-level deploy tokens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5470|2024-07-11T06:57:04.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6385|2024-07-11T06:56:54.515Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6385</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6385|2024-07-11T06:56:54.515Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2880|2024-07-11T06:57:24.360Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2880</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.5 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 in which a user with `admin_group_member` custom role permission could ban group members.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2880|2024-07-11T06:57:24.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5470|2024-07-11T15:08:22.150Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5470</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4 and from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 where a Guest user with `admin_push_rules` permission may have been able to create project-level deploy tokens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5470|2024-07-11T15:08:22.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6385|2024-07-12T03:55:20.246Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6385</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6385|2024-07-12T03:55:20.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3115|2024-07-15T18:33:50.330Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3115</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.0 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows an attacker to access issues and epics without having an SSO session using Duo Chat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3115|2024-07-15T18:33:50.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4895|2024-07-19T21:11:58.103Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4895</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 to 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. This vulnerability allows for bypassing the 'group ip restriction' settings to access environment details of projects</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4895|2024-07-19T21:11:58.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5257|2024-07-23T18:30:27.972Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5257</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4 and from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 where a Developer user with `admin_compliance_framework` custom role may have been able to modify the URL for a group namespace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5257|2024-07-23T18:30:27.972Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2191|2024-07-24T15:05:28.063Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2191</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows merge request title to be visible publicly despite being set as project members only.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2191|2024-07-24T15:05:28.063Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2829|2024-07-25T04:09:56.499Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2829</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.5 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. A crafted wildcard filter in FileFinder may lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2829|2024-07-25T04:09:56.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6489|2024-07-25T04:09:01.484Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6489</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability was identified in GitLab CE/EE, versions 16.7.7 prior to 16.8.6, 16.9 prior to 16.9.4 and 16.10 prior to 16.10.2 which allows an attacker to spike the GitLab instance resources usage resulting in service degradation via chat integration feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6489|2024-07-25T04:09:01.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3509|2024-07-25T04:05:21.486Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3509</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for group members with sub-maintainer role to change the title of privately accessible deploy keys associated with projects in the group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3509|2024-07-25T04:05:21.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0861|2024-07-25T04:09:31.507Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0861</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. Users with the `Guest` role can change `Custom dashboard projects` settings contrary to permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0861|2024-07-25T04:09:31.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4895|2024-07-25T04:07:31.588Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4895</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 12.0 to 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. This vulnerability allows for bypassing the 'group ip restriction' settings to access environment details of projects</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4895|2024-07-25T04:07:31.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0410|2024-07-25T04:09:26.496Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0410</link>
      <description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 15.1 prior to 16.7.6, 16.8 prior to 16.8.3, and 16.9 prior to 16.9.1. A developer could bypass CODEOWNERS approvals by creating a merge conflict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0410|2024-07-25T04:09:26.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1451|2024-07-25T04:09:41.499Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1451</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. A crafted payload  added to the user profile page could lead to a stored XSS on the client side, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1451|2024-07-25T04:09:41.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2279|2024-07-25T04:09:46.504Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2279</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 to 16.8.6 all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. Using the autocomplete for issues references feature a crafted payload may lead to a stored XSS, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2279|2024-07-25T04:09:46.504Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3092|2024-07-25T04:10:01.503Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3092</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. A payload may lead to a Stored XSS while using the diff viewer, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3092|2024-07-25T04:10:01.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6840|2024-07-25T04:09:16.492Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6840</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.4 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows a maintainer to change the name of a protected branch that bypasses the security policy added to block MR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6840|2024-07-25T04:09:16.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6736|2024-07-25T04:09:11.484Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6736</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 11.3 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for an attacker to cause a client-side denial of service using malicious crafted content in the CODEOWNERS file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6736|2024-07-25T04:09:11.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1347|2024-07-25T04:09:36.499Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1347</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker through a crafted email address may be able to bypass domain based restrictions on an instance or a group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1347|2024-07-25T04:09:36.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6678|2024-07-25T04:09:06.484Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6678</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions before 16.8.6, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a  denial of service using malicious crafted content in a junit test report file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6678|2024-07-25T04:09:06.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2434|2024-07-25T04:09:51.497Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2434</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions of GitLab CE/EE  16.9 prior to 16.9.6, 16.10 prior to 16.10.4, and 16.11 prior to 16.11.1 where path traversal could lead to DoS and restricted file read.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2434|2024-07-25T04:09:51.497Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6477|2024-07-25T04:08:56.492Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6477</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. When a user is assigned a custom role with admin_group_member permission, they may be able to make a group, other members or themselves Owners of that group, which may lead to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6477|2024-07-25T04:08:56.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6371|2024-07-25T04:08:51.479Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6371</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.8.5, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.3, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.1. A wiki page with a crafted payload may lead to a Stored XSS, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6371|2024-07-25T04:08:51.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 07:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7047|2024-07-26T19:21:17.148Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7047</link>
      <description>A cross site scripting vulnerability exists in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.6 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary scripts under the context of the current logged in user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7047|2024-07-26T19:21:17.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1299|2024-07-30T15:26:03.018Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1299</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 16.8 prior to 16.8.4 and 16.9 prior to 16.9.2. It was possible for a user with custom role of `manage_group_access_tokens` to rotate group access tokens with owner privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1299|2024-07-30T15:26:03.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:39:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0231|2024-08-01T17:41:16.067Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0231</link>
      <description>A resource misdirection vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE versions 12.0 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allows an attacker to craft a repository import in such a way as to misdirect commits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0231|2024-08-01T17:41:16.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0199|2024-08-01T17:41:16.006Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0199</link>
      <description>An authorization bypass vulnerability was discovered in GitLab affecting versions 11.3 prior to 16.7.7, 16.7.6 prior to 16.8.4, and 16.8.3 prior to 16.9.2. An attacker could bypass CODEOWNERS by utilizing a crafted payload in an old feature branch to perform malicious actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0199|2024-08-01T17:41:16.006Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2829|2024-08-01T19:25:41.746Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2829</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.5 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. A crafted wildcard filter in FileFinder may lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2829|2024-08-01T19:25:41.746Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2454|2024-08-01T19:11:53.493Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2454</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.11 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. The pins endpoint is susceptible to DoS through a crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2454|2024-08-01T19:11:53.493Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2191|2024-08-01T19:03:39.103Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2191</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows merge request title to be visible publicly despite being set as project members only.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2191|2024-08-01T19:03:39.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2874|2024-08-01T19:25:42.188Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2874</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.10.6, version 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1. A runner registered with a crafted description has the potential to disrupt the loading of targeted GitLab web resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2874|2024-08-01T19:25:42.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 07:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2818|2024-08-01T19:25:41.894Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2818</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.8.5, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.3, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.1. It was possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using malicious crafted description parameter for labels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2818|2024-08-01T19:25:41.894Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 07:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2279|2024-08-01T19:11:52.092Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2279</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 to 16.8.6 all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. Using the autocomplete for issues references feature a crafted payload may lead to a stored XSS, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2279|2024-08-01T19:11:52.092Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3092|2024-08-01T19:32:42.686Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3092</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. A payload may lead to a Stored XSS while using the diff viewer, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3092|2024-08-01T19:32:42.686Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2651|2024-08-01T19:18:48.247Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2651</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.9.7, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.5, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using maliciously crafted markdown content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2651|2024-08-01T19:18:48.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3115|2024-08-01T19:32:42.612Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3115</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.0 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows an attacker to access issues and epics without having an SSO session using Duo Chat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3115|2024-08-01T19:32:42.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2177|2024-08-01T19:03:39.319Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2177</link>
      <description>A Cross Window Forgery vulnerability exists within GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.3 prior to 16.11.5, 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and 17.1 prior to 17.1.1. This condition allows for an attacker to abuse the OAuth authentication flow via a crafted payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2177|2024-08-01T19:03:39.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 13:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2434|2024-08-01T19:11:53.542Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2434</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions of GitLab CE/EE  16.9 prior to 16.9.6, 16.10 prior to 16.10.4, and 16.11 prior to 16.11.1 where path traversal could lead to DoS and restricted file read.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2434|2024-08-01T19:11:53.542Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2880|2024-08-01T19:25:42.152Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2880</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.5 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 in which a user with `admin_group_member` custom role permission could ban group members.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2880|2024-08-01T19:25:42.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5469|2024-08-01T21:11:12.757Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5469</link>
      <description>DoS in KAS in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.10.0 prior to 16.10.6 and 16.11.0 prior to 16.11.3 allows an attacker to crash KAS via crafted gRPC requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5469|2024-08-01T21:11:12.757Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 04:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7091|2024-08-01T21:52:30.873Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7091</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.6 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where it was possible to disclose limited information of an exported group or project to another user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7091|2024-08-01T21:52:30.873Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6595|2024-08-01T21:41:03.899Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6595</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 11.8 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 where it was possible to upload an NPM package with conflicting package data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6595|2024-08-01T21:41:03.899Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 01:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5655|2024-08-01T21:18:06.633Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5655</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5655|2024-08-01T21:18:06.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7060|2024-08-01T21:52:30.379Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7060</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE in project/group exports affecting all versions from 15.4 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allows unauthorized users to view the resultant export.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7060|2024-08-01T21:52:30.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6385|2024-08-01T21:41:03.228Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6385</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.8 prior to 16.11.6, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2, which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6385|2024-08-01T21:41:03.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7047|2024-08-01T21:45:38.425Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7047</link>
      <description>A cross site scripting vulnerability exists in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.6 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary scripts under the context of the current logged in user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7047|2024-08-01T21:45:38.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5257|2024-08-01T21:03:11.049Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5257</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4 and from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 where a Developer user with `admin_compliance_framework` custom role may have been able to modify the URL for a group namespace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5257|2024-08-01T21:03:11.049Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5470|2024-08-01T21:11:12.792Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5470</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.4 and from 17.1 prior to 17.1.2 where a Guest user with `admin_push_rules` permission may have been able to create project-level deploy tokens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5470|2024-08-01T21:11:12.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 06:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5067|2024-08-01T21:03:10.510Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5067</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.11 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where certain project-level analytics settings could be leaked in DOM to group members with Developer or higher roles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5067|2024-08-01T21:03:10.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5258|2024-08-01T21:03:11.132Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5258</link>
      <description>An authorization vulnerability exists within GitLab from versions 16.10 before 16.10.6, 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1 where an authenticated attacker could utilize a crafted naming convention to bypass pipeline authorization logic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5258|2024-08-01T21:03:11.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5430|2024-08-01T21:11:12.743Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5430</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.10 prior to 16.11.5, starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.3, and starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.1, which allows a project maintainer can delete the merge request approval policy via graphQL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5430|2024-08-01T21:11:12.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5318|2024-08-01T21:11:12.380Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5318</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 11.11 prior to 16.10.6, starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.3, and starting from 17.0 prior to 17.0.1. A Guest user can view dependency lists of private projects through job artifacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5318|2024-08-01T21:11:12.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7057|2024-08-01T21:45:38.455Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7057</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where job artifacts can be inappropriately exposed to users lacking the proper authorization level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7057|2024-08-01T21:45:38.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6323|2024-08-01T21:33:05.449Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6323</link>
      <description>Improper authorization in global search in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.11 prior to 16.11.5 and 17.0 prior to 17.0.3 and 17.1 prior to 17.1.1 allows an attacker leak content of a private repository in a public project.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6323|2024-08-01T21:33:05.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3509|2024-08-02T06:55:03.388Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3509</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for group members with sub-maintainer role to change the title of privately accessible deploy keys associated with projects in the group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3509|2024-08-02T06:55:03.388Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6489|2024-08-02T08:28:21.821Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6489</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability was identified in GitLab CE/EE, versions 16.7.7 prior to 16.8.6, 16.9 prior to 16.9.4 and 16.10 prior to 16.10.2 which allows an attacker to spike the GitLab instance resources usage resulting in service degradation via chat integration feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6489|2024-08-02T08:28:21.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6502|2024-08-02T08:35:13.273Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6502</link>
      <description>A Denial of Service (DoS) condition has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.10.6, version 16.11 before 16.11.3, and 17.0 before 17.0.1. It is possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using a crafted wiki page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6502|2024-08-02T08:35:13.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7045|2024-08-02T08:50:07.755Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7045</link>
      <description>A CSRF vulnerability exists within GitLab CE/EE from versions 13.11 before 16.10.6, from 16.11 before 16.11.3, from 17.0 before 17.0.1. By leveraging this vulnerability, an attacker could exfiltrate anti-CSRF tokens via the Kubernetes Agent Server (KAS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7045|2024-08-02T08:50:07.755Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6682|2024-08-02T08:35:14.911Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6682</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. A problem with the processing logic for Discord Integrations Chat Messages can lead to a regular expression DoS attack on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6682|2024-08-02T08:35:14.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:42:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6840|2024-08-02T08:42:08.148Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6840</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.4 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows a maintainer to change the name of a protected branch that bypasses the security policy added to block MR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6840|2024-08-02T08:42:08.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6688|2024-08-02T08:35:14.844Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6688</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. A problem with the processing logic for Google Chat Messages integration may lead to a regular expression DoS attack on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6688|2024-08-02T08:35:14.844Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6736|2024-08-02T08:35:15.057Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6736</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 11.3 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. It was possible for an attacker to cause a client-side denial of service using malicious crafted content in the CODEOWNERS file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6736|2024-08-02T08:35:15.057Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6564|2024-08-02T08:35:14.927Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6564</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE Premium and Ultimate affecting versions 16.4.3, 16.5.3, and 16.6.1. In projects using subgroups to define who can push and/or merge to protected branches, there may have been instances in which subgroup members with the Developer role were able to push or merge to protected branches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6564|2024-08-02T08:35:14.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6678|2024-08-02T08:35:14.893Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6678</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions before 16.8.6, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.4, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a  denial of service using malicious crafted content in a junit test report file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6678|2024-08-02T08:35:14.893Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6477|2024-08-02T08:28:21.814Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6477</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.7.6, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.3, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.1. When a user is assigned a custom role with admin_group_member permission, they may be able to make a group, other members or themselves Owners of that group, which may lead to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6477|2024-08-02T08:28:21.814Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 23:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6371|2024-08-02T08:28:21.792Z -- gitlab -- gitlab</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6371</link>
      <description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.8.5, all versions starting from 16.9 before 16.9.3, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.1. A wiki page with a crafted payload may lead to a Stored XSS, allowing attackers to perform arbitrary actions on behalf of victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6371|2024-08-02T08:28:21.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 07:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
