<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Mobile Vikings -- Django AJAX Utilities</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mobile%20vikings/django%20ajax%20utilities.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Mobile Vikings -- Django AJAX Utilities</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20182|2024-08-05T21:45:26.271Z -- mobile%20vikings -- django%20ajax%20utilities
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20182</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Mobile Vikings Django AJAX Utilities up to 1.2.1 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function Pagination of the file django_ajax/static/ajax-utilities/js/pagination.js of the component Backslash Handler. The manipulation of the argument url leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The patch is named 329eb1dd1580ca1f9d4f95bc69939833226515c9. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-222611.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Mobile Vikings Django AJAX Utilities bis 1.2.1 gefunden. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion Pagination der Datei django_ajax/static/ajax-utilities/js/pagination.js der Komponente Backslash Handler. Durch Manipulation des Arguments url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Patch wird als 329eb1dd1580ca1f9d4f95bc69939833226515c9 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20182|2024-08-05T21:45:26.271Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
