<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for kyubisation -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/kyubisation/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for kyubisation -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:23:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28444|2024-08-02T12:38:25.348Z -- kyubisation -- angular-server-side-configuration
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28444</link>
      <description>angular-server-side-configuration helps configure an angular application at runtime on the server or in a docker container via environment variables. angular-server-side-configuration detects used environment variables in TypeScript (.ts) files during build time of an Angular CLI project. The detected environment variables are written to a ngssc.json file in the output directory.
During deployment of an Angular based app, the environment variables based on the variables from ngssc.json are inserted into the apps index.html (or defined index file). With version 15.0.0 the environment variable detection was widened to the entire project, relative to the angular.json file from the Angular CLI. In a monorepo setup, this could lead to environment variables intended for a backend/service to be detected and written to the ngssc.json, which would then be populated and exposed via index.html. This has NO IMPACT, in a plain Angular project that has no backend component. This vulnerability has been mitigated in version 15.1.0, by adding an option `searchPattern` which restricts the detection file range by default. As a workaround, manually edit or create ngssc.json or run script after ngssc.json generation.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28444|2024-08-02T12:38:25.348Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 19:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
