<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for ForU -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/foru/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for ForU -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-0425|2024-01-11T20:00:05.796Z -- ForU -- CMS
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0425</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in ForU CMS up to 2020-06-23. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/index.php?act=reset_admin_psw. The manipulation leads to weak password recovery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250444.
In ForU CMS bis 2020-06-23 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /admin/index.php?act=reset_admin_psw. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine weak password recovery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0425|2024-01-11T20:00:05.796Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0729|2024-01-19T18:31:04.550Z -- ForU -- CMS
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0729</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in ForU CMS up to 2020-06-23. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file cms_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument a_name leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251552.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in ForU CMS bis 2020-06-23 entdeckt. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei cms_admin.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments a_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0729|2024-01-19T18:31:04.550Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 18:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0728|2024-01-19T18:31:03.499Z -- ForU -- CMS
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0728</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in ForU CMS up to 2020-06-23. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file channel.php. The manipulation of the argument c_cmodel leads to file inclusion. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251551.
In ForU CMS bis 2020-06-23 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei channel.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments c_cmodel mit unbekannten Daten kann eine file inclusion-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0728|2024-01-19T18:31:03.499Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 18:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0426|2024-01-11T21:00:04.664Z -- ForU -- CMS
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0426</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in ForU CMS up to 2020-06-23. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/cms_template.php. The manipulation of the argument t_name/t_path leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250445 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in ForU CMS bis 2020-06-23 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei admin/cms_template.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments t_name/t_path mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0426|2024-01-11T21:00:04.664Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 21:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>