<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ForU -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/foru/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ForU -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:23:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5221|2024-08-02T07:52:08.541Z -- foru -- cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5221</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in ForU CMS. This affects an unknown part of the file /install/index.php. The manipulation of the argument db_name leads to code injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-240363. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in ForU CMS entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /install/index.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments db_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine code injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Dieses Produkt setzt Rolling Releases ein. Aus diesem Grund sind Details zu betroffenen oder zu aktualisierende Versionen nicht verfügbar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5221|2024-08-02T07:52:08.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 13:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5259|2024-08-02T07:52:08.544Z -- foru -- cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5259</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in ForU CMS. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/cms_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument del leads to denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-240868.
In ForU CMS wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /admin/cms_admin.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments del mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Dieses Produkt verzichtet auf eine Versionierung und verwendet stattdessen Rolling Releases. Deshalb sind keine Details zu betroffenen oder zu aktualisierende Versionen vorhanden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5259|2024-08-02T07:52:08.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 11:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
