<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Repox -- Repox</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/repox/repox.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Repox -- Repox</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:22:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6722|2024-08-02T08:35:14.917Z -- repox -- repox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6722</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability has been detected in Repox, which allows an attacker to read arbitrary files on the running server, resulting in a disclosure of sensitive information. An attacker could access files such as application code or data, backend credentials, operating system files...</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6722|2024-08-02T08:35:14.917Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 10:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6720|2024-08-02T08:35:14.839Z -- repox -- repox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6720</link>
      <description>An XSS vulnerability stored in Repox has been identified, which allows a local attacker to store a specially crafted JavaScript payload on the server, due to the lack of proper sanitisation of field elements, allowing the attacker to trigger the malicious payload when the application loads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6720|2024-08-02T08:35:14.839Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 10:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6718|2024-08-02T08:35:14.908Z -- repox -- repox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6718</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass vulnerability has been found in Repox, which allows a remote user to send a specially crafted POST request, due to the lack of any authentication method, resulting in the alteration or creation of users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6718|2024-08-02T08:35:14.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 09:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6721|2024-08-02T08:35:14.894Z -- repox -- repox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6721</link>
      <description>An XEE vulnerability has been found in Repox, which allows a remote attacker to interfere with the application's XML data processing in the fileupload function, resulting in interaction between the attacker and the server's file system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6721|2024-08-02T08:35:14.894Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 10:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6719|2024-08-02T08:35:14.925Z -- repox -- repox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6719</link>
      <description>An XSS vulnerability has been detected in Repox, which allows an attacker to compromise interactions between a user and the vulnerable application, and can be exploited by a third party by sending a specially crafted JavaScript payload to a user, and thus gain full control of their session.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6719|2024-08-02T08:35:14.925Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 09:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6723|2024-08-02T08:35:14.869Z -- repox -- repox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6723</link>
      <description>An unrestricted file upload vulnerability has been identified in Repbox, which allows an attacker to upload malicious files via the transforamationfileupload function, due to the lack of proper file type validation controls, resulting in a full system compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6723|2024-08-02T08:35:14.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 10:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
