<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for owen2345 -- camaleon-cms</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/owen2345/camaleon-cms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for owen2345 -- camaleon-cms</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 18:24:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-46987|2024-09-18T17:15:45.829Z -- owen2345 -- camaleon-cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46987</link>
      <description>Camaleon CMS is a dynamic and advanced content management system based on Ruby on Rails. A path traversal vulnerability accessible via MediaController's download_private_file method allows authenticated users to download any file on the web server Camaleon CMS is running on (depending on the file permissions). This issue may lead to Information Disclosure. This issue has been addressed in release version 2.8.2. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-46987|2024-09-18T17:15:45.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 17:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-46986|2024-09-18T17:14:09.127Z -- owen2345 -- camaleon-cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46986</link>
      <description>Camaleon CMS is a dynamic and advanced content management system based on Ruby on Rails. An arbitrary file write vulnerability accessible via the upload method of the MediaController allows authenticated users to write arbitrary files to any location on the web server Camaleon CMS is running on (depending on the permissions of the underlying filesystem). E.g. This can lead to a delayed remote code execution in case an attacker is able to write a Ruby file into the config/initializers/ subfolder of the Ruby on Rails application. This issue has been addressed in release version 2.8.2. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-46986|2024-09-18T17:14:09.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 17:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
