<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cesanta -- Mongoose</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cesanta/mongoose.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cesanta -- Mongoose</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2921|2024-08-05T14:09:17.774Z -- cesanta -- mongoose
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2921</link>
      <description>An exploitable memory corruption vulnerability exists in the Websocket protocol implementation of Cesanta Mongoose 6.8. A specially crafted websocket packet can cause an integer overflow, leading to a heap buffer overflow and resulting in denial of service and potential remote code execution. An attacker needs to send a specially crafted websocket packet over network to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2921|2024-08-05T14:09:17.774Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2894|2024-08-05T14:09:17.439Z -- cesanta -- mongoose
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2894</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the MQTT packet parsing functionality of Cesanta Mongoose 6.8. A specially crafted MQTT SUBSCRIBE packet can cause a stack buffer overflow resulting in remote code execution. An attacker needs to send a specially crafted MQTT packet over the network to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2894|2024-08-05T14:09:17.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2909|2024-08-05T14:09:17.496Z -- cesanta -- mongoose
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2909</link>
      <description>An infinite loop programming error exists in the DNS server functionality of Cesanta Mongoose 6.8 library. A specially crafted DNS request can cause an infinite loop resulting in high CPU usage and Denial Of Service. An attacker can send a packet over the network to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2909|2024-08-05T14:09:17.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2891|2024-08-05T14:09:17.156Z -- cesanta -- mongoose
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2891</link>
      <description>An exploitable use-after-free vulnerability exists in the HTTP server implementation of Cesanta Mongoose 6.8. An ordinary HTTP POST request with a CGI target can cause a reuse of previously freed pointer potentially resulting in remote code execution. An attacker needs to send this HTTP request over the network to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2891|2024-08-05T14:09:17.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2895|2024-08-05T14:09:17.423Z -- cesanta -- mongoose
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2895</link>
      <description>An exploitable arbitrary memory read vulnerability exists in the MQTT packet parsing functionality of Cesanta Mongoose 6.8. A specially crafted MQTT SUBSCRIBE packet can cause an arbitrary out-of-bounds memory read potentially resulting in information disclosure and denial of service. An attacker needs to send a specially crafted MQTT packet over the network to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2895|2024-08-05T14:09:17.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2892|2024-08-05T14:09:17.432Z -- cesanta -- mongoose
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2892</link>
      <description>An exploitable arbitrary memory read vulnerability exists in the MQTT packet parsing functionality of Cesanta Mongoose 6.8. A specially crafted MQTT packet can cause an arbitrary out-of-bounds memory read and write potentially resulting in information disclosure, denial of service and remote code execution. An attacker needs to send a specially crafted MQTT packet over the network to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2892|2024-08-05T14:09:17.432Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2922|2024-08-05T14:09:17.795Z -- cesanta -- mongoose
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2922</link>
      <description>An exploitable memory corruption vulnerability exists in the Websocket protocol implementation of Cesanta Mongoose 6.8. A specially crafted websocket packet can cause a buffer to be allocated while leaving stale pointers which leads to a use-after-free vulnerability which can be exploited to achieve remote code execution. An attacker needs to send a specially crafted websocket packet over the network to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2922|2024-08-05T14:09:17.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2893|2024-08-05T14:09:17.693Z -- cesanta -- mongoose
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2893</link>
      <description>An exploitable NULL pointer dereference vulnerability exists in the MQTT packet parsing functionality of Cesanta Mongoose 6.8. An MQTT SUBSCRIBE packet can cause a NULL pointer dereference leading to server crash and denial of service. An attacker needs to send a specially crafted MQTT packet over the network to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2893|2024-08-05T14:09:17.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
