<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for HashiCorp -- Vault</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/hashicorp/vault.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for HashiCorp -- Vault</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5954|2023-11-09T20:13:49.346Z -- hashicorp -- vault
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5954</link>
      <description>HashiCorp Vault and Vault Enterprise inbound client requests triggering a policy check can lead to an unbounded consumption of memory. A large number of these requests may lead to denial-of-service. Fixed in Vault 1.15.2, 1.14.6, and 1.13.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5954|2023-11-09T20:13:49.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 20:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5077|2023-09-28T23:24:28.643Z -- hashicorp -- vault
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5077</link>
      <description>The Vault and Vault Enterprise ("Vault") Google Cloud secrets engine did not preserve existing Google Cloud IAM Conditions upon creating or updating rolesets. Fixed in Vault 1.13.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5077|2023-09-28T23:24:28.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 23:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0665|2023-03-30T00:24:44.582Z -- hashicorp -- vault
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0665</link>
      <description>HashiCorp Vault's PKI mount issuer endpoints did not correctly authorize access to remove an issuer or modify issuer metadata, potentially resulting in denial of service of the PKI mount. This bug did not affect public or private key material, trust chains or certificate issuance. Fixed in Vault 1.13.1, 1.12.5, and 1.11.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0665|2023-03-30T00:24:44.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0620|2023-03-30T18:41:52.858Z -- hashicorp -- vault
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0620</link>
      <description>HashiCorp Vault and Vault Enterprise versions 0.8.0 through 1.13.1 are vulnerable to an SQL injection attack when configuring the Microsoft SQL (MSSQL) Database Storage Backend. When configuring the MSSQL plugin through the local, certain parameters are not sanitized when passed to the user-provided MSSQL database. An attacker may modify these parameters to execute a malicious SQL command.

This issue is fixed in versions 1.13.1, 1.12.5, and 1.11.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0620|2023-03-30T18:41:52.858Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4680|2023-09-14T23:06:24.546Z -- hashicorp -- vault
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4680</link>
      <description>HashiCorp Vault and Vault Enterprise transit secrets engine allowed authorized users to specify arbitrary nonces, even with convergent encryption disabled. The encrypt endpoint, in combination with an offline attack, could be used to decrypt arbitrary ciphertext and potentially derive the authentication subkey when using transit secrets engine without convergent encryption. Introduced in 1.6.0 and fixed in 1.14.3, 1.13.7, and 1.12.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4680|2023-09-14T23:06:24.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 23:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24999|2023-03-10T23:12:47.638Z -- hashicorp -- vault
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-24999</link>
      <description>HashiCorp Vault and Vault Enterprise’s approle auth method allowed any authenticated user with access to an approle destroy endpoint to destroy the secret ID of any other role by providing the secret ID accessor. This vulnerability is fixed in Vault 1.13.0, 1.12.4, 1.11.8, 1.10.11 and above.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24999|2023-03-10T23:12:47.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 23:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25000|2023-03-30T00:24:51.132Z -- hashicorp -- vault
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-25000</link>
      <description>HashiCorp Vault's implementation of Shamir's secret sharing used precomputed table lookups, and was vulnerable to cache-timing attacks. An attacker with access to, and the ability to observe a large number of unseal operations on the host through a side channel may reduce the search space of a brute force effort to recover the Shamir shares. Fixed in Vault 1.13.1, 1.12.5, and 1.11.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25000|2023-03-30T00:24:51.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3462|2023-07-31T22:40:23.432Z -- hashicorp -- vault
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3462</link>
      <description>HashiCorp's Vault and Vault Enterprise are vulnerable to user enumeration when using the LDAP auth method. An attacker may submit requests of existent and non-existent LDAP users and observe the response from Vault to check if the account is valid on the LDAP server. This vulnerability is fixed in Vault 1.14.1 and 1.13.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3462|2023-07-31T22:40:23.432Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 22:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6337|2023-12-08T21:12:31.712Z -- hashicorp -- vault
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6337</link>
      <description>HashiCorp Vault and Vault Enterprise 1.12.0 and newer are vulnerable to a denial of service through memory exhaustion of the host when handling large unauthenticated and authenticated HTTP requests from a client. Vault will attempt to map the request to memory, resulting in the exhaustion of available memory on the host, which may cause Vault to crash.

Fixed in Vault 1.15.4, 1.14.8, 1.13.12.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6337|2023-12-08T21:12:31.712Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 21:12:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2121|2023-06-09T16:59:49.065Z -- hashicorp -- vault
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2121</link>
      <description>Vault and Vault Enterprise's (Vault) key-value v2 (kv-v2) diff viewer allowed HTML injection into the Vault web UI through key values. This vulnerability, CVE-2023-2121, is fixed in Vault 1.14.0, 1.13.3, 1.12.7, and 1.11.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2121|2023-06-09T16:59:49.065Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 16:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0831|2024-02-01T16:07:23.308Z -- hashicorp -- vault
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0831</link>
      <description>Vault and Vault Enterprise (“Vault”) may expose sensitive information when enabling an audit device which specifies the `log_raw` option, which may log sensitive information to other audit devices, regardless of whether they are configured to use `log_raw`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0831|2024-02-01T16:07:23.308Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 01:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2048|2024-03-04T19:56:47.253Z -- hashicorp -- vault
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2048</link>
      <description>Vault and Vault Enterprise (“Vault”) TLS certificate auth method did not correctly validate client certificates when configured with a non-CA certificate as trusted certificate. In this configuration, an attacker may be able to craft a malicious certificate that could be used to bypass authentication. Fixed in Vault 1.15.5 and 1.14.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2048|2024-03-04T19:56:47.253Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 19:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2660|2024-04-04T17:55:20.192Z -- hashicorp -- vault
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2660</link>
      <description>Vault and Vault Enterprise TLS certificates auth method did not correctly validate OCSP responses when one or more OCSP sources were configured. Fixed in Vault 1.16.0 and Vault Enterprise 1.16.1, 1.15.7, and 1.14.11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2660|2024-04-04T17:55:20.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
