<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IEEE -- Standard</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ieee/standard.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IEEE -- Standard</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:24:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-13093|2024-08-05T18:58:12.372Z -- ieee -- standard
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13093</link>
      <description>The P1735 IEEE standard describes flawed methods for encrypting electronic-design intellectual property (IP), as well as the management of access rights for such IP, including modification of encrypted IP cyphertext to insert hardware trojans. The methods are flawed and, in the most egregious cases, enable attack vectors that allow recovery of the entire underlying plaintext IP. Implementations of IEEE P1735 may be weak to cryptographic attacks that allow an attacker to obtain plaintext intellectual property without the key, among other impacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-13093|2024-08-05T18:58:12.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-13095|2024-08-05T18:58:12.316Z -- ieee -- standard
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13095</link>
      <description>The P1735 IEEE standard describes flawed methods for encrypting electronic-design intellectual property (IP), as well as the management of access rights for such IP, including modification of a license-deny response to a license grant. The methods are flawed and, in the most egregious cases, enable attack vectors that allow recovery of the entire underlying plaintext IP. Implementations of IEEE P1735 may be weak to cryptographic attacks that allow an attacker to obtain plaintext intellectual property without the key, among other impacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-13095|2024-08-05T18:58:12.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-13094|2024-08-05T18:58:12.444Z -- ieee -- standard
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13094</link>
      <description>The P1735 IEEE standard describes flawed methods for encrypting electronic-design intellectual property (IP), as well as the management of access rights for such IP, including modification of the encryption key and insertion of hardware trojans in any IP. The methods are flawed and, in the most egregious cases, enable attack vectors that allow recovery of the entire underlying plaintext IP. Implementations of IEEE P1735 may be weak to cryptographic attacks that allow an attacker to obtain plaintext intellectual property without the key, among other impacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-13094|2024-08-05T18:58:12.444Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-13091|2024-08-05T18:58:12.350Z -- ieee -- standard
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13091</link>
      <description>The P1735 IEEE standard describes flawed methods for encrypting electronic-design intellectual property (IP), as well as the management of access rights for such IP, including improperly specified padding in CBC mode allows use of an EDA tool as a decryption oracle. The methods are flawed and, in the most egregious cases, enable attack vectors that allow recovery of the entire underlying plaintext IP. Implementations of IEEE P1735 may be weak to cryptographic attacks that allow an attacker to obtain plaintext intellectual property without the key, among other impacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-13091|2024-08-05T18:58:12.350Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-13097|2024-08-05T18:58:12.321Z -- ieee -- standard
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13097</link>
      <description>The P1735 IEEE standard describes flawed methods for encrypting electronic-design intellectual property (IP), as well as the management of access rights for such IP, including modification of Rights Block to remove or relax license requirement. The methods are flawed and, in the most egregious cases, enable attack vectors that allow recovery of the entire underlying plaintext IP. Implementations of IEEE P1735 may be weak to cryptographic attacks that allow an attacker to obtain plaintext intellectual property without the key, among other impacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-13097|2024-08-05T18:58:12.321Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-13092|2024-08-05T18:58:12.398Z -- ieee -- standard
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13092</link>
      <description>The P1735 IEEE standard describes flawed methods for encrypting electronic-design intellectual property (IP), as well as the management of access rights for such IP, including improperly specified HDL syntax allows use of an EDA tool as a decryption oracle. The methods are flawed and, in the most egregious cases, enable attack vectors that allow recovery of the entire underlying plaintext IP. Implementations of IEEE P1735 may be weak to cryptographic attacks that allow an attacker to obtain plaintext intellectual property without the key, among other impacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-13092|2024-08-05T18:58:12.398Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-13096|2024-08-05T18:58:12.330Z -- ieee -- standard
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13096</link>
      <description>The P1735 IEEE standard describes flawed methods for encrypting electronic-design intellectual property (IP), as well as the management of access rights for such IP, including modification of Rights Block to remove or relax access control. The methods are flawed and, in the most egregious cases, enable attack vectors that allow recovery of the entire underlying plaintext IP. Implementations of IEEE P1735 may be weak to cryptographic attacks that allow an attacker to obtain plaintext intellectual property without the key, among other impacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-13096|2024-08-05T18:58:12.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
