<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for jellyfin -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/jellyfin/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for jellyfin -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29490|2024-08-03T22:11:05.554Z -- jellyfin -- jellyfin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29490</link>
      <description>Jellyfin is a free software media system that provides media from a dedicated server to end-user devices via multiple apps. Verions prior to 10.7.3 vulnerable to unauthenticated Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) attacks via the imageUrl parameter. This issue potentially exposes both internal and external HTTP servers or other resources available via HTTP `GET` that are visible from the Jellyfin server. The vulnerability is patched in version 10.7.3. As a workaround, disable external access to the API endpoints `/Items/*/RemoteImages/Download`, `/Items/RemoteSearch/Image` and `/Images/Remote` via reverse proxy, or limit to known-friendly IPs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29490|2024-08-03T22:11:05.554Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 18:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21402|2024-08-03T18:09:16.077Z -- jellyfin -- jellyfin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21402</link>
      <description>Jellyfin is a Free Software Media System. In Jellyfin before version 10.7.1, with certain endpoints, well crafted requests will allow arbitrary file read from a Jellyfin server's file system. This issue is more prevalent when Windows is used as the host OS. Servers that are exposed to the public Internet are potentially at risk. This is fixed in version 10.7.1. As a workaround, users may be able to restrict some access by enforcing strict security permissions on their filesystem, however, it is recommended to update as soon as possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21402|2024-08-03T18:09:16.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 19:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
