<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TxtDot -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/txtdot/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TxtDot -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 17:21:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-41812|2024-07-26T16:49:52.343Z -- txtdot -- txtdot
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41812</link>
      <description>txtdot is an HTTP proxy that parses only text, links, and pictures from pages, removing ads and heavy scripts. Prior to version 1.7.0, a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the `/get` route of txtdot allows remote attackers to use the server as a proxy to send HTTP GET requests to arbitrary targets and retrieve information in the internal network. Version 1.7.0 prevents displaying the response of forged requests, but the requests can still be sent. For complete mitigation, a firewall between txtdot and other internal network resources should be set.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-41812|2024-07-26T16:49:52.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-41813|2024-07-26T16:51:33.606Z -- txtdot -- txtdot
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41813</link>
      <description>txtdot is an HTTP proxy that parses only text, links, and pictures from pages, removing ads and heavy scripts. Starting in version 1.4.0 and prior to version 1.6.1, a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the `/proxy` route of txtdot allows remote attackers to use the server as a proxy to send HTTP GET requests to arbitrary targets and retrieve information in the internal network. Version 1.6.1 patches the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-41813|2024-07-26T16:51:33.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
