<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for OWASP -- ModSecurity Core Rule Set</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/owasp/modsecurity%20core%20rule%20set.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for OWASP -- ModSecurity Core Rule Set</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 18:24:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39957|2024-08-03T12:07:42.939Z -- owasp -- modsecurity%20core%20rule%20set
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39957</link>
      <description>The OWASP ModSecurity Core Rule Set (CRS) is affected by a response body bypass. A client can issue an HTTP Accept header field containing an optional "charset" parameter in order to receive the response in an encoded form. Depending on the "charset", this response can not be decoded by the web application firewall. A restricted resource, access to which would ordinarily be detected, may therefore bypass detection. The legacy CRS versions 3.0.x and 3.1.x are affected, as well as the currently supported versions 3.2.1 and 3.3.2. Integrators and users are advised to upgrade to 3.2.2 and 3.3.3 respectively.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39957|2024-08-03T12:07:42.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39958|2024-08-03T12:07:42.945Z -- owasp -- modsecurity%20core%20rule%20set
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39958</link>
      <description>The OWASP ModSecurity Core Rule Set (CRS) is affected by a response body bypass to sequentially exfiltrate small and undetectable sections of data by repeatedly submitting an HTTP Range header field with a small byte range. A restricted resource, access to which would ordinarily be detected, may be exfiltrated from the backend, despite being protected by a web application firewall that uses CRS. Short subsections of a restricted resource may bypass pattern matching techniques and allow undetected access. The legacy CRS versions 3.0.x and 3.1.x are affected, as well as the currently supported versions 3.2.1 and 3.3.2. Integrators and users are advised to upgrade to 3.2.2 and 3.3.3 respectively and to configure a CRS paranoia level of 3 or higher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39958|2024-08-03T12:07:42.945Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39956|2024-08-03T12:07:43.072Z -- owasp -- modsecurity%20core%20rule%20set
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39956</link>
      <description>The OWASP ModSecurity Core Rule Set (CRS) is affected by a partial rule set bypass for HTTP multipart requests by submitting a payload that uses a character encoding scheme via the Content-Type or the deprecated Content-Transfer-Encoding multipart MIME header fields that will not be decoded and inspected by the web application firewall engine and the rule set. The multipart payload will therefore bypass detection. A vulnerable backend that supports these encoding schemes can potentially be exploited. The legacy CRS versions 3.0.x and 3.1.x are affected, as well as the currently supported versions 3.2.1 and 3.3.2. Integrators and users are advised upgrade to 3.2.2 and 3.3.3 respectively. The mitigation against these vulnerabilities depends on the installation of the latest ModSecurity version (v2.9.6 / v3.0.8).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39956|2024-08-03T12:07:43.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39955|2024-08-03T12:07:42.978Z -- owasp -- modsecurity%20core%20rule%20set
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39955</link>
      <description>The OWASP ModSecurity Core Rule Set (CRS) is affected by a partial rule set bypass by submitting a specially crafted HTTP Content-Type header field that indicates multiple character encoding schemes. A vulnerable back-end can potentially be exploited by declaring multiple Content-Type "charset" names and therefore bypassing the configurable CRS Content-Type header "charset" allow list. An encoded payload can bypass CRS detection this way and may then be decoded by the backend. The legacy CRS versions 3.0.x and 3.1.x are affected, as well as the currently supported versions 3.2.1 and 3.3.2. Integrators and users are advised to upgrade to 3.2.2 and 3.3.3 respectively.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39955|2024-08-03T12:07:42.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
