<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for listingthemes -- WP Directory Kit</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/listingthemes/wp%20directory%20kit.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for listingthemes -- WP Directory Kit</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:20:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2351|2024-08-02T06:19:14.857Z -- listingthemes -- wp%20directory%20kit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2351</link>
      <description>The WP Directory Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ajax_admin' function in versions up to, and including, 1.2.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level permissions or above to delete or change plugin settings, import demo data, delete Directory Kit related posts and terms, and install arbitrary plugins. A partial patch was introduced in version 1.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2351|2024-08-02T06:19:14.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 01:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2280|2024-08-02T06:19:14.860Z -- listingthemes -- wp%20directory%20kit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2280</link>
      <description>The WP Directory Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ajax_public' function in versions up to, and including, 1.2.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete or change plugin settings, import demo data, delete Directory Kit related posts and terms, and install arbitrary plugins. A partial patch was introduced in version 1.2.0 and an additional partial patch was introduced in version 1.2.2, but the issue was not fully patched until 1.2.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2280|2024-08-02T06:19:14.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2279|2024-08-02T06:19:14.490Z -- listingthemes -- wp%20directory%20kit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2279</link>
      <description>The WP Directory Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.2.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'admin_page_display' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete or change plugin settings, import demo data, modify or delete Directory Kit related posts and terms via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Partial patches were made avilable in versions 1.2.0 and 1.2.1 but the issue was not fully patched until 1.2.2</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2279|2024-08-02T06:19:14.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 05:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2835|2024-08-02T06:33:05.501Z -- listingthemes -- wp%20directory%20kit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2835</link>
      <description>The WP Directory Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'search' parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.2.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2835|2024-08-02T06:33:05.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 06:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2277|2024-08-02T06:19:14.514Z -- listingthemes -- wp%20directory%20kit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2277</link>
      <description>The WP Directory Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.1.9. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'insert' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings and inject malicious JavaScript via a forged request, granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2277|2024-08-02T06:19:14.514Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 01:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2278|2024-08-02T06:19:14.209Z -- listingthemes -- wp%20directory%20kit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2278</link>
      <description>The WP Directory Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in versions up to, and including, 1.1.9 via the 'wdk_public_action' function. This allows unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2278|2024-08-02T06:19:14.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 01:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3217|2024-06-04T17:31:47.944Z -- listingthemes -- wp%20directory%20kit</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3217</link>
      <description>The WP Directory Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'attribute_value' and 'attribute_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3217|2024-06-04T17:31:47.944Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 07:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3217|2024-08-01T20:05:08.233Z -- listingthemes -- wp%20directory%20kit</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3217</link>
      <description>The WP Directory Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'attribute_value' and 'attribute_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3217|2024-08-01T20:05:08.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 07:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
