<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for freeswitch -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/freeswitch/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for freeswitch -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:22:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32307|2024-08-02T15:10:24.454Z -- freeswitch -- sofia-sip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32307</link>
      <description>Sofia-SIP is an open-source SIP User-Agent library, compliant with the IETF RFC3261 specification.
Referring to [GHSA-8599-x7rq-fr54](https://github.com/freeswitch/sofia-sip/security/advisories/GHSA-8599-x7rq-fr54), several other potential heap-over-flow and integer-overflow in stun_parse_attr_error_code and stun_parse_attr_uint32 were found because the lack of attributes length check when Sofia-SIP handles STUN packets. The previous patch of [GHSA-8599-x7rq-fr54](https://github.com/freeswitch/sofia-sip/security/advisories/GHSA-8599-x7rq-fr54) fixed the vulnerability when attr_type did not match the enum value, but there are also vulnerabilities in the handling of other valid cases. The OOB read and integer-overflow made by attacker may lead to crash, high consumption of memory or even other more serious consequences. These issue have been addressed in version 1.13.15. Users are advised to upgrade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32307|2024-08-02T15:10:24.454Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 22:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22741|2024-08-02T10:20:30.275Z -- freeswitch -- sofia-sip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22741</link>
      <description>Sofia-SIP is an open-source SIP User-Agent library, compliant with the IETF RFC3261 specification. In affected versions Sofia-SIP **lacks both message length and attributes length checks** when it handles STUN packets, leading to controllable heap-over-flow. For example, in stun_parse_attribute(), after we get the attribute's type and length value, the length will be used directly to copy from the heap, regardless of the message's left size. Since network users control the overflowed length, and the data is written to heap chunks later, attackers may achieve remote code execution by heap grooming or other exploitation methods. The bug was introduced 16 years ago in sofia-sip 1.12.4 (plus some patches through 12/21/2006) to in tree libs with git-svn-id: http://svn.freeswitch.org/svn/freeswitch/trunk@3774 d0543943-73ff-0310-b7d9-9358b9ac24b2. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22741|2024-08-02T10:20:30.275Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 21:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
