<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for syoyo -- tinydng</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/syoyo/tinydng.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for syoyo -- tinydng</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:23:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1570|2024-08-02T05:49:11.694Z -- syoyo -- tinydng
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1570</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in syoyo tinydng. Affected by this issue is the function __interceptor_memcpy of the file tiny_dng_loader.h. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-223562 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in syoyo tinydng entdeckt. Dies betrifft die Funktion __interceptor_memcpy der Datei tiny_dng_loader.h. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine heap-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Dieses Produkt verzichtet auf eine Versionierung und verwendet stattdessen Rolling Releases. Deshalb sind keine Details zu betroffenen oder zu aktualisierende Versionen vorhanden. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1570|2024-08-02T05:49:11.694Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 14:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
