<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Artesãos -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/artes%C3%A3os/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Artesãos -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36663|2024-08-04T17:30:08.469Z -- artes%C3%A3os -- seotools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36663</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Artesãos SEOTools up to 0.17.1. This affects the function makeTag of the file OpenGraph.php. The manipulation of the argument value leads to open redirect. Upgrading to version 0.17.2 is able to address this issue. The patch is named ca27cd0edf917e0bc805227013859b8b5a1f01fb. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-222231.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Artesãos SEOTools bis 0.17.1 gefunden. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion makeTag der Datei OpenGraph.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments value mit unbekannten Daten kann eine open redirect-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 0.17.2 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als ca27cd0edf917e0bc805227013859b8b5a1f01fb bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36663|2024-08-04T17:30:08.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 06:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36664|2024-08-04T17:30:08.702Z -- artes%C3%A3os -- seotools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36664</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Artesãos SEOTools up to 0.17.1 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function setTitle of the file SEOMeta.php. The manipulation of the argument title leads to open redirect. Upgrading to version 0.17.2 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is ca27cd0edf917e0bc805227013859b8b5a1f01fb. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-222232.
In Artesãos SEOTools bis 0.17.1 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Betroffen ist die Funktion setTitle der Datei SEOMeta.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments title mit unbekannten Daten kann eine open redirect-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 0.17.2 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als ca27cd0edf917e0bc805227013859b8b5a1f01fb bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36664|2024-08-04T17:30:08.702Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36665|2024-08-04T17:30:08.470Z -- artes%C3%A3os -- seotools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36665</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Artesãos SEOTools up to 0.17.1 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function eachValue of the file TwitterCards.php. The manipulation of the argument value leads to open redirect. Upgrading to version 0.17.2 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is ca27cd0edf917e0bc805227013859b8b5a1f01fb. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-222233 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Artesãos SEOTools bis 0.17.1 gefunden. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion eachValue der Datei TwitterCards.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments value mit unbekannten Daten kann eine open redirect-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 0.17.2 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als ca27cd0edf917e0bc805227013859b8b5a1f01fb bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36665|2024-08-04T17:30:08.470Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 18:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
