<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Avast -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/avast/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Avast -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:23:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1585|2024-08-02T05:57:23.319Z -- avast -- avast%20antivirus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1585</link>
      <description>Avast and AVG Antivirus for Windows were susceptible to a Time-of-check/Time-of-use (TOCTOU)  vulnerability in the Quarantine process, leading to arbitrary file/directory deletion. The issue was fixed with Avast and AVG Antivirus version 22.11 and virus definitions from 14 February 2023 or later.  </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1585|2024-08-02T05:57:23.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 18:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1586|2024-08-02T05:57:24.083Z -- avast -- avast%20antivirus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1586</link>
      <description>Avast and AVG Antivirus for Windows were susceptible to a Time-of-check/Time-of-use (TOCTOU)  vulnerability in the restore process leading to arbitrary file creation. The issue was fixed with Avast and AVG Antivirus version 22.11</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1586|2024-08-02T05:57:24.083Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 18:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1587|2024-08-02T05:57:23.265Z -- avast -- avast%20antivirus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1587</link>
      <description>Avast and AVG Antivirus for Windows were susceptible to a NULL pointer dereference issue via RPC-interface. The issue was fixed with Avast and AVG Antivirus version 22.11</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1587|2024-08-02T05:57:23.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 18:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42124|2024-06-05T19:29:39.890Z -- avast -- premium%20security</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42124</link>
      <description>Avast Premium Security Sandbox Protection Incorrect Authorization Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Avast Premium Security. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the sandbox feature. The issue results from incorrect authorization. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code outside the sandbox at medium integrity. Was ZDI-CAN-20178.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42124|2024-06-05T19:29:39.890Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42125|2024-06-10T20:49:48.706Z -- avast -- premium%20security</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42125</link>
      <description>Avast Premium Security Sandbox Protection Link Following Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Avast Premium Security. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the sandbox feature. By creating a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the service to create arbitrary namespace objects. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20383.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42125|2024-06-10T20:49:48.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5102|2024-06-11T20:42:36.851Z -- avast -- antivirus</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5102</link>
      <description>A sym-linked file accessed via the repair function in Avast Antivirus &lt;24.2 on Windows may allow user to elevate privilege to delete arbitrary files or run processes as NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM. The vulnerability exists within the "Repair" (settings -&gt; troubleshooting -&gt; repair) feature, which attempts to delete a file in the current user's AppData directory as NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM. A low-privileged user can make a pseudo-symlink and a junction folder and point to a file on the system. This can provide a low-privileged user an Elevation of Privilege to win a race-condition which will re-create the system files and make Windows callback to a specially-crafted file which could be used to launch a privileged shell instance.

This issue affects Avast Antivirus prior to 24.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5102|2024-06-11T20:42:36.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5102|2024-08-01T21:03:10.574Z -- avast -- antivirus</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5102</link>
      <description>A sym-linked file accessed via the repair function in Avast Antivirus &lt;24.2 on Windows may allow user to elevate privilege to delete arbitrary files or run processes as NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM. The vulnerability exists within the "Repair" (settings -&gt; troubleshooting -&gt; repair) feature, which attempts to delete a file in the current user's AppData directory as NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM. A low-privileged user can make a pseudo-symlink and a junction folder and point to a file on the system. This can provide a low-privileged user an Elevation of Privilege to win a race-condition which will re-create the system files and make Windows callback to a specially-crafted file which could be used to launch a privileged shell instance.

This issue affects Avast Antivirus prior to 24.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5102|2024-08-01T21:03:10.574Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
