<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for MediaArea -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mediaarea/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for MediaArea -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 18:24:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36646|2024-08-04T17:30:08.335Z -- mediaarea -- zenlib
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36646</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in MediaArea ZenLib up to 0.4.38. This affects the function Ztring::Date_From_Seconds_1970_Local of the file Source/ZenLib/Ztring.cpp. The manipulation of the argument Value leads to unchecked return value to null pointer dereference. Upgrading to version 0.4.39 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 6475fcccd37c9cf17e0cfe263b5fe0e2e47a8408. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-217629 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in MediaArea ZenLib bis 0.4.38 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion Ztring::Date_From_Seconds_1970_Local der Datei Source/ZenLib/Ztring.cpp. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments Value mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unchecked return value to null pointer dereference-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 0.4.39 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 6475fcccd37c9cf17e0cfe263b5fe0e2e47a8408 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36646|2024-08-04T17:30:08.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 19:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
