<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Micro Focus -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/micro%20focus/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Micro Focus -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 17:22:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32265|2024-10-21T13:05:58.689Z -- micro%20focus -- enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32265</link>
      <description>
A potential security vulnerability has been identified in the Enterprise Server Common Web Administration (ESCWA) component used in Enterprise Server, Enterprise Test Server, Enterprise Developer, Visual COBOL, and COBOL Server.
An attacker would need to be authenticated into ESCWA to attempt to exploit this vulnerability. As described in the hardening guide in the product documentation, other mitigations including restricting network access to ESCWA and restricting users’ permissions in the Micro Focus Directory Server also reduce the exposure to this issue.

Given the right conditions this vulnerability could be exploited to expose a service account password. The account corresponding to the exposed credentials usually has limited privileges and, in many cases would only be useful for extracting details of other user accounts and similar information.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32265|2024-10-21T13:05:58.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 13:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32263|2024-10-21T13:05:36.364Z -- micro%20focus -- dimensions%20cm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32263</link>
      <description>
A potential vulnerability has been identified in the Micro Focus Dimensions CM Plugin for Jenkins. The vulnerability could be exploited to retrieve a login certificate if an authenticated user is duped into using an attacker-controlled Dimensions CM server.  This vulnerability only applies when the Jenkins plugin is configured to use login certificate credentials.


  https://www.jenkins.io/security/advisory/2023-06-14/ 

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32263|2024-10-21T13:05:36.364Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 15:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32262|2024-10-21T13:05:07.646Z -- micro%20focus -- dimensions%20cm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32262</link>
      <description>
A potential vulnerability has been identified in the Micro Focus Dimensions CM Plugin for Jenkins. The vulnerability allows attackers with Item/Configure permission to access and capture credentials they are not entitled to.
See the following Jenkins security advisory for details:  *   https://www.jenkins.io/security/advisory/2023-06-14/ https://www.jenkins.io/security/advisory/2023-06-14/ 




</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32262|2024-10-21T13:05:07.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 15:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
