<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Micro Focus -- Micro Focus Enterprise Developer, Micro Focus Enterprise Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/micro%20focus/micro%20focus%20enterprise%20developer%2C%20micro%20focus%20enterprise%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Micro Focus -- Micro Focus Enterprise Developer, Micro Focus Enterprise Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:22:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7423|2024-08-05T16:04:11.690Z -- micro%20focus -- micro%20focus%20enterprise%20developer%2C%20micro%20focus%20enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7423</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CWE-352) vulnerability in esfadmingui in Micro Focus Enterprise Developer and Enterprise Server 2.3, 2.3 Update 1 before Hotfix 8, and 2.3 Update 2 before Hotfix 9 allows remote unauthenticated attackers to forge requests, if this component is configured. This includes creating new privileged credentials, resulting in privilege elevation (CWE-275). Note esfadmingui is not enabled by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7423|2024-08-05T16:04:11.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12469|2024-08-05T08:38:05.945Z -- micro%20focus -- micro%20focus%20enterprise%20developer%2C%20micro%20focus%20enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12469</link>
      <description>Incorrect handling of an invalid value for an HTTP request parameter by Directory Server (aka Enterprise Server Administration web UI) in Micro Focus Enterprise Developer and Enterprise Server 2.3 Update 2 and earlier, 3.0 before Patch Update 12, and 4.0 before Patch Update 2 causes a null pointer dereference (CWE-476) and subsequent denial of service due to process termination.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12469|2024-08-05T08:38:05.945Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7424|2024-08-05T16:04:11.286Z -- micro%20focus -- micro%20focus%20enterprise%20developer%2C%20micro%20focus%20enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7424</link>
      <description>A Path Traversal (CWE-22) vulnerability in esfadmingui in Micro Focus Enterprise Developer and Enterprise Server 2.3, 2.3 Update 1 before Hotfix 8, and 2.3 Update 2 before Hotfix 9 allows remote authenticated users to download arbitrary files from a system running the product, if this component is configured. Note esfadmingui is not enabled by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7424|2024-08-05T16:04:11.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7422|2024-08-05T16:04:11.693Z -- micro%20focus -- micro%20focus%20enterprise%20developer%2C%20micro%20focus%20enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7422</link>
      <description>Reflected and stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS, CWE-79) vulnerabilities in esfadmingui in Micro Focus Enterprise Developer and Enterprise Server 2.3, 2.3 Update 1 before Hotfix 8, and 2.3 Update 2 before Hotfix 9 allow remote authenticated attackers to bypass protection mechanisms (CWE-693) and other security features, if this component is configured. Note esfadmingui is not enabled by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7422|2024-08-05T16:04:11.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7420|2024-08-05T16:04:11.250Z -- micro%20focus -- micro%20focus%20enterprise%20developer%2C%20micro%20focus%20enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7420</link>
      <description>An Authentication Bypass (CWE-287) vulnerability in ESMAC (aka Enterprise Server Monitor and Control) in Micro Focus Enterprise Developer and Enterprise Server 2.3 and earlier, 2.3 Update 1 before Hotfix 8, and 2.3 Update 2 before Hotfix 9 allows remote unauthenticated attackers to view and alter configuration information and alter the state of the running product (CWE-275).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7420|2024-08-05T16:04:11.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7421|2024-08-05T16:04:11.241Z -- micro%20focus -- micro%20focus%20enterprise%20developer%2C%20micro%20focus%20enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7421</link>
      <description>Reflected and stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS, CWE-79) vulnerabilities in Directory Server (aka Enterprise Server Administration web UI) and ESMAC (aka Enterprise Server Monitor and Control) in Micro Focus Enterprise Developer and Enterprise Server 2.3 and earlier, 2.3 Update 1 before Hotfix 8, and 2.3 Update 2 before Hotfix 9 allow remote authenticated attackers to bypass protection mechanisms (CWE-693) and other security features.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7421|2024-08-05T16:04:11.241Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5187|2024-08-05T14:55:35.343Z -- micro%20focus -- micro%20focus%20enterprise%20developer%2C%20micro%20focus%20enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5187</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CWE-352) vulnerability in Directory Server (aka Enterprise Server Administration web UI) in Micro Focus Enterprise Developer and Enterprise Server 2.3 and earlier, 2.3 Update 1 before Hotfix 8, and 2.3 Update 2 before Hotfix 9 allows remote unauthenticated attackers to view and alter (CWE-275) configuration information and inject OS commands (CWE-78) via forged requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5187|2024-08-05T14:55:35.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
