<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for CollaboraOnline -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/collaboraonline/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for CollaboraOnline -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 05:22:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43817|2024-08-04T04:03:08.905Z -- collaboraonline -- online
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43817</link>
      <description>Collabora Online is a collaborative online office suite based on LibreOffice technology. In affected versions a reflected XSS vulnerability was found in Collabora Online. An attacker could inject unescaped HTML into a variable as they created the Collabora Online iframe, and execute scripts inside the context of the Collabora Online iframe. This would give access to a small set of user settings stored in the browser, as well as the session's authentication token which was also passed in at iframe creation time. Users should upgrade to Collabora Online 6.4.16 or higher or Collabora Online 4.2.20 or higher. Collabora Online Development Edition 21.11 is not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43817|2024-08-04T04:03:08.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 19:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29182|2024-06-04T17:57:56.571Z -- collaboraonline -- online</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29182</link>
      <description>Collabora Online is a collaborative online office suite based on LibreOffice. A stored cross-site scripting vulnerability was found in Collabora Online. An attacker could create a document with an XSS payload in document text referenced by field which, if hovered over to produce a tooltip, could be executed by the user's browser. Users should upgrade to Collabora Online 23.05.10.1 or higher. Earlier series of Collabora Online, 22.04, 21.11, etc. are unaffected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29182|2024-06-04T17:57:56.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 14:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25114|2024-06-04T17:35:48.290Z -- collaboraonline -- online</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25114</link>
      <description>Collabora Online is a collaborative online office suite based on LibreOffice technology. Each document in Collabora Online is opened by a separate "Kit" instance in a different "jail" with a unique directory "jailID" name. For security reasons, this directory name is randomly generated and should not be given out to the client. In affected versions of Collabora Online it is possible to use the CELL() function, with the "filename" argument, in the spreadsheet component to get a path which includes this JailID. The impact of this vulnerability in its own is low because it requires to be chained with another vulnerability. Users should upgrade to Collabora Online 23.05.9; Collabora Online 22.05.22; Collabora Online 21.11.10 or higher. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25114|2024-06-04T17:35:48.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 21:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29182|2024-08-02T01:10:54.093Z -- collaboraonline -- online</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29182</link>
      <description>Collabora Online is a collaborative online office suite based on LibreOffice. A stored cross-site scripting vulnerability was found in Collabora Online. An attacker could create a document with an XSS payload in document text referenced by field which, if hovered over to produce a tooltip, could be executed by the user's browser. Users should upgrade to Collabora Online 23.05.10.1 or higher. Earlier series of Collabora Online, 22.04, 21.11, etc. are unaffected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29182|2024-08-02T01:10:54.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 14:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
