<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for PX4 -- PX4-Autopilot</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/px4/px4-autopilot.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for PX4 -- PX4-Autopilot</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:23:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46256|2024-08-02T20:37:40.220Z -- px4 -- px4-autopilot
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46256</link>
      <description>PX4-Autopilot provides PX4 flight control solution for drones. In versions 1.14.0-rc1 and prior, PX4-Autopilot has a heap buffer overflow vulnerability in the parser function due to the absence of `parserbuf_index` value checking. A malfunction of the sensor device can cause a heap buffer overflow with leading unexpected drone behavior. Malicious applications can exploit the vulnerability even if device sensor malfunction does not occur. Up to the maximum value of an `unsigned int`, bytes sized data can be written to the heap memory area. As of time of publication, no fixed version is available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46256|2024-08-02T20:37:40.220Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-47625|2024-08-02T21:16:42.208Z -- px4 -- px4-autopilot
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47625</link>
      <description>PX4 autopilot is a flight control solution for drones. In affected versions a global buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the CrsfParser_TryParseCrsfPacket function in /src/drivers/rc/crsf_rc/CrsfParser.cpp:298 due to the invalid size check. A malicious user may create an RC packet remotely and that packet goes into the device where the _rcs_buf reads. The global buffer overflow vulnerability will be triggered and the drone can behave unexpectedly. This issue has been addressed in version 1.14.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-47625|2024-08-02T21:16:42.208Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 20:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
