<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for QEMU -- Qemu:</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qemu/qemu%3A.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for QEMU -- Qemu:</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2620|2024-08-05T14:02:07.311Z -- qemu -- qemu%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2620</link>
      <description>Quick emulator (QEMU) before 2.8 built with the Cirrus CLGD 54xx VGA Emulator support is vulnerable to an out-of-bounds access issue. The issue could occur while copying VGA data in cirrus_bitblt_cputovideo. A privileged user inside guest could use this flaw to crash the QEMU process OR potentially execute arbitrary code on host with privileges of the QEMU process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2620|2024-08-05T14:02:07.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2633|2024-08-05T14:02:06.898Z -- qemu -- qemu%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2633</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds memory access issue was found in Quick Emulator (QEMU) before 1.7.2 in the VNC display driver. This flaw could occur while refreshing the VNC display surface area in the 'vnc_refresh_server_surface'. A user inside a guest could use this flaw to crash the QEMU process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2633|2024-08-05T14:02:06.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2630|2024-08-05T14:02:07.177Z -- qemu -- qemu%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2630</link>
      <description>A stack buffer overflow flaw was found in the Quick Emulator (QEMU) before 2.9 built with the Network Block Device (NBD) client support. The flaw could occur while processing server's response to a 'NBD_OPT_LIST' request. A malicious NBD server could use this issue to crash a remote NBD client resulting in DoS or potentially execute arbitrary code on client host with privileges of the QEMU process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2630|2024-08-05T14:02:07.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
