<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ckeditor -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ckeditor/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ckeditor -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:21:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31175|2024-08-03T07:11:39.611Z -- ckeditor -- ckeditor5
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31175</link>
      <description>CKEditor 5 is a JavaScript rich text editor. A cross-site scripting vulnerability has been discovered affecting three optional CKEditor 5's packages in versions prior to 35.0.1. The vulnerability allowed to trigger a JavaScript code after fulfilling special conditions. The affected packages are `@ckeditor/ckeditor5-markdown-gfm`, `@ckeditor/ckeditor5-html-support`, and `@ckeditor/ckeditor5-html-embed`. The specific conditions are 1) Using one of the affected packages. In case of `ckeditor5-html-support` and `ckeditor5-html-embed`, additionally, it was required to use a configuration that allows unsafe markup inside the editor. 2) Destroying the editor instance and 3) Initializing the editor on an element and using an element other than `&lt;textarea&gt;` as a base. The root cause of the issue was a mechanism responsible for updating the source element with the markup coming from the CKEditor 5 data pipeline after destroying the editor. This vulnerability might affect a small percent of integrators that depend on dynamic editor initialization/destroy and use Markdown, General HTML Support or HTML embed features. The problem has been recognized and patched. The fix is available in version 35.0.1. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31175|2024-08-03T07:11:39.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 19:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24729|2024-08-03T04:20:49.845Z -- ckeditor -- ckeditor4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24729</link>
      <description>CKEditor4 is an open source what-you-see-is-what-you-get HTML editor. CKEditor4 prior to version 4.18.0 contains a vulnerability in the `dialog` plugin. The vulnerability allows abuse of a dialog input validator regular expression, which can cause a significant performance drop resulting in a browser tab freeze. A patch is available in version 4.18.0. There are currently no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24729|2024-08-03T04:20:49.845Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24728|2024-08-03T04:20:49.856Z -- ckeditor -- ckeditor4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24728</link>
      <description>CKEditor4 is an open source what-you-see-is-what-you-get HTML editor. A vulnerability has been discovered in the core HTML processing module and may affect all plugins used by CKEditor 4 prior to version 4.18.0. The vulnerability allows someone to inject malformed HTML bypassing content sanitization, which could result in executing JavaScript code. This problem has been patched in version 4.18.0. There are currently no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24728|2024-08-03T04:20:49.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24815|2024-07-05T17:21:42.034Z -- ckeditor -- ckeditor4</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24815</link>
      <description>CKEditor4 is an open source what-you-see-is-what-you-get HTML editor. A cross-site scripting vulnerability has been discovered in the core HTML parsing module in versions of CKEditor4 prior to 4.24.0-lts. It may affect all editor instances that enabled full-page editing mode or enabled CDATA elements in Advanced Content Filtering configuration (defaults to `script` and `style` elements). The vulnerability allows attackers to inject malformed HTML content bypassing Advanced Content Filtering mechanism, which could result in executing JavaScript code. An attacker could abuse faulty CDATA content detection and use it to prepare an intentional attack on the editor. A fix is available in version 4.24.0-lts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24815|2024-07-05T17:21:42.034Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24815|2024-02-07T17:29:51.330Z -- ckeditor -- ckeditor4</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24815</link>
      <description>CKEditor4 is an open source what-you-see-is-what-you-get HTML editor. A cross-site scripting vulnerability has been discovered in the core HTML parsing module in versions of CKEditor4 prior to 4.24.0-lts. It may affect all editor instances that enabled full-page editing mode or enabled CDATA elements in Advanced Content Filtering configuration (defaults to `script` and `style` elements). The vulnerability allows attackers to inject malformed HTML content bypassing Advanced Content Filtering mechanism, which could result in executing JavaScript code. An attacker could abuse faulty CDATA content detection and use it to prepare an intentional attack on the editor. A fix is available in version 4.24.0-lts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24815|2024-02-07T17:29:51.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24816|2024-06-04T17:43:36.184Z -- ckeditor -- ckeditor4</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24816</link>
      <description>CKEditor4 is an open source what-you-see-is-what-you-get HTML editor. A cross-site scripting vulnerability vulnerability has been discovered in versions prior to 4.24.0-lts in samples that use the `preview` feature. All integrators that use these samples in the production code can be affected. The vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code by abusing the misconfigured preview feature. It affects all users using the CKEditor 4 at version &lt; 4.24.0-lts with affected samples used in a production environment. A fix is available in version 4.24.0-lts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24816|2024-06-04T17:43:36.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
