<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ckeditor -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ckeditor/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ckeditor -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 21:22:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-37695|2024-08-04T01:23:01.506Z -- ckeditor -- ckeditor4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-37695</link>
      <description>ckeditor is an open source WYSIWYG HTML editor with rich content support. A potential vulnerability has been discovered in CKEditor 4 [Fake Objects](https://ckeditor.com/cke4/addon/fakeobjects) package. The vulnerability allowed to inject malformed Fake Objects HTML, which could result in executing JavaScript code. It affects all users using the CKEditor 4 plugins listed above at version &lt; 4.16.2. The problem has been recognized and patched. The fix will be available in version 4.16.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-37695|2024-08-04T01:23:01.506Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 23:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41165|2024-08-04T02:59:31.758Z -- ckeditor -- ckeditor4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41165</link>
      <description>CKEditor4 is an open source WYSIWYG HTML editor. In affected version a vulnerability has been discovered in the core HTML processing module and may affect all plugins used by CKEditor 4. The vulnerability allowed to inject malformed comments HTML bypassing content sanitization, which could result in executing JavaScript code. It affects all users using the CKEditor 4 at version &lt; 4.17.0. The problem has been recognized and patched. The fix will be available in version 4.17.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41165|2024-08-04T02:59:31.758Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 19:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41164|2024-08-04T02:59:31.641Z -- ckeditor -- ckeditor4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41164</link>
      <description>CKEditor4 is an open source WYSIWYG HTML editor. In affected versions a vulnerability has been discovered in the Advanced Content Filter (ACF) module and may affect all plugins used by CKEditor 4. The vulnerability allowed to inject malformed HTML bypassing content sanitization, which could result in executing JavaScript code. It affects all users using the CKEditor 4 at version &lt; 4.17.0. The problem has been recognized and patched. The fix will be available in version 4.17.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41164|2024-08-04T02:59:31.641Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24816|2024-06-04T17:43:36.184Z -- ckeditor -- ckeditor4</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24816</link>
      <description>CKEditor4 is an open source what-you-see-is-what-you-get HTML editor. A cross-site scripting vulnerability vulnerability has been discovered in versions prior to 4.24.0-lts in samples that use the `preview` feature. All integrators that use these samples in the production code can be affected. The vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code by abusing the misconfigured preview feature. It affects all users using the CKEditor 4 at version &lt; 4.24.0-lts with affected samples used in a production environment. A fix is available in version 4.24.0-lts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24816|2024-06-04T17:43:36.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24815|2024-02-07T17:29:51.330Z -- ckeditor -- ckeditor4</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24815</link>
      <description>CKEditor4 is an open source what-you-see-is-what-you-get HTML editor. A cross-site scripting vulnerability has been discovered in the core HTML parsing module in versions of CKEditor4 prior to 4.24.0-lts. It may affect all editor instances that enabled full-page editing mode or enabled CDATA elements in Advanced Content Filtering configuration (defaults to `script` and `style` elements). The vulnerability allows attackers to inject malformed HTML content bypassing Advanced Content Filtering mechanism, which could result in executing JavaScript code. An attacker could abuse faulty CDATA content detection and use it to prepare an intentional attack on the editor. A fix is available in version 4.24.0-lts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24815|2024-02-07T17:29:51.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24815|2024-07-05T17:21:42.034Z -- ckeditor -- ckeditor4</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24815</link>
      <description>CKEditor4 is an open source what-you-see-is-what-you-get HTML editor. A cross-site scripting vulnerability has been discovered in the core HTML parsing module in versions of CKEditor4 prior to 4.24.0-lts. It may affect all editor instances that enabled full-page editing mode or enabled CDATA elements in Advanced Content Filtering configuration (defaults to `script` and `style` elements). The vulnerability allows attackers to inject malformed HTML content bypassing Advanced Content Filtering mechanism, which could result in executing JavaScript code. An attacker could abuse faulty CDATA content detection and use it to prepare an intentional attack on the editor. A fix is available in version 4.24.0-lts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24815|2024-07-05T17:21:42.034Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
