<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Tacitine -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tacitine/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Tacitine -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40628|2024-08-03T12:21:46.247Z -- tacitine -- firewall
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40628</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exists in Tacitine Firewall, all versions of EN6200-PRIME QUAD-35 and EN6200-PRIME QUAD-100 between 19.1.1 to 22.20.1 (inclusive), due to improper control of code generation in the Tacitine Firewall web-based management interface. An unauthenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted http request on the targeted device. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the targeted device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40628|2024-08-03T12:21:46.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40630|2024-08-03T12:21:46.556Z -- tacitine -- firewall
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40630</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exists in Tacitine Firewall, all versions of EN6200-PRIME QUAD-35 and EN6200-PRIME QUAD-100 between 19.1.1 to 22.20.1 (inclusive), due to improper session management in the Tacitine Firewall web-based management interface. An unauthenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted http request on the targeted device. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to perform session fixation on the targeted device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40630|2024-08-03T12:21:46.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40629|2024-08-03T12:21:46.533Z -- tacitine -- firewall
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40629</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exists in Tacitine Firewall, all versions of EN6200-PRIME QUAD-35 and EN6200-PRIME QUAD-100 between 19.1.1 to 22.20.1 (inclusive), due to insecure design in the Tacitine Firewall web-based management interface. An unauthenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted http request on the targeted device. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to view sensitive information on the targeted device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40629|2024-08-03T12:21:46.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
