<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Fortinet -- Fortinet FortiClientLinux</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/fortinet/fortinet%20forticlientlinux.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Fortinet -- Fortinet FortiClientLinux</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 03:23:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16155|2024-08-05T01:10:41.242Z -- fortinet -- fortinet%20forticlientlinux
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16155</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability in FortiClient for Linux 6.2.1 and below may allow a user with low privilege to overwrite system files as root with arbitrary content through system backup file via specially crafted "BackupConfig" type IPC client requests to the fctsched process. Further more, FortiClient for Linux 6.2.2 and below allow low privilege user write the system backup file under root privilege through GUI thus can cause root system file overwrite.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16155|2024-08-05T01:10:41.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 14:47:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16152|2024-08-05T01:10:41.743Z -- fortinet -- fortinet%20forticlientlinux
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16152</link>
      <description>A Denial of service (DoS) vulnerability in FortiClient for Linux 6.2.1 and below may allow an user with low privilege to cause FortiClient processes running under root privilege crashes via sending specially crafted IPC client requests to the fctsched process due the nanomsg not been correctly validated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16152|2024-08-05T01:10:41.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 15:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17652|2024-08-05T01:47:13.604Z -- fortinet -- fortinet%20forticlientlinux
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17652</link>
      <description>A stack buffer overflow vulnerability in FortiClient for Linux 6.2.1 and below may allow a user with low privilege to cause FortiClient processes running under root priviledge crashes via sending specially crafted "StartAvCustomScan" type IPC client requests to the fctsched process due the argv data not been well sanitized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17652|2024-08-05T01:47:13.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 15:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15711|2024-08-05T00:56:22.368Z -- fortinet -- fortinet%20forticlientlinux
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15711</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability in FortiClient for Linux 6.2.1 and below may allow an user with low privilege to run system commands under root privilege via injecting specially crafted "ExportLogs" type IPC client requests to the fctsched process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15711|2024-08-05T00:56:22.368Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 15:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
