<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for go-vela -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/go-vela/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for go-vela -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21432|2024-08-03T18:16:22.403Z -- go-vela -- server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21432</link>
      <description>Vela is a Pipeline Automation (CI/CD) framework built on Linux container technology written in Golang. An authentication mechanism added in version 0.7.0 enables some malicious user to obtain secrets utilizing the injected credentials within the `~/.netrc` file. Refer to the referenced GitHub Security Advisory for complete details. This is fixed in version 0.7.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21432|2024-08-03T18:16:22.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 18:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39395|2024-08-03T12:07:41.884Z -- go-vela -- server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39395</link>
      <description>Vela is a Pipeline Automation (CI/CD) framework built on Linux container technology written in Golang. In Vela Server and Vela Worker prior to version 0.16.0 and Vela UI prior to version 0.17.0, some default configurations for Vela allow exploitation and container breakouts. Users should upgrade to Server 0.16.0, Worker 0.16.0, and UI 0.17.0 to fix the issue. After upgrading, Vela administrators will need to explicitly change the default settings to configure Vela as desired. Some of the fixes will interrupt existing workflows and will require Vela administrators to modify default settings. However, not applying the patch (or workarounds) will continue existing risk exposure. Some workarounds are available. Vela administrators can adjust the worker's `VELA_RUNTIME_PRIVILEGED_IMAGES` setting to be explicitly empty, leverage the `VELA_REPO_ALLOWLIST` setting on the server component to restrict access to a list of repositories that are allowed to be enabled, and/or audit enabled repositories and disable pull_requests if they are not needed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39395|2024-08-03T12:07:41.884Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28236|2024-06-04T18:03:18.752Z -- go-vela -- worker</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28236</link>
      <description>Vela is a Pipeline Automation (CI/CD) framework built on Linux container technology written in Golang. Vela pipelines can use variable substitution combined with insensitive fields like `parameters`, `image` and `entrypoint` to inject secrets into a plugin/image and — by using common substitution string manipulation — can bypass log masking and expose secrets without the use of the commands block. This unexpected behavior primarily impacts secrets restricted by the "no commands" option. This can lead to unintended use of the secret value, and increased risk of exposing the secret during image execution bypassing log masking. **To exploit this** the pipeline author must be supplying the secrets to a plugin that is designed in such a way that will print those parameters in logs. Plugin parameters are not designed for sensitive values and are often intentionally printed throughout execution for informational/debugging purposes. Parameters should therefore be treated as insensitive. While Vela provides secrets masking, secrets exposure is not entirely solved by the masking process. A docker image (plugin) can easily expose secrets if they are not handled properly, or altered in some way. There is a responsibility on the end-user to understand how values injected into a plugin are used. This is a risk that exists for many CICD systems (like GitHub Actions) that handle sensitive runtime variables. Rather, the greater risk is that users who restrict a secret to the "no commands" option and use image restriction can still have their secret value exposed via substitution tinkering, which turns the image and command restrictions into a false sense of security. This issue has been addressed in version 0.23.2. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should not provide sensitive values to plugins that can potentially expose them, especially in `parameters` that are not intended to be used for sensitive values, ensure plugins (especially those that utilize shared secrets) follow best practices to avoid logging parameters that are expected to be sensitive, minimize secrets with `pull_request` events enabled, as this allows users to change pipeline configurations and pull in secrets to steps not typically part of the CI process, make use of the build approval setting, restricting builds from untrusted users, and limit use of shared secrets, as they are less restrictive to access by nature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28236|2024-06-04T18:03:18.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 20:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28236|2024-08-02T00:48:49.488Z -- go-vela -- worker</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28236</link>
      <description>Vela is a Pipeline Automation (CI/CD) framework built on Linux container technology written in Golang. Vela pipelines can use variable substitution combined with insensitive fields like `parameters`, `image` and `entrypoint` to inject secrets into a plugin/image and — by using common substitution string manipulation — can bypass log masking and expose secrets without the use of the commands block. This unexpected behavior primarily impacts secrets restricted by the "no commands" option. This can lead to unintended use of the secret value, and increased risk of exposing the secret during image execution bypassing log masking. **To exploit this** the pipeline author must be supplying the secrets to a plugin that is designed in such a way that will print those parameters in logs. Plugin parameters are not designed for sensitive values and are often intentionally printed throughout execution for informational/debugging purposes. Parameters should therefore be treated as insensitive. While Vela provides secrets masking, secrets exposure is not entirely solved by the masking process. A docker image (plugin) can easily expose secrets if they are not handled properly, or altered in some way. There is a responsibility on the end-user to understand how values injected into a plugin are used. This is a risk that exists for many CICD systems (like GitHub Actions) that handle sensitive runtime variables. Rather, the greater risk is that users who restrict a secret to the "no commands" option and use image restriction can still have their secret value exposed via substitution tinkering, which turns the image and command restrictions into a false sense of security. This issue has been addressed in version 0.23.2. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should not provide sensitive values to plugins that can potentially expose them, especially in `parameters` that are not intended to be used for sensitive values, ensure plugins (especially those that utilize shared secrets) follow best practices to avoid logging parameters that are expected to be sensitive, minimize secrets with `pull_request` events enabled, as this allows users to change pipeline configurations and pull in secrets to steps not typically part of the CI process, make use of the build approval setting, restricting builds from untrusted users, and limit use of shared secrets, as they are less restrictive to access by nature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28236|2024-08-02T00:48:49.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 20:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
