<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for specialk -- User Submitted Posts – Enable Users to Submit Posts from the Front End</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/specialk/user%20submitted%20posts%20%E2%80%93%20enable%20users%20to%20submit%20posts%20from%20the%20front%20end.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for specialk -- User Submitted Posts – Enable Users to Submit Posts from the Front End</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 14:22:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4779|2024-08-02T07:38:00.519Z -- specialk -- user%20submitted%20posts%20%E2%80%93%20enable%20users%20to%20submit%20posts%20from%20the%20front%20end
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4779</link>
      <description>The User Submitted Posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's [usp_gallery] shortcode in versions up to, and including, 20230811 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes like 'before'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4779|2024-08-02T07:38:00.519Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 06:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4308|2024-08-02T07:24:04.489Z -- specialk -- user%20submitted%20posts%20%E2%80%93%20enable%20users%20to%20submit%20posts%20from%20the%20front%20end
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4308</link>
      <description>The User Submitted Posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘user-submitted-content’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 20230809 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4308|2024-08-02T07:24:04.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 07:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
