<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for cifi -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cifi/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for cifi -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-0366|2024-02-05T21:22:01.289Z -- cifi -- Starbox – the Author Box for Humans
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0366</link><description>The Starbox – the Author Box for Humans plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.7 via the action function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for subscribers to view plugin preferences and potentially other user settings.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0366|2024-02-05T21:22:01.289Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0597|2024-02-05T21:21:55.121Z -- cifi -- SEO Plugin by Squirrly SEO
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0597</link><description>The SEO Plugin by Squirrly SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to and including 12.3.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0597|2024-02-05T21:21:55.121Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:21:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0256|2024-02-07T04:31:24.549Z -- cifi -- Starbox – the Author Box for Humans
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0256</link><description>The Starbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Profile Display Name and Social Settings in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0256|2024-02-07T04:31:24.549Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 04:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>