<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for averta -- Master Slider – Responsive Touch Slider</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/averta/master%20slider%20%E2%80%93%20responsive%20touch%20slider.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for averta -- Master Slider – Responsive Touch Slider</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 23:21:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2023-6382|2024-06-01T04:30:32.590Z -- averta -- Master Slider – Responsive Touch Slider</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6382</link><description>The Master Slider – Responsive Touch Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ms_slide' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied 'css_class' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6382|2024-06-01T04:30:32.590Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 04:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4470|2024-05-21T06:49:54.875Z -- averta -- Master Slider – Responsive Touch Slider</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4470</link><description>The Master Slider – Responsive Touch Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ms_slide_info' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied 'tag_name' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4470|2024-05-21T06:49:54.875Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 06:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0611|2024-03-02T11:15:34.620Z -- averta -- Master Slider – Responsive Touch Slider</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0611</link><description>The Master Slider – Responsive Touch Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the slides callback functionality in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0611|2024-03-02T11:15:34.620Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 11:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1449|2024-03-02T11:15:35.352Z -- averta -- Master Slider – Responsive Touch Slider</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1449</link><description>The Master Slider – Responsive Touch Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's ms_slide shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1449|2024-03-02T11:15:35.352Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 11:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>