<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for averta -- Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/averta/shortcodes%20and%20extra%20features%20for%20phlox%20theme.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for averta -- Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 16:23:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1348|2024-06-06T13:10:44.478Z -- averta -- shortcodes%20and%20extra%20features%20for%20phlox%20theme</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1348</link>
      <description>The Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the custom JS parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.15.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1348|2024-06-06T13:10:44.478Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3517|2024-05-02T16:52:28.825Z -- averta -- shortcodes%20and%20extra%20features%20for%20phlox%20theme</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3517</link>
      <description>The Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Accordion Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.15.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3517|2024-05-02T16:52:28.825Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31099|2024-06-05T14:01:11.056Z -- averta -- shortcodes%20and%20extra%20features%20for%20phlox%20theme</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31099</link>
      <description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Averta Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme auxin-elements.This issue affects Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme: from n/a through 2.15.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31099|2024-06-05T14:01:11.056Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 14:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
