<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for averta -- Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/averta/shortcodes%20and%20extra%20features%20for%20phlox%20theme.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for averta -- Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1357|2024-04-16T09:33:00.476Z -- averta -- Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1357</link><description>The Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's aux_timeline shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.15.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as thumb_mode and date_type. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1357|2024-04-16T09:33:00.476Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1533|2024-05-02T16:52:22.761Z -- averta -- Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1533</link><description>The Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the HTML Element in all versions up to, and including, 2.15.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Requires Elementor and the Phlox theme to be installed.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1533|2024-05-02T16:52:22.761Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1396|2024-05-02T16:52:07.802Z -- averta -- Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1396</link><description>The Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘title_tag’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.15.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1396|2024-05-02T16:52:07.802Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1348|2024-05-02T16:51:44.976Z -- averta -- Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1348</link><description>The Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the custom JS parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.15.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1348|2024-05-02T16:51:44.976Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31099|2024-04-01T14:07:10.063Z -- Averta -- Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31099</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Averta Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme.This issue affects Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme: from n/a through 2.15.5.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31099|2024-04-01T14:07:10.063Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 14:07:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3341|2024-05-02T16:51:58.753Z -- averta -- Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3341</link><description>The Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'aux_gmaps' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.15.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3341|2024-05-02T16:51:58.753Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3517|2024-05-02T16:52:28.825Z -- averta -- Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3517</link><description>The Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Accordion Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.15.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3517|2024-05-02T16:52:28.825Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>