<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for BUFFALO INC. -- Buffalo network devices</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/buffalo%20inc./buffalo%20network%20devices.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for BUFFALO INC. -- Buffalo network devices</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39044|2024-08-03T11:10:32.333Z -- buffalo%20inc. -- buffalo%20network%20devices
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39044</link>
      <description>Hidden functionality vulnerability in multiple Buffalo network devices allows a network-adjacent attacker with an administrative privilege to execute an arbitrary OS command. The affected products/versions are as follows: WCR-300 firmware Ver. 1.87 and earlier, WHR-HP-G300N firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WHR-HP-GN firmware Ver. 1.87 and earlier, WPL-05G300 firmware Ver. 1.88 and earlier, WZR-300HP firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WZR-450HP firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WZR-600DHP firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WZR-900DHP firmware Ver. 1.15 and earlier, WZR-HP-AG300H firmware Ver. 1.76 and earlier, WZR-HP-G302H firmware Ver. 1.86 and earlier, WLAE-AG300N firmware Ver. 1.86 and earlier, FS-600DHP firmware Ver. 3.40 and earlier, FS-G300N firmware Ver. 3.14 and earlier, FS-HP-G300N firmware Ver. 3.33 and earlier, FS-R600DHP firmware Ver. 3.40 and earlier, BHR-4GRV firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, DWR-HP-G300NH firmware Ver. 1.84 and earlier, DWR-PG firmware Ver. 1.83 and earlier, HW-450HP-ZWE firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WER-A54G54 firmware Ver. 1.43 and earlier, WER-AG54 firmware Ver. 1.43 and earlier, WER-AM54G54 firmware Ver. 1.43 and earlier, WER-AMG54 firmware Ver. 1.43 and earlier, WHR-300 firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WHR-300HP firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WHR-AM54G54 firmware Ver. 1.43 and earlier, WHR-AMG54 firmware Ver. 1.43 and earlier, WHR-AMPG firmware Ver. 1.52 and earlier, WHR-G firmware Ver. 1.49 and earlier, WHR-G300N firmware Ver. 1.65 and earlier, WHR-G301N firmware Ver. 1.87 and earlier, WHR-G54S firmware Ver. 1.43 and earlier, WHR-G54S-NI firmware Ver. 1.24 and earlier, WHR-HP-AMPG firmware Ver. 1.43 and earlier, WHR-HP-G firmware Ver. 1.49 and earlier, WHR-HP-G54 firmware Ver. 1.43 and earlier, WLI-H4-D600 firmware Ver. 1.88 and earlier, WLI-TX4-AG300N firmware Ver. 1.53 and earlier, WS024BF firmware Ver. 1.60 and earlier, WS024BF-NW firmware Ver. 1.60 and earlier, WZR2-G108 firmware Ver. 1.33 and earlier, WZR2-G300N firmware Ver. 1.55 and earlier, WZR-450HP-CWT firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WZR-450HP-UB firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WZR-600DHP2 firmware Ver. 1.15 and earlier, WZR-AGL300NH firmware Ver. 1.55 and earlier, WZR-AMPG144NH firmware Ver. 1.49 and earlier, WZR-AMPG300NH firmware Ver. 1.51 and earlier, WZR-D1100H firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WZR-G144N firmware Ver. 1.48 and earlier, WZR-G144NH firmware Ver. 1.48 and earlier, WZR-HP-G300NH firmware Ver. 1.84 and earlier, WZR-HP-G301NH firmware Ver. 1.84 and earlier, and WZR-HP-G450H firmware Ver. 1.90 and earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39044|2024-08-03T11:10:32.333Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-20716|2024-08-03T17:53:21.257Z -- buffalo%20inc. -- buffalo%20network%20devices
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-20716</link>
      <description>Hidden functionality in multiple Buffalo network devices (BHR-4RV firmware Ver.2.55 and prior, FS-G54 firmware Ver.2.04 and prior, WBR2-B11 firmware Ver.2.32 and prior, WBR2-G54 firmware Ver.2.32 and prior, WBR2-G54-KD firmware Ver.2.32 and prior, WBR-B11 firmware Ver.2.23 and prior, WBR-G54 firmware Ver.2.23 and prior, WBR-G54L firmware Ver.2.20 and prior, WHR2-A54G54 firmware Ver.2.25 and prior, WHR2-G54 firmware Ver.2.23 and prior, WHR2-G54V firmware Ver.2.55 and prior, WHR3-AG54 firmware Ver.2.23 and prior, WHR-G54 firmware Ver.2.16 and prior, WHR-G54-NF firmware Ver.2.10 and prior, WLA2-G54 firmware Ver.2.24 and prior, WLA2-G54C firmware Ver.2.24 and prior, WLA-B11 firmware Ver.2.20 and prior, WLA-G54 firmware Ver.2.20 and prior, WLA-G54C firmware Ver.2.20 and prior, WLAH-A54G54 firmware Ver.2.54 and prior, WLAH-AM54G54 firmware Ver.2.54 and prior, WLAH-G54 firmware Ver.2.54 and prior, WLI2-TX1-AG54 firmware Ver.2.53 and prior, WLI2-TX1-AMG54 firmware Ver.2.53 and prior, WLI2-TX1-G54 firmware Ver.2.20 and prior, WLI3-TX1-AMG54 firmware Ver.2.53 and prior, WLI3-TX1-G54 firmware Ver.2.53 and prior, WLI-T1-B11 firmware Ver.2.20 and prior, WLI-TX1-G54 firmware Ver.2.20 and prior, WVR-G54-NF firmware Ver.2.02 and prior, WZR-G108 firmware Ver.2.41 and prior, WZR-G54 firmware Ver.2.41 and prior, WZR-HP-G54 firmware Ver.2.41 and prior, WZR-RS-G54 firmware Ver.2.55 and prior, and WZR-RS-G54HP firmware Ver.2.55 and prior) allows a remote attacker to enable the debug option and to execute arbitrary code or OS commands, change the configuration, and cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-20716|2024-08-03T17:53:21.257Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40966|2024-08-03T12:28:42.948Z -- buffalo%20inc. -- buffalo%20network%20devices
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40966</link>
      <description>Authentication bypass vulnerability in multiple Buffalo network devices allows a network-adjacent attacker to bypass authentication and access the device. The affected products/versions are as follows: WCR-300 firmware Ver. 1.87 and earlier, WHR-HP-G300N firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WHR-HP-GN firmware Ver. 1.87 and earlier, WPL-05G300 firmware Ver. 1.88 and earlier, WRM-D2133HP firmware Ver. 2.85 and earlier, WRM-D2133HS firmware Ver. 2.96 and earlier, WTR-M2133HP firmware Ver. 2.85 and earlier, WTR-M2133HS firmware Ver. 2.96 and earlier, WXR-1900DHP firmware Ver. 2.50 and earlier, WXR-1900DHP2 firmware Ver. 2.59 and earlier, WXR-1900DHP3 firmware Ver. 2.63 and earlier, WXR-5950AX12 firmware Ver. 3.40 and earlier, WXR-6000AX12B firmware Ver. 3.40 and earlier, WXR-6000AX12S firmware Ver. 3.40 and earlier, WZR-300HP firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WZR-450HP firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WZR-600DHP firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WZR-900DHP firmware Ver. 1.15 and earlier, WZR-1750DHP2 firmware Ver. 2.31 and earlier, WZR-HP-AG300H firmware Ver. 1.76 and earlier, WZR-HP-G302H firmware Ver. 1.86 and earlier, WEM-1266 firmware Ver. 2.85 and earlier, WEM-1266WP firmware Ver. 2.85 and earlier, WLAE-AG300N firmware Ver. 1.86 and earlier, FS-600DHP firmware Ver. 3.40 and earlier, FS-G300N firmware Ver. 3.14 and earlier, FS-HP-G300N firmware Ver. 3.33 and earlier, FS-R600DHP firmware Ver. 3.40 and earlier, BHR-4GRV firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, DWR-HP-G300NH firmware Ver. 1.84 and earlier, DWR-PG firmware Ver. 1.83 and earlier, HW-450HP-ZWE firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WER-A54G54 firmware Ver. 1.43 and earlier, WER-AG54 firmware Ver. 1.43 and earlier, WER-AM54G54 firmware Ver. 1.43 and earlier, WER-AMG54 firmware Ver. 1.43 and earlier, WHR-300 firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WHR-300HP firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WHR-AM54G54 firmware Ver. 1.43 and earlier, WHR-AMG54 firmware Ver. 1.43 and earlier, WHR-AMPG firmware Ver. 1.52 and earlier, WHR-G firmware Ver. 1.49 and earlier, WHR-G300N firmware Ver. 1.65 and earlier, WHR-G301N firmware Ver. 1.87 and earlier, WHR-G54S firmware Ver. 1.43 and earlier, WHR-G54S-NI firmware Ver. 1.24 and earlier, WHR-HP-AMPG firmware Ver. 1.43 and earlier, WHR-HP-G firmware Ver. 1.49 and earlier, WHR-HP-G54 firmware Ver. 1.43 and earlier, WLI-H4-D600 firmware Ver. 1.88 and earlier, WS024BF firmware Ver. 1.60 and earlier, WS024BF-NW firmware Ver. 1.60 and earlier, WXR-1750DHP firmware Ver. 2.60 and earlier, WXR-1750DHP2 firmware Ver. 2.60 and earlier, WZR-1166DHP firmware Ver. 2.18 and earlier, WZR-1166DHP2 firmware Ver. 2.18 and earlier, WZR-1750DHP firmware Ver. 2.30 and earlier, WZR2-G300N firmware Ver. 1.55 and earlier, WZR-450HP-CWT firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WZR-450HP-UB firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WZR-600DHP2 firmware Ver. 1.15 and earlier, WZR-600DHP3 firmware Ver. 2.19 and earlier, WZR-900DHP2 firmware Ver. 2.19 and earlier, WZR-AGL300NH firmware Ver. 1.55 and earlier, WZR-AMPG144NH firmware Ver. 1.49 and earlier, WZR-AMPG300NH firmware Ver. 1.51 and earlier, WZR-D1100H firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WZR-G144N firmware Ver. 1.48 and earlier, WZR-G144NH firmware Ver. 1.48 and earlier, WZR-HP-G300NH firmware Ver. 1.84 and earlier, WZR-HP-G301NH firmware Ver. 1.84 and earlier, WZR-HP-G450H firmware Ver. 1.90 and earlier, WZR-S1750DHP firmware Ver. 2.32 and earlier, WZR-S600DHP firmware Ver. 2.19 and earlier, and WZR-S900DHP firmware Ver. 2.19 and earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40966|2024-08-03T12:28:42.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34840|2024-08-03T09:22:10.744Z -- buffalo%20inc. -- buffalo%20network%20devices
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34840</link>
      <description>Use of hard-coded credentials vulnerability in multiple Buffalo network devices allows a network-adjacent attacker to alter?configuration settings of the device. The affected products/versions are as follows: WZR-300HP firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WZR-450HP firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WZR-600DHP firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WZR-900DHP firmware Ver. 1.15 and earlier, HW-450HP-ZWE firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WZR-450HP-CWT firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WZR-450HP-UB firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier, WZR-600DHP2 firmware Ver. 1.15 and earlier, and WZR-D1100H firmware Ver. 2.00 and earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34840|2024-08-03T09:22:10.744Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
