<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Intel Corporation -- Multiple</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/intel%20corporation/multiple.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Intel Corporation -- Multiple</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:24:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3620|2024-08-05T04:50:29.256Z -- intel%20corporation -- multiple
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3620</link>
      <description>Systems with microprocessors utilizing speculative execution and address translations may allow unauthorized disclosure of information residing in the L1 data cache to an attacker with local user access via a terminal page fault and a side-channel analysis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3620|2024-08-05T04:50:29.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3640|2024-08-05T04:50:30.422Z -- intel%20corporation -- multiple
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3640</link>
      <description>Systems with microprocessors utilizing speculative execution and that perform speculative reads of system registers may allow unauthorized disclosure of system parameters to an attacker with local user access via a side-channel analysis, aka Rogue System Register Read (RSRE), Variant 3a.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3640|2024-08-05T04:50:30.422Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3646|2024-08-05T04:50:30.406Z -- intel%20corporation -- multiple
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3646</link>
      <description>Systems with microprocessors utilizing speculative execution and address translations may allow unauthorized disclosure of information residing in the L1 data cache to an attacker with local user access with guest OS privilege via a terminal page fault and a side-channel analysis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3646|2024-08-05T04:50:30.406Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3639|2024-08-05T04:50:30.281Z -- intel%20corporation -- multiple
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3639</link>
      <description>Systems with microprocessors utilizing speculative execution and speculative execution of memory reads before the addresses of all prior memory writes are known may allow unauthorized disclosure of information to an attacker with local user access via a side-channel analysis, aka Speculative Store Bypass (SSB), Variant 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3639|2024-08-05T04:50:30.281Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3615|2024-08-05T04:50:30.411Z -- intel%20corporation -- multiple
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3615</link>
      <description>Systems with microprocessors utilizing speculative execution and Intel software guard extensions (Intel SGX) may allow unauthorized disclosure of information residing in the L1 data cache from an enclave to an attacker with local user access via a side-channel analysis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3615|2024-08-05T04:50:30.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
