<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for simplesamlphp -- simplesamlphp-module-openidprovider</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/simplesamlphp/simplesamlphp-module-openidprovider.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for simplesamlphp -- simplesamlphp-module-openidprovider</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:23:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2010-10008|2024-08-07T04:17:10.297Z -- simplesamlphp -- simplesamlphp-module-openidprovider
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2010-10008</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in simplesamlphp simplesamlphp-module-openidprovider up to 0.8.x. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file templates/trust.tpl.php. The manipulation of the argument StateID leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 0.9.0 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 8365d48c863cf06ccf1465cc0a161cefae29d69d. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-218473 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.
In simplesamlphp simplesamlphp-module-openidprovider bis 0.8.x wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei templates/trust.tpl.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments StateID mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 0.9.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 8365d48c863cf06ccf1465cc0a161cefae29d69d bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2010-10008|2024-08-07T04:17:10.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 07:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
