<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Sante -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sante/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Sante -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 21:21:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34297|2024-06-05T20:49:38.853Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34297</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34297|2024-06-05T20:49:38.853Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1863|2024-04-01T21:46:30.404Z -- sante -- pacs%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1863</link>
      <description>Sante PACS Server Token Endpoint SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante PACS Server. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of HTTP requests on port 3000. When parsing the token parameter, the process does not properly validate a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of NETWORK SERVICE. Was ZDI-CAN-21539.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1863|2024-04-01T21:46:30.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34295|2024-06-05T19:48:19.234Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34295</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34295|2024-06-05T19:48:19.234Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
