<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Sante -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sante/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Sante -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24063|2024-08-03T03:59:23.650Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24063</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro 13.2.0.21165. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15105.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24063|2024-08-03T03:59:23.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24058|2024-08-03T03:59:23.491Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24058</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro 11.8.7.0. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of J2K files. Crafted data in a J2K file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15095.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24058|2024-08-03T03:59:23.491Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 19:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24064|2024-08-03T03:59:23.635Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24064</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro 11.8.8.0. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of J2K images. Crafted data in a J2K file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15161.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24064|2024-08-03T03:59:23.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 19:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28668|2024-08-03T06:03:52.656Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28668</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro 11.9.2. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of J2K files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated data structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16679.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28668|2024-08-03T06:03:52.656Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 15:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24059|2024-08-03T03:59:23.699Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24059</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro 11.8.7.0. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. Crafted data in a DCM file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process Was ZDI-CAN-15098.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24059|2024-08-03T03:59:23.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 19:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24061|2024-08-03T03:59:23.579Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24061</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro 11.8.7.0. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15100.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24061|2024-08-03T03:59:23.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 19:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2272|2024-08-03T00:32:09.547Z -- sante -- pacs%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2272</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Sante PACS Server 3.0.4. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the processing of calls to the login endpoint. When parsing the username element, the process does not properly validate a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-17331.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2272|2024-08-03T00:32:09.547Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 15:20:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24062|2024-08-03T03:59:23.459Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24062</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro 13.2.0.21165. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15104.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24062|2024-08-03T03:59:23.459Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 19:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24055|2024-08-03T03:59:23.490Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24055</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro 11.8.7.0. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of GIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14972.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24055|2024-08-03T03:59:23.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 19:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24057|2024-08-03T03:59:23.637Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24057</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro 11.8.7.0. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of J2K files. Crafted data in a J2K file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15077.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24057|2024-08-03T03:59:23.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 19:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24060|2024-08-03T03:59:23.571Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24060</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro 11.8.7.0. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. Crafted data in a DCM file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15099.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24060|2024-08-03T03:59:23.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 19:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24056|2024-08-03T03:59:23.649Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24056</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro 11.8.7.0. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of J2K files. Crafted data in a J2K file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15076.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24056|2024-08-03T03:59:23.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 19:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34294|2024-08-02T16:10:06.367Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34294</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21086.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34294|2024-08-02T16:10:06.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34297|2024-08-02T16:10:06.338Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34297</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34297|2024-08-02T16:10:06.338Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34296|2024-08-02T16:10:06.467Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34296</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34296|2024-08-02T16:10:06.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34295|2024-08-02T16:10:05.507Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34295</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34295|2024-08-02T16:10:05.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35734|2024-08-02T16:30:44.957Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35734</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21405.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35734|2024-08-02T16:30:44.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1863|2024-08-01T18:56:22.314Z -- sante -- pacs%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1863</link>
      <description>Sante PACS Server Token Endpoint SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante PACS Server. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of HTTP requests on port 3000. When parsing the token parameter, the process does not properly validate a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of NETWORK SERVICE. Was ZDI-CAN-21539.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1863|2024-08-01T18:56:22.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32133|2024-06-18T18:13:39.137Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32133</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro J2K File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of J2K images. Crafted data in a J2K image can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15628.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32133|2024-06-18T18:13:39.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1863|2024-04-01T21:46:30.404Z -- sante -- pacs%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1863</link>
      <description>Sante PACS Server Token Endpoint SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante PACS Server. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of HTTP requests on port 3000. When parsing the token parameter, the process does not properly validate a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of NETWORK SERVICE. Was ZDI-CAN-21539.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1863|2024-04-01T21:46:30.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35734|2024-06-04T17:18:35.926Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35734</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21405.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35734|2024-06-04T17:18:35.926Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51637|2024-06-04T17:20:15.737Z -- sante -- pacs%20server%20pg</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51637</link>
      <description>Sante PACS Server PG Patient Query SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante PACS Server PG. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the DICOM service, which listens on TCP port 11122 by default. When parsing the NAME element of the PATIENT record, the process does not properly validate a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of NETWORK SERVICE. Was ZDI-CAN-21579.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51637|2024-06-04T17:20:15.737Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 19:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34296|2024-06-05T19:46:46.708Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34296</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21126.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34296|2024-06-05T19:46:46.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34297|2024-06-05T20:49:38.853Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34297</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34297|2024-06-05T20:49:38.853Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34294|2024-06-04T17:21:17.587Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34294</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21086.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34294|2024-06-04T17:21:17.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34295|2024-06-05T19:48:19.234Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34295</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21125.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34295|2024-06-05T19:48:19.234Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32134|2024-05-03T01:56:22.551Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32134</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM images. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15629.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32134|2024-05-03T01:56:22.551Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32135|2024-06-05T19:35:16.162Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32135</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18863.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32135|2024-06-05T19:35:16.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32132|2024-06-04T17:26:11.421Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32132</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM images. Crafted data in a DCM image can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15627.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32132|2024-06-04T17:26:11.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32133|2024-06-04T17:26:17.433Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32133</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro J2K File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of J2K images. Crafted data in a J2K image can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15628.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32133|2024-06-04T17:26:17.433Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32131|2024-05-03T01:56:20.395Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32131</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM images. Crafted data in a DCM image can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15626.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32131|2024-05-03T01:56:20.395Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32131|2024-07-17T16:08:20.396Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32131</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM images. Crafted data in a DCM image can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15626.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32131|2024-07-17T16:08:20.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32131|2024-08-02T15:03:29.242Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32131</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM images. Crafted data in a DCM image can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15626.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32131|2024-08-02T15:03:29.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32134|2024-08-02T15:03:28.990Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32134</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM images. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15629.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32134|2024-08-02T15:03:28.990Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32135|2024-08-02T15:03:29.097Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32135</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18863.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32135|2024-08-02T15:03:29.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32133|2024-08-02T15:03:29.242Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32133</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro J2K File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of J2K images. Crafted data in a J2K image can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15628.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32133|2024-08-02T15:03:29.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32132|2024-08-02T15:03:29.080Z -- sante -- dicom%20viewer%20pro</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32132</link>
      <description>Sante DICOM Viewer Pro DCM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM images. Crafted data in a DCM image can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15627.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32132|2024-08-02T15:03:29.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51637|2024-08-02T22:40:33.763Z -- sante -- pacs%20server%20pg</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51637</link>
      <description>Sante PACS Server PG Patient Query SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante PACS Server PG. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the DICOM service, which listens on TCP port 11122 by default. When parsing the NAME element of the PATIENT record, the process does not properly validate a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of NETWORK SERVICE. Was ZDI-CAN-21579.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51637|2024-08-02T22:40:33.763Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 19:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
