<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Inductive Automation -- Ignition</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/inductive%20automation/ignition.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Inductive Automation -- Ignition</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:23:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1704|2024-08-03T00:10:03.916Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1704</link>
      <description>Due to an XML external entity reference, the software parses XML in the backup/restore functionality without XML security flags, which may lead to a XXE attack while restoring the backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1704|2024-08-03T00:10:03.916Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35871|2024-08-03T09:44:22.103Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35871</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition 8.1.15 (b2022030114). Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the authenticateAdSso method. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing the execution of python code. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-17206.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35871|2024-08-03T09:44:22.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 18:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35872|2024-08-03T09:44:22.147Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35872</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition 8.1.15 (b2022030114). User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of ZIP files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-17115.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35872|2024-08-03T09:44:22.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 18:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35869|2024-08-03T09:44:22.094Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35869</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition 8.1.15 (b2022030114). Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within com.inductiveautomation.ignition.gateway.web.pages. The issue results from the lack of proper authentication prior to access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-17211.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35869|2024-08-03T09:44:22.094Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 18:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35870|2024-08-03T09:44:22.285Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35870</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition 8.1.15 (b2022030114). Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed. The specific flaw exists within com.inductiveautomation.metro.impl. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-17265.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35870|2024-08-03T09:44:22.285Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 18:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35873|2024-08-03T09:44:22.090Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35873</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition 8.1.15 (b2022030114). User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the processing of ZIP files. Crafted data in a ZIP file can cause the application to execute arbitrary Python scripts. The user interface fails to provide sufficient indication of the hazard. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-16949.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35873|2024-08-03T09:44:22.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 18:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50232|2024-08-02T22:09:49.865Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50232</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition getParams Argument Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must connect to a malicious server.

The specific flaw exists within the getParams method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to prepare an argument for a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-22028.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50232|2024-08-02T22:09:49.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50223|2024-08-02T22:09:49.796Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50223</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition ExtendedDocumentCodec Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the ExtendedDocumentCodec class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-22127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50223|2024-08-02T22:09:49.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50222|2024-08-02T22:09:49.870Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50222</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition ResponseParser Notification Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must connect to a malicious server.

The specific flaw exists within the ResponseParser method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-22067.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50222|2024-08-02T22:09:49.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50220|2024-08-02T22:09:49.876Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50220</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition Base64Element Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Base64Element class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-21801.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50220|2024-08-02T22:09:49.876Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50221|2024-08-02T22:09:49.681Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50221</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition ResponseParser SerializedResponse Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must connect to a malicious server.

The specific flaw exists within the ResponseParser method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-21926.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50221|2024-08-02T22:09:49.681Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50219|2024-08-02T22:09:49.777Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50219</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition RunQuery Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the RunQuery class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-21625.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50219|2024-08-02T22:09:49.777Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50218|2024-08-02T22:09:49.786Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50218</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition ModuleInvoke Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the ModuleInvoke class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-21624.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50218|2024-08-02T22:09:49.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50233|2024-08-02T22:09:49.895Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50233</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition getJavaExecutable Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must connect to a malicious server.

The specific flaw exists within the getJavaExecutable method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-22029.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50233|2024-08-02T22:09:49.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38121|2024-08-02T17:30:14.050Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38121</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition OPC UA Quick Client Cross-Site Scripting Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of the id parameter provided to the Inductive Automation Ignition web interface. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can lead to the injection of an arbitrary script. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20355.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38121|2024-08-02T17:30:14.050Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38122|2024-08-02T17:30:13.908Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38122</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition OPC UA Quick Client Permissive Cross-domain Policy Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of the web server. The issue results from the lack of appropriate Content Security Policy headers. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20539.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38122|2024-08-02T17:30:13.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38123|2024-08-02T17:30:14.068Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38123</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition OPC UA Quick Client Missing Authentication for Critical Function Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the server configuration. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to password change functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-20540.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38123|2024-08-02T17:30:14.068Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38124|2024-08-02T17:30:14.097Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38124</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition OPC UA Quick Client Task Scheduling Exposed Dangerous Function Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Ignition Gateway server. The issue results from the exposure of a dangerous function. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20541.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38124|2024-08-02T17:30:14.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38122|2024-07-19T21:01:09.444Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38122</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition OPC UA Quick Client Permissive Cross-domain Policy Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of the web server. The issue results from the lack of appropriate Content Security Policy headers. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20539.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38122|2024-07-19T21:01:09.444Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50233|2024-07-19T21:03:14.575Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50233</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition getJavaExecutable Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must connect to a malicious server.

The specific flaw exists within the getJavaExecutable method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-22029.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50233|2024-07-19T21:03:14.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50221|2024-06-17T20:01:39.250Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50221</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition ResponseParser SerializedResponse Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must connect to a malicious server.

The specific flaw exists within the ResponseParser method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-21926.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50221|2024-06-17T20:01:39.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50223|2024-06-17T17:05:08.998Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50223</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition ExtendedDocumentCodec Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the ExtendedDocumentCodec class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-22127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50223|2024-06-17T17:05:08.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38121|2024-05-03T01:59:18.329Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38121</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition OPC UA Quick Client Cross-Site Scripting Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of the id parameter provided to the Inductive Automation Ignition web interface. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can lead to the injection of an arbitrary script. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20355.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38121|2024-05-03T01:59:18.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38123|2024-06-04T17:28:11.909Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38123</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition OPC UA Quick Client Missing Authentication for Critical Function Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the server configuration. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to password change functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-20540.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38123|2024-06-04T17:28:11.909Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38122|2024-06-06T18:51:11.923Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38122</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition OPC UA Quick Client Permissive Cross-domain Policy Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of the web server. The issue results from the lack of appropriate Content Security Policy headers. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20539.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38122|2024-06-06T18:51:11.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38124|2024-06-04T17:27:56.867Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38124</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition OPC UA Quick Client Task Scheduling Exposed Dangerous Function Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Ignition Gateway server. The issue results from the exposure of a dangerous function. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20541.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38124|2024-06-04T17:27:56.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39472|2024-06-04T17:27:10.426Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39472</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition SimpleXMLReader XML External Entity Processing Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the SimpleXMLReader class. Due to the improper restriction of XML External Entity (XXE) references, a crafted document specifying a URI causes the XML parser to access the URI and embed the contents back into the XML document for further processing. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of the SYSTEM.
. Was ZDI-CAN-17571.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39472|2024-06-04T17:27:10.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39473|2024-05-03T02:10:39.937Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39473</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition AbstractGatewayFunction Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the AbstractGatewayFunction class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-17587.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39473|2024-05-03T02:10:39.937Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39474|2024-05-03T02:10:40.714Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39474</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition downloadLaunchClientJar Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must connect to a malicious server.

The specific flaw exists within the downloadLaunchClientJar function. The issue results from the lack of validating a remote JAR file prior to loading it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-19915.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39474|2024-05-03T02:10:40.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39475|2024-05-03T02:10:41.406Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39475</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition ParameterVersionJavaSerializationCodec Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the ParameterVersionJavaSerializationCodec class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20290.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39475|2024-05-03T02:10:41.406Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39476|2024-05-03T02:10:42.122Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39476</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition JavaSerializationCodec Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the JavaSerializationCodec class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20291.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39476|2024-05-03T02:10:42.122Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39477|2024-06-05T17:35:42.447Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39477</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition ConditionRefresh Resource Exhaustion Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of OPC UA ConditionRefresh requests. By sending a large number of requests, an attacker can consume all available resources on the server. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-20499.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39477|2024-06-05T17:35:42.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50232|2024-05-03T02:14:48.881Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50232</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition getParams Argument Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must connect to a malicious server.

The specific flaw exists within the getParams method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to prepare an argument for a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-22028.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50232|2024-05-03T02:14:48.881Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50233|2024-05-03T02:14:49.645Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50233</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition getJavaExecutable Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must connect to a malicious server.

The specific flaw exists within the getJavaExecutable method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-22029.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50233|2024-05-03T02:14:49.645Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50222|2024-06-04T17:17:59.944Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50222</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition ResponseParser Notification Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must connect to a malicious server.

The specific flaw exists within the ResponseParser method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-22067.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50222|2024-06-04T17:17:59.944Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50218|2024-06-04T17:17:58.468Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50218</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition ModuleInvoke Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the ModuleInvoke class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-21624.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50218|2024-06-04T17:17:58.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50219|2024-06-04T17:17:51.888Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50219</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition RunQuery Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the RunQuery class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-21625.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50219|2024-06-04T17:17:51.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50223|2024-05-03T02:14:42.233Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50223</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition ExtendedDocumentCodec Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the ExtendedDocumentCodec class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-22127.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50223|2024-05-03T02:14:42.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50220|2024-06-04T17:17:50.778Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50220</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition Base64Element Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Base64Element class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-21801.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50220|2024-06-04T17:17:50.778Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50221|2024-05-03T02:14:40.701Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50221</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition ResponseParser SerializedResponse Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must connect to a malicious server.

The specific flaw exists within the ResponseParser method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-21926.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50221|2024-05-03T02:14:40.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50232|2024-06-14T19:25:30.871Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50232</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition getParams Argument Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must connect to a malicious server.

The specific flaw exists within the getParams method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to prepare an argument for a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-22028.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50232|2024-06-14T19:25:30.871Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39474|2024-06-17T19:35:38.394Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39474</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition downloadLaunchClientJar Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must connect to a malicious server.

The specific flaw exists within the downloadLaunchClientJar function. The issue results from the lack of validating a remote JAR file prior to loading it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-19915.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39474|2024-06-17T19:35:38.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39473|2024-07-05T21:00:08.201Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39473</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition AbstractGatewayFunction Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the AbstractGatewayFunction class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-17587.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39473|2024-07-05T21:00:08.201Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39475|2024-07-05T20:59:42.213Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39475</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition ParameterVersionJavaSerializationCodec Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the ParameterVersionJavaSerializationCodec class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20290.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39475|2024-07-05T20:59:42.213Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39476|2024-07-05T20:59:53.039Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39476</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition JavaSerializationCodec Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the JavaSerializationCodec class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20291.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39476|2024-07-05T20:59:53.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38121|2024-07-29T20:29:46.334Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38121</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition OPC UA Quick Client Cross-Site Scripting Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of the id parameter provided to the Inductive Automation Ignition web interface. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can lead to the injection of an arbitrary script. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20355.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38121|2024-07-29T20:29:46.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39476|2024-08-02T18:10:20.678Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39476</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition JavaSerializationCodec Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the JavaSerializationCodec class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20291.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39476|2024-08-02T18:10:20.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39472|2024-08-02T18:10:20.889Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39472</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition SimpleXMLReader XML External Entity Processing Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the SimpleXMLReader class. Due to the improper restriction of XML External Entity (XXE) references, a crafted document specifying a URI causes the XML parser to access the URI and embed the contents back into the XML document for further processing. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of the SYSTEM.
. Was ZDI-CAN-17571.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39472|2024-08-02T18:10:20.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39475|2024-08-02T18:10:20.695Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39475</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition ParameterVersionJavaSerializationCodec Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the ParameterVersionJavaSerializationCodec class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20290.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39475|2024-08-02T18:10:20.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39473|2024-08-02T18:10:20.890Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39473</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition AbstractGatewayFunction Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the AbstractGatewayFunction class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-17587.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39473|2024-08-02T18:10:20.890Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39477|2024-08-02T18:10:20.832Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39477</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition ConditionRefresh Resource Exhaustion Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of OPC UA ConditionRefresh requests. By sending a large number of requests, an attacker can consume all available resources on the server. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-20499.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39477|2024-08-02T18:10:20.832Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39474|2024-08-02T18:10:21.129Z -- inductive%20automation -- ignition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39474</link>
      <description>Inductive Automation Ignition downloadLaunchClientJar Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Inductive Automation Ignition. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must connect to a malicious server.

The specific flaw exists within the downloadLaunchClientJar function. The issue results from the lack of validating a remote JAR file prior to loading it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-19915.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39474|2024-08-02T18:10:21.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
