<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for datahub-project -- datahub</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/datahub-project/datahub.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for datahub-project -- datahub</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:19:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25558|2024-08-02T11:25:19.203Z -- datahub-project -- datahub
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25558</link>
      <description>DataHub is an open-source metadata platform. When the DataHub frontend is configured to authenticate via SSO, it will leverage the pac4j library. The processing of the `id_token` is done in an unsafe manner which is not properly accounted for by the DataHub frontend. Specifically, if any of the id_token claims value start with the {#sb64} prefix, pac4j considers the value to be a serialized Java object and will deserialize it. This issue may lead to Remote Code Execution (RCE) in the worst case. Although a `RestrictedObjectInputStream` is in place, that puts some restriction on what classes can be deserialized, it still allows a broad range of java packages and potentially exploitable with different gadget chains. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds. This vulnerability was discovered and reported by the GitHub Security lab and is tracked as GHSL-2022-086.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25558|2024-08-02T11:25:19.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 22:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25561|2024-08-02T11:25:19.204Z -- datahub-project -- datahub
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25561</link>
      <description>DataHub is an open-source metadata platform. In the event a system is using Java Authentication and Authorization Service (JAAS) authentication and that system is given a configuration which contains an error, the authentication for the system will fail open and allow an attacker to login using any username and password. The reason for this is that while an error is thrown in the `authenticateJaasUser` method it is swallowed without propagating the error. As a result of this issue unauthenticated users may gain access to the system. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue. This vulnerability was discovered and reported by the GitHub Security lab and is tracked as GHSL-2022-081.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25561|2024-08-02T11:25:19.204Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 22:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25560|2024-08-02T11:25:19.241Z -- datahub-project -- datahub
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25560</link>
      <description>DataHub is an open-source metadata platform. The AuthServiceClient which is responsible for creation of new accounts, verifying credentials, resetting them or requesting access tokens, crafts multiple JSON strings using format strings with user-controlled data. This means that an attacker may be able to augment these JSON strings to be sent to the backend and that can potentially be abused by including new or colliding values. This issue may lead to an authentication bypass and the creation of system accounts, which effectively can lead to full system compromise. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability. This vulnerability was discovered and reported by the GitHub Security lab and is tracked as GHSL-2022-080.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25560|2024-08-02T11:25:19.241Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 22:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25562|2024-08-02T11:25:19.291Z -- datahub-project -- datahub
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25562</link>
      <description>DataHub is an open-source metadata platform. In versions of DataHub prior to 0.8.45 Session cookies are only cleared on new sign-in events and not on logout events. Any authentication checks using the `AuthUtils.hasValidSessionCookie()` method could be bypassed by using a cookie from a logged out session, as a result any logged out session cookie may be accepted as valid and therefore lead to an authentication bypass to the system. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue. This vulnerability was discovered and reported by the GitHub Security lab and is tracked as GHSL-2022-083.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25562|2024-08-02T11:25:19.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25559|2024-08-02T11:25:19.184Z -- datahub-project -- datahub
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25559</link>
      <description>DataHub is an open-source metadata platform. When not using authentication for the metadata service, which is the default configuration, the Metadata service (GMS) will use the X-DataHub-Actor HTTP header to infer the user the frontend is sending the request on behalf of. When the backends retrieves the header, its name is retrieved in a case-insensitive way. This case differential can be abused by an attacker to smuggle an X-DataHub-Actor header with different casing  (eg: X-DATAHUB-ACTOR). This issue may lead to an authorization bypass by allowing any user to impersonate the system user account and perform any actions on its behalf. This vulnerability was discovered and reported by the GitHub Security lab and is tracked as GHSL-2022-079.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25559|2024-08-02T11:25:19.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 22:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25557|2024-08-02T11:25:19.251Z -- datahub-project -- datahub
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25557</link>
      <description>DataHub is an open-source metadata platform. The DataHub frontend acts as a proxy able to forward any REST or GraphQL requests to the backend. The goal of this proxy is to perform authentication if needed and forward HTTP requests to the DataHub Metadata Store (GMS). It has been discovered that the proxy does not adequately construct the URL when forwarding data to GMS, allowing external users to reroute requests from the DataHub Frontend to any arbitrary hosts. As a result attackers may be able to reroute a request from originating from the frontend proxy to any other server and return the result. This vulnerability was discovered and reported by the GitHub Security lab and is tracked as GHSL-2022-076.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25557|2024-08-02T11:25:19.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 22:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
