<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ultimatemember -- Ultimate Member – User Profile, User Registration, Login &amp; Membership Plugin</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ultimatemember/ultimate%20member%20%E2%80%93%20user%20profile%2C%20user%20registration%2C%20login%20%26%20membership%20plugin.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ultimatemember -- Ultimate Member – User Profile, User Registration, Login &amp; Membership Plugin</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 07:20:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3361|2024-08-03T01:07:06.558Z -- ultimatemember -- ultimate%20member%20%E2%80%93%20user%20profile%2C%20user%20registration%2C%20login%20%26%20membership%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3361</link>
      <description>The Ultimate Member plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to directory traversal in versions up to, and including 2.5.0 due to insufficient input validation on the 'template' attribute used in shortcodes. This makes it possible for attackers with administrative privileges to supply arbitrary paths using traversal (../../) to access and include files outside of the intended directory. If an attacker can successfully upload a php file then remote code execution via inclusion may also be possible. Note: for users with less than administrative capabilities, /wp-admin access needs to be enabled for that user in order for this to be exploitable by those users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3361|2024-08-03T01:07:06.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 20:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3383|2024-08-03T01:07:06.541Z -- ultimatemember -- ultimate%20member%20%E2%80%93%20user%20profile%2C%20user%20registration%2C%20login%20%26%20membership%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3383</link>
      <description>The Ultimate Member plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in versions up to, and including, 2.5.0 via the get_option_value_from_callback function that accepts user supplied input and passes it through call_user_func(). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrative capabilities, to execute code on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3383|2024-08-03T01:07:06.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 20:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3384|2024-08-03T01:07:06.585Z -- ultimatemember -- ultimate%20member%20%E2%80%93%20user%20profile%2C%20user%20registration%2C%20login%20%26%20membership%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3384</link>
      <description>The Ultimate Member plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in versions up to, and including, 2.5.0 via the populate_dropdown_options function that accepts user supplied input and passes it through call_user_func(). This is restricted to non-parameter PHP functions like phpinfo(); since user supplied parameters are not passed through the function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrative privileges, to execute code on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3384|2024-08-03T01:07:06.585Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 20:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
