<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Lenovo -- XClarity Administrator (LXCA)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/lenovo/xclarity%20administrator%20%28lxca%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Lenovo -- XClarity Administrator (LXCA)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 23:23:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6182|2024-09-17T02:11:43.067Z -- lenovo -- xclarity%20administrator%20%28lxca%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6182</link>
      <description>A stored CSV Injection vulnerability was reported in Lenovo XClarity Administrator (LXCA) versions prior to 2.5.0 that could allow an administrative user to store malformed data in LXCA Jobs and Event Log data, that could result in crafted formulas stored in an exported CSV file. The crafted formula is not executed on LXCA itself.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6182|2024-09-17T02:11:43.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 18:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6181|2024-09-17T01:21:39.959Z -- lenovo -- xclarity%20administrator%20%28lxca%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6181</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was reported in Lenovo XClarity Administrator (LXCA) versions prior to 2.5.0 that could allow a crafted URL, if visited, to cause JavaScript code to be executed in the user's web browser. The JavaScript code is not executed on LXCA itself.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6181|2024-09-17T01:21:39.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 18:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6180|2024-09-17T02:52:15.667Z -- lenovo -- xclarity%20administrator%20%28lxca%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6180</link>
      <description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was reported in Lenovo XClarity Administrator (LXCA) versions prior to 2.5.0 that could allow an administrative user to cause JavaScript code to be stored in LXCA which may then be executed in the user's web browser. The JavaScript code is not executed on LXCA itself.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6180|2024-09-17T02:52:15.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 18:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6194|2024-09-17T03:12:43.770Z -- lenovo -- xclarity%20administrator%20%28lxca%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6194</link>
      <description>An XML External Entity (XXE) processing vulnerability was reported in Lenovo XClarity Administrator (LXCA) versions prior to 2.6.6 that could allow information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6194|2024-09-17T03:12:43.770Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 17:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6193|2024-09-17T02:47:43.822Z -- lenovo -- xclarity%20administrator%20%28lxca%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6193</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability was reported in Lenovo XClarity Administrator (LXCA) versions prior to 2.6.6 that could allow unauthenticated access to some configuration files which may contain usernames, license keys, IP addresses, and encrypted password hashes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6193|2024-09-17T02:47:43.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 17:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
