<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Zoom Video Communications Inc -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/zoom%20video%20communications%20inc/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Zoom Video Communications Inc -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 06:24:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22782|2024-08-03T03:21:49.155Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20client%20for%20meetings%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22782</link>
      <description>The Zoom Client for Meetings for Windows prior to version 5.9.7, Zoom Rooms for Conference Room for Windows prior to version 5.10.0, Zoom Plugins for Microsoft Outlook for Windows prior to version 5.10.3, and Zoom VDI Windows Meeting Clients prior to version 5.9.6; was susceptible to a local privilege escalation issue during the installer repair operation. A malicious actor could utilize this to potentially delete system level files or folders, causing integrity or availability issues on the user’s host machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22782|2024-08-03T03:21:49.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22783|2024-08-03T03:21:49.154Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20on-premise%20meeting%20connector%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22783</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Zoom On-Premise Meeting Connector Controller version 4.8.102.20220310 and On-Premise Meeting Connector MMR version 4.8.102.20220310 exposes process memory fragments to connected clients, which could be observed by a passive attacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22783|2024-08-03T03:21:49.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22781|2024-08-03T03:21:49.113Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20client%20for%20meetings%20for%20macos%20%28standard%20and%20for%20it%20admin%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22781</link>
      <description>The Zoom Client for Meetings for MacOS (Standard and for IT Admin) prior to version 5.9.6 failed to properly check the package version during the update process. This could lead to a malicious actor updating an unsuspecting user’s currently installed version to a less secure version.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22781|2024-08-03T03:21:49.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22787|2024-08-03T03:21:49.132Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20client%20for%20meetings%20for%20android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22787</link>
      <description>The Zoom Client for Meetings (for Android, iOS, Linux, macOS, and Windows) before version 5.10.0 fails to properly validate the hostname during a server switch request. This issue could be used in a more sophisticated attack to trick an unsuspecting users client to connect to a malicious server when attempting to use Zoom services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22787|2024-08-03T03:21:49.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22784|2024-08-03T03:21:49.159Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20client%20for%20meetings%20for%20android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22784</link>
      <description>The Zoom Client for Meetings (for Android, iOS, Linux, MacOS, and Windows) before version 5.10.0 failed to properly parse XML stanzas in XMPP messages. This can allow a malicious user to break out of the current XMPP message context and create a new message context to have the receiving users client perform a variety of actions.This issue could be used in a more sophisticated attack to forge XMPP messages from the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22784|2024-08-03T03:21:49.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22780|2024-08-03T03:21:49.147Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20client%20for%20meetings%20for%20android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22780</link>
      <description>The Zoom Client for Meetings chat functionality was susceptible to Zip bombing attacks in the following product versions: Android before version 5.8.6, iOS before version 5.9.0, Linux before version 5.8.6, macOS before version 5.7.3, and Windows before version 5.6.3. This could lead to availability issues on the client host by exhausting system resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22780|2024-08-03T03:21:49.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22786|2024-08-03T03:21:49.134Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20client%20for%20meetings%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22786</link>
      <description>The Zoom Client for Meetings for Windows before version 5.10.0 and Zoom Rooms for Conference Room for Windows before version 5.10.0, fails to properly check the installation version during the update process. This issue could be used in a more sophisticated attack to trick a user into downgrading their Zoom client to a less secure version.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22786|2024-08-03T03:21:49.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22785|2024-08-03T03:21:49.145Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20client%20for%20meetings%20for%20android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22785</link>
      <description>The Zoom Client for Meetings (for Android, iOS, Linux, MacOS, and Windows) before version 5.10.0 failed to properly constrain client session cookies to Zoom domains. This issue could be used in a more sophisticated attack to send an unsuspecting users Zoom-scoped session cookies to a non-Zoom domain. This could potentially allow for spoofing of a Zoom user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22785|2024-08-03T03:21:49.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22779|2024-08-03T03:21:49.090Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- keybase%20client%20for%20macos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22779</link>
      <description>The Keybase Clients for macOS and Windows before version 5.9.0 fails to properly remove exploded messages initiated by a user. This can occur if the receiving user switches to a non-chat feature and places the host in a sleep state before the sending user explodes the messages. This could lead to disclosure of sensitive information which was meant to be deleted from a user’s filesystem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22779|2024-08-03T03:21:49.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22788|2024-08-03T03:21:49.153Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20client%20for%20meetings
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22788</link>
      <description>The Zoom Opener installer is downloaded by a user from the Launch meeting page, when attempting to join a meeting without having the Zoom Meeting Client installed. The Zoom Opener installer for Zoom Client for Meetings before version 5.10.3 and Zoom Rooms for Conference Room for Windows before version 5.10.3 are susceptible to a DLL injection attack. This vulnerability could be used to run arbitrary code on the victims host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22788|2024-08-03T03:21:49.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
