<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Zoom Video Communications Inc -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/zoom%20video%20communications%20inc/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Zoom Video Communications Inc -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 02:24:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22779|2024-09-17T00:05:46.594Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- keybase%20client%20for%20macos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22779</link>
      <description>The Keybase Clients for macOS and Windows before version 5.9.0 fails to properly remove exploded messages initiated by a user. This can occur if the receiving user switches to a non-chat feature and places the host in a sleep state before the sending user explodes the messages. This could lead to disclosure of sensitive information which was meant to be deleted from a user’s filesystem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22779|2024-09-17T00:05:46.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 22:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22783|2024-09-17T01:16:05.149Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20on-premise%20meeting%20connector%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22783</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Zoom On-Premise Meeting Connector Controller version 4.8.102.20220310 and On-Premise Meeting Connector MMR version 4.8.102.20220310 exposes process memory fragments to connected clients, which could be observed by a passive attacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22783|2024-09-17T01:16:05.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 15:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34421|2024-09-17T01:41:23.193Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- keybase%20client%20for%20android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34421</link>
      <description>The Keybase Client for Android before version 5.8.0 and the Keybase Client for iOS before version 5.8.0 fails to properly remove exploded messages initiated by a user if the receiving user places the chat session in the background while the sending user explodes the messages. This could lead to disclosure of sensitive information which was meant to be deleted from the customer's device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34421|2024-09-17T01:41:23.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 22:58:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28763|2024-09-17T01:11:21.229Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20client%20for%20meetings%20%28for%20android%2C%20ios%2C%20linux%2C%20macos%2C%20and%20windows%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28763</link>
      <description>The Zoom Client for Meetings (for Android, iOS, Linux, macOS, and Windows) before version 5.12.2 is susceptible to a URL parsing vulnerability. If a malicious Zoom meeting URL is opened, the malicious link may direct the user to connect to an arbitrary network address, leading to additional attacks including session takeovers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28763|2024-09-17T01:11:21.229Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 19:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34425|2024-09-17T00:36:09.085Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20client%20for%20meetings%20for%20android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34425</link>
      <description>The Zoom Client for Meetings before version 5.7.3 (for Android, iOS, Linux, macOS, and Windows) contain a server side request forgery vulnerability in the chat\'s "link preview" functionality. In versions prior to 5.7.3, if a user were to enable the chat\'s "link preview" feature, a malicious actor could trick the user into potentially sending arbitrary HTTP GET requests to URLs that the actor cannot reach directly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34425|2024-09-17T00:36:09.085Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 19:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28762|2024-09-17T02:01:09.817Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20client%20for%20meetings%20for%20macos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28762</link>
      <description>Zoom Client for Meetings for macOS (Standard and for IT Admin) starting with 5.10.6 and prior to 5.12.0 contains a debugging port misconfiguration. When camera mode rendering context is enabled as part of the Zoom App Layers API by running certain Zoom Apps, a local debugging port is opened by the Zoom client. A local malicious user could use this debugging port to connect to and control the Zoom Apps running in the Zoom client.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28762|2024-09-17T02:01:09.817Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 14:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28761|2024-09-17T01:26:13.252Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20on-premise%20meeting%20connector%20mmr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28761</link>
      <description>Zoom On-Premise Meeting Connector MMR before version 4.8.20220916.131 contains an improper access control vulnerability. As a result, a malicious actor in a meeting or webinar they are authorized to join could prevent participants from receiving audio and video causing meeting disruptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28761|2024-09-17T01:26:13.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 14:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28756|2024-09-17T01:15:56.201Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20client%20for%20meetings%20for%20macos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28756</link>
      <description>The Zoom Client for Meetings for macOS (Standard and for IT Admin) starting with version 5.7.3 and before 5.11.5 contains a vulnerability in the auto update process. A local low-privileged user could exploit this vulnerability to escalate their privileges to root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28756|2024-09-17T01:15:56.201Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 22:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28758|2024-09-17T00:16:32.793Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20on-premise%20meeting%20connector%20mmr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28758</link>
      <description>Zoom On-Premise Meeting Connector MMR before version 4.8.20220815.130 contains an improper access control vulnerability. As a result, a malicious actor could obtain the audio and video feed of a meeting they were not authorized to join and cause other meeting disruptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28758|2024-09-17T00:16:32.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 20:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
