<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Zoom Video Communications Inc -- Zoom Client for Meetings (for Android, iOS, Linux, macOS, and Windows)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/zoom%20video%20communications%20inc/zoom%20client%20for%20meetings%20%28for%20android%2C%20ios%2C%20linux%2C%20macos%2C%20and%20windows%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Zoom Video Communications Inc -- Zoom Client for Meetings (for Android, iOS, Linux, macOS, and Windows)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 08:24:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28764|2024-09-17T03:13:55.211Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20client%20for%20meetings%20%28for%20android%2C%20ios%2C%20linux%2C%20macos%2C%20and%20windows%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28764</link>
      <description>The Zoom Client for Meetings (for Android, iOS, Linux, macOS, and Windows) before version 5.12.6 is susceptible to a local information exposure vulnerability. A failure to clear data from a local SQL database after a meeting ends and the usage of an insufficiently secure per-device key encrypting that database results in a local malicious user being able to obtain meeting information such as in-meeting chat for the previous meeting attended from that local user account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28764|2024-09-17T03:13:55.211Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 20:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28755|2024-09-17T02:53:24.397Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20client%20for%20meetings%20%28for%20android%2C%20ios%2C%20linux%2C%20macos%2C%20and%20windows%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28755</link>
      <description>The Zoom Client for Meetings (for Android, iOS, Linux, macOS, and Windows) before version 5.11.0 are susceptible to a URL parsing vulnerability. If a malicious Zoom meeting URL is opened, the malicious link may direct the user to connect to an arbitrary network address, leading to additional attacks including the potential for remote code execution through launching executables from arbitrary paths.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28755|2024-09-17T02:53:24.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 14:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28763|2024-09-17T01:11:21.229Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20client%20for%20meetings%20%28for%20android%2C%20ios%2C%20linux%2C%20macos%2C%20and%20windows%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28763</link>
      <description>The Zoom Client for Meetings (for Android, iOS, Linux, macOS, and Windows) before version 5.12.2 is susceptible to a URL parsing vulnerability. If a malicious Zoom meeting URL is opened, the malicious link may direct the user to connect to an arbitrary network address, leading to additional attacks including session takeovers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28763|2024-09-17T01:11:21.229Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 19:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34423|2024-09-17T03:23:26.376Z -- zoom%20video%20communications%20inc -- zoom%20client%20for%20meetings%20%28for%20android%2C%20ios%2C%20linux%2C%20macos%2C%20and%20windows%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34423</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in Zoom Client for Meetings (for Android, iOS, Linux, macOS, and Windows) before version 5.8.4, Zoom Client for Meetings for Blackberry (for Android and iOS) before version 5.8.1, Zoom Client for Meetings for intune (for Android and iOS) before version 5.8.4, Zoom Client for Meetings for Chrome OS before version 5.0.1, Zoom Rooms for Conference Room (for Android, AndroidBali, macOS, and Windows) before version 5.8.3, Controllers for Zoom Rooms (for Android, iOS, and Windows) before version 5.8.3, Zoom VDI Windows Meeting Client before version 5.8.4, Zoom VDI Azure Virtual Desktop Plugins (for Windows x86 or x64, IGEL x64, Ubuntu x64, HP ThinPro OS x64) before version 5.8.4.21112, Zoom VDI Citrix Plugins (for Windows x86 or x64, Mac Universal Installer &amp; Uninstaller, IGEL x64, eLux RP6 x64, HP ThinPro OS x64, Ubuntu x64, CentOS x 64, Dell ThinOS) before version 5.8.4.21112, Zoom VDI VMware Plugins (for Windows x86 or x64, Mac Universal Installer &amp; Uninstaller, IGEL x64, eLux RP6 x64, HP ThinPro OS x64, Ubuntu x64, CentOS x 64, Dell ThinOS) before version 5.8.4.21112, Zoom Meeting SDK for Android before version 5.7.6.1922, Zoom Meeting SDK for iOS before version 5.7.6.1082, Zoom Meeting SDK for macOS before version 5.7.6.1340, Zoom Meeting SDK for Windows before version 5.7.6.1081, Zoom Video SDK (for Android, iOS, macOS, and Windows) before version 1.1.2, Zoom On-Premise Meeting Connector Controller before version 4.8.12.20211115, Zoom On-Premise Meeting Connector MMR before version 4.8.12.20211115, Zoom On-Premise Recording Connector before version 5.1.0.65.20211116, Zoom On-Premise Virtual Room Connector before version 4.4.7266.20211117, Zoom On-Premise Virtual Room Connector Load Balancer before version 2.5.5692.20211117, Zoom Hybrid Zproxy before version 1.0.1058.20211116, and Zoom Hybrid MMR before version 4.6.20211116.131_x86-64. This can potentially allow a malicious actor to crash the service or application, or leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34423|2024-09-17T03:23:26.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 16:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
