<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Philips -- IntelliVue MX40 Patient Worn Monitor</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/philips/intellivue%20mx40%20patient%20worn%20monitor.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Philips -- IntelliVue MX40 Patient Worn Monitor</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:43:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-9657|2024-09-16T16:13:21.087Z -- philips -- intellivue%20mx40%20patient%20worn%20monitor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-9657</link>
      <description>Under specific 802.11 network conditions, a partial re-association of the Philips IntelliVue MX40 Version B.06.18 WLAN monitor to the central monitoring station is possible. In this state, the central monitoring station can indicate the MX40 is not connected or associated to the central monitor, and thus should be operating in local monitoring mode (local audio-on, screen-on), but the MX40 WLAN itself can instead still be operating in telemetry mode (local audio-off, screen-off). If a patient experiences an alarm event and clinical staff expects the MX40 to provide local alarming when it is not available from the local device, a delay of treatment can occur. CVSS v3 base score: 6.5, CVSS vector string: AV:A/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H. Philips has released software update, Version B.06.18, to fix the improper cleanup on thrown exception vulnerability, and implement mitigations to reduce the risk associated with the improper handling of exceptional conditions vulnerability. The software update implements messaging and alarming on the MX40 and at the central monitoring station, when the MX40 disconnects from the access point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-9657|2024-09-16T16:13:21.087Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-9658|2024-09-16T17:15:12.054Z -- philips -- intellivue%20mx40%20patient%20worn%20monitor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-9658</link>
      <description>Certain 802.11 network management messages have been determined to invoke wireless access point blacklisting security defenses when not required, which can necessitate intervention by hospital staff to reset the device and reestablish a network connection to the Wi-Fi access point. During this state, the Philips IntelliVue MX40 Version B.06.18 can either connect to an alternative access point within signal range for association to a central monitoring station, or it can remain in local monitoring mode until the device is reset by hospital staff. CVSS v3 base score: 6.5, CVSS vector string: AV:A/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H. Philips has released software update, Version B.06.18, to fix the improper cleanup on thrown exception vulnerability, and implement mitigations to reduce the risk associated with the improper handling of exceptional conditions vulnerability. The software update implements messaging and alarming on the MX40 and at the central monitoring station, when the MX40 disconnects from the access point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-9658|2024-09-16T17:15:12.054Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
