<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Qualcomm, Inc. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qualcomm%2C%20inc./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Qualcomm, Inc. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 11:20:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3645|2024-08-04T07:37:55.730Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3645</link>
      <description>Firmware will hit assert in WLAN firmware If encrypted data length in FILS IE of reassoc response is more than 528 bytes in Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in IPQ6018, IPQ8074, Kamorta, Nicobar, QCA6390, QCA8081, QCN7605, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, Rennell, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA845, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3645|2024-08-04T07:37:55.730Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 15:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3648|2024-08-04T07:37:55.727Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3648</link>
      <description>u'Possible out of bound write in DSP driver code due to lack of check of data received from user' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in MSM8909W</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3648|2024-08-04T07:37:55.727Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35117|2024-08-04T00:33:51.189Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35117</link>
      <description>An Out of Bounds read may potentially occur while processing an IBSS beacon, in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35117|2024-08-04T00:33:51.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 04:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3687|2024-08-04T07:44:50.254Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- unspecified
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3687</link>
      <description>Local privilege escalation in admin services in Windows environment can occur due to an arbitrary read issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3687|2024-08-04T07:44:50.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 09:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3621|2024-08-04T07:37:55.644Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3621</link>
      <description>u'Lack of check to ensure that the TX read index &amp; RX write index that are read from shared memory are less than the FIFO size results into memory corruption and potential information leakage' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Bitra, IPQ6018, IPQ8074, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9645, MDM9650, MDM9655, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA8081, QCM2150, QCN7605, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, QCS610, QM215, Rennell, SA415M, SA6155P, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3621|2024-08-04T07:37:55.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3619|2024-08-04T07:37:55.528Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3619</link>
      <description>u'Non-secure memory is touched multiple times during TrustZone\u2019s execution and can lead to privilege escalation or memory corruption' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8098, IPQ8074, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9650, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8998, QCA8081, QCS404, QCS605, QCS610, QM215, Rennell, SA415M, SC7180, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX24, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3619|2024-08-04T07:37:55.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3620|2024-08-04T07:37:55.732Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3620</link>
      <description>u'Lack of check of integer overflow while doing a round up operation for data read from shared memory for G-link SMEM transport can lead to corruption and potential information leak' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Bitra, IPQ6018, IPQ8074, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9645, MDM9650, MDM9655, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA8081, QCM2150, QCN7605, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, QCS610, QM215, Rennell, SA415M, SA6155P, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3620|2024-08-04T07:37:55.732Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3615|2024-08-04T07:37:55.571Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3615</link>
      <description>Valid deauth/disassoc frames is dropped in case if RMF is enabled and some rouge peer keep on sending rogue deauth/disassoc frames due to improper enum values used to check the frame subtype in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile in APQ8009, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9650, MSM8996AU, QCA6174A, QCA6574AU, QCA9377, QCA9379, QCN7605, QCS605, SC8180X, SDM630, SDM636, SDM660, SDM845, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3615|2024-08-04T07:37:55.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 15:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3643|2024-08-04T07:37:55.789Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables%2C%20snapdragon%
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3643</link>
      <description>u'Information disclosure issue can occur due to partial secure display-touch session tear-down' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8076, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, IPQ6018, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9650, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, QCS610, QM215, Rennell, SA415M, SA515M, SA6155P, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3643|2024-08-04T07:37:55.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3652|2024-08-04T07:37:55.726Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3652</link>
      <description>Possible buffer over-read issue in windows x86 wlan driver function while processing beacon or request frame due to lack of check of length of variable received. in Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity in MSM8998, QCA6390, SC7180, SC8180X, SDM850</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3652|2024-08-04T07:37:55.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 10:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35071|2024-08-04T00:33:50.864Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20networking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35071</link>
      <description>Possible buffer over read due to lack of size validation while copying data from DBR buffer to RX buffer and can lead to Denial of Service in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35071|2024-08-04T00:33:50.864Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3628|2024-08-04T07:37:55.503Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3628</link>
      <description>Improper access due to socket opened by the logging application without specifying localhost address in Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Mobile in APQ8053, Rennell, SDX20</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3628|2024-08-04T07:37:55.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3664|2024-08-04T07:44:50.004Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3664</link>
      <description>Out of bound read access in hypervisor due to an invalid read access attempt by passing invalid addresses in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3664|2024-08-04T07:44:50.004Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 06:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35121|2024-08-04T00:33:51.231Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35121</link>
      <description>An array index is improperly used to lock and unlock a mutex which can lead to a Use After Free condition In the Synx driver in Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35121|2024-08-04T00:33:51.231Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35101|2024-08-04T00:33:51.107Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35101</link>
      <description>Improper handling of writes to virtual GICR control can lead to assertion failure in the hypervisor in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35101|2024-08-04T00:33:51.107Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35080|2024-08-04T00:33:51.047Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35080</link>
      <description>Disabled SMMU from secure side while RPM is assigned a secure stream can lead to information disclosure in Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35080|2024-08-04T00:33:51.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3665|2024-08-04T07:44:50.115Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3665</link>
      <description>A possible buffer overflow would occur while processing command from firmware due to the group_id obtained from the firmware being out of range in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9615, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8909W, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, QCA6174A, QCA9377, QCA9379, SDM439, SDM636, SDM660, SDX20, SDX24, SM8150</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3665|2024-08-04T07:44:50.115Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35108|2024-08-04T00:33:51.030Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35108</link>
      <description>Improper checking of AP-S lock bit while verifying the secure resource group permissions can lead to non secure read and write access in Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35108|2024-08-04T00:33:51.030Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 11:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3688|2024-08-04T07:44:50.024Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3688</link>
      <description>Possible buffer overflow while parsing mp4 clip with corrupted sample atoms due to improper validation of index in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA6574AU, QCM2150, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, SA6155P, Saipan, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX20, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3688|2024-08-04T07:44:50.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 11:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35091|2024-08-04T00:33:50.676Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35091</link>
      <description>Possible out of bounds read due to improper typecasting while handling page fault for global memory in Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35091|2024-08-04T00:33:50.676Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35132|2024-08-04T00:33:51.259Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35132</link>
      <description>Out of bound write in DSP service due to improper bound check for response buffer size in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35132|2024-08-04T00:33:51.259Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 11:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35110|2024-08-04T00:33:51.166Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35110</link>
      <description>Possible buffer overflow to improper validation of hash segment of file while allocating memory in Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35110|2024-08-04T00:33:51.166Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 04:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3694|2024-08-04T07:44:50.016Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3694</link>
      <description>u'Use out of range pointer issue can occur due to incorrect buffer range check during the execution of qseecom' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music in Bitra, Nicobar, Saipan, SM6150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3694|2024-08-04T07:44:50.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35120|2024-08-04T00:33:51.114Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35120</link>
      <description>Improper handling between export and release functions on the same handle from client can lead to use after free in Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35120|2024-08-04T00:33:51.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3644|2024-08-04T07:37:55.806Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3644</link>
      <description>u'Information disclosure issue occurs as in current logic Secure Touch session is released without terminating display session' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9650, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, QCS610, Rennell, SA415M, SA515M, SA6155P, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM630, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3644|2024-08-04T07:37:55.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3702|2024-08-04T07:44:50.151Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables%2C%20snapdragon%
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3702</link>
      <description>u'Specifically timed and handcrafted traffic can cause internal errors in a WLAN device that lead to improper layer 2 Wi-Fi encryption with a consequent possibility of information disclosure over the air for a discrete set of traffic' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8053, IPQ4019, IPQ8064, MSM8909W, MSM8996AU, QCA9531, QCN5502, QCS405, SDX20, SM6150, SM7150</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3702|2024-08-04T07:44:50.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35090|2024-08-04T00:33:51.072Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35090</link>
      <description>Possible hypervisor memory corruption due to TOC TOU race condition when updating address mappings in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35090|2024-08-04T00:33:51.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35083|2024-08-04T00:33:50.937Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35083</link>
      <description>Possible out of bound read due to improper validation of certificate chain in SSL or Internet key exchange in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35083|2024-08-04T00:33:50.937Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3701|2024-08-04T07:44:50.084Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3701</link>
      <description>Use after free issue while processing error notification from camx driver due to not properly releasing the sequence data in Snapdragon Mobile in Saipan, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3701|2024-08-04T07:44:50.084Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 11:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35078|2024-08-04T00:33:50.820Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35078</link>
      <description>Possible memory leak due to improper validation of certificate chain length while parsing server certificate chain in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35078|2024-08-04T00:33:50.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35073|2024-08-04T00:33:50.914Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35073</link>
      <description>Possible assertion due to improper validation of rank restriction field in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35073|2024-08-04T00:33:50.914Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35109|2024-08-04T00:33:50.586Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35109</link>
      <description>Possible address manipulation from APP-NS while APP-S is configuring an RG where it tries to merge the address ranges in Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35109|2024-08-04T00:33:50.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 11:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3696|2024-08-04T07:44:50.158Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20networking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3696</link>
      <description>u'Use after free while installing new security rule in ipcrtr as old one is deleted and this rule could still be in use for checking security permission for particular process' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, IPQ4019, IPQ6018, IPQ8064, IPQ8074, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8996AU, QCA4531, QCA6574AU, QCA9531, QCM2150, QCS605, SDM429W, SDX20, SDX24</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3696|2024-08-04T07:44:50.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35134|2024-08-04T00:33:51.174Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35134</link>
      <description>Due to insufficient validation of ELF headers, an Incorrect Calculation of Buffer Size can occur in Boot leading to memory corruption in Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35134|2024-08-04T00:33:51.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 11:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35094|2024-08-04T00:33:50.636Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35094</link>
      <description>Improper verification of timeout-based authentication in identity credential can lead to invalid authorization in HLOS in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35094|2024-08-04T00:33:50.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3674|2024-08-04T07:44:50.124Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3674</link>
      <description>Information can leak into userspace due to improper transfer of data from kernel to userspace in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in Nicobar, QCS405, Saipan, SC8180X, SDX55, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3674|2024-08-04T07:44:50.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 06:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3673|2024-08-04T07:44:50.255Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3673</link>
      <description>u'Buffer overflow can happen as part of SIP message packet processing while storing values in array due to lack of check to validate the index length' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables in Agatti, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Bitra, Kamorta, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, Nicobar, QCA6390, QCA6574AU, QCM2150, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, SA6155P, SA8155P, Saipan, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3673|2024-08-04T07:44:50.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3653|2024-08-04T07:37:55.683Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3653</link>
      <description>Possible buffer over-read in windows wlan driver function due to lack of check of length of variable received from userspace in Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity in MSM8998, QCA6390, SC7180, SC8180X, SDM850</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3653|2024-08-04T07:37:55.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 10:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3668|2024-08-04T07:44:49.935Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3668</link>
      <description>u'Buffer overflow while parsing PMF enabled MCBC frames due to frame length being lesser than what is expected while parsing' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in IPQ6018, IPQ8074, Kamorta, Nicobar, QCA6390, QCA8081, QCN7605, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, Rennell, SA415M, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA845, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3668|2024-08-04T07:44:49.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35122|2024-08-04T00:33:51.150Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35122</link>
      <description>Non-secure region can try modifying RG permissions of IO space xPUs due to improper input validation in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35122|2024-08-04T00:33:51.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 11:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3624|2024-08-04T07:37:55.564Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3624</link>
      <description>u'A potential buffer overflow exists due to integer overflow when parsing handler options due to wrong data type usage in operation' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9615, MDM9625, MDM9635M, MDM9640, MDM9645, MDM9650, MDM9655, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCN7605, QCS605, QCS610, QM215, Rennell, SA415M, SA515M, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3624|2024-08-04T07:37:55.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35081|2024-08-04T00:33:50.565Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35081</link>
      <description>Possible buffer overflow due to improper validation of SSID length received from beacon or probe response during an IBSS session in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35081|2024-08-04T00:33:50.565Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3616|2024-08-04T07:37:55.683Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3616</link>
      <description>Buffer overflow in display function due to memory copy without checking length of size using strcpy function in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, QCS605, QM215, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM845, SDX20, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3616|2024-08-04T07:37:55.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 15:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3703|2024-08-04T07:44:50.073Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3703</link>
      <description>u'Buffer over-read issue in Bluetooth peripheral firmware due to lack of check for invalid opcode and length of opcode received from central device(This CVE is equivalent to Link Layer Length Overfow issue (CVE-2019-16336,CVE-2019-17519) and Silent Length Overflow issue(CVE-2019-17518) mentioned in sweyntooth paper)' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music in APQ8053, APQ8076, AR9344, Bitra, Kamorta, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MSM8905, MSM8917, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, Nicobar, QCA6174A, QCA9377, QCM2150, QCM6125, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, QCS610, QM215, Rennell, SC8180X, SDM429, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX20, SDX24, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3703|2024-08-04T07:44:50.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3611|2024-08-04T07:37:55.518Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20networking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3611</link>
      <description>u'XBL SEC clears only ZI region when loading Qualcomm-signed segments can lead to improper access issue' in Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8098, Kamorta, MSM8998, QCS404, QCS605, SDA660, SDA845, SDM630, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3611|2024-08-04T07:37:55.518Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3685|2024-08-04T07:44:50.046Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wear
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3685</link>
      <description>Pointer variable which is freed is not cleared can result in memory corruption and leads to denial of service in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3685|2024-08-04T07:44:50.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 09:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35116|2024-08-04T00:33:51.053Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35116</link>
      <description>APK can load a crafted model into the CDSP which can lead to a compromise of CDSP and other APK`s data executing there in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35116|2024-08-04T00:33:51.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3633|2024-08-04T07:37:55.809Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3633</link>
      <description>Array out of bound may occur while playing mp3 file as no check is there on offset if it is greater than the buffer allocated or not in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, Saipan, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX20, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3633|2024-08-04T07:37:55.809Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 15:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35068|2024-08-04T00:33:50.600Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35068</link>
      <description>Lack of null check while freeing the device information buffer in the Bluetooth HFP protocol can lead to a NULL pointer dereference in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35068|2024-08-04T00:33:50.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 10:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3692|2024-08-04T07:44:50.194Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3692</link>
      <description>u'Possible buffer overflow while updating output buffer for IMEI and Gateway Address due to lack of check of input validation for parameters received from server' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile in Agatti, Kamorta, Nicobar, QCM6125, QCS610, Rennell, SA415M, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3692|2024-08-04T07:44:50.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35114|2024-08-04T00:33:51.178Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35114</link>
      <description>Improper buffer initialization on the backend driver can lead to buffer overflow in Snapdragon Auto</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35114|2024-08-04T00:33:51.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3678|2024-08-04T07:44:50.131Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20networking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3678</link>
      <description>u'A buffer overflow could occur if the API is improperly used due to UIE init does not contain a buffer size a param' in Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in Agatti, Kamorta, QCS404, QCS605, SDA845, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3678|2024-08-04T07:44:50.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35118|2024-08-04T00:33:50.924Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35118</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write can occur due to an incorrect input check in the camera driver in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35118|2024-08-04T00:33:50.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3636|2024-08-04T07:37:55.772Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20networking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3636</link>
      <description>u'Out of bound writes happen when accessing usage_table header entry beyond the memory allocated for the header' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in Kamorta, QCS404, QCS610, Rennell, SC7180, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3636|2024-08-04T07:37:55.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35135|2024-08-04T00:33:51.106Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35135</link>
      <description>A null pointer dereference may potentially occur during RSA key import in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35135|2024-08-04T00:33:51.106Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 11:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3638|2024-08-04T07:37:55.799Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20networking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3638</link>
      <description>u'An Unaligned address or size can propagate to the database due to improper page permissions and can lead to improper access control' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in Agatti, Bitra, Kamorta, QCA6390, QCS404, QCS610, Rennell, SA515M, SC7180, SC8180X, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3638|2024-08-04T07:37:55.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35123|2024-08-04T00:33:51.180Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35123</link>
      <description>Buffer copy in GATT multi notification due to improper length check for the data coming over-the-air in Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35123|2024-08-04T00:33:51.180Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3656|2024-08-04T07:44:50.134Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3656</link>
      <description>Out of bound access can happen in MHI command process due to lack of check of command channel id value received from MHI devices in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, Kamorta, MDM9607, MSM8917, MSM8953, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, SA6155P, SA8155P, Saipan, SC8180X, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM632, SDM710, SDM845, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3656|2024-08-04T07:44:50.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 06:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3622|2024-08-04T07:37:55.751Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3622</link>
      <description>u'Channel name string which has been read from shared memory is potentially subjected to string manipulations but not validated for NULL termination can results into memory corruption' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Bitra, IPQ6018, IPQ8074, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9645, MDM9650, MDM9655, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA8081, QCM2150, QCN7605, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, QCS610, QM215, Rennell, SA415M, SA6155P, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3622|2024-08-04T07:37:55.751Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3657|2024-08-04T07:44:50.236Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3657</link>
      <description>u'Remote code execution can happen by sending a carefully crafted POST query when Device configuration is accessed from a tethered client through webserver due to lack of array bound check.' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, IPQ4019, IPQ6018, IPQ8064, IPQ8074, MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, QCA6574AU, QCS405, QCS610, QRB5165, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM845, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM8250</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3657|2024-08-04T07:44:50.236Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3614|2024-08-04T07:37:55.503Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3614</link>
      <description>Possible buffer overflow while copying the frame to local buffer due to lack of check of length before copying in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8076, APQ8096, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, IPQ6018, IPQ8074, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA6174A, QCA6574AU, QCA6584AU, QCA9377, QCA9379, QCA9886, QCM2150, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, SC7180, SC8180X, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX20, SDX24, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3614|2024-08-04T07:37:55.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3630|2024-08-04T07:37:55.797Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3630</link>
      <description>Possibility of out of bound access while processing the responses from video firmware in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, SA415M, SA6155P, Saipan, SC8180X, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3630|2024-08-04T07:37:55.797Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 15:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3632|2024-08-04T07:37:55.748Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3632</link>
      <description>u'Incorrect validation of ring context fetched from host memory can lead to memory overflow' in Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Mobile in QSM8350, SC7180, SDX55, SDX55M, SM6150, SM6250, SM6250P, SM7125, SM7150, SM7150P, SM7250, SM7250P, SM8150, SM8150P, SM8250, SM8350, SM8350P, SXR2130, SXR2130P</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3632|2024-08-04T07:37:55.748Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 10:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35076|2024-08-04T00:33:50.668Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35076</link>
      <description>Possible null pointer dereference due to improper validation of RRC connection reconfiguration message in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35076|2024-08-04T00:33:50.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35106|2024-08-04T00:33:51.195Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35106</link>
      <description>Possible out of bound read due to improper length calculation of WMI message. in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35106|2024-08-04T00:33:51.195Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 04:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3626|2024-08-04T07:37:55.606Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3626</link>
      <description>Any application can bind to it and exercise the APIs due to no protection for AIDL uimlpaservice in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA6574AU, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, Saipan, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3626|2024-08-04T07:37:55.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35115|2024-08-04T00:33:50.623Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35115</link>
      <description>Improper handling of multiple session supported by PVM backend can lead to use after free in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35115|2024-08-04T00:33:50.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 04:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35100|2024-08-04T00:33:50.866Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35100</link>
      <description>Possible buffer over read due to improper calculation of string length while parsing Id3 tag in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35100|2024-08-04T00:33:50.866Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35133|2024-08-04T00:33:51.177Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35133</link>
      <description>Use after free in the synx driver issue while performing other functions during multiple invocation of synx release calls in Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35133|2024-08-04T00:33:51.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 11:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35093|2024-08-04T00:33:51.165Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- bluecore
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35093</link>
      <description>Possible memory corruption in BT controller when it receives an oversized LMP packet over 2-DH1 link and leads to denial of service in BlueCore</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35093|2024-08-04T00:33:51.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 07:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3613|2024-08-04T07:37:55.541Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3613</link>
      <description>Double free issue in kernel memory mapping due to lack of memory protection mechanism in Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music in SM8150</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3613|2024-08-04T07:37:55.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35077|2024-08-04T00:33:50.913Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35077</link>
      <description>Possible use after free scenario in compute offloads to DSP while multiple calls spawn a dynamic process in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35077|2024-08-04T00:33:50.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 10:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3635|2024-08-04T07:37:55.552Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3635</link>
      <description>Stack based overflow If the maximum number of arguments allowed per request in perflock exceeds in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, Saipan, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3635|2024-08-04T07:37:55.552Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3691|2024-08-04T07:44:50.152Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wear
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3691</link>
      <description>Possible out of bound memory access in audio due to integer underflow while processing modified contents in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3691|2024-08-04T07:44:50.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 09:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35098|2024-08-04T00:33:50.910Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35098</link>
      <description>Improper validation of session id in PCM routing process can lead to memory corruption in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35098|2024-08-04T00:33:50.910Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:51:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3684|2024-08-04T07:44:50.287Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3684</link>
      <description>u'QSEE reads the access permission policy for the SMEM TOC partition from the SMEM TOC contents populated by XBL Loader and applies them without validation' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in Agatti, APQ8009, APQ8098, Bitra, IPQ6018, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9650, MSM8905, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA6390, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, QCS610, Rennell, SA415M, SA515M, SA6155P, SA8155P, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM630, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3684|2024-08-04T07:44:50.287Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3623|2024-08-04T07:37:55.614Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3623</link>
      <description>kernel failure due to load failures while running v1 path directly via kernel in Snapdragon Mobile in SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3623|2024-08-04T07:37:55.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 15:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35097|2024-08-04T00:33:51.022Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35097</link>
      <description>Possible authentication bypass due to improper order of signature verification and hashing in the signature verification call in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35097|2024-08-04T00:33:51.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 11:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3661|2024-08-04T07:44:50.323Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3661</link>
      <description>Buffer overflow will happen while parsing mp4 clip with corrupted sample atoms values which exceeds MAX_UINT32 range due to lack of validation checks in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, QCA6574AU, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, Saipan, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX20, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3661|2024-08-04T07:44:50.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35082|2024-08-04T00:33:50.973Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20industrial%20iot
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35082</link>
      <description>Improper integrity check can lead to race condition between tasks PDCP and RRC? right after a valid RRC security mode command packet has been received in Snapdragon Industrial IOT</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35082|2024-08-04T00:33:50.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3669|2024-08-04T07:44:50.107Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3669</link>
      <description>u'Buffer Overflow issue in WLAN tcp ip verification due to usage of out of range pointer offset' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8098, IPQ5018, IPQ6018, IPQ8074, Kamorta, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA6390, QCA8081, QCN7605, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, Rennell, SA415M, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA845, SDM630, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3669|2024-08-04T07:44:50.107Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3662|2024-08-04T07:44:50.042Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3662</link>
      <description>Buffer overflow can occur while parsing eac3 header while playing the clip which is nonstandard in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, QCA6574AU, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, Saipan, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM845, SDX20, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3662|2024-08-04T07:44:50.042Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35130|2024-08-04T00:33:51.033Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35130</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in graphics support layer due to use after free condition in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35130|2024-08-04T00:33:51.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3671|2024-08-04T07:44:49.923Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3671</link>
      <description>Use-after-free issue could occur due to dangling pointer when generating a frame buffer in OpenGL ES in Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music in APQ8009, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCS405, Saipan, SDM845, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3671|2024-08-04T07:44:49.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 11:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35103|2024-08-04T00:33:51.119Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20networking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35103</link>
      <description>Possible out of bound write due to improper validation of number of timer values received from firmware while syncing timers in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35103|2024-08-04T00:33:51.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 04:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35089|2024-08-04T00:33:50.935Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35089</link>
      <description>Possible buffer overflow due to lack of input IB amount validation while processing the user command in Snapdragon Auto</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35089|2024-08-04T00:33:50.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 04:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3686|2024-08-04T07:44:50.093Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wear
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3686</link>
      <description>Possible memory out of bound issue during music playback when an incorrect bit stream content is copied into array without checking the length of array in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3686|2024-08-04T07:44:50.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 09:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3618|2024-08-04T07:37:55.494Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20networking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3618</link>
      <description>NULL exception due to accessing bad pointer while posting events on RT FIFO in Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in IPQ6018, IPQ8074, QCA8081, SC8180X, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3618|2024-08-04T07:37:55.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 15:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3639|2024-08-04T07:37:55.802Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3639</link>
      <description>u'When a non standard SIP sigcomp message is received from the network, then there may be chances of using more UDVM cycle or memory overflow' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8037, APQ8053, MDM9250, MDM9607, MDM9628, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8108, MSM8208, MSM8209, MSM8608, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, QCM4290, QCM6125, QCS410, QCS4290, QCS603, QCS605, QCS610, QCS6125, QM215, QSM8350, SA415M, SA6145P, SA6150P, SA6155P, SA8150P, SA8155, SA8155P, SA8195P, SC7180, SC8180X, SC8180X+SDX55, SC8180XP, SDA429W, SDA640, SDA660, SDA670, SDA845, SDA855, SDM1000, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM455, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM640, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM712, SDM845, SDM850, SDX24, SDX50M, SDX55, SDX55M, SM4125, SM4250, SM4250P, SM6115, SM6115P, SM6125, SM6150, SM6150P, SM6250, SM6250P, SM7125, SM7150, SM7150P, SM7250, SM7250P, SM8150, SM8150P, SM8350, SM8350P, SXR1120, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3639|2024-08-04T07:37:55.802Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 10:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35112|2024-08-04T00:33:51.088Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35112</link>
      <description>A user with user level permission can access graphics protected region due to improper access control in register configuration in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35112|2024-08-04T00:33:51.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3690|2024-08-04T07:44:49.961Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3690</link>
      <description>u'Due to an incorrect SMMU configuration, the modem crypto engine can potentially compromise the hypervisor' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in Agatti, Bitra, Kamorta, Nicobar, QCA6390, QCS404, QCS605, QCS610, Rennell, SA415M, SA515M, SA6155P, SA8155P, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA845, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3690|2024-08-04T07:44:49.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35102|2024-08-04T00:33:51.064Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35102</link>
      <description>Possible buffer overflow due to lack of validation for the length of NAI string read from EFS in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35102|2024-08-04T00:33:51.064Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3646|2024-08-04T07:37:55.866Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3646</link>
      <description>u'Buffer overflow seen as the destination buffer size is lesser than the source buffer size in video application' in Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in Bitra, MSM8909W, QCM2150, QCS405, QCS605, Saipan, SC8180X, SDA845, SDM429W, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3646|2024-08-04T07:37:55.866Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3641|2024-08-04T07:37:55.792Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3641</link>
      <description>Integer overflow may occur if atom size is less than atom offset as there is improper validation of atom size in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, QCA6574AU, QCM2150, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, SA6155P, Saipan, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM845, SDX20, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3641|2024-08-04T07:37:55.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 15:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35079|2024-08-04T00:33:51.063Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35079</link>
      <description>Improper validation of permissions for third party application accessing Telephony service API can lead to information disclosure in Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35079|2024-08-04T00:33:51.063Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3634|2024-08-04T07:37:55.749Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3634</link>
      <description>u'Multiple Read overflows issue due to improper length check while decoding Generic NAS transport/EMM info' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9625, MDM9635M, MDM9640, MDM9645, MDM9650, MDM9655, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCS605, QCS610, QM215, Rennell, SA415M, Saipan, SC7180, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3634|2024-08-04T07:37:55.749Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 06:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3676|2024-08-04T07:44:50.129Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3676</link>
      <description>Possible memory corruption in perfservice due to improper validation array length taken from user application. in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile in APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, Saipan, SDM429, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3676|2024-08-04T07:44:50.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3647|2024-08-04T07:37:55.791Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3647</link>
      <description>u'Potential buffer overflow when accessing npu debugfs node "off"/"log" with large buffer size' in Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music in MDM9607, QCS405, SC8180X, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3647|2024-08-04T07:37:55.791Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35074|2024-08-04T00:33:51.125Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35074</link>
      <description>Possible integer overflow due to improper fragment datatype while calculating number of fragments in a request message in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35074|2024-08-04T00:33:51.125Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 10:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35129|2024-08-04T00:33:51.116Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20networking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35129</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in BT controller due to improper length check while processing vendor specific commands in Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35129|2024-08-04T00:33:51.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35085|2024-08-04T00:33:51.001Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35085</link>
      <description>Possible buffer overflow due to lack of buffer length check during management frame Rx handling in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35085|2024-08-04T00:33:51.001Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3699|2024-08-04T07:44:50.106Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20w
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3699</link>
      <description>Possible out of bound access while processing assoc response from host due to improper length check before copying into buffer in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, Nicobar, QCA6174A, QCA6574AU, QCA9377, QCA9379, QCM2150, QCN7605, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, SA6155P, Saipan, SC8180X, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM845, SDX20, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3699|2024-08-04T07:44:50.106Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 11:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3693|2024-08-04T07:44:50.097Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3693</link>
      <description>u'Use out of range pointer issue can occur due to incorrect buffer range check during the execution of qseecom.' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8098, Bitra, MSM8909W, MSM8996AU, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCS605, Saipan, SDM429W, SDX20, SM6150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3693|2024-08-04T07:44:50.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3700|2024-08-04T07:44:50.097Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20ne
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3700</link>
      <description>Possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check and could lead to local information disclosure in the wifi driver with no additional execution privileges needed in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8053, APQ8096AU, IPQ4019, IPQ8064, IPQ8074, MDM9607, MSM8909W, MSM8996AU, QCA6574AU, QCA9531, QCA9558, QCA9980, SC8180X, SDM439, SDX55, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3700|2024-08-04T07:44:50.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 11:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3704|2024-08-04T07:44:50.142Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3704</link>
      <description>u'While processing invalid connection request PDU which is nonstandard (interval or timeout is 0) from central device may lead peripheral system enter into dead lock state.(This CVE is equivalent to InvalidConnectionRequest(CVE-2019-19193) mentioned in sweyntooth paper)' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in Agatti, APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, AR9344, Bitra, IPQ5018, Kamorta, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8996AU, Nicobar, QCA6174A, QCA6390, QCA6574AU, QCA9377, QCA9886, QCM6125, QCN7605, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, QCS610, QRB5165, Rennell, SA415M, SA515M, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA845, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3704|2024-08-04T07:44:50.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35070|2024-08-04T00:33:51.154Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35070</link>
      <description>RPM secure Stream can access any secure resource due to improper SMMU configuration and can lead to information disclosure in Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35070|2024-08-04T00:33:51.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35104|2024-08-04T00:33:51.212Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35104</link>
      <description>Possible buffer overflow due to improper parsing of headers while playing the FLAC audio clip in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35104|2024-08-04T00:33:51.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3640|2024-08-04T07:37:55.771Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20networking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3640</link>
      <description>u'Resizing the usage table header before passing all the checks leads to the function exiting with a usage table in invalid state when a HLOS adversary calls the function with wrong input' in Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in Bitra, Kamorta, QCS404, QCS610, Rennell, Saipan, SC7180, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3640|2024-08-04T07:37:55.771Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35096|2024-08-04T00:33:50.577Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35096</link>
      <description>Improper memory allocation during counter check DLM handling can lead to denial of service in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35096|2024-08-04T00:33:50.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35084|2024-08-04T00:33:51.079Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35084</link>
      <description>Possible out of bound read due to lack of length check of data length for a DIAG event in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35084|2024-08-04T00:33:51.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35119|2024-08-04T00:33:51.031Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35119</link>
      <description>Potential out of Bounds read in FIPS event processing due to improper validation of the length from the firmware in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35119|2024-08-04T00:33:51.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3679|2024-08-04T07:44:49.932Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20networking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3679</link>
      <description>u'During execution after Address Space Layout Randomization is turned on for QTEE, part of code is still mapped at known address including code segments' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in Bitra, Kamorta, Nicobar, QCS404, QCS610, Rennell, SA6155P, SA8155P, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3679|2024-08-04T07:44:49.932Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 06:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3651|2024-08-04T07:37:55.801Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20w
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3651</link>
      <description>Active command timeout since WM status change cmd is not removed from active queue if peer sends multiple deauth frames. in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, QCA6174A, QCA6574AU, QCA9377, QCA9379, QCM2150, QCN7605, QCS605, QM215, SC8180X, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM845, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3651|2024-08-04T07:37:55.801Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 10:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3670|2024-08-04T07:44:50.035Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3670</link>
      <description>u'Potential out of bounds read while processing downlink NAS transport message due to improper length check of Information Element(IEI) NAS message container' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables in Agatti, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9625, MDM9635M, MDM9640, MDM9645, MDM9650, MDM9655, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCM6125, QCS605, QCS610, QM215, Rennell, SA415M, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3670|2024-08-04T07:44:50.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3660|2024-08-04T07:44:50.138Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3660</link>
      <description>Possible null-pointer dereference can occur while parsing mp4 clip with corrupted sample table atoms in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, QCA6574AU, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, Saipan, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM845, SDX20, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3660|2024-08-04T07:44:50.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3654|2024-08-04T07:37:55.785Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3654</link>
      <description>u'Buffer overflow occurs while processing SIP message packet due to lack of check of index validation before copying into it' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables in Agatti, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Bitra, Kamorta, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA6390, QCA6574AU, QCM2150, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, SA6155P, SA8155P, Saipan, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3654|2024-08-04T07:37:55.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3663|2024-08-04T07:44:50.160Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3663</link>
      <description>Buffer over-write may occur during fetching track decoder specific information if cb size exceeds buffer size in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, QCA6574AU, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, Saipan, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX20, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3663|2024-08-04T07:44:50.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35075|2024-08-04T00:33:50.482Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35075</link>
      <description>Possible null pointer dereference due to lack of WDOG structure validation during registration in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35075|2024-08-04T00:33:50.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 10:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35087|2024-08-04T00:33:50.476Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35087</link>
      <description>Possible null pointer access due to improper validation of system information message to be processed in Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35087|2024-08-04T00:33:50.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35072|2024-08-04T00:33:50.583Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35072</link>
      <description>Possible buffer overflow due to improper validation of array index while processing external DIAG command in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35072|2024-08-04T00:33:50.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35111|2024-08-04T00:33:51.189Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35111</link>
      <description>Improper validation of tag id while RRC sending tag id to MAC can lead to TOCTOU race condition in Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35111|2024-08-04T00:33:51.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35126|2024-08-04T00:33:51.149Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35126</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in DSP service due to improper validation of input parameters in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35126|2024-08-04T00:33:51.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35069|2024-08-04T00:33:51.119Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35069</link>
      <description>Improper validation of data length received from DMA buffer can lead to memory corruption. in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35069|2024-08-04T00:33:51.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 10:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3617|2024-08-04T07:37:55.590Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3617</link>
      <description>u'Buffer over-read Issue in Q6 testbus framework due to diag packet length is not completely validated before accessing the field and leads to Information disclosure.' in Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile in Kamorta, Nicobar, QCS605, QCS610, Rennell, SC7180, SDA660, SDM630, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3617|2024-08-04T07:37:55.590Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 06:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3666|2024-08-04T07:44:50.046Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3666</link>
      <description>u'Out of bounds memory access during memory copy while processing Host command' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, IPQ4019, IPQ6018, IPQ8064, IPQ8074, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, QCA6174A, QCA6574, QCA6574AU, QCA6584AU, QCA8081, QCA9377, QCA9379, QCA9531, QCA9558, QCA9563, QCA9880, QCA9886, QCA9980, QCN5500, QCN5502, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, SA6155P, SDA845, SDM630, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3666|2024-08-04T07:44:50.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35088|2024-08-04T00:33:51.026Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20netwo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35088</link>
      <description>Possible out of bound read due to improper validation of IE length during SSID IE parse when channel is DFS in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35088|2024-08-04T00:33:51.026Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 04:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3667|2024-08-04T07:44:50.107Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3667</link>
      <description>u'Buffer Overflow in mic calculation for WPA due to copying data into buffer without validating the length of buffer' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8098, IPQ5018, IPQ6018, IPQ8074, Kamorta, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA6390, QCA8081, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, Rennell, SA415M, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA845, SDM630, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3667|2024-08-04T07:44:50.107Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3642|2024-08-04T07:37:55.720Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3642</link>
      <description>Use after free issue in camera applications when used randomly over multiple operations due to pointer not set to NULL after free/destroy of the object in Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Mobile in Kamorta, QCS605, Rennell, Saipan, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3642|2024-08-04T07:37:55.720Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35092|2024-08-04T00:33:51.105Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35092</link>
      <description>Processing DCB/AVB algorithm with an invalid queue index from IOCTL request could lead to arbitrary address modification in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35092|2024-08-04T00:33:51.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3680|2024-08-04T07:44:50.075Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3680</link>
      <description>A race condition can occur when using the fastrpc memory mapping API. in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8053, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8953, QCS605, QM215, SA415M, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM632, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX24, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3680|2024-08-04T07:44:50.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 15:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3610|2024-08-04T07:37:55.529Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20w
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3610</link>
      <description>Possibility of double free of the drawobj that is added to the drawqueue array of the context during IOCTL commands as there is no refcount taken for this object in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, Nicobar, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, SA415M, Saipan, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3610|2024-08-04T07:37:55.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 15:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3625|2024-08-04T07:37:55.724Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3625</link>
      <description>When making query to DSP capabilities, Stack out of bounds occurs due to wrong buffer length configured for DSP attributes in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Mobile in SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3625|2024-08-04T07:37:55.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 15:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3658|2024-08-04T07:44:50.156Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3658</link>
      <description>Possible null-pointer dereference can occur while parsing mp4 clip with corrupted sample table atoms in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, QCA6574AU, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, Saipan, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX20, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3658|2024-08-04T07:44:50.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3629|2024-08-04T07:37:55.508Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3629</link>
      <description>u'Stack out of bound issue occurs when making query to DSP capabilities due to wrong assumption was made on determining the buffer size for the DSP attributes' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in Bitra, Kamorta, Rennell, SC7180, SDM845, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3629|2024-08-04T07:37:55.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35086|2024-08-04T00:33:50.622Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35086</link>
      <description>Possible buffer over read due to improper validation of SIB type when processing a NR system Information message in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35086|2024-08-04T00:33:50.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3698|2024-08-04T07:44:50.009Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20w
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3698</link>
      <description>Out of bound write while QoS DSCP mapping due to improper input validation for data received from association response frame in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9650, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, Nicobar, QCA6174A, QCA6574AU, QCA9377, QCA9379, QCM2150, QCN7605, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, SA6155P, Saipan, SC8180X, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM845, SDX20, SDX55, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3698|2024-08-04T07:44:50.009Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 11:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35113|2024-08-04T00:33:51.210Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35113</link>
      <description>Possible authentication bypass due to improper order of signature verification and hashing in the signature verification call in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35113|2024-08-04T00:33:51.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 11:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35095|2024-08-04T00:33:51.044Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35095</link>
      <description>Improper serialization of message queue client registration can lead to race condition allowing multiple gunyah message clients to register with same label in Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35095|2024-08-04T00:33:51.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35105|2024-08-04T00:33:51.023Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35105</link>
      <description>Possible out of bounds access due to improper input validation during graphics profiling in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35105|2024-08-04T00:33:51.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 04:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3675|2024-08-04T07:44:49.927Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wir
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3675</link>
      <description>u'Potential integer underflow while parsing Service Info and IPv6 link-local TLVs that comes as part of NDPE attribute' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in IPQ5018, IPQ6018, IPQ8074, Kamorta, Nicobar, QCA6390, QCN7605, QCS404, QCS405, Rennell, SA415M, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3675|2024-08-04T07:44:49.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21463|2024-08-01T22:20:40.754Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21463</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing Codec2 during v13k decoder pitch synthesis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21463|2024-08-01T22:20:40.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21458|2024-08-01T22:20:40.616Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21458</link>
      <description>Information disclosure while handling SA query action frame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21458|2024-08-01T22:20:40.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21456|2024-08-01T22:20:40.691Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21456</link>
      <description>Information Disclosure while parsing beacon frame in STA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21456|2024-08-01T22:20:40.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21461|2024-08-01T22:20:40.630Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21461</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while performing finish HMAC operation when context is freed by keymaster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21461|2024-08-01T22:20:40.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21473|2024-08-01T22:20:40.649Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21473</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while redirecting log file to any file location with any file name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21473|2024-08-01T22:20:40.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21453|2024-08-01T22:20:40.696Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21453</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while decoding message of size that exceeds the available system memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21453|2024-08-01T22:20:40.696Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21476|2024-08-01T22:20:40.882Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21476</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when the channel ID passed by user is not validated and further used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21476|2024-08-01T22:20:40.882Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23351|2024-08-01T22:59:32.248Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23351</link>
      <description>Memory corruption as GPU registers beyond the last protected range can be accessed through LPAC submissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23351|2024-08-01T22:59:32.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21469|2024-08-01T22:20:40.597Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21469</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when an invoke call and a TEE call are bound for the same trusted application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21469|2024-08-01T22:20:40.597Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21454|2024-08-01T22:20:40.818Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21454</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while decoding the ToBeSignedMessage in Automotive Telematics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21454|2024-08-01T22:20:40.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21478|2024-08-01T22:20:40.820Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21478</link>
      <description>transient DOS when setting up a fence callback to free a KGSL memory entry object during DMA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21478|2024-08-01T22:20:40.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21465|2024-08-01T22:20:40.847Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21465</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing key blob passed by the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21465|2024-08-01T22:20:40.847Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21471|2024-08-01T22:20:40.607Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21471</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when IOMMU unmap of a GPU buffer fails in Linux.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21471|2024-08-01T22:20:40.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21477|2024-08-01T22:20:40.972Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21477</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while parsing a protected 802.11az Fine Time Measurement (FTM) frame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21477|2024-08-01T22:20:40.972Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21474|2024-08-01T22:20:40.824Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21474</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when size of buffer from previous call is used without validation or re-initialization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21474|2024-08-01T22:20:40.824Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21480|2024-08-01T22:20:40.887Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21480</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while playing audio file having large-sized input buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21480|2024-08-01T22:20:40.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21462|2024-08-01T22:20:40.868Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21462</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while loading the TA ELF file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21462|2024-08-01T22:20:40.868Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21475|2024-08-01T22:20:40.866Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21475</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when the payload received from firmware is not as per the expected protocol size.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21475|2024-08-01T22:20:40.866Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21472|2024-08-01T22:20:40.700Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21472</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in Kernel while handling GPU operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21472|2024-08-01T22:20:40.700Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21457|2024-08-01T22:20:40.823Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21457</link>
      <description>INformation disclosure while handling Multi-link IE in beacon frame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21457|2024-08-01T22:20:40.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21466|2024-08-01T22:20:40.840Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21466</link>
      <description>Information disclosure while parsing sub-IE length during new IE generation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21466|2024-08-01T22:20:40.840Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21468|2024-08-01T22:20:40.611Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21468</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when there is failed unmap operation in GPU.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21468|2024-08-01T22:20:40.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21470|2024-08-01T22:20:41.033Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21470</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while allocating memory for graphics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21470|2024-08-01T22:20:41.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21482|2024-08-01T22:20:40.623Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21482</link>
      <description>Memory corruption during the secure boot process, when the `bootm` command is used, it bypasses the authentication of the kernel/rootfs image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21482|2024-08-01T22:20:40.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21452|2024-08-01T22:20:40.547Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21452</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while decoding an ASN.1 OER message containing a SEQUENCE of unknown extensions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21452|2024-08-01T22:20:40.547Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21460|2024-08-01T22:20:40.789Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21460</link>
      <description>Information disclosure when ASLR relocates the IMEM and Secure DDR portions as one chunk in virtual address space.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21460|2024-08-01T22:20:40.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33095|2024-07-29T20:04:16.019Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33095</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing multiple payload container type with incorrect container length received in DL NAS transport OTA in NR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33095|2024-07-29T20:04:16.019Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43521|2024-07-24T15:41:23.626Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43521</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when multiple listeners are being registered with the same file descriptor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43521|2024-07-24T15:41:23.626Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21454|2024-07-24T15:37:08.089Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21454</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while decoding the ToBeSignedMessage in Automotive Telematics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21454|2024-07-24T15:37:08.089Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28547|2024-07-11T20:25:27.385Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28547</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in SPS Application while requesting for public key in sorter TA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28547|2024-07-11T20:25:27.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33101|2024-07-11T20:16:26.319Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33101</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing DL NAS TRANSPORT message with payload length 0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33101|2024-07-11T20:16:26.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43548|2024-07-11T20:36:57.576Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43548</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while parsing qcp clip with invalid chunk data size.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43548|2024-07-11T20:36:57.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33023|2024-07-11T20:06:30.125Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33023</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing finish_sign command to pass a rsp buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33023|2024-07-11T20:06:30.125Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21463|2024-07-11T20:05:13.403Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21463</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing Codec2 during v13k decoder pitch synthesis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21463|2024-07-11T20:05:13.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33103|2024-07-05T17:22:07.936Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33103</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing CAG info IE received from NW.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33103|2024-07-05T17:22:07.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33111|2024-07-05T17:22:23.789Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33111</link>
      <description>Information disclosure when VI calibration state set by ADSP is greater than MAX_FBSP_STATE in the response payload to AFE calibration command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33111|2024-07-05T17:22:23.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21465|2024-07-04T03:55:52.464Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21465</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing key blob passed by the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21465|2024-07-04T03:55:52.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23373|2024-07-04T03:55:55.080Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23373</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when IOMMU unmap operation fails, the DMA and anon buffers are getting released.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23373|2024-07-04T03:55:55.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23380|2024-07-04T03:55:55.986Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23380</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while handling user packets during VBO bind operation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23380|2024-07-04T03:55:55.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21461|2024-07-04T03:55:50.770Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21461</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while performing finish HMAC operation when context is freed by keymaster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21461|2024-07-04T03:55:50.770Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23372|2024-07-04T03:55:54.250Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23372</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while invoking IOCTL call for GPU memory allocation and size param is greater than expected size.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23372|2024-07-04T03:55:54.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23368|2024-07-04T03:55:53.409Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23368</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when allocating and accessing an entry in an SMEM partition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23368|2024-07-04T03:55:53.409Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43554|2024-07-04T03:55:51.605Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43554</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing IOCTL handler in FastRPC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43554|2024-07-04T03:55:51.605Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23368|2024-07-01T17:06:44.905Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23368</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when allocating and accessing an entry in an SMEM partition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23368|2024-07-01T17:06:44.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43554|2024-07-01T17:02:34.510Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43554</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing IOCTL handler in FastRPC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43554|2024-07-01T17:02:34.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21456|2024-07-01T17:01:35.060Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21456</link>
      <description>Information Disclosure while parsing beacon frame in STA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21456|2024-07-01T17:01:35.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21465|2024-07-01T14:17:12.663Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21465</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing key blob passed by the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21465|2024-07-01T14:17:12.663Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21482|2024-07-01T14:17:16.594Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21482</link>
      <description>Memory corruption during the secure boot process, when the `bootm` command is used, it bypasses the authentication of the kernel/rootfs image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21482|2024-07-01T14:17:16.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23373|2024-07-01T14:17:20.786Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23373</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when IOMMU unmap operation fails, the DMA and anon buffers are getting released.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23373|2024-07-01T14:17:20.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21457|2024-07-01T14:17:05.569Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21457</link>
      <description>INformation disclosure while handling Multi-link IE in beacon frame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21457|2024-07-01T14:17:05.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23380|2024-07-01T14:17:21.973Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23380</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while handling user packets during VBO bind operation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23380|2024-07-01T14:17:21.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21460|2024-07-01T14:17:07.936Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21460</link>
      <description>Information disclosure when ASLR relocates the IMEM and Secure DDR portions as one chunk in virtual address space.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21460|2024-07-01T14:17:07.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21462|2024-07-01T14:17:11.022Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21462</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while loading the TA ELF file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21462|2024-07-01T14:17:11.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21461|2024-07-01T14:17:09.366Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21461</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while performing finish HMAC operation when context is freed by keymaster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21461|2024-07-01T14:17:09.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23372|2024-07-01T14:17:19.388Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23372</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while invoking IOCTL call for GPU memory allocation and size param is greater than expected size.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23372|2024-07-01T14:17:19.388Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23368|2024-07-01T14:17:17.981Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23368</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when allocating and accessing an entry in an SMEM partition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23368|2024-07-01T14:17:17.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21458|2024-07-01T14:17:06.770Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21458</link>
      <description>Information disclosure while handling SA query action frame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21458|2024-07-01T14:17:06.770Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21469|2024-07-01T14:17:15.436Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21469</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when an invoke call and a TEE call are bound for the same trusted application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21469|2024-07-01T14:17:15.436Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43554|2024-07-01T14:17:03.207Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43554</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing IOCTL handler in FastRPC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43554|2024-07-01T14:17:03.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21466|2024-07-01T14:17:14.036Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21466</link>
      <description>Information disclosure while parsing sub-IE length during new IE generation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21466|2024-07-01T14:17:14.036Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21456|2024-07-01T14:17:04.379Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21456</link>
      <description>Information Disclosure while parsing beacon frame in STA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21456|2024-07-01T14:17:04.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21477|2024-06-18T19:27:02.097Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21477</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while parsing a protected 802.11az Fine Time Measurement (FTM) frame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21477|2024-06-18T19:27:02.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43528|2024-06-13T18:55:25.147Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43528</link>
      <description>Information disclosure when the ADSP payload size received in HLOS in response to Audio Stream Manager matrix session is less than this expected size.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43528|2024-06-13T18:55:25.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21477|2024-05-06T14:32:18.401Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21477</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while parsing a protected 802.11az Fine Time Measurement (FTM) frame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21477|2024-05-06T14:32:18.401Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21476|2024-06-04T17:37:39.316Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21476</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when the channel ID passed by user is not validated and further used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21476|2024-06-04T17:37:39.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21471|2024-05-06T14:32:13.229Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21471</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when IOMMU unmap of a GPU buffer fails in Linux.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21471|2024-05-06T14:32:13.229Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21470|2024-04-12T08:39:07.646Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21470</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while allocating memory for graphics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21470|2024-04-12T08:39:07.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21453|2024-04-12T08:39:02.719Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21453</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while decoding message of size that exceeds the available system memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21453|2024-04-12T08:39:02.719Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21473|2024-06-04T17:37:57.845Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21473</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while redirecting log file to any file location with any file name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21473|2024-06-04T17:37:57.845Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21472|2024-04-12T08:39:08.788Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21472</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in Kernel while handling GPU operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21472|2024-04-12T08:39:08.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21468|2024-04-12T08:39:06.476Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21468</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when there is failed unmap operation in GPU.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21468|2024-04-12T08:39:06.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21452|2024-04-12T08:39:01.550Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21452</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while decoding an ASN.1 OER message containing a SEQUENCE of unknown extensions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21452|2024-04-12T08:39:01.550Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21463|2024-04-12T08:39:05.043Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21463</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing Codec2 during v13k decoder pitch synthesis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21463|2024-04-12T08:39:05.043Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21475|2024-06-04T17:38:05.618Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21475</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when the payload received from firmware is not as per the expected protocol size.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21475|2024-06-04T17:38:05.618Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21480|2024-06-04T17:38:10.980Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21480</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while playing audio file having large-sized input buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21480|2024-06-04T17:38:10.980Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21478|2024-06-04T17:38:13.715Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21478</link>
      <description>transient DOS when setting up a fence callback to free a KGSL memory entry object during DMA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21478|2024-06-04T17:38:13.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21454|2024-04-12T08:39:03.871Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21454</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while decoding the ToBeSignedMessage in Automotive Telematics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21454|2024-04-12T08:39:03.871Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21474|2024-06-04T17:38:18.133Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21474</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when size of buffer from previous call is used without validation or re-initialization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21474|2024-06-04T17:38:18.133Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23354|2024-06-04T17:45:47.597Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23354</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when the IOCTL call is interrupted by a signal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23354|2024-06-04T17:45:47.597Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23363|2024-06-03T10:05:27.911Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23363</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing an improperly formatted Fine Time Measurement (FTM) management frame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23363|2024-06-03T10:05:27.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23360|2024-06-05T04:01:22.984Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23360</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while creating a LPAC client as LPAC engine was allowed to access GPU registers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23360|2024-06-05T04:01:22.984Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23351|2024-06-04T17:46:12.184Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23351</link>
      <description>Memory corruption as GPU registers beyond the last protected range can be accessed through LPAC submissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23351|2024-06-04T17:46:12.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33103|2024-04-12T14:31:39.192Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33103</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing CAG info IE received from NW.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33103|2024-04-12T14:31:39.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33115|2024-04-12T08:38:59.243Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33115</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing buffer initialization, when trusted report for certain report types are generated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33115|2024-04-12T08:38:59.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33119|2024-06-04T17:22:02.558Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33119</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while loading a VM from a signed VM image that is not coherent in the processor cache.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33119|2024-06-04T17:22:02.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33066|2024-04-12T14:31:12.239Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33066</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in Audio while processing RT proxy port register driver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33066|2024-04-12T14:31:12.239Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33084|2024-04-12T14:31:20.245Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33084</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing IE fragments from server during DTLS handshake.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33084|2024-04-12T14:31:20.245Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33099|2024-06-04T17:22:03.865Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33099</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing SMS container of non-standard size received in DL NAS transport in NR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33099|2024-06-04T17:22:03.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33105|2024-04-12T14:31:46.898Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33105</link>
      <description>Transient DOS in WLAN Host and Firmware when large number of open authentication frames are sent with an invalid transaction sequence number.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33105|2024-04-12T14:31:46.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33095|2024-04-12T14:31:31.612Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33095</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing multiple payload container type with incorrect container length received in DL NAS transport OTA in NR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33095|2024-04-12T14:31:31.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33104|2024-04-12T14:31:43.117Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33104</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing PDU Release command with a parameter PDU ID out of range.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33104|2024-04-12T14:31:43.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33023|2024-04-12T08:38:53.261Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33023</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing finish_sign command to pass a rsp buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33023|2024-04-12T08:38:53.261Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33078|2024-04-12T14:31:16.358Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33078</link>
      <description>Information Disclosure while processing IOCTL request in FastRPC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33078|2024-04-12T14:31:16.358Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33111|2024-04-12T08:38:58.088Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33111</link>
      <description>Information disclosure when VI calibration state set by ADSP is greater than MAX_FBSP_STATE in the response payload to AFE calibration command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33111|2024-04-12T08:38:58.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33096|2024-04-12T14:31:35.474Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33096</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing DL NAS Transport message, as specified in 3GPP 24.501 v16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33096|2024-04-12T14:31:35.474Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33101|2024-04-12T08:38:56.953Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33101</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing DL NAS TRANSPORT message with payload length 0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33101|2024-04-12T08:38:56.953Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33100|2024-06-04T17:22:07.938Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33100</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing DL NAS Transport message when message ID is not defined in the 3GPP specification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33100|2024-06-04T17:22:07.938Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33090|2024-04-12T14:31:27.926Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33090</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing channel information for speaker protection v2 module in ADSP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33090|2024-04-12T14:31:27.926Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33086|2024-04-12T14:31:24.171Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33086</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing multiple IKEV2 Informational Request to device from IPSEC server with different identifiers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33086|2024-04-12T14:31:24.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43539|2024-04-12T14:31:50.623Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43539</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing an improperly formatted 802.11az Fine Time Measurement protocol frame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43539|2024-04-12T14:31:50.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43542|2024-06-05T04:01:21.896Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43542</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while copying a keyblob`s material when the key material`s size is not accurately checked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43542|2024-06-05T04:01:21.896Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43515|2024-04-12T08:39:00.417Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43515</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in HLOS while running kernel address sanitizers (syzkaller) on tmecom with DEBUG_FS enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43515|2024-04-12T08:39:00.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43555|2024-06-03T10:05:22.819Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43555</link>
      <description>Information disclosure in Video while parsing mp2 clip with invalid section length.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43555|2024-06-03T10:05:22.819Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43543|2024-06-04T17:25:54.520Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43543</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in Audio during a playback or a recording due to race condition between allocation and deallocation of graph object.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43543|2024-06-04T17:25:54.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43538|2024-06-10T10:49:07.728Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43538</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in TZ Secure OS while Tunnel Invoke Manager initialization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43538|2024-06-10T10:49:07.728Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43525|2024-06-04T17:25:54.975Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43525</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while copying the sound model data from user to kernel buffer during sound model register.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43525|2024-06-04T17:25:54.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43548|2024-04-12T14:32:10.256Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43548</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while parsing qcp clip with invalid chunk data size.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43548|2024-04-12T14:32:10.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43529|2024-06-04T17:25:55.922Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43529</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing IKEv2 Informational request messages, when a malformed fragment packet is received.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43529|2024-06-04T17:25:55.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43544|2024-06-04T17:25:56.870Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43544</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when IPC callback handle is used after it has been released during register callback by another thread.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43544|2024-06-04T17:25:56.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43552|2024-04-12T14:32:21.789Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43552</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing MBSSID beacon containing several subelement IE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43552|2024-04-12T14:32:21.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43553|2024-04-12T14:32:25.551Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43553</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while parsing beacon/probe response frame when AP sends more supported links in MLIE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43553|2024-04-12T14:32:25.551Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43545|2024-06-04T17:25:58.189Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43545</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when more scan frequency list or channels are sent from the user space.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43545|2024-06-04T17:25:58.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43528|2024-05-06T14:32:08.355Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43528</link>
      <description>Information disclosure when the ADSP payload size received in HLOS in response to Audio Stream Manager matrix session is less than this expected size.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43528|2024-05-06T14:32:08.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43549|2024-04-12T14:32:14.131Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43549</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing TPC target power table in FTM TPC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43549|2024-04-12T14:32:14.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43524|2024-06-04T17:25:59.064Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43524</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when the bandpass filter order received from AHAL is not within the expected range.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43524|2024-06-04T17:25:59.064Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43531|2024-05-06T14:32:11.964Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43531</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while verifying the serialized header when the key pairs are generated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43531|2024-05-06T14:32:11.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43527|2024-05-06T14:32:07.170Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43527</link>
      <description>Information disclosure while parsing dts header atom in Video.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43527|2024-05-06T14:32:07.170Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43550|2024-04-12T14:32:18.004Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43550</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing a QMI request for allocating memory from a DHMS supported subsystem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43550|2024-04-12T14:32:18.004Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43546|2024-04-12T14:32:02.233Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43546</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while invoking HGSL IOCTL context create.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43546|2024-04-12T14:32:02.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43547|2024-04-12T14:32:06.223Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43547</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while invoking IOCTLs calls in Automotive Multimedia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43547|2024-04-12T14:32:06.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43551|2024-06-05T13:10:59.039Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43551</link>
      <description>Cryptographic issue while performing attach with a LTE network, a rogue base station can skip the authentication phase and immediately send the Security Mode Command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43551|2024-06-05T13:10:59.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43526|2024-06-04T17:26:00.841Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43526</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while querying module parameters from Listen Sound model client in kernel from user space.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43526|2024-06-04T17:26:00.841Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43530|2024-06-04T17:26:01.732Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43530</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in HLOS while checking for the storage type.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43530|2024-06-04T17:26:01.732Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43556|2024-06-05T04:01:20.793Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43556</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in Hypervisor when platform information mentioned is not aligned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43556|2024-06-05T04:01:20.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43540|2024-04-12T14:31:54.617Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43540</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing the IOCTL FM HCI WRITE request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43540|2024-04-12T14:31:54.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43537|2024-06-04T17:26:03.543Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43537</link>
      <description>Information disclosure while handling T2LM Action Frame in WLAN Host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43537|2024-06-04T17:26:03.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43521|2024-05-06T14:32:02.380Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43521</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when multiple listeners are being registered with the same file descriptor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43521|2024-05-06T14:32:02.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43541|2024-04-12T14:31:58.348Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43541</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while invoking the SubmitCommands call on Gfx engine during the graphics render.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43541|2024-04-12T14:31:58.348Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28578|2024-04-12T14:27:07.966Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-28578</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in Core Services while executing the command for removing a single event listener.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28578|2024-04-12T14:27:07.966Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28547|2024-04-12T08:38:51.581Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-28547</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in SPS Application while requesting for public key in sorter TA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28547|2024-04-12T08:38:51.581Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28582|2024-04-12T14:30:48.100Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-28582</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in Data Modem while verifying hello-verify message during the DTLS handshake.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28582|2024-04-12T14:30:48.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43555|2024-06-17T15:13:20.369Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43555</link>
      <description>Information disclosure in Video while parsing mp2 clip with invalid section length.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43555|2024-06-17T15:13:20.369Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33078|2024-06-28T01:33:16.484Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33078</link>
      <description>Information Disclosure while processing IOCTL request in FastRPC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33078|2024-06-28T01:33:16.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33090|2024-06-28T01:32:59.239Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33090</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing channel information for speaker protection v2 module in ADSP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33090|2024-06-28T01:32:59.239Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21466|2024-07-01T16:44:36.703Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21466</link>
      <description>Information disclosure while parsing sub-IE length during new IE generation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21466|2024-07-01T16:44:36.703Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21469|2024-07-01T16:42:14.617Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21469</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when an invoke call and a TEE call are bound for the same trusted application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21469|2024-07-01T16:42:14.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21458|2024-07-01T16:54:19.394Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21458</link>
      <description>Information disclosure while handling SA query action frame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21458|2024-07-01T16:54:19.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23372|2024-07-01T16:33:35.879Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23372</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while invoking IOCTL call for GPU memory allocation and size param is greater than expected size.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23372|2024-07-01T16:33:35.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21461|2024-07-01T16:48:50.339Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21461</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while performing finish HMAC operation when context is freed by keymaster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21461|2024-07-01T16:48:50.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21462|2024-07-01T16:48:04.446Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21462</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while loading the TA ELF file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21462|2024-07-01T16:48:04.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21460|2024-07-01T16:52:31.688Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21460</link>
      <description>Information disclosure when ASLR relocates the IMEM and Secure DDR portions as one chunk in virtual address space.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21460|2024-07-01T16:52:31.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23380|2024-07-01T16:27:46.472Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23380</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while handling user packets during VBO bind operation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23380|2024-07-01T16:27:46.472Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21457|2024-07-01T16:53:28.583Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21457</link>
      <description>INformation disclosure while handling Multi-link IE in beacon frame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21457|2024-07-01T16:53:28.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23373|2024-07-01T16:32:38.919Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23373</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when IOMMU unmap operation fails, the DMA and anon buffers are getting released.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23373|2024-07-01T16:32:38.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21482|2024-07-01T16:34:44.883Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21482</link>
      <description>Memory corruption during the secure boot process, when the `bootm` command is used, it bypasses the authentication of the kernel/rootfs image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21482|2024-07-01T16:34:44.883Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21465|2024-07-01T16:46:58.328Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21465</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing key blob passed by the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21465|2024-07-01T16:46:58.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43515|2024-07-01T20:35:45.276Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43515</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in HLOS while running kernel address sanitizers (syzkaller) on tmecom with DEBUG_FS enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43515|2024-07-01T20:35:45.276Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23363|2024-07-23T16:23:53.796Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23363</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing an improperly formatted Fine Time Measurement (FTM) management frame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23363|2024-07-23T16:23:53.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43531|2024-07-23T20:39:56.986Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43531</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while verifying the serialized header when the key pairs are generated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43531|2024-07-23T20:39:56.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43552|2024-07-25T19:47:24.198Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43552</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing MBSSID beacon containing several subelement IE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43552|2024-07-25T19:47:24.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43553|2024-07-25T19:46:49.223Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43553</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while parsing beacon/probe response frame when AP sends more supported links in MLIE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43553|2024-07-25T19:46:49.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43540|2024-07-25T19:48:06.783Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43540</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing the IOCTL FM HCI WRITE request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43540|2024-07-25T19:48:06.783Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21453|2024-08-01T14:05:32.525Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21453</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while decoding message of size that exceeds the available system memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21453|2024-08-01T14:05:32.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28578|2024-08-02T13:43:23.548Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28578</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in Core Services while executing the command for removing a single event listener.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28578|2024-08-02T13:43:23.548Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28582|2024-08-02T13:43:23.082Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28582</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in Data Modem while verifying hello-verify message during the DTLS handshake.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28582|2024-08-02T13:43:23.082Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28547|2024-08-02T13:43:22.683Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28547</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in SPS Application while requesting for public key in sorter TA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28547|2024-08-02T13:43:22.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33084|2024-08-02T15:32:46.678Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33084</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing IE fragments from server during DTLS handshake.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33084|2024-08-02T15:32:46.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33119|2024-08-02T15:39:34.342Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33119</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while loading a VM from a signed VM image that is not coherent in the processor cache.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33119|2024-08-02T15:39:34.342Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33096|2024-08-02T15:32:46.723Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33096</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing DL NAS Transport message, as specified in 3GPP 24.501 v16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33096|2024-08-02T15:32:46.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33103|2024-08-02T15:32:46.745Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33103</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing CAG info IE received from NW.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33103|2024-08-02T15:32:46.745Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33066|2024-08-02T15:32:46.577Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33066</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in Audio while processing RT proxy port register driver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33066|2024-08-02T15:32:46.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33023|2024-08-02T15:32:46.521Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33023</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing finish_sign command to pass a rsp buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33023|2024-08-02T15:32:46.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33115|2024-08-02T15:39:34.352Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33115</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing buffer initialization, when trusted report for certain report types are generated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33115|2024-08-02T15:39:34.352Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33111|2024-08-02T15:39:34.383Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33111</link>
      <description>Information disclosure when VI calibration state set by ADSP is greater than MAX_FBSP_STATE in the response payload to AFE calibration command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33111|2024-08-02T15:39:34.383Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33105|2024-08-02T15:32:47.098Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33105</link>
      <description>Transient DOS in WLAN Host and Firmware when large number of open authentication frames are sent with an invalid transaction sequence number.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33105|2024-08-02T15:32:47.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33086|2024-08-02T15:32:46.733Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33086</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing multiple IKEV2 Informational Request to device from IPSEC server with different identifiers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33086|2024-08-02T15:32:46.733Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33104|2024-08-02T15:32:46.675Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33104</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing PDU Release command with a parameter PDU ID out of range.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33104|2024-08-02T15:32:46.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33100|2024-08-02T15:32:46.711Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33100</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing DL NAS Transport message when message ID is not defined in the 3GPP specification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33100|2024-08-02T15:32:46.711Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33090|2024-08-02T15:32:46.628Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33090</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing channel information for speaker protection v2 module in ADSP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33090|2024-08-02T15:32:46.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33095|2024-08-02T15:32:46.639Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33095</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing multiple payload container type with incorrect container length received in DL NAS transport OTA in NR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33095|2024-08-02T15:32:46.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33101|2024-08-02T15:32:46.752Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33101</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing DL NAS TRANSPORT message with payload length 0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33101|2024-08-02T15:32:46.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33078|2024-08-02T15:32:46.612Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33078</link>
      <description>Information Disclosure while processing IOCTL request in FastRPC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33078|2024-08-02T15:32:46.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33099|2024-08-02T15:32:46.647Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33099</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing SMS container of non-standard size received in DL NAS transport in NR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33099|2024-08-02T15:32:46.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43524|2024-08-02T19:44:42.864Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43524</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when the bandpass filter order received from AHAL is not within the expected range.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43524|2024-08-02T19:44:42.864Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43545|2024-08-02T19:44:43.816Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43545</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when more scan frequency list or channels are sent from the user space.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43545|2024-08-02T19:44:43.816Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43528|2024-08-02T19:44:43.328Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43528</link>
      <description>Information disclosure when the ADSP payload size received in HLOS in response to Audio Stream Manager matrix session is less than this expected size.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43528|2024-08-02T19:44:43.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43537|2024-08-02T19:44:43.656Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43537</link>
      <description>Information disclosure while handling T2LM Action Frame in WLAN Host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43537|2024-08-02T19:44:43.656Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43538|2024-08-02T19:44:43.850Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43538</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in TZ Secure OS while Tunnel Invoke Manager initialization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43538|2024-08-02T19:44:43.850Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43526|2024-08-02T19:44:43.825Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43526</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while querying module parameters from Listen Sound model client in kernel from user space.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43526|2024-08-02T19:44:43.825Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43551|2024-08-02T19:44:43.781Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43551</link>
      <description>Cryptographic issue while performing attach with a LTE network, a rogue base station can skip the authentication phase and immediately send the Security Mode Command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43551|2024-08-02T19:44:43.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43515|2024-08-02T19:44:43.903Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43515</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in HLOS while running kernel address sanitizers (syzkaller) on tmecom with DEBUG_FS enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43515|2024-08-02T19:44:43.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43556|2024-08-02T19:44:43.798Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43556</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in Hypervisor when platform information mentioned is not aligned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43556|2024-08-02T19:44:43.798Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43550|2024-08-02T19:44:43.822Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43550</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing a QMI request for allocating memory from a DHMS supported subsystem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43550|2024-08-02T19:44:43.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43554|2024-08-02T19:44:42.916Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43554</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing IOCTL handler in FastRPC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43554|2024-08-02T19:44:42.916Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43546|2024-08-02T19:44:43.813Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43546</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while invoking HGSL IOCTL context create.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43546|2024-08-02T19:44:43.813Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43547|2024-08-02T19:44:44.192Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43547</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while invoking IOCTLs calls in Automotive Multimedia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43547|2024-08-02T19:44:44.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43542|2024-08-02T19:44:43.783Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43542</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while copying a keyblob`s material when the key material`s size is not accurately checked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43542|2024-08-02T19:44:43.783Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43555|2024-08-02T19:44:43.706Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43555</link>
      <description>Information disclosure in Video while parsing mp2 clip with invalid section length.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43555|2024-08-02T19:44:43.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43539|2024-08-02T19:44:43.680Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43539</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing an improperly formatted 802.11az Fine Time Measurement protocol frame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43539|2024-08-02T19:44:43.680Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43552|2024-08-02T19:44:43.808Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43552</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing MBSSID beacon containing several subelement IE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43552|2024-08-02T19:44:43.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43529|2024-08-02T19:44:43.778Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43529</link>
      <description>Transient DOS while processing IKEv2 Informational request messages, when a malformed fragment packet is received.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43529|2024-08-02T19:44:43.778Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43548|2024-08-02T19:44:43.762Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43548</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while parsing qcp clip with invalid chunk data size.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43548|2024-08-02T19:44:43.762Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43525|2024-08-02T19:44:43.157Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43525</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while copying the sound model data from user to kernel buffer during sound model register.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43525|2024-08-02T19:44:43.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43544|2024-08-02T19:44:43.639Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43544</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when IPC callback handle is used after it has been released during register callback by another thread.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43544|2024-08-02T19:44:43.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43530|2024-08-02T19:44:43.809Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43530</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in HLOS while checking for the storage type.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43530|2024-08-02T19:44:43.809Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43540|2024-08-02T19:44:43.794Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43540</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing the IOCTL FM HCI WRITE request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43540|2024-08-02T19:44:43.794Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43541|2024-08-02T19:44:42.722Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43541</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while invoking the SubmitCommands call on Gfx engine during the graphics render.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43541|2024-08-02T19:44:42.722Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43527|2024-08-02T19:44:43.662Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43527</link>
      <description>Information disclosure while parsing dts header atom in Video.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43527|2024-08-02T19:44:43.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43553|2024-08-02T19:44:43.819Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43553</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while parsing beacon/probe response frame when AP sends more supported links in MLIE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43553|2024-08-02T19:44:43.819Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43521|2024-08-02T19:44:42.853Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43521</link>
      <description>Memory corruption when multiple listeners are being registered with the same file descriptor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43521|2024-08-02T19:44:42.853Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43543|2024-08-02T19:44:43.789Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43543</link>
      <description>Memory corruption in Audio during a playback or a recording due to race condition between allocation and deallocation of graph object.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43543|2024-08-02T19:44:43.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43531|2024-08-02T19:44:43.817Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43531</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while verifying the serialized header when the key pairs are generated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43531|2024-08-02T19:44:43.817Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43549|2024-08-02T19:44:42.792Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43549</link>
      <description>Memory corruption while processing TPC target power table in FTM TPC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43549|2024-08-02T19:44:42.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
