<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qualcomm%2C%20inc./snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:20:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13902|2024-08-05T09:14:47.318Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13902</link>
      <description>Out of bounds memory read and access due to improper array index validation may lead to unexpected behavior while decoding XTRA file in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9615, MDM9635M, MDM9640, MDM9650, MDM9655, MSM8909W, MSM8996AU, QCS605, Qualcomm 215, SD 210/SD 212/SD 205, SD 425, SD 427, SD 430, SD 435, SD 439 / SD 429, SD 450, SD 625, SD 632, SD 636, SD 650/52, SD 675, SD 712 / SD 710 / SD 670, SD 730, SD 820, SD 820A, SD 835, SD 845 / SD 850, SD 855, SD 8CX, SDA660, SDM439, SDM630, SDM660, SDX20, Snapdragon_High_Med_2016, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13902|2024-08-05T09:14:47.318Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:02:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13911|2024-08-05T09:14:47.243Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13911</link>
      <description>Out of bounds memory read and access may lead to unexpected behavior in GNSS XTRA Parser in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9615, MDM9635M, MDM9640, MDM9650, MDM9655, MSM8909W, MSM8996AU, QCS605, Qualcomm 215, SD 210/SD 212/SD 205, SD 425, SD 427, SD 430, SD 435, SD 439 / SD 429, SD 450, SD 625, SD 632, SD 636, SD 650/52, SD 675, SD 712 / SD 710 / SD 670, SD 730, SD 820, SD 820A, SD 835, SD 845 / SD 850, SD 855, SD 8CX, SDA660, SDM439, SDM630, SDM660, SDX20, Snapdragon_High_Med_2016, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13911|2024-08-05T09:14:47.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:02:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14073|2024-08-05T00:12:42.172Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14073</link>
      <description>Copying RTCP messages into the output buffer without checking the destination buffer size which could lead to a remote stack overflow when processing large data or non-standard feedback messages in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8076, APQ8096, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9615, MDM9635M, MDM9640, MDM9645, MDM9650, MDM9655, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, SA415M, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14073|2024-08-05T00:12:42.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14072|2024-08-05T00:12:42.163Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14072</link>
      <description>Unhandled paging request is observed due to dereferencing an already freed object because of race condition between sparse free and sparse bind ioctls which access the same physical entry in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, MDM9607, MSM8909W, MSM8939, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, Nicobar, QCS405, QCS605, Rennell, SA6155P, Saipan, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM450, SDM632, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14072|2024-08-05T00:12:42.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 08:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
