<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qualcomm%2C%20inc./snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20networking.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14081|2024-08-05T00:12:42.399Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20networking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14081</link>
      <description>Buffer Over-read when WLAN module gets a WMI message for SAR limits with invalid number of limits to be enforced in Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8098, IPQ8074, MSM8998, QCA8081, QCN7605, QCS605, SDA660, SDA845, SDM630, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14081|2024-08-05T00:12:42.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 08:56:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14082|2024-08-05T00:12:42.599Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20networking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14082</link>
      <description>Potential buffer over-read due to lack of bound check of memory offset passed in WLAN firmware in Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in IPQ8074, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, QCN7605, SM8150</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14082|2024-08-05T00:12:42.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 08:56:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
