<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qualcomm%2C%20inc./snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 05:23:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14088|2024-08-05T00:12:42.182Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14088</link>
      <description>Possible use after free issue while CRM is accessing the link pointer from device private data due to lack of resource protection in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, QCS605, SDM429W, SDX24, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14088|2024-08-05T00:12:42.182Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 05:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14099|2024-08-05T00:12:42.783Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14099</link>
      <description>Device misbehavior may be observed when incorrect offset, length or number of buffers is passed by user space in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8053, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8953, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Saipan, SC8180X, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM632, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14099|2024-08-05T00:12:42.783Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 11:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14127|2024-08-05T00:12:42.717Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14127</link>
      <description>Possible buffer overflow while playing mkv clip due to lack of validation of atom size buffer in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8064, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, SA6155P, Saipan, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX20, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14127|2024-08-05T00:12:42.717Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 10:46:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
