<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qualcomm%2C%20inc./snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 16:23:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11223|2024-08-04T11:28:13.385Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11223</link>
      <description>Out of bound in camera driver due to lack of check of validation of array index before copying into array in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11223|2024-08-04T11:28:13.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 06:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3626|2024-08-04T07:37:55.606Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3626</link>
      <description>Any application can bind to it and exercise the APIs due to no protection for AIDL uimlpaservice in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA6574AU, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, Saipan, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3626|2024-08-04T07:37:55.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3635|2024-08-04T07:37:55.552Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3635</link>
      <description>Stack based overflow If the maximum number of arguments allowed per request in perflock exceeds in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, Saipan, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3635|2024-08-04T07:37:55.552Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3639|2024-08-04T07:37:55.802Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3639</link>
      <description>u'When a non standard SIP sigcomp message is received from the network, then there may be chances of using more UDVM cycle or memory overflow' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8037, APQ8053, MDM9250, MDM9607, MDM9628, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8108, MSM8208, MSM8209, MSM8608, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, QCM4290, QCM6125, QCS410, QCS4290, QCS603, QCS605, QCS610, QCS6125, QM215, QSM8350, SA415M, SA6145P, SA6150P, SA6155P, SA8150P, SA8155, SA8155P, SA8195P, SC7180, SC8180X, SC8180X+SDX55, SC8180XP, SDA429W, SDA640, SDA660, SDA670, SDA845, SDA855, SDM1000, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM455, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM640, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM712, SDM845, SDM850, SDX24, SDX50M, SDX55, SDX55M, SM4125, SM4250, SM4250P, SM6115, SM6115P, SM6125, SM6150, SM6150P, SM6250, SM6250P, SM7125, SM7150, SM7150P, SM7250, SM7250P, SM8150, SM8150P, SM8350, SM8350P, SXR1120, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3639|2024-08-04T07:37:55.802Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 10:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3634|2024-08-04T07:37:55.749Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3634</link>
      <description>u'Multiple Read overflows issue due to improper length check while decoding Generic NAS transport/EMM info' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9625, MDM9635M, MDM9640, MDM9645, MDM9650, MDM9655, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCS605, QCS610, QM215, Rennell, SA415M, Saipan, SC7180, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3634|2024-08-04T07:37:55.749Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 06:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11175|2024-08-04T11:28:13.362Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11175</link>
      <description>u'Use after free issue in Bluetooth transport driver when a method in the object is accessed after the object has been deleted due to improper timer handling.' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009W, MSM8909W, QCS605, QM215, SA6155, SA6155P, SA8155, SA8155P, SDA640, SDA670, SDA855, SDM1000, SDM640, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX50M, SDX55, SDX55M, SM6125, SM6350, SM7225, SM7250, SM7250P, SM8150, SM8150P, SM8250, SXR1120, SXR1130, SXR2130, SXR2130P</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11175|2024-08-04T11:28:13.362Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 10:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3670|2024-08-04T07:44:50.035Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3670</link>
      <description>u'Potential out of bounds read while processing downlink NAS transport message due to improper length check of Information Element(IEI) NAS message container' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables in Agatti, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9625, MDM9635M, MDM9640, MDM9645, MDM9650, MDM9655, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCM6125, QCS605, QCS610, QM215, Rennell, SA415M, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3670|2024-08-04T07:44:50.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3680|2024-08-04T07:44:50.075Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3680</link>
      <description>A race condition can occur when using the fastrpc memory mapping API. in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8053, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8953, QCS605, QM215, SA415M, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM632, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX24, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3680|2024-08-04T07:44:50.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 15:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35113|2024-08-04T00:33:51.210Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35113</link>
      <description>Possible authentication bypass due to improper order of signature verification and hashing in the signature verification call in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35113|2024-08-04T00:33:51.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 11:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
