<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qualcomm%2C%20inc./snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 15:22:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11156|2024-08-04T11:28:13.416Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11156</link>
      <description>u'Buffer over-read issue in Bluetooth estack due to lack of check for invalid length of L2cap packet received from peer device.' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in QCA6390, QCN7605, QCS404, SA415M, SA515M, SC8180X, SDX55, SM8250</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11156|2024-08-04T11:28:13.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11234|2024-08-04T11:28:13.531Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11234</link>
      <description>When sending a socket event message to a user application, invalid information will be passed if socket is freed by other thread resulting in a Use After Free condition in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11234|2024-08-04T11:28:13.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 07:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3621|2024-08-04T07:37:55.644Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3621</link>
      <description>u'Lack of check to ensure that the TX read index &amp; RX write index that are read from shared memory are less than the FIFO size results into memory corruption and potential information leakage' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Bitra, IPQ6018, IPQ8074, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9645, MDM9650, MDM9655, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA8081, QCM2150, QCN7605, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, QCS610, QM215, Rennell, SA415M, SA6155P, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3621|2024-08-04T07:37:55.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3620|2024-08-04T07:37:55.732Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3620</link>
      <description>u'Lack of check of integer overflow while doing a round up operation for data read from shared memory for G-link SMEM transport can lead to corruption and potential information leak' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Bitra, IPQ6018, IPQ8074, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9645, MDM9650, MDM9655, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA8081, QCM2150, QCN7605, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, QCS610, QM215, Rennell, SA415M, SA6155P, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3620|2024-08-04T07:37:55.732Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11141|2024-08-04T11:28:12.559Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11141</link>
      <description>u'Buffer over-read issue in Bluetooth estack due to lack of check for invalid length of L2cap configuration request received from peer device.' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8053, QCA6390, QCN7605, SA415M, SA515M, SC8180X, SDX55, SM8250</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11141|2024-08-04T11:28:12.559Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11278|2024-08-04T11:28:13.796Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11278</link>
      <description>Possible denial of service while handling host WMI command due to improper validation in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11278|2024-08-04T11:28:13.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 06:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35083|2024-08-04T00:33:50.937Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35083</link>
      <description>Possible out of bound read due to improper validation of certificate chain in SSL or Internet key exchange in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35083|2024-08-04T00:33:50.937Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11280|2024-08-04T11:28:13.809Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11280</link>
      <description>Denial of service while processing fine timing measurement request (FTMR) frame with reserved bits set in the FTM parameter IE due to improper error handling in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11280|2024-08-04T11:28:13.809Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 06:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11297|2024-08-04T11:28:13.877Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11297</link>
      <description>Denial of service in WLAN module due to improper check of subtypes in logic where excessive frames are dropped in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11297|2024-08-04T11:28:13.877Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 06:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11134|2024-08-04T11:21:14.790Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11134</link>
      <description>Possible stack out of bound write might happen due to time bitmap length and bit duration fields of the attributes like NAN ranging setup attribute inside a NAN management frame are not Properly validated in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11134|2024-08-04T11:21:14.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 05:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3668|2024-08-04T07:44:49.935Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3668</link>
      <description>u'Buffer overflow while parsing PMF enabled MCBC frames due to frame length being lesser than what is expected while parsing' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in IPQ6018, IPQ8074, Kamorta, Nicobar, QCA6390, QCA8081, QCN7605, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, Rennell, SA415M, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA845, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3668|2024-08-04T07:44:49.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11215|2024-08-04T11:28:13.759Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11215</link>
      <description>An out of bounds read can happen when processing VSA attribute due to improper minimum required length check in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11215|2024-08-04T11:28:13.759Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 09:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11126|2024-08-04T11:21:14.624Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11126</link>
      <description>Possible out of bound read while WLAN frame parsing due to lack of check for body and header length in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11126|2024-08-04T11:21:14.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 05:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3624|2024-08-04T07:37:55.564Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3624</link>
      <description>u'A potential buffer overflow exists due to integer overflow when parsing handler options due to wrong data type usage in operation' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9615, MDM9625, MDM9635M, MDM9640, MDM9645, MDM9650, MDM9655, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCN7605, QCS605, QCS610, QM215, Rennell, SA415M, SA515M, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3624|2024-08-04T07:37:55.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11287|2024-08-04T11:28:13.836Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11287</link>
      <description>Allowing RTT frames to be linked with non randomized MAC address by comparing the sequence numbers can lead to information disclosure. in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11287|2024-08-04T11:28:13.836Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 06:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11169|2024-08-04T11:28:13.197Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11169</link>
      <description>u'Buffer over-read while processing received L2CAP packet due to lack of integer overflow check' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8053, QCA6390, QCN7605, QCN7606, SA415M, SA515M, SA6155P, SA8155P, SC8180X, SDX55</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11169|2024-08-04T11:28:13.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3622|2024-08-04T07:37:55.751Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3622</link>
      <description>u'Channel name string which has been read from shared memory is potentially subjected to string manipulations but not validated for NULL termination can results into memory corruption' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Bitra, IPQ6018, IPQ8074, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9645, MDM9650, MDM9655, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA8081, QCM2150, QCN7605, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, QCS610, QM215, Rennell, SA415M, SA6155P, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3622|2024-08-04T07:37:55.751Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11270|2024-08-04T11:28:13.840Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11270</link>
      <description>Possible denial of service due to RTT responder consistently rejects all FTMR by transmitting FTM1 with failure status in the FTM parameter IE in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11270|2024-08-04T11:28:13.840Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 06:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11214|2024-08-04T11:28:13.404Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11214</link>
      <description>Buffer over-read while processing NDL attribute if attribute length is larger than expected and then FW is treating it as more number of immutable schedules in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11214|2024-08-04T11:28:13.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 09:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3669|2024-08-04T07:44:50.107Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3669</link>
      <description>u'Buffer Overflow issue in WLAN tcp ip verification due to usage of out of range pointer offset' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8098, IPQ5018, IPQ6018, IPQ8074, Kamorta, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA6390, QCA8081, QCN7605, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, Rennell, SA415M, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA845, SDM630, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3669|2024-08-04T07:44:50.107Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11154|2024-08-04T11:28:12.474Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11154</link>
      <description>u'Buffer overflow while processing a crafted PDU data packet in bluetooth due to lack of check of buffer size before copying' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8053, QCA6390, QCN7605, QCN7606, SA415M, SA515M, SA6155P, SA8155P, SC8180X, SDX55</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11154|2024-08-04T11:28:12.474Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11264|2024-08-04T11:28:13.784Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11264</link>
      <description>Improper authentication of Non-EAPOL/WAPI plaintext frames during four-way handshake can lead to arbitrary network packet injection in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11264|2024-08-04T11:28:13.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11238|2024-08-04T11:28:13.795Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11238</link>
      <description>Possible Buffer over-read in ARP/NS parsing due to lack of check of packet length received in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11238|2024-08-04T11:28:13.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 05:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11225|2024-08-04T11:28:13.852Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11225</link>
      <description>Out of bound access in WLAN driver due to lack of validation of array length before copying into array in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11225|2024-08-04T11:28:13.852Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 09:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11281|2024-08-04T11:28:13.781Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11281</link>
      <description>Allowing RTT frames to be linked with non randomized MAC address by comparing the sequence numbers can lead to information disclosure. in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11281|2024-08-04T11:28:13.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 06:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11272|2024-08-04T11:28:13.859Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11272</link>
      <description>Before enqueuing a frame to the PE queue for further processing, an entry in a hash table can be deleted and using a stale version later can lead to use after free condition in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11272|2024-08-04T11:28:13.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 06:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35084|2024-08-04T00:33:51.079Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35084</link>
      <description>Possible out of bound read due to lack of length check of data length for a DIAG event in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35084|2024-08-04T00:33:51.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11155|2024-08-04T11:28:12.529Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11155</link>
      <description>u'Buffer overflow while processing PDU packet in bluetooth due to lack of check of buffer length before copying into it.' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8053, QCA6390, QCN7605, QCN7606, SA415M, SA515M, SA6155P, SA8155P, SC8180X, SDX55</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11155|2024-08-04T11:28:12.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3666|2024-08-04T07:44:50.046Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3666</link>
      <description>u'Out of bounds memory access during memory copy while processing Host command' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, IPQ4019, IPQ6018, IPQ8064, IPQ8074, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, QCA6174A, QCA6574, QCA6574AU, QCA6584AU, QCA8081, QCA9377, QCA9379, QCA9531, QCA9558, QCA9563, QCA9880, QCA9886, QCA9980, QCN5500, QCN5502, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, SA6155P, SDA845, SDM630, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3666|2024-08-04T07:44:50.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
