<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qualcomm%2C%20inc./snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20networking.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 16:24:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11132|2024-08-04T11:21:14.727Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20networking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11132</link>
      <description>u'Buffer over read in boot due to size check ignored before copying GUID attribute from request to response' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, MDM8207, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9207, MDM9250, MDM9607, MDM9628, MDM9650, MSM8108, MSM8208, MSM8209, MSM8608, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8998, QCM4290, QCS405, QCS410, QCS4290, QCS603, QCS605, QCS610, QSM8250, SA415M, SA515M, SA6145P, SA6150P, SA6155, SA6155P, SA8150P, SA8155, SA8155P, SA8195P, SC7180, SC8180X, SC8180X+SDX55, SC8180XP, SDA640, SDA670, SDA845, SDA855, SDM1000, SDM640, SDM670, SDM710, SDM712, SDM830, SDM845, SDM850, SDX24, SDX50M, SDX55, SDX55M, SM4125, SM4250, SM4250P, SM6115, SM6115P, SM6125, SM6150, SM6150P, SM6250, SM6250P, SM6350, SM7125, SM7150, SM7150P, SM7225, SM7250, SM7250P, SM8150, SM8150P, SM8250, SXR1120, SXR1130, SXR2130, SXR2130P, WCD9330</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11132|2024-08-04T11:21:14.727Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 10:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11127|2024-08-04T11:21:14.682Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20networking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11127</link>
      <description>u'Integer overflow can cause a buffer overflow due to lack of table length check in the extensible boot Loader during the validation of security metadata while processing objects to be loaded' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in MDM9205, QCM4290, QCS405, QCS410, QCS4290, QCS610, QSM8250, SA415M, SA515M, SA6145P, SA6150P, SA6155, SA6155P, SA8150P, SA8155, SA8155P, SA8195P, SC7180, SC8180X, SC8180X+SDX55, SC8180XP, SDA640, SDA845, SDA855, SDM1000, SDM640, SDM830, SDM845, SDM850, SDX24, SDX50M, SDX55, SDX55M, SM4125, SM4250, SM4250P, SM6115, SM6115P, SM6150, SM6150P, SM6250, SM6250P, SM6350, SM7125, SM7150, SM7150P, SM7225, SM7250, SM7250P, SM8150, SM8150P, SM8250, SXR2130, SXR2130P</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11127|2024-08-04T11:21:14.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 10:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3679|2024-08-04T07:44:49.932Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20and%20networking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3679</link>
      <description>u'During execution after Address Space Layout Randomization is turned on for QTEE, part of code is still mapped at known address including code segments' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in Bitra, Kamorta, Nicobar, QCS404, QCS610, Rennell, SA6155P, SA8155P, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3679|2024-08-04T07:44:49.932Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 06:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
