<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qualcomm%2C%20inc./snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35132|2024-08-04T00:33:51.259Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35132</link>
      <description>Out of bound write in DSP service due to improper bound check for response buffer size in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35132|2024-08-04T00:33:51.259Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 11:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11294|2024-08-04T11:28:14.038Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11294</link>
      <description>Out of bound write in logger due to prefix size is not validated while prepended to logging string in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11294|2024-08-04T11:28:14.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 09:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35078|2024-08-04T00:33:50.820Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35078</link>
      <description>Possible memory leak due to improper validation of certificate chain length while parsing server certificate chain in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35078|2024-08-04T00:33:50.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3673|2024-08-04T07:44:50.255Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3673</link>
      <description>u'Buffer overflow can happen as part of SIP message packet processing while storing values in array due to lack of check to validate the index length' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables in Agatti, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Bitra, Kamorta, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, Nicobar, QCA6390, QCA6574AU, QCM2150, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, SA6155P, SA8155P, Saipan, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3673|2024-08-04T07:44:50.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35122|2024-08-04T00:33:51.150Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35122</link>
      <description>Non-secure region can try modifying RG permissions of IO space xPUs due to improper input validation in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35122|2024-08-04T00:33:51.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 11:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11290|2024-08-04T11:28:13.851Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11290</link>
      <description>Use after free condition in msm ioctl events due to race between the ioctl register and deregister events in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11290|2024-08-04T11:28:13.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 06:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35116|2024-08-04T00:33:51.053Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35116</link>
      <description>APK can load a crafted model into the CDSP which can lead to a compromise of CDSP and other APK`s data executing there in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35116|2024-08-04T00:33:51.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11148|2024-08-04T11:28:12.539Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11148</link>
      <description>Use after free issue in HIDL while using callback to post event in Rx thread when internal mutex is not acquired and meantime close is triggered and callback instance is deleted in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11148|2024-08-04T11:28:12.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 09:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3654|2024-08-04T07:37:55.785Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3654</link>
      <description>u'Buffer overflow occurs while processing SIP message packet due to lack of check of index validation before copying into it' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Wearables in Agatti, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Bitra, Kamorta, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA6390, QCA6574AU, QCM2150, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, SA6155P, SA8155P, Saipan, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3654|2024-08-04T07:37:55.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
