<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qualcomm%2C%20inc./snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:23:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3648|2024-08-04T07:37:55.727Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3648</link>
      <description>u'Possible out of bound write in DSP driver code due to lack of check of data received from user' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in MSM8909W</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3648|2024-08-04T07:37:55.727Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2323|2024-08-04T18:49:47.817Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2323</link>
      <description>Lack of check to ensure crypto engine data passed by user is initialized can result in bus error in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8909W, MSM8996AU, QCS405, QCS605, Qualcomm 215, SD 210/SD 212/SD 205, SD 425, SD 427, SD 430, SD 435, SD 439 / SD 429, SD 450, SD 625, SD 632, SD 636, SD 665, SD 675, SD 712 / SD 710 / SD 670, SD 730, SD 820, SD 820A, SD 835, SD 845 / SD 850, SD 855, SDA660, SDM439, SDM630, SDM660, SDX20, SDX24</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2323|2024-08-04T18:49:47.817Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 17:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11168|2024-08-04T11:28:13.156Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11168</link>
      <description>u'Null-pointer dereference can occur while accessing data buffer beyond its size that leads to access the buffer beyond its range' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8009W, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8064AU, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, MDM9206, MDM9650, MSM8909W, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, QCM4290, QCS405, QCS4290, QCS603, QCS605, QM215, QSM8350, SA6155, SA6155P, SA8155, SA8155P, SDA429W, SDA640, SDA660, SDA845, SDA855, SDM1000, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM450, SDM632, SDM640, SDM830, SDM845, SDW2500, SDX20, SDX20M, SDX50M, SDX55, SDX55M, SM4250, SM4250P, SM6115, SM6115P, SM6125, SM6250, SM6350, SM7125, SM7225, SM7250, SM7250P, SM8150, SM8150P, SM8250, SM8350, SM8350P, SXR2130, SXR2130P, WCD9330</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11168|2024-08-04T11:28:13.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 10:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3674|2024-08-04T07:44:50.124Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3674</link>
      <description>Information can leak into userspace due to improper transfer of data from kernel to userspace in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in Nicobar, QCS405, Saipan, SC8180X, SDX55, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3674|2024-08-04T07:44:50.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 06:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2287|2024-08-04T18:42:51.341Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2287</link>
      <description>Improper validation for inputs received from firmware can lead to an out of bound write issue in video driver. in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8909W, MSM8996AU, QCA6574AU, QCS405, QCS605, Qualcomm 215, SD 210/SD 212/SD 205, SD 425, SD 427, SD 430, SD 435, SD 439 / SD 429, SD 450, SD 625, SD 632, SD 636, SD 665, SD 675, SD 712 / SD 710 / SD 670, SD 730, SD 820, SD 820A, SD 835, SD 845 / SD 850, SD 855, SDA660, SDM439, SDM630, SDM660, SDX20, SDX24</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2287|2024-08-04T18:42:51.341Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 13:47:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3633|2024-08-04T07:37:55.809Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3633</link>
      <description>Array out of bound may occur while playing mp3 file as no check is there on offset if it is greater than the buffer allocated or not in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, Saipan, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX20, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3633|2024-08-04T07:37:55.809Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 15:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11152|2024-08-04T11:28:12.405Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11152</link>
      <description>Race condition in HAL layer while processing callback objects received from HIDL due to lack of synchronization between accessing objects in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11152|2024-08-04T11:28:12.405Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 09:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2260|2024-08-04T18:42:51.123Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2260</link>
      <description>A race condition occurs while processing perf-event which can lead to a use after free condition in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8909W, QCS405, QCS605, Qualcomm 215, SD 210/SD 212/SD 205, SD 425, SD 427, SD 430, SD 435, SD 439 / SD 429, SD 450, SD 625, SD 632, SD 636, SD 665, SD 712 / SD 710 / SD 670, SD 730, SD 820A, SD 835, SD 845 / SD 850, SD 855, SDM439, SDM630, SDM660, SDX20, SDX24, Snapdragon_High_Med_2016, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2260|2024-08-04T18:42:51.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 13:47:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3656|2024-08-04T07:44:50.134Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3656</link>
      <description>Out of bound access can happen in MHI command process due to lack of check of command channel id value received from MHI devices in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, Kamorta, MDM9607, MSM8917, MSM8953, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, SA6155P, SA8155P, Saipan, SC8180X, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM632, SDM710, SDM845, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3656|2024-08-04T07:44:50.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 06:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11160|2024-08-04T11:28:12.569Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11160</link>
      <description>Resource leakage issue during dci client registration due to reference count is not decremented if dci client registration fails in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11160|2024-08-04T11:28:12.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 05:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11128|2024-08-04T11:21:14.669Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11128</link>
      <description>u'Possible out of bound access while copying the mask file content into the buffer without checking the buffer size' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Bitra, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9607, MDM9650, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8998, QCM2150, QCS405, QCS605, QCS610, QM215, Rennell, SA515M, SA6155P, Saipan, SC8180X, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM632, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11128|2024-08-04T11:21:14.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11196|2024-08-04T11:28:13.538Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11196</link>
      <description>u'Integer overflow to buffer overflow occurs while playback of ASF clip having unexpected number of codec entries' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8009W, APQ8017, APQ8037, APQ8053, APQ8064AU, APQ8096, APQ8096AU, APQ8096SG, APQ8098, MDM9206, MDM9650, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8996SG, MSM8998, QCM4290, QCM6125, QCS405, QCS410, QCS4290, QCS603, QCS605, QCS610, QCS6125, QM215, SA6145P, SA6150P, SA6155, SA6155P, SA8150P, SA8155, SA8155P, SA8195P, SDA429W, SDA640, SDA660, SDA670, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM455, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM640, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM830, SDM845, SDW2500, SDX20, SDX20M, SDX50M, SDX55, SDX55M, SM4125, SM4250, SM4250P, SM6115, SM6115P, SM6125, SM6150, SM6150P, SM6250, SM6250P, SM6350, SM7125, SM7150, SM7150P, SM7225, SM7250, SM7250P, SM8150, SM8150P, SM8250, SXR1120, SXR1130, SXR2130, SXR2130P, WCD9330</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11196|2024-08-04T11:28:13.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 10:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2333|2024-08-04T18:49:47.907Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2333</link>
      <description>Buffer overflow due to improper validation of buffer size while IPA driver processing to perform read operation in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in MDM9150, MDM9607, MDM9650, MSM8909W, MSM8996AU, QCS605, Qualcomm 215, SD 210/SD 212/SD 205, SD 425, SD 427, SD 430, SD 435, SD 439 / SD 429, SD 450, SD 625, SD 632, SD 636, SD 665, SD 675, SD 712 / SD 710 / SD 670, SD 730, SD 820, SD 820A, SD 835, SD 845 / SD 850, SD 855, SDA660, SDM439, SDM630, SDM660, SDX20, SDX24</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2333|2024-08-04T18:49:47.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11120|2024-08-04T11:21:14.759Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11120</link>
      <description>u'Calling thread may free the data buffer pointer that was passed to the callback and later when event loop executes the callback, data buffer may not be valid and will lead to use after free scenario' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Bitra, Kamorta, MSM8917, MSM8953, MSM8998, QCM2150, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, Saipan, SDM429, SDM439, SDM450, SDM632, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11120|2024-08-04T11:21:14.759Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3641|2024-08-04T07:37:55.792Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3641</link>
      <description>Integer overflow may occur if atom size is less than atom offset as there is improper validation of atom size in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, QCA6574AU, QCM2150, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, SA6155P, Saipan, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM845, SDX20, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3641|2024-08-04T07:37:55.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 15:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3693|2024-08-04T07:44:50.097Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3693</link>
      <description>u'Use out of range pointer issue can occur due to incorrect buffer range check during the execution of qseecom.' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8098, Bitra, MSM8909W, MSM8996AU, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCS605, Saipan, SDM429W, SDX20, SM6150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3693|2024-08-04T07:44:50.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2298|2024-08-04T18:42:50.971Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2298</link>
      <description>Protection is missing while accessing md sessions info via macro which can lead to use-after-free in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8909W, QCS405, QCS605, SD 210/SD 212/SD 205, SD 425, SD 427, SD 430, SD 435, SD 450, SD 625, SD 636, SD 712 / SD 710 / SD 670, SD 820, SD 820A, SD 845 / SD 850, SD 855, SDM660, SDX20, SDX24</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2298|2024-08-04T18:42:50.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 16:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2283|2024-08-04T18:42:51.045Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2283</link>
      <description>Improper validation of read and write index of tx and rx fifo`s before calculating pointer can lead to out-of-bound access in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8909W, MSM8996AU, QCS605, Qualcomm 215, SD 210/SD 212/SD 205, SD 425, SD 427, SD 430, SD 435, SD 439 / SD 429, SD 450, SD 625, SD 632, SD 636, SD 675, SD 712 / SD 710 / SD 670, SD 730, SD 820, SD 820A, SD 835, SD 845 / SD 850, SD 855, SDA660, SDM439, SDM630, SDM660, SDX20, SDX24</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2283|2024-08-04T18:42:51.045Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 17:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11193|2024-08-04T11:28:13.195Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11193</link>
      <description>u'Buffer over read can happen while parsing mkv clip due to improper typecasting of data returned from atomsize' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8009W, APQ8017, APQ8037, APQ8053, APQ8064AU, APQ8096, APQ8096AU, APQ8096SG, APQ8098, MDM9206, MDM9650, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8996SG, MSM8998, QCM4290, QCM6125, QCS405, QCS410, QCS4290, QCS603, QCS605, QCS610, QCS6125, QM215, QSM8350, SA6145P, SA6155, SA6155P, SA8155, SA8155P, SDA429W, SDA640, SDA660, SDA670, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM455, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM640, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM830, SDM845, SDW2500, SDX20, SDX20M, SDX50M, SDX55, SDX55M, SM4125, SM4250, SM4250P, SM6115, SM6115P, SM6125, SM6150, SM6150P, SM6250, SM6250P, SM6350, SM7125, SM7150, SM7150P, SM7225, SM7250, SM7250P, SM8150, SM8150P, SM8250, SM8350, SM8350P, SXR1120, SXR1130, SXR2130, SXR2130P, WCD9330</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11193|2024-08-04T11:28:13.195Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 10:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3629|2024-08-04T07:37:55.508Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3629</link>
      <description>u'Stack out of bound issue occurs when making query to DSP capabilities due to wrong assumption was made on determining the buffer size for the DSP attributes' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in Bitra, Kamorta, Rennell, SC7180, SDM845, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3629|2024-08-04T07:37:55.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
