<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qualcomm%2C%20inc./snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 08:23:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3648|2024-08-04T07:37:55.727Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3648</link>
      <description>u'Possible out of bound write in DSP driver code due to lack of check of data received from user' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in MSM8909W</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3648|2024-08-04T07:37:55.727Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3674|2024-08-04T07:44:50.124Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3674</link>
      <description>Information can leak into userspace due to improper transfer of data from kernel to userspace in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in Nicobar, QCS405, Saipan, SC8180X, SDX55, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3674|2024-08-04T07:44:50.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 06:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3633|2024-08-04T07:37:55.809Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3633</link>
      <description>Array out of bound may occur while playing mp3 file as no check is there on offset if it is greater than the buffer allocated or not in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, Saipan, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX20, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3633|2024-08-04T07:37:55.809Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 15:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3656|2024-08-04T07:44:50.134Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3656</link>
      <description>Out of bound access can happen in MHI command process due to lack of check of command channel id value received from MHI devices in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, Kamorta, MDM9607, MSM8917, MSM8953, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, SA6155P, SA8155P, Saipan, SC8180X, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM632, SDM710, SDM845, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3656|2024-08-04T07:44:50.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 06:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3641|2024-08-04T07:37:55.792Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3641</link>
      <description>Integer overflow may occur if atom size is less than atom offset as there is improper validation of atom size in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MSM8905, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, QCA6574AU, QCM2150, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, SA6155P, Saipan, SDA660, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM845, SDX20, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3641|2024-08-04T07:37:55.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 15:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3693|2024-08-04T07:44:50.097Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3693</link>
      <description>u'Use out of range pointer issue can occur due to incorrect buffer range check during the execution of qseecom.' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8098, Bitra, MSM8909W, MSM8996AU, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCS605, Saipan, SDM429W, SDX20, SM6150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3693|2024-08-04T07:44:50.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3629|2024-08-04T07:37:55.508Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wearables
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3629</link>
      <description>u'Stack out of bound issue occurs when making query to DSP capabilities due to wrong assumption was made on determining the buffer size for the DSP attributes' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in Bitra, Kamorta, Rennell, SC7180, SDM845, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3629|2024-08-04T07:37:55.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
