<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qualcomm%2C%20inc./snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:29:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14135|2024-08-05T00:12:42.588Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14135</link>
      <description>Possible integer overflow to buffer overflow in WLAN while parsing nonstandard NAN IE messages. in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096, APQ8096AU, IPQ8074, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8996AU, QCA4010, QCA6174A, QCA6574AU, QCA6584AU, QCA8081, QCA9377, QCA9379, QCA9886, QCN7605, QCS405, QCS605, SA6155P, Saipan, SDA845, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14135|2024-08-05T00:12:42.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 10:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14074|2024-08-05T00:12:42.155Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14074</link>
      <description>u'Heap overflow in diag command handler due to lack of check of packet length received from user' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8076, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, Bitra, IPQ6018, IPQ8074, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9625, MDM9635M, MDM9640, MDM9645, MDM9650, MDM9655, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA8081, QCM2150, QCN7605, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, QCS610, QM215, Rennell, SA415M, SA6155P, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14074|2024-08-05T00:12:42.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14097|2024-08-05T00:12:42.546Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14097</link>
      <description>Possible buffer overflow in WLAN Parser due to lack of length check when copying data in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8096, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, IPQ6018, IPQ8074, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA6174A, QCA6574, QCA6574AU, QCA6584, QCA6584AU, QCA8081, QCA9377, QCA9379, QCN7605, QCS405, QCS605, Rennell, SA6155P, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM630, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14097|2024-08-05T00:12:42.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 08:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
