<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qualcomm%2C%20inc./snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2307|2024-08-04T18:49:46.219Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2307</link>
      <description>Possible integer underflow due to lack of validation before calculation of data length in 802.11 Rx management configuration in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music in MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8996AU, QCA6174A, QCA6574AU, QCA9377, QCA9379, QCS405, QCS605, SD 210/SD 212/SD 205, SD 425, SD 427, SD 430, SD 435, SD 450, SD 600, SD 625, SD 636, SD 665, SD 675, SD 712 / SD 710 / SD 670, SD 730, SD 820, SD 820A, SD 835, SD 845 / SD 850, SD 855, SDM630, SDM660, SDX20, SDX24</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2307|2024-08-04T18:49:46.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 16:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10598|2024-08-04T22:24:18.831Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10598</link>
      <description>Out of bound access can occur while processing peer info in IBSS connection mode due to lack of upper bounds check to ensure that for loop further will not cause an overflow in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music in APQ8053, APQ8096AU, MDM9607, MSM8996AU, QCA6574AU, QCN7605, QCS605, SDA660, SDA845, SDM630, SDM636, SDM660, SDM845, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10598|2024-08-04T22:24:18.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 05:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10563|2024-08-04T22:24:18.713Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10563</link>
      <description>Buffer over-read can occur in fast message handler due to improper input validation while processing a message from firmware in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music in APQ8053, APQ8096AU, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, QCN7605, QCS405, QCS605, SDA660, SDM636, SDM660, SDX20, SDX24</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10563|2024-08-04T22:24:18.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 14:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10537|2024-08-04T22:24:18.700Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10537</link>
      <description>Improper validation of event buffer extracted from FW response can lead to integer overflow, which will allow to pass the length check and eventually will lead to buffer overwrite when event data is copied to context buffer in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music in MDM9607, Nicobar, QCA6574AU, QCN7605, QCS405, QCS605, SDM660, SDM845, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10537|2024-08-04T22:24:18.700Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 05:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10507|2024-08-04T22:24:18.563Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10507</link>
      <description>Lack of check of extscan change results received from firmware can lead to an out of buffer read in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music in MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8996AU, QCA6174A, QCA6574AU, QCA9377, QCA9379, QCS605, SD 210/SD 212/SD 205, SD 425, SD 430, SD 600, SD 625, SD 636, SD 665, SD 675, SD 712 / SD 710 / SD 670, SD 730, SD 820A, SD 835, SD 845 / SD 850, SD 855, SDA660, SDM630, SDM660, SDX20, SDX24</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10507|2024-08-04T22:24:18.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10557|2024-08-04T22:24:18.849Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10557</link>
      <description>Out-of-bound read in the wireless driver in the Linux kernel due to lack of check of buffer length. in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9650, MSM8996AU, QCA6174A, QCA6574AU, QCA9377, QCA9379, QCN7605, QCS605, SDA660, SDA845, SDM630, SDM636, SDM660, SDX20, SDX55, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10557|2024-08-04T22:24:18.849Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 05:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2309|2024-08-04T18:49:46.396Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2309</link>
      <description>While storing calibrated data from firmware in cache, An integer overflow may occur since data length received may exceed real data length. in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music in MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8996AU, QCA6174A, QCA6574AU, QCA9377, QCA9379, SD 210/SD 212/SD 205, SD 425, SD 625, SD 636, SD 712 / SD 710 / SD 670, SD 820A, SD 845 / SD 850, SDM660, SDX20</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2309|2024-08-04T18:49:46.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 16:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10542|2024-08-04T22:24:18.835Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10542</link>
      <description>Buffer over-read may occur when downloading a corrupted firmware file that has chunk length in header which doesn`t match the contents in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music in MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9615, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8996AU, QCA6174A, QCA6574AU, QCA9377, QCA9379, SD 210/SD 212/SD 205, SD 425, SD 427, SD 430, SD 435, SD 450, SD 600, SD 625, SD 712 / SD 710 / SD 670, SD 820, SD 820A, SD 845 / SD 850, SDX20</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10542|2024-08-04T22:24:18.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 17:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2268|2024-08-04T18:42:50.889Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2268</link>
      <description>Possible OOB read issue in P2P action frames while handling WLAN management frame in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9650, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, QCA6174A, QCA6574AU, QCA9377, QCA9379, QCS405, QCS605, SDA660, SDM630, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX20, SM6150</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2268|2024-08-04T18:42:50.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 14:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2312|2024-08-04T18:49:46.394Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2312</link>
      <description>When handling the vendor command there exists a potential buffer overflow due to lack of input validation of data buffer received in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music in MDM9607, MDM9640, MSM8996AU, QCA6174A, QCA6574AU, QCA9377, QCA9379, QCS405, QCS605, SD 210/SD 212/SD 205, SD 425, SD 427, SD 430, SD 435, SD 450, SD 600, SD 625, SD 636, SD 665, SD 675, SD 712 / SD 710 / SD 670, SD 730, SD 820, SD 820A, SD 835, SD 845 / SD 850, SD 855, SDM630, SDM660, SDX24</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2312|2024-08-04T18:49:46.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 16:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2305|2024-08-04T18:49:46.210Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2305</link>
      <description>Out of bound access when reason code is extracted from frame data without validating the frame length in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music in MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8996AU, QCA6174A, QCA6574AU, QCA9377, QCA9379, QCS405, QCS605, SD 425, SD 427, SD 430, SD 435, SD 450, SD 625, SD 636, SD 665, SD 675, SD 712 / SD 710 / SD 670, SD 730, SD 820, SD 820A, SD 835, SD 845 / SD 850, SD 855, SDA660, SDM630, SDM660, SDX20, SDX24</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2305|2024-08-04T18:49:46.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 16:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
