<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qualcomm%2C%20inc./snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2240|2024-08-04T18:42:50.915Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2240</link>
      <description>While sending the rendered surface content to the screen, Error handling is not properly checked results in an unpredictable behaviour in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in IPQ4019, IPQ8064, IPQ8074, MDM9150, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8996AU, QCA6174A, QCA6564, QCA6574, QCA6574AU, QCA6584, QCA6584AU, QCA8081, QCA9377, QCA9379, QCA9531, QCA9880, QCA9886, QCA9980, QCN5502, QCS404, QCS605, SD 210/SD 212/SD 205, SD 425, SD 600, SD 625, SD 636, SD 675, SD 712 / SD 710 / SD 670, SD 730, SD 820, SD 820A, SD 835, SD 845 / SD 850, SD 855, SD 8CX, SDA660, SDM630, SDM660, SDX20, SDX24, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2240|2024-08-04T18:42:50.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 16:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11269|2024-08-04T11:28:13.880Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11269</link>
      <description>Possible memory corruption while processing EAPOL frames due to lack of validation of key length before using it in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11269|2024-08-04T11:28:13.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 06:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11276|2024-08-04T11:28:13.815Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11276</link>
      <description>Possible buffer over read while processing P2P IE and NOA attribute of beacon and probe response frames due to improper validation of P2P IE and NOA attribute lengths in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11276|2024-08-04T11:28:13.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 06:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11191|2024-08-04T11:28:13.539Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11191</link>
      <description>Out of bound read occurs while processing crafted SDP due to lack of check of null string in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11191|2024-08-04T11:28:13.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 07:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3665|2024-08-04T07:44:50.115Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3665</link>
      <description>A possible buffer overflow would occur while processing command from firmware due to the group_id obtained from the firmware being out of range in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in APQ8009, APQ8053, APQ8096AU, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9615, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8909W, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, QCA6174A, QCA9377, QCA9379, SDM439, SDM636, SDM660, SDX20, SDX24, SM8150</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3665|2024-08-04T07:44:50.115Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11275|2024-08-04T11:28:13.848Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11275</link>
      <description>Possible buffer over-read while parsing quiet IE in Rx beacon frame due to improper check of IE length in received beacon in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11275|2024-08-04T11:28:13.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 06:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11213|2024-08-04T11:28:13.428Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11213</link>
      <description>Out of bound reads might occur in while processing Service descriptor due to improper validation of length of fields in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11213|2024-08-04T11:28:13.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 09:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3703|2024-08-04T07:44:50.073Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3703</link>
      <description>u'Buffer over-read issue in Bluetooth peripheral firmware due to lack of check for invalid opcode and length of opcode received from central device(This CVE is equivalent to Link Layer Length Overfow issue (CVE-2019-16336,CVE-2019-17519) and Silent Length Overflow issue(CVE-2019-17518) mentioned in sweyntooth paper)' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music in APQ8053, APQ8076, AR9344, Bitra, Kamorta, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MSM8905, MSM8917, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, Nicobar, QCA6174A, QCA9377, QCM2150, QCM6125, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, QCS610, QM215, Rennell, SC8180X, SDM429, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX20, SDX24, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3703|2024-08-04T07:44:50.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11301|2024-08-04T11:28:13.862Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11301</link>
      <description>Improper authentication of un-encrypted plaintext Wi-Fi frames in an encrypted network can lead to information disclosure in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11301|2024-08-04T11:28:13.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3614|2024-08-04T07:37:55.503Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3614</link>
      <description>Possible buffer overflow while copying the frame to local buffer due to lack of check of length before copying in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8076, APQ8096, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, IPQ6018, IPQ8074, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCA6174A, QCA6574AU, QCA6584AU, QCA9377, QCA9379, QCA9886, QCM2150, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, SC7180, SC8180X, SDM429, SDM429W, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDX20, SDX24, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3614|2024-08-04T07:37:55.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11159|2024-08-04T11:28:12.378Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11159</link>
      <description>Buffer over-read can happen while processing WPA,RSN IE of beacon and response frames if IE length is less than length of frame pointer being accessed in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11159|2024-08-04T11:28:12.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 05:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2294|2024-08-04T18:42:50.893Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2294</link>
      <description>Usage of hard-coded magic number for calculating heap guard bytes can allow users to corrupt heap blocks without heap algorithm knowledge in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables in MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9615, MDM9625, MDM9635M, MDM9655, MSM8909W, MSM8996AU, QCS605, Qualcomm 215, SD 210/SD 212/SD 205, SD 410/12, SD 425, SD 427, SD 430, SD 435, SD 439 / SD 429, SD 450, SD 625, SD 632, SD 636, SD 650/52, SD 665, SD 675, SD 712 / SD 710 / SD 670, SD 730, SD 820, SD 820A, SD 835, SD 845 / SD 850, SD 855, SD 8CX, SDA660, SDM439, SDM630, SDM660, Snapdragon_High_Med_2016, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2294|2024-08-04T18:42:50.893Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11241|2024-08-04T11:28:13.847Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11241</link>
      <description>Out of bound read will happen if EAPOL Key length is less than expected while processing NAN shared key descriptor attribute in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11241|2024-08-04T11:28:13.847Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 05:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3704|2024-08-04T07:44:50.142Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3704</link>
      <description>u'While processing invalid connection request PDU which is nonstandard (interval or timeout is 0) from central device may lead peripheral system enter into dead lock state.(This CVE is equivalent to InvalidConnectionRequest(CVE-2019-19193) mentioned in sweyntooth paper)' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in Agatti, APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, AR9344, Bitra, IPQ5018, Kamorta, MDM9607, MDM9640, MDM9650, MSM8996AU, Nicobar, QCA6174A, QCA6390, QCA6574AU, QCA9377, QCA9886, QCM6125, QCN7605, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, QCS610, QRB5165, Rennell, SA415M, SA515M, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA845, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX20, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3704|2024-08-04T07:44:50.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11119|2024-08-04T11:21:14.640Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11119</link>
      <description>Buffer over-read can happen when the buffer length received from response handlers is more than the size of the payload in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11119|2024-08-04T11:21:14.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 09:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11296|2024-08-04T11:28:13.857Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11296</link>
      <description>Arithmetic overflow can happen while processing NOA IE due to improper error handling in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11296|2024-08-04T11:28:13.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 06:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11212|2024-08-04T11:28:13.406Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11212</link>
      <description>Out of bounds reads while parsing NAN beacons attributes and OUIs due to improper length of field check in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11212|2024-08-04T11:28:13.406Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 09:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2321|2024-08-04T18:49:46.410Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2321</link>
      <description>Incorrect length used while validating the qsee log buffer sent from HLOS which could then lead to remap conflict in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096, APQ8096AU, APQ8098, IPQ4019, IPQ8074, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9207C, MDM9607, MDM9650, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8909W, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8939, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, QCA8081, QCS404, QCS605, QM215, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX24, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, Snapdragon_High_Med_2016, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2321|2024-08-04T18:49:46.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 08:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11235|2024-08-04T11:28:13.379Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11235</link>
      <description>Buffer overflow might occur while parsing unified command due to lack of check of input data received in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11235|2024-08-04T11:28:13.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 05:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2275|2024-08-04T18:42:51.125Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2275</link>
      <description>While deserializing any key blob during key operations, buffer overflow could occur exposing partial key information if any key operations are invoked(Depends on CVE-2018-13907) in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon IoT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wearables, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9650, MSM8909W, MSM8996AU, QCS404, QCS605, Qualcomm 215, SD 210/SD 212/SD 205, SD 410/12, SD 425, SD 427, SD 430, SD 435, SD 439 / SD 429, SD 450, SD 625, SD 632, SD 636, SD 650/52, SD 712 / SD 710 / SD 670, SD 820, SD 820A, SD 835, SD 845 / SD 850, SD 855, SD 8CX, SDA660, SDM439, SDM630, SDM660, Snapdragon_High_Med_2016, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2275|2024-08-04T18:42:51.125Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 17:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
