<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qualcomm%2C%20inc./snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20a.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 18:24:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14119|2024-08-05T00:12:42.511Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14119</link>
      <description>u'While processing SMCInvoke asynchronous message header, message count is modified leading to a TOCTOU race condition and lead to memory corruption' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in IPQ6018, Kamorta, MDM9205, MDM9607, Nicobar, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, QCS610, Rennell, SA415M, SA515M, SA6155P, SC7180, SC8180X, SDM670, SDM710, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14119|2024-08-05T00:12:42.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14116|2024-08-05T00:12:42.575Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14116</link>
      <description>Privilege escalation by using an altered debug policy image can occur as the XPU protecting the debug policy regions are disabled during the crash dump boot flow in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in IPQ6018</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14116|2024-08-05T00:12:42.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 10:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14077|2024-08-05T00:12:42.201Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14077</link>
      <description>Out of bound memory access while processing ese transmit command due to passing Response buffer received from user in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8098, IPQ6018, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9607, MDM9650, MSM8909, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, Rennell, SA415M, SA6155P, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM630, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14077|2024-08-05T00:12:42.201Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 15:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14076|2024-08-05T00:12:42.167Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14076</link>
      <description>Buffer overflow occurs while processing an subsample data length out of range due to lack of user input validation in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8009, APQ8098, Kamorta, MDM9150, MDM9205, MDM9206, MDM9607, MDM9650, MSM8905, MSM8909, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, Rennell, SA415M, SC7180, SC8180X, SDA845, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14076|2024-08-05T00:12:42.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14071|2024-08-05T00:12:42.152Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile%2C%20snapdragon%20voice%20%26%20music%2C%20snapdragon%20wired%20infrastructure%20a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14071</link>
      <description>Compromised reset handler may bypass access control due to AC config is being reset if debug path is enabled to collect secure or non-secure ram dumps in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile, Snapdragon Voice &amp; Music, Snapdragon Wired Infrastructure and Networking in APQ8017, APQ8053, APQ8096, APQ8096AU, IPQ6018, MDM9205, MSM8917, MSM8920, MSM8937, MSM8940, MSM8953, MSM8996, MSM8996AU, MSM8998, Nicobar, QCM2150, QCS404, QCS405, QCS605, QM215, Rennell, SA6155P, SC8180X, SDA660, SDA845, SDM429, SDM439, SDM450, SDM630, SDM632, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14071|2024-08-05T00:12:42.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 08:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
