<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qualcomm%2C%20inc./snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 08:24:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14086|2024-08-05T00:12:42.450Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14086</link>
      <description>Possible integer overflow while checking the length of frame which is a 32 bit integer and is added to another 32 bit integer which can lead to unexpected result during the check in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile in APQ8098, MDM9607, MSM8998, QCA6584, QCN7605, QCS605, SDA660, SDM630, SDM636, SDM660, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14086|2024-08-05T00:12:42.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 08:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14085|2024-08-05T00:12:42.171Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20electronics%20connectivity%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14085</link>
      <description>Possible Integer underflow in WLAN function due to lack of check of data received from user side in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer Electronics Connectivity, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile in QCN7605, QCS605, SDA845, SDM670, SDM710, SDM845, SDM850, SM8150, SXR1130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14085|2024-08-05T00:12:42.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 08:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
