<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qualcomm%2C%20inc./snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3692|2024-08-04T07:44:50.194Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3692</link>
      <description>u'Possible buffer overflow while updating output buffer for IMEI and Gateway Address due to lack of check of input validation for parameters received from server' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile in Agatti, Kamorta, Nicobar, QCM6125, QCS610, Rennell, SA415M, Saipan, SC7180, SC8180X, SDX24, SDX55, SM6150, SM7150, SM8150, SM8250, SXR2130</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3692|2024-08-04T07:44:50.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 06:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11201|2024-08-04T11:28:13.600Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11201</link>
      <description>Arbitrary access to DSP memory due to improper check in loaded library for data received from CPU side' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile in QCM6125, QCS410, QCS603, QCS605, QCS610, QCS6125, SA6145P, SA6155, SA6155P, SA8155, SA8155P, SDA640, SDA845, SDM640, SDM830, SDM845, SDX50M, SDX55, SDX55M, SM6125, SM6150, SM6250, SM6250P, SM7125, SM7150, SM7150P, SM8150, SM8150P</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11201|2024-08-04T11:28:13.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 10:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11206|2024-08-04T11:28:13.377Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11206</link>
      <description>Possible buffer overflow in Fastrpc while handling received parameters due to lack of validation on input parameters' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile in APQ8098, MSM8998, QCM4290, QCM6125, QCS410, QCS4290, QCS610, QCS6125, QSM8250, QSM8350, SA6145P, SA6150P, SA6155, SA6155P, SA8150P, SA8155, SA8155P, SA8195P, SC7180, SDA640, SDA660, SDA845, SDA855, SDM640, SDM660, SDM830, SDM845, SDM850, SDX50M, SDX55, SDX55M, SM4250, SM4250P, SM6115, SM6115P, SM6125, SM6150, SM6150P, SM6250, SM6250P, SM6350, SM7125, SM7150, SM7150P, SM7225, SM7250, SM7250P, SM8150, SM8150P, SM8250, SM8350, SM8350P, SXR2130, SXR2130P</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11206|2024-08-04T11:28:13.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 10:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11207|2024-08-04T11:28:13.402Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11207</link>
      <description>Buffer overflow in LibFastCV library due to improper size checks with respect to buffer length' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile in APQ8052, APQ8056, APQ8076, APQ8096, APQ8096SG, APQ8098, MDM9655, MSM8952, MSM8956, MSM8976, MSM8976SG, MSM8996, MSM8996SG, MSM8998, QCM4290, QCM6125, QCS410, QCS4290, QCS610, QCS6125, QSM8250, SA6145P, SA6150P, SA6155, SA6155P, SA8150P, SA8155, SA8155P, SA8195P, SC7180, SDA640, SDA660, SDA845, SDA855, SDM640, SDM660, SDM830, SDM845, SDM850, SDX50M, SDX55, SDX55M, SM4250, SM4250P, SM6115, SM6115P, SM6125, SM6150, SM6150P, SM6250, SM6250P, SM6350, SM7125, SM7150, SM7150P, SM7225, SM7250, SM7250P, SM8150, SM8150P, SM8250, SXR2130, SXR2130P</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11207|2024-08-04T11:28:13.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 10:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11202|2024-08-04T11:28:13.386Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20consumer%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11202</link>
      <description>Buffer overflow/underflow occurs when typecasting the buffer passed by CPU internally in the library which is not aligned with the actual size of the structure' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Consumer IOT, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile in QCM6125, QCS410, QCS603, QCS605, QCS610, QCS6125, SA6145P, SA6155, SA6155P, SA8155, SA8155P, SDA640, SDA670, SDA845, SDM640, SDM670, SDM710, SDM830, SDM845, SDX50M, SDX55, SDX55M, SM6125, SM6150, SM6150P, SM6250, SM6250P, SM7125, SM7150, SM7150P, SM8150, SM8150P</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11202|2024-08-04T11:28:13.386Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 10:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
