<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qualcomm%2C%20inc./snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Qualcomm, Inc. -- Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 17:21:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11184|2024-08-04T11:28:13.313Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11184</link>
      <description>u'Possible buffer overflow will occur in video while parsing mp4 clip with crafted esds atom size.' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile in QCM4290, QCS4290, QM215, QSM8350, SA6145P, SA6155, SA6155P, SA8155, SA8155P, SDX55, SDX55M, SM4250, SM4250P, SM6115, SM6115P, SM6125, SM6250, SM6350, SM7125, SM7225, SM7250, SM7250P, SM8150, SM8150P, SM8250, SM8350, SM8350P, SXR2130, SXR2130P</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11184|2024-08-04T11:28:13.313Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 10:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11130|2024-08-04T11:21:14.678Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11130</link>
      <description>u'Possible buffer overflow in WIFI hal process due to copying data without checking the buffer length' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile in QCM4290, QCS4290, QM215, QSM8350, SA6145P, SA6155, SA6155P, SA8155, SA8155P, SC8180X, SC8180XP, SDX55, SDX55M, SM4250, SM4250P, SM6115, SM6115P, SM6125, SM6250, SM6350, SM7125, SM7225, SM7250, SM7250P, SM8150, SM8150P, SM8250, SM8350, SM8350P, SXR2130, SXR2130P</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11130|2024-08-04T11:21:14.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 10:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11121|2024-08-04T11:21:14.614Z -- qualcomm%2C%20inc. -- snapdragon%20auto%2C%20snapdragon%20compute%2C%20snapdragon%20industrial%20iot%2C%20snapdragon%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11121</link>
      <description>u'Possible buffer overflow in WIFI hal process due to usage of memcpy without checking length of destination buffer' in Snapdragon Auto, Snapdragon Compute, Snapdragon Industrial IOT, Snapdragon Mobile in QCM4290, QCS4290, QM215, QSM8350, SA6145P, SA6155, SA6155P, SA8155, SA8155P, SC8180X, SC8180XP, SDX55, SDX55M, SM4250, SM4250P, SM6115, SM6115P, SM6125, SM6250, SM6350, SM7125, SM7225, SM7250, SM7250P, SM8150, SM8150P, SM8250, SM8350, SM8350P, SXR2130, SXR2130P</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11121|2024-08-04T11:21:14.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 10:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
