<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:45:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14997|2024-08-05T00:34:53.000Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14997</link>
      <description>The AccessLogFilter class in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote anonymous attackers to learn details about other users, including their username, via an information expose through caching vulnerability when Jira is configured with a reverse Proxy and or a load balancer with caching or a CDN.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14997|2024-08-05T00:34:53.000Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15013|2024-08-05T00:34:53.218Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15013</link>
      <description>The WorkflowResource class removeStatus method in Jira before version 7.13.12, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.4.3, and from version 8.5.0 before version 8.5.2 allows authenticated remote attackers who do not have project administration access to remove a configured issue status from a project via a missing authorisation check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15013|2024-08-05T00:34:53.218Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15005|2024-08-05T00:34:53.099Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15005</link>
      <description>The Atlassian Troubleshooting and Support Tools plugin prior to version 1.17.2 allows an unprivileged user to initiate periodic log scans and send the results to a user-specified email address due to a missing authorization check. The email message may contain configuration information about the application that the plugin is installed into. A vulnerable version of the plugin is included with Bitbucket Server / Data Center before 6.6.0, Confluence Server / Data Center before 7.0.1, Jira Server / Data Center before 8.3.2, Crowd / Crowd Data Center before 3.6.0, Fisheye before 4.7.2, Crucible before 4.7.2, and Bamboo before 6.10.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15005|2024-08-05T00:34:53.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15010|2024-08-05T00:34:53.027Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15010</link>
      <description>Bitbucket Server and Bitbucket Data Center versions starting from version 3.0.0 before version 5.16.11, from version 6.0.0 before 6.0.11, from version 6.1.0 before 6.1.9, from version 6.2.0 before 6.2.7, from version 6.3.0 before 6.3.6, from version 6.4.0 before 6.4.4, from version 6.5.0 before 6.5.3, from version 6.6.0 before 6.6.3, from version 6.7.0 before 6.7.3, from version 6.8.0 before 6.8.2, and from version 6.9.0 before 6.9.1 had a Remote Code Execution vulnerability via certain user input fields. A remote attacker with user level permissions can exploit this vulnerability to run arbitrary commands on the victim's systems. Using a specially crafted payload as user input, the attacker can execute arbitrary commands on the victim's Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15010|2024-08-05T00:34:53.027Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15008|2024-08-05T00:34:53.154Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15008</link>
      <description>The /plugins/servlet/branchreview resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.7.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the reviewedBranch parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15008|2024-08-05T00:34:53.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14995|2024-08-05T00:34:53.143Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14995</link>
      <description>The /rest/api/1.0/render resource in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote anonymous attackers to determine if an attachment with a specific name exists and if an issue key is valid via a missing permissions check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14995|2024-08-05T00:34:53.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15007|2024-08-05T00:34:52.856Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15007</link>
      <description>The review resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.7.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the name of a missing branch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15007|2024-08-05T00:34:52.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14998|2024-08-05T00:34:53.105Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14998</link>
      <description>The Webwork action Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) protection implementation in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote attackers to bypass its protection via "cookie tossing" a CSRF cookie from a subdomain of a Jira instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14998|2024-08-05T00:34:53.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14999|2024-08-05T00:34:53.081Z -- atlassian -- universal%20plugin%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14999</link>
      <description>The Uninstall REST endpoint in Atlassian Universal Plugin Manager before version 2.22.19, from version 3.0.0 before version 3.0.3 and from version 4.0.0 before version 4.0.3 allows remote attackers to uninstall plugins using a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability on an authenticated administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14999|2024-08-05T00:34:53.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14996|2024-08-05T00:34:53.093Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14996</link>
      <description>The FilterPickerPopup.jspa resource in Jira before version 7.13.7, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.3.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the searchOwnerUserName parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14996|2024-08-05T00:34:53.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15000|2024-08-05T00:34:52.974Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15000</link>
      <description>The commit diff rest endpoint in Bitbucket Server and Data Center before 5.16.10 (the fixed version for 5.16.x ), from 6.0.0 before 6.0.10 (the fixed version for 6.0.x), from 6.1.0 before 6.1.8 (the fixed version for 6.1.x), from 6.2.0 before 6.2.6 (the fixed version for 6.2.x), from 6.3.0 before 6.3.5 (the fixed version for 6.3.x), from 6.4.0 before 6.4.3 (the fixed version for 6.4.x), and from 6.5.0 before 6.5.2 (the fixed version for 6.5.x) allows remote attackers who have permission to access a repository, if public access is enabled for a project or repository then attackers are able to exploit this issue anonymously, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the system and execute commands via injecting additional arguments into git commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15000|2024-08-05T00:34:52.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15003|2024-08-05T00:34:53.128Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20desk%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15003</link>
      <description>The Customer Context Filter in Atlassian Jira Service Desk Server and Jira Service Desk Data Center before 3.9.17, from 3.10.0 before 3.16.10, from 4.0.0 before 4.2.6, from 4.3.0 before 4.3.5, from 4.4.0 before 4.4.3, and from 4.5.0 before 4.5.1 allows remote attackers with portal access to view arbitrary issues in Jira Service Desk projects via authorization bypass. Note that when the 'Anyone can email the service desk or raise a request in the portal' setting is enabled, an attacker can grant themselves portal access, allowing them to exploit the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15003|2024-08-05T00:34:53.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14994|2024-08-05T00:34:52.769Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20desk%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14994</link>
      <description>The Customer Context Filter in Atlassian Jira Service Desk Server and Jira Service Desk Data Center before version 3.9.16, from version 3.10.0 before version 3.16.8, from version 4.0.0 before version 4.1.3, from version 4.2.0 before version 4.2.5, from version 4.3.0 before version 4.3.4, and version 4.4.0 allows remote attackers with portal access to view arbitrary issues in Jira Service Desk projects via a path traversal vulnerability. Note that when the 'Anyone can email the service desk or raise a request in the portal' setting is enabled, an attacker can grant themselves portal access, allowing them to exploit the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14994|2024-08-05T00:34:52.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15012|2024-08-05T00:34:53.124Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15012</link>
      <description>Bitbucket Server and Bitbucket Data Center from version 4.13. before 5.16.11, from version 6.0.0 before 6.0.11, from version 6.1.0 before 6.1.9, from version 6.2.0 before 6.2.7, from version 6.3.0 before 6.3.6, from version 6.4.0 before 6.4.4, from version 6.5.0 before 6.5.3, from version 6.6.0 before 6.6.3, from version 6.7.0 before 6.7.3, from version 6.8.0 before 6.8.2, from version 6.9.0 before 6.9.1 had a Remote Code Execution vulnerability via the edit-file request. A remote attacker with write permission on a repository can write to any arbitrary file to the victims Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center instance using the edit-file endpoint, if the user has Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center running, and has the permission to write the file at that destination. In some cases, this can result in execution of arbitrary code by the victims Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15012|2024-08-05T00:34:53.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15011|2024-08-05T00:34:53.139Z -- atlassian -- application%20links
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15011</link>
      <description>The ListEntityLinksServlet resource in Application Links before version 5.0.12, from version 5.1.0 before version 5.2.11, from version 5.3.0 before version 5.3.7, from version 5.4.0 before 5.4.13, and from version 6.0.0 before 6.0.5 disclosed application link information to non-admin users via a missing permissions check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15011|2024-08-05T00:34:53.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15004|2024-08-05T00:34:52.994Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20desk%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15004</link>
      <description>The Customer Context Filter in Atlassian Jira Service Desk Server and Jira Service Desk Data Center before 3.9.17, from 3.10.0 before 3.16.10, from 4.0.0 before 4.2.6, from 4.3.0 before 4.3.5, from 4.4.0 before 4.4.3, and from 4.5.0 before 4.5.1 allows remote attackers with portal access to view arbitrary issues in Jira Service Desk projects via a path traversal vulnerability. Note that when the 'Anyone can email the service desk or raise a request in the portal' setting is enabled, an attacker can grant themselves portal access, allowing them to exploit the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15004|2024-08-05T00:34:52.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15006|2024-08-05T00:34:53.000Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15006</link>
      <description>There was a man-in-the-middle (MITM) vulnerability present in the Confluence Previews plugin in Confluence Server and Confluence Data Center. This plugin was used to facilitate communication with the Atlassian Companion application. The Confluence Previews plugin in Confluence Server and Confluence Data Center communicated with the Companion application via the atlassian-domain-for-localhost-connections-only.com domain name, the DNS A record of which points at 127.0.0.1. Additionally, a signed certificate for the domain was publicly distributed with the Companion application. An attacker in the position to control DNS resolution of their victim could carry out a man-in-the-middle (MITM) attack between Confluence Server (or Confluence Data Center) and the atlassian-domain-for-localhost-connections-only.com domain intended to be used with the Companion application. This certificate has been revoked, however, usage of the atlassian-domain-for-localhost-connections-only.com domain name was still present in Confluence Server and Confluence Data Center. An attacker could perform the described attack by denying their victim access to certificate revocation information, and carry out a man-in-the-middle (MITM) attack to observe files being edited using the Companion application and/or modify them, and access some limited user information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15006|2024-08-05T00:34:53.000Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15009|2024-08-05T00:34:53.014Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15009</link>
      <description>The /json/profile/removeStarAjax.do resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.0 allows remote attackers to remove another user's favourite setting for a project via an improper authorization vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15009|2024-08-05T00:34:53.014Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15001|2024-08-05T00:34:52.905Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15001</link>
      <description>The Jira Importers Plugin in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Cente from version with 7.0.10 before 7.6.16, from 7.7.0 before 7.13.8, from 8.0.0 before 8.1.3, from 8.2.0 before 8.2.5, from 8.3.0 before 8.3.4 and from 8.4.0 before 8.4.1 allows remote attackers with Administrator permissions to gain remote code execution via a template injection vulnerability through the use of a crafted PUT request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15001|2024-08-05T00:34:52.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T07:52:01.198Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T07:52:01.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21684|2024-07-24T18:45:23.880Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21684</link>
      <description>There is a low severity open redirect vulnerability within affected versions of Bitbucket Data Center. Versions of Bitbucket DC from 8.0.0 to 8.9.12 and 8.19.0 to 8.19.1 are affected by this vulnerability. It is patched in 8.9.13 and 8.19.2.

This open redirect vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 3.1 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect a victim user upon login to Bitbucket Data Center to any arbitrary site which can be utilized for further exploitation which has low impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center customers upgrade to the version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the  supported fixed versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21684|2024-07-24T18:45:23.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-17T15:27:45.652Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-17T15:27:45.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-26T17:43:55.994Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-26T17:43:55.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-18T17:00:02.531Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-18T17:00:02.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-06-10T17:30:00.572Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-06-10T17:30:00.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21682|2024-02-20T18:00:00.699Z -- atlassian -- assets%20discovery%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21682</link>
      <description>This High severity Injection vulnerability was introduced in Assets Discovery 1.0 - 6.2.0 (all versions). 

Assets Discovery, which can be downloaded via Atlassian Marketplace, is a network scanning tool that can be used with or without an agent with Jira Service Management Cloud, Data Center or Server. It detects hardware and software that is connected to your local network and extracts detailed information about each asset. This data can then be imported into Assets in Jira Service Management to help you manage all of the devices and configuration items within your local network.

This Injection vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to modify the actions taken by a system call which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Assets Discovery customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/assetapps/assets-discovery-3-2-1-cloud-6-2-1-data_center-1333987182.html). You can download the latest version of Assets Discovery from the Atlassian Marketplace (https://marketplace.atlassian.com/apps/1214668/assets-discovery?hosting=datacenter&amp;amp;tab=installation).

This vulnerability was reported via our Penetration Testing program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21682|2024-02-20T18:00:00.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21677|2024-03-19T17:30:00.500Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21677</link>
      <description>This High severity Path Traversal vulnerability was introduced in version 6.13.0 of Confluence Data Center. This Path Traversal vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.3, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit an undefinable vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions: Data Center Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version and that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version.

If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives. 

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21677|2024-03-19T17:30:00.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21678|2024-06-04T17:38:08.576Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21678</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in version 2.7.0 of Confluence Data Center.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.5, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, low impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.
Data Center

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.7.0 to 8.7.1|8.8.0 recommended or 8.7.2|
|from 8.6.0 to 8.6.1|8.8.0 recommended|
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
Server

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:

 
||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS recommended |
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|

See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html]). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives]).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21678|2024-06-04T17:38:08.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21677|2024-06-21T18:07:46.098Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21677</link>
      <description>This High severity Path Traversal vulnerability was introduced in version 6.13.0 of Confluence Data Center. This Path Traversal vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.3, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit an undefinable vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions: Data Center Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version and that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version.

If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives. 

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21677|2024-06-21T18:07:46.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21686|2024-07-16T20:00:02.617Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21686</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.13 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.3, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21686|2024-07-16T20:00:02.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-16T20:30:00.385Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-16T20:30:00.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-20T03:55:33.558Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-20T03:55:33.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T06:47:39.038Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T06:47:39.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21684|2024-08-01T22:27:36.150Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21684</link>
      <description>There is a low severity open redirect vulnerability within affected versions of Bitbucket Data Center. Versions of Bitbucket DC from 8.0.0 to 8.9.12 and 8.19.0 to 8.19.1 are affected by this vulnerability. It is patched in 8.9.13 and 8.19.2.

This open redirect vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 3.1 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect a victim user upon login to Bitbucket Data Center to any arbitrary site which can be utilized for further exploitation which has low impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center customers upgrade to the version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the  supported fixed versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21684|2024-08-01T22:27:36.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-08-01T22:27:36.035Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-08-01T22:27:36.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21682|2024-08-01T22:27:35.986Z -- atlassian -- assets%20discovery%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21682</link>
      <description>This High severity Injection vulnerability was introduced in Assets Discovery 1.0 - 6.2.0 (all versions). 

Assets Discovery, which can be downloaded via Atlassian Marketplace, is a network scanning tool that can be used with or without an agent with Jira Service Management Cloud, Data Center or Server. It detects hardware and software that is connected to your local network and extracts detailed information about each asset. This data can then be imported into Assets in Jira Service Management to help you manage all of the devices and configuration items within your local network.

This Injection vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to modify the actions taken by a system call which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Assets Discovery customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/assetapps/assets-discovery-3-2-1-cloud-6-2-1-data_center-1333987182.html). You can download the latest version of Assets Discovery from the Atlassian Marketplace (https://marketplace.atlassian.com/apps/1214668/assets-discovery?hosting=datacenter&amp;amp;tab=installation).

This vulnerability was reported via our Penetration Testing program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21682|2024-08-01T22:27:35.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21677|2024-08-01T22:27:35.969Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21677</link>
      <description>This High severity Path Traversal vulnerability was introduced in version 6.13.0 of Confluence Data Center. This Path Traversal vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.3, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit an undefinable vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions: Data Center Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version and that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version.

If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives. 

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21677|2024-08-01T22:27:35.969Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-08-01T22:27:35.803Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-08-01T22:27:35.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21678|2024-08-01T22:27:35.810Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21678</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in version 2.7.0 of Confluence Data Center.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.5, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, low impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.
Data Center

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.7.0 to 8.7.1|8.8.0 recommended or 8.7.2|
|from 8.6.0 to 8.6.1|8.8.0 recommended|
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
Server

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:

 
||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS recommended |
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|

See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html]). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives]).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21678|2024-08-01T22:27:35.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-08-01T22:27:36.189Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-08-01T22:27:36.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21686|2024-08-01T22:27:36.033Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21686</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.13 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.3, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21686|2024-08-01T22:27:36.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
