<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 12:25:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36803|2024-08-03T10:14:28.492Z -- atlassian -- jira%20align
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36803</link>
      <description>The MasterUserEdit API in Atlassian Jira Align Server before version 10.109.2 allows An authenticated attacker with the People role permission to use the MasterUserEdit API to modify any users role to Super Admin. This vulnerability was reported by Jacob Shafer from Bishop Fox.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36803|2024-08-03T10:14:28.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26136|2024-08-03T04:56:37.592Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26136</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in multiple Atlassian products allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to bypass Servlet Filters used by first and third party apps. The impact depends on which filters are used by each app, and how the filters are used. This vulnerability can result in authentication bypass and cross-site scripting. Atlassian has released updates that fix the root cause of this vulnerability, but has not exhaustively enumerated all potential consequences of this vulnerability. Atlassian Bamboo versions are affected before 8.0.9, from 8.1.0 before 8.1.8, and from 8.2.0 before 8.2.4. Atlassian Bitbucket versions are affected before 7.6.16, from 7.7.0 before 7.17.8, from 7.18.0 before 7.19.5, from 7.20.0 before 7.20.2, from 7.21.0 before 7.21.2, and versions 8.0.0 and 8.1.0. Atlassian Confluence versions are affected before 7.4.17, from 7.5.0 before 7.13.7, from 7.14.0 before 7.14.3, from 7.15.0 before 7.15.2, from 7.16.0 before 7.16.4, from 7.17.0 before 7.17.4, and version 7.21.0. Atlassian Crowd versions are affected before 4.3.8, from 4.4.0 before 4.4.2, and version 5.0.0. Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible versions before 4.8.10 are affected. Atlassian Jira versions are affected before 8.13.22, from 8.14.0 before 8.20.10, and from 8.21.0 before 8.22.4. Atlassian Jira Service Management versions are affected before 4.13.22, from 4.14.0 before 4.20.10, and from 4.21.0 before 4.22.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26136|2024-08-03T04:56:37.592Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36802|2024-08-03T10:14:28.397Z -- atlassian -- jira%20align
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36802</link>
      <description>The ManageJiraConnectors API in Atlassian Jira Align before version 10.109.2 allows remote attackers to exploit this issue to access internal network resources via a Server-Side Request Forgery. This can be exploited by a remote, unauthenticated attacker with Super Admin privileges by sending a specially crafted HTTP request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36802|2024-08-03T10:14:28.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26134|2024-08-03T04:56:37.787Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26134</link>
      <description>In affected versions of Confluence Server and Data Center, an OGNL injection vulnerability exists that would allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on a Confluence Server or Data Center instance. The affected versions are from 1.3.0 before 7.4.17, from 7.13.0 before 7.13.7, from 7.14.0 before 7.14.3, from 7.15.0 before 7.15.2, from 7.16.0 before 7.16.4, from 7.17.0 before 7.17.4, and from 7.18.0 before 7.18.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26134|2024-08-03T04:56:37.787Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36800|2024-08-03T10:14:28.408Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36800</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow remote attackers without the "Browse Users" permission to view groups via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the browsegroups.action endpoint. The affected versions are before version 4.22.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36800|2024-08-03T10:14:28.408Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36799|2024-08-03T10:14:28.495Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36799</link>
      <description>This issue exists to document that a security improvement in the way that Jira Server and Data Center use templates has been implemented. Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allowed remote attackers with system administrator permissions to execute arbitrary code via Template Injection leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE) in the Email Templates feature. In this case the security improvement was to protect against using the XStream library to be able to execute arbitrary code in velocity templates. The affected versions are before version 8.13.19, from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.7, and from version 8.21.0 before 8.22.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36799|2024-08-03T10:14:28.495Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36804|2024-08-03T10:14:28.471Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36804</link>
      <description>Multiple API endpoints in Atlassian Bitbucket Server and Data Center 7.0.0 before version 7.6.17, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.17.10, from version 7.18.0 before version 7.21.4, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.3, from version 8.1.0 before version 8.1.3, and from version 8.2.0 before version 8.2.2, and from version 8.3.0 before 8.3.1 allows remote attackers with read permissions to a public or private Bitbucket repository to execute arbitrary code by sending a malicious HTTP request. This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty Program by TheGrandPew.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36804|2024-08-03T10:14:28.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26138|2024-08-03T04:56:37.662Z -- atlassian -- questions%20for%20confluence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26138</link>
      <description>The Atlassian Questions For Confluence app for Confluence Server and Data Center creates a Confluence user account in the confluence-users group with the username disabledsystemuser and a hardcoded password. A remote, unauthenticated attacker with knowledge of the hardcoded password could exploit this to log into Confluence and access all content accessible to users in the confluence-users group. This user account is created when installing versions 2.7.34, 2.7.35, and 3.0.2 of the app.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26138|2024-08-03T04:56:37.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36801|2024-08-03T10:14:28.388Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36801</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (RXSS) vulnerability in the TeamManagement.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.20.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36801|2024-08-03T10:14:28.388Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26135|2024-08-03T04:56:37.610Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26135</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Mobile Plugin for Jira Data Center and Server allows a remote, authenticated user (including a user who joined via the sign-up feature) to perform a full read server-side request forgery via a batch endpoint. This affects Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center from version 8.0.0 before version 8.13.22, from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.10, from version 8.21.0 before 8.22.4. This also affects Jira Management Server and Data Center versions from version 4.0.0 before 4.13.22, from version 4.14.0 before 4.20.10 and from version 4.21.0 before 4.22.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26135|2024-08-03T04:56:37.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26133|2024-08-03T04:56:37.656Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26133</link>
      <description>SharedSecretClusterAuthenticator in Atlassian Bitbucket Data Center versions 5.14.0 and later before 7.6.14, 7.7.0 and later prior to 7.17.6, 7.18.0 and later prior to 7.18.4, 7.19.0 and later prior to 7.19.4, and 7.20.0 allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code via Java deserialization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26133|2024-08-03T04:56:37.656Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26137|2024-08-03T04:56:37.614Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26137</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in multiple Atlassian products allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to cause additional Servlet Filters to be invoked when the application processes requests or responses. Atlassian has confirmed and fixed the only known security issue associated with this vulnerability: Cross-origin resource sharing (CORS) bypass. Sending a specially crafted HTTP request can invoke the Servlet Filter used to respond to CORS requests, resulting in a CORS bypass. An attacker that can trick a user into requesting a malicious URL can access the vulnerable application with the victim’s permissions. Atlassian Bamboo versions are affected before 8.0.9, from 8.1.0 before 8.1.8, and from 8.2.0 before 8.2.4. Atlassian Bitbucket versions are affected before 7.6.16, from 7.7.0 before 7.17.8, from 7.18.0 before 7.19.5, from 7.20.0 before 7.20.2, from 7.21.0 before 7.21.2, and versions 8.0.0 and 8.1.0. Atlassian Confluence versions are affected before 7.4.17, from 7.5.0 before 7.13.7, from 7.14.0 before 7.14.3, from 7.15.0 before 7.15.2, from 7.16.0 before 7.16.4, from 7.17.0 before 7.17.4, and version 7.21.0. Atlassian Crowd versions are affected before 4.3.8, from 4.4.0 before 4.4.2, and version 5.0.0. Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible versions before 4.8.10 are affected. Atlassian Jira versions are affected before 8.13.22, from 8.14.0 before 8.20.10, and from 8.21.0 before 8.22.4. Atlassian Jira Service Management versions are affected before 4.13.22, from 4.14.0 before 4.20.10, and from 4.21.0 before 4.22.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26137|2024-08-03T04:56:37.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T07:52:01.198Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T07:52:01.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21684|2024-07-24T18:45:23.880Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21684</link>
      <description>There is a low severity open redirect vulnerability within affected versions of Bitbucket Data Center. Versions of Bitbucket DC from 8.0.0 to 8.9.12 and 8.19.0 to 8.19.1 are affected by this vulnerability. It is patched in 8.9.13 and 8.19.2.

This open redirect vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 3.1 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect a victim user upon login to Bitbucket Data Center to any arbitrary site which can be utilized for further exploitation which has low impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center customers upgrade to the version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the  supported fixed versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21684|2024-07-24T18:45:23.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-17T15:27:45.652Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-17T15:27:45.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-26T17:43:55.994Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-26T17:43:55.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-18T17:00:02.531Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-18T17:00:02.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-06-10T17:30:00.572Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-06-10T17:30:00.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21682|2024-02-20T18:00:00.699Z -- atlassian -- assets%20discovery%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21682</link>
      <description>This High severity Injection vulnerability was introduced in Assets Discovery 1.0 - 6.2.0 (all versions). 

Assets Discovery, which can be downloaded via Atlassian Marketplace, is a network scanning tool that can be used with or without an agent with Jira Service Management Cloud, Data Center or Server. It detects hardware and software that is connected to your local network and extracts detailed information about each asset. This data can then be imported into Assets in Jira Service Management to help you manage all of the devices and configuration items within your local network.

This Injection vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to modify the actions taken by a system call which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Assets Discovery customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/assetapps/assets-discovery-3-2-1-cloud-6-2-1-data_center-1333987182.html). You can download the latest version of Assets Discovery from the Atlassian Marketplace (https://marketplace.atlassian.com/apps/1214668/assets-discovery?hosting=datacenter&amp;amp;tab=installation).

This vulnerability was reported via our Penetration Testing program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21682|2024-02-20T18:00:00.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21677|2024-03-19T17:30:00.500Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21677</link>
      <description>This High severity Path Traversal vulnerability was introduced in version 6.13.0 of Confluence Data Center. This Path Traversal vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.3, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit an undefinable vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions: Data Center Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version and that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version.

If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives. 

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21677|2024-03-19T17:30:00.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21678|2024-06-04T17:38:08.576Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21678</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in version 2.7.0 of Confluence Data Center.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.5, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, low impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.
Data Center

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.7.0 to 8.7.1|8.8.0 recommended or 8.7.2|
|from 8.6.0 to 8.6.1|8.8.0 recommended|
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
Server

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:

 
||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS recommended |
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|

See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html]). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives]).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21678|2024-06-04T17:38:08.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21677|2024-06-21T18:07:46.098Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21677</link>
      <description>This High severity Path Traversal vulnerability was introduced in version 6.13.0 of Confluence Data Center. This Path Traversal vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.3, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit an undefinable vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions: Data Center Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version and that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version.

If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives. 

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21677|2024-06-21T18:07:46.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21686|2024-07-16T20:00:02.617Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21686</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.13 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.3, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21686|2024-07-16T20:00:02.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-16T20:30:00.385Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-16T20:30:00.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-20T03:55:33.558Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-20T03:55:33.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T06:47:39.038Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T06:47:39.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21684|2024-08-01T22:27:36.150Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21684</link>
      <description>There is a low severity open redirect vulnerability within affected versions of Bitbucket Data Center. Versions of Bitbucket DC from 8.0.0 to 8.9.12 and 8.19.0 to 8.19.1 are affected by this vulnerability. It is patched in 8.9.13 and 8.19.2.

This open redirect vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 3.1 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect a victim user upon login to Bitbucket Data Center to any arbitrary site which can be utilized for further exploitation which has low impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center customers upgrade to the version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the  supported fixed versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21684|2024-08-01T22:27:36.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-08-01T22:27:36.035Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-08-01T22:27:36.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21682|2024-08-01T22:27:35.986Z -- atlassian -- assets%20discovery%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21682</link>
      <description>This High severity Injection vulnerability was introduced in Assets Discovery 1.0 - 6.2.0 (all versions). 

Assets Discovery, which can be downloaded via Atlassian Marketplace, is a network scanning tool that can be used with or without an agent with Jira Service Management Cloud, Data Center or Server. It detects hardware and software that is connected to your local network and extracts detailed information about each asset. This data can then be imported into Assets in Jira Service Management to help you manage all of the devices and configuration items within your local network.

This Injection vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to modify the actions taken by a system call which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Assets Discovery customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/assetapps/assets-discovery-3-2-1-cloud-6-2-1-data_center-1333987182.html). You can download the latest version of Assets Discovery from the Atlassian Marketplace (https://marketplace.atlassian.com/apps/1214668/assets-discovery?hosting=datacenter&amp;amp;tab=installation).

This vulnerability was reported via our Penetration Testing program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21682|2024-08-01T22:27:35.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21677|2024-08-01T22:27:35.969Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21677</link>
      <description>This High severity Path Traversal vulnerability was introduced in version 6.13.0 of Confluence Data Center. This Path Traversal vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.3, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit an undefinable vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions: Data Center Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version and that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version.

If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives. 

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21677|2024-08-01T22:27:35.969Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-08-01T22:27:35.803Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-08-01T22:27:35.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21678|2024-08-01T22:27:35.810Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21678</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in version 2.7.0 of Confluence Data Center.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.5, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, low impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.
Data Center

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.7.0 to 8.7.1|8.8.0 recommended or 8.7.2|
|from 8.6.0 to 8.6.1|8.8.0 recommended|
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
Server

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:

 
||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS recommended |
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|

See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html]). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives]).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21678|2024-08-01T22:27:35.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-08-01T22:27:36.189Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-08-01T22:27:36.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21686|2024-08-01T22:27:36.033Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21686</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.13 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.3, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21686|2024-08-01T22:27:36.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
