<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 22:22:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4015|2024-09-16T18:09:13.525Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4015</link>
      <description>The /json/fe/activeUserFinder.do resource in Altassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.1 allows remote attackers to view user user email addresses via a information disclosure vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4015|2024-09-16T18:09:13.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 06:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4016|2024-09-16T16:49:09.315Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4016</link>
      <description>The /plugins/servlet/jira-blockers/ resource in the crucible-jira-ril plugin in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.1 allows remote attackers to get the ID of configured Jira application links via an information disclosure vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4016|2024-09-16T16:49:09.315Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 06:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18107|2024-09-16T20:06:27.427Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18107</link>
      <description>Various resources in the Crowd Demo application of Atlassian Crowd before version 3.1.1 allow remote attackers to modify add, modify and delete users &amp; groups via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability. Please be aware that the Demo application is not enabled by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18107|2024-09-16T20:06:27.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 03:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4029|2024-09-16T17:54:34.534Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4029</link>
      <description>The /rest/project-templates/1.0/createshared resource in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.5, from 8.6.0 before 8.7.2, and from 8.8.0 before 8.8.1 allows remote attackers to enumerate project names via an improper authorization vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4029|2024-09-16T17:54:34.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 01:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36801|2024-09-16T20:31:54.645Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36801</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (RXSS) vulnerability in the TeamManagement.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.20.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36801|2024-09-16T20:31:54.645Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 02:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18104|2024-09-16T19:46:59.715Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18104</link>
      <description>The Webhooks component of Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.7 and from version 7.7.0 before version 7.11.0 allows remote attackers who are able to observe or otherwise intercept webhook events to learn information about changes in issues that should not be sent because they are not contained within the results of a specified JQL query.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18104|2024-09-16T19:46:59.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29451|2024-09-16T16:33:16.867Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29451</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to enumerate Jira projects via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the Jira Projects plugin report page. The affected versions are before version 8.5.11, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.3, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.14.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29451|2024-09-16T16:33:16.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43959|2024-09-16T17:18:47.343Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43959</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to access the content of internal network resources via a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the CSV importing feature of JSM Insight. When running in an environment like Amazon EC2, this flaw may be used to access to a metadata resource that provides access credentials and other potentially confidential information. The affected versions are before version 4.13.20, from version 4.14.0 before 4.20.8, and from version 4.21.0 before 4.22.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43959|2024-09-16T17:18:47.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 08:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26078|2024-09-16T16:17:58.100Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26078</link>
      <description>The number range searcher component in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.16.1 allows remote attackers inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26078|2024-09-16T16:17:58.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 22:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4020|2024-09-16T17:29:09.909Z -- atlassian -- companion%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4020</link>
      <description>The file downloading functionality in the Atlassian Companion App before version 1.0.0 allows remote attackers, who control a Confluence Server instance that the Companion App is connected to, execute arbitrary .exe files via a Protection Mechanism Failure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4020|2024-09-16T17:29:09.909Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 06:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14190|2024-09-16T17:18:22.523Z -- atlassian -- fisheye
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14190</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Fisheye/Crucible allow remote attackers to achieve Regex Denial of Service via user-supplied regex in EyeQL. The affected versions are before version 4.8.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14190|2024-09-16T17:18:22.523Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 22:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18080|2024-09-16T20:47:51.576Z -- atlassian -- bamboo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18080</link>
      <description>The saveConfigureSecurity resource in Atlassian Bamboo before version 6.3.1 allows remote attackers to modify security settings via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18080|2024-09-16T20:47:51.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13395|2024-09-16T16:42:34.901Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13395</link>
      <description>Various resources in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.8, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3 and before version 7.11.1 allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the epic colour field of an issue while an issue is being moved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13395|2024-09-16T16:42:34.901Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26080|2024-09-16T21:58:04.290Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26080</link>
      <description>EditworkflowScheme.jspa in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, and from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.6, and from 8.14.0 before 8.16.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26080|2024-09-16T21:58:04.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 22:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26081|2024-09-16T20:58:34.696Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26081</link>
      <description>REST API in Atlassian Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.16.1 allows remote attackers to enumerate usernames via a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability in the `/rest/api/latest/user/avatar/temporary` endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26081|2024-09-16T20:58:34.696Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 03:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43957|2024-09-16T16:53:50.144Z -- atlassian -- fisheye
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43957</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Fisheye &amp; Crucible allowed remote attackers to browse local files via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the WEB-INF directory and bypass the fix for CVE-2020-29446 due to a lack of url decoding. The affected versions are before version 4.8.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43957|2024-09-16T16:53:50.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18037|2024-09-16T20:27:24.181Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18037</link>
      <description>The git repository tag rest resource in Atlassian Bitbucket Server from version 3.7.0 before 4.14.11 (the fixed version for 4.14.x), from version 5.0.0 before 5.0.9 (the fixed version for 5.0.x), from version 5.1.0 before 5.1.8 (the fixed version for 5.1.x), from version 5.2.0 before 5.2.6 (the fixed version for 5.2.x), from version 5.3.0 before 5.3.4 (the fixed version for 5.3.x), from version 5.4.0 before 5.4.2 (the fixed version for 5.4.x), from version 5.5.0 before 5.5.1 (the fixed version for 5.5.x) and before 5.6.0 allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files via a path traversal vulnerability through the name of a git tag.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18037|2024-09-16T20:27:24.181Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4018|2024-09-16T19:14:26.996Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4018</link>
      <description>The setup resources in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.1 allows remote attackers to complete the setup process via a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4018|2024-09-16T19:14:26.996Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 06:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18113|2024-09-16T16:43:26.413Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18113</link>
      <description>The DefaultOSWorkflowConfigurator class in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.18.1 allows remote attackers who can trick a system administrator to import their malicious workflow to execute arbitrary code via a Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability. The vulnerability allowed for various problematic OSWorkflow classes to be used as part of workflows. The fix for this issue blocks usage of unsafe conditions, validators, functions and registers that are build-in into OSWorkflow library and other Jira dependencies. Atlassian-made functions or functions provided by 3rd party plugins are not affected by this fix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18113|2024-09-16T16:43:26.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 02:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43945|2024-09-16T16:47:56.975Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43945</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers with Roadmaps Administrator permissions to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (SXSS) vulnerability in the /rest/jpo/1.0/hierarchyConfiguration endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43945|2024-09-16T16:47:56.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 00:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16859|2024-09-16T17:15:00.298Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16859</link>
      <description>The review attachment resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.3.2, from version 4.4.0 before 4.4.3 and before version 4.5.0 allows remote attackers to read files contained within context path of the running application through a path traversal vulnerability in the command parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16859|2024-09-16T17:15:00.298Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14591|2024-09-16T20:46:54.683Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14591</link>
      <description>Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible versions less than 4.4.3 and version 4.5.0 are vulnerable to argument injection through filenames in Mercurial repositories, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code on a system running the impacted software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14591|2024-09-16T20:46:54.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16862|2024-09-16T18:48:43.537Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16862</link>
      <description>The IncomingMailServers resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.2 allows remote attackers to modify the "incoming mail" whitelist setting via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16862|2024-09-16T18:48:43.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39121|2024-09-16T16:48:52.686Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39121</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to enumerate the keys of private Jira projects via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /rest/api/latest/projectvalidate/key endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.18, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.10, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.18.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39121|2024-09-16T16:48:52.686Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 01:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43943|2024-09-16T20:32:38.613Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43943</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow attackers with administrator privileges to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the "Object Schema" field of /secure/admin/InsightDefaultCustomFieldConfig.jspa. The affected versions are before version 4.21.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43943|2024-09-16T20:32:38.613Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 04:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36799|2024-09-16T16:43:15.537Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36799</link>
      <description>This issue exists to document that a security improvement in the way that Jira Server and Data Center use templates has been implemented. Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allowed remote attackers with system administrator permissions to execute arbitrary code via Template Injection leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE) in the Email Templates feature. In this case the security improvement was to protect against using the XStream library to be able to execute arbitrary code in velocity templates. The affected versions are before version 8.13.19, from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.7, and from version 8.21.0 before 8.22.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36799|2024-09-16T16:43:15.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 01:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8444|2024-09-16T16:33:26.240Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8444</link>
      <description>The wikirenderer component in Jira before version 7.13.6, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.3.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in image attribute specification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8444|2024-09-16T16:33:26.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 13:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18089|2024-09-16T16:59:05.739Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18089</link>
      <description>The view review history resource in Atlassian Crucible before version 4.4.3 (the fixed version for 4.4.x) and 4.5.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the invited reviewers for a review.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18089|2024-09-16T16:59:05.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5225|2024-09-16T18:49:04.214Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5225</link>
      <description>In browser editing in Atlassian Bitbucket Server from version 4.13.0 before 5.4.8 (the fixed version for 4.13.0 through 5.4.7), 5.5.0 before 5.5.8 (the fixed version for 5.5.x), 5.6.0 before 5.6.5 (the fixed version for 5.6.x), 5.7.0 before 5.7.3 (the fixed version for 5.7.x), and 5.8.0 before 5.8.2 (the fixed version for 5.8.x), allows authenticated users to gain remote code execution using the in browser editing feature via editing a symbolic link within a repository.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5225|2024-09-16T18:49:04.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13403|2024-09-16T18:08:58.970Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13403</link>
      <description>The two-dimensional filter statistics gadget in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.10, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.12.4, and from version 7.13.0 before version 7.13.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the name of a saved filter when displayed on a Jira dashboard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13403|2024-09-16T18:08:58.970Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26136|2024-09-16T21:07:32.270Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26136</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in multiple Atlassian products allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to bypass Servlet Filters used by first and third party apps. The impact depends on which filters are used by each app, and how the filters are used. This vulnerability can result in authentication bypass and cross-site scripting. Atlassian has released updates that fix the root cause of this vulnerability, but has not exhaustively enumerated all potential consequences of this vulnerability. Atlassian Bamboo versions are affected before 8.0.9, from 8.1.0 before 8.1.8, and from 8.2.0 before 8.2.4. Atlassian Bitbucket versions are affected before 7.6.16, from 7.7.0 before 7.17.8, from 7.18.0 before 7.19.5, from 7.20.0 before 7.20.2, from 7.21.0 before 7.21.2, and versions 8.0.0 and 8.1.0. Atlassian Confluence versions are affected before 7.4.17, from 7.5.0 before 7.13.7, from 7.14.0 before 7.14.3, from 7.15.0 before 7.15.2, from 7.16.0 before 7.16.4, from 7.17.0 before 7.17.4, and version 7.21.0. Atlassian Crowd versions are affected before 4.3.8, from 4.4.0 before 4.4.2, and version 5.0.0. Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible versions before 4.8.10 are affected. Atlassian Jira versions are affected before 8.13.22, from 8.14.0 before 8.20.10, and from 8.21.0 before 8.22.4. Atlassian Jira Service Management versions are affected before 4.13.22, from 4.14.0 before 4.20.10, and from 4.21.0 before 4.22.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26136|2024-09-16T21:07:32.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 17:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13393|2024-09-16T18:23:29.602Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20questions
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13393</link>
      <description>The convertCommentToAnswer resource in Atlassian Confluence Questions before version 2.6.6, the bundled version of Confluence Questions was updated to a fixed version in Confluence version 6.9.0, allows remote attackers to modify a comment into an answer via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13393|2024-09-16T18:23:29.602Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14997|2024-09-16T18:44:06.559Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14997</link>
      <description>The AccessLogFilter class in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote anonymous attackers to learn details about other users, including their username, via an information expose through caching vulnerability when Jira is configured with a reverse Proxy and or a load balancer with caching or a CDN.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14997|2024-09-16T18:44:06.559Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 13:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13398|2024-09-16T18:34:54.617Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13398</link>
      <description>The administrative smart-commits resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.5.4 allows remote attackers to modify smart-commit settings via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13398|2024-09-16T18:34:54.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18082|2024-09-16T18:38:32.846Z -- atlassian -- bamboo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18082</link>
      <description>The plan configure branches resource in Atlassian Bamboo before version 6.2.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the name of a branch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18082|2024-09-16T18:38:32.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11588|2024-09-16T16:57:57.828Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11588</link>
      <description>The ViewSystemInfo class doGarbageCollection method in Jira before version 7.13.6, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.2.3, and from version 8.3.0 before version 8.3.2 allows remote attackers to trigger garbage collection via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11588|2024-09-16T16:57:57.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 13:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5232|2024-09-16T17:37:58.152Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5232</link>
      <description>The EditIssue.jspa resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.7 and from version 7.7.0 before version 7.10.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the issuetype parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5232|2024-09-16T17:37:58.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39127|2024-09-16T19:10:18.202Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39127</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to the query component JQL endpoint via a Broken Access Control vulnerability (BAC) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 8.5.10, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39127|2024-09-16T19:10:18.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 02:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8451|2024-09-16T19:14:27.449Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8451</link>
      <description>The /plugins/servlet/gadgets/makeRequest resource in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote attackers to access the content of internal network resources via a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability due to a logic bug in the JiraWhitelist class.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8451|2024-09-16T19:14:27.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 13:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18091|2024-09-16T20:22:54.697Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18091</link>
      <description>The admin backupprogress action in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.4.3 (the fixed version for 4.4.x) and before 4.5.0 allows remote attackers with administrative privileges to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the filename of a backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18091|2024-09-16T20:22:54.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3398|2024-09-16T17:49:22.832Z -- atlassian -- confluence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3398</link>
      <description>Confluence Server and Data Center had a path traversal vulnerability in the downloadallattachments resource. A remote attacker who has permission to add attachments to pages and / or blogs or to create a new space or a personal space or who has 'Admin' permissions for a space can exploit this path traversal vulnerability to write files to arbitrary locations which can lead to remote code execution on systems that run a vulnerable version of Confluence Server or Data Center. All versions of Confluence Server from 2.0.0 before 6.6.13 (the fixed version for 6.6.x), from 6.7.0 before 6.12.4 (the fixed version for 6.12.x), from 6.13.0 before 6.13.4 (the fixed version for 6.13.x), from 6.14.0 before 6.14.3 (the fixed version for 6.14.x), and from 6.15.0 before 6.15.2 are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3398|2024-09-16T17:49:22.832Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 17:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14589|2024-09-16T19:10:55.831Z -- atlassian -- bamboo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14589</link>
      <description>It was possible for double OGNL evaluation in FreeMarker templates through Struts FreeMarker tags to occur. An attacker who has restricted administration rights to Bamboo or who hosts a website that a Bamboo administrator visits, is able to exploit this vulnerability to execute Java code of their choice on systems that run a vulnerable version of Bamboo. All versions of Bamboo before 6.1.6 (the fixed version for 6.1.x) and from 6.2.0 before 6.2.5 (the fixed version for 6.2.x) are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14589|2024-09-16T19:10:55.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20404|2024-09-16T17:43:28.548Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20404</link>
      <description>The API in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.6.0 allows authenticated remote attackers to determine project titles they do not have access to via an improper authorization vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20404|2024-09-16T17:43:28.548Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 03:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18034|2024-09-16T17:38:29.337Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18034</link>
      <description>The source browse resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.5.1 and 4.6.0 allows allows remote attackers that have write access to an indexed repository to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in via a specially crafted repository branch name when trying to display deleted files of the branch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18034|2024-09-16T17:38:29.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3400|2024-09-16T16:54:02.769Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3400</link>
      <description>The labels gadget in Jira before version 7.13.2, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the jql parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3400|2024-09-16T16:54:02.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 19:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20098|2024-09-16T20:12:46.255Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20098</link>
      <description>The VerifySmtpServerConnection!add.jspa component in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.7.0 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery (CSRF). An attacker could exploit this by tricking an administrative user into making malicious HTTP requests, allowing the attacker to enumerate hosts and open ports on the internal network where Jira server is present.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20098|2024-09-16T20:12:46.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 14:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14168|2024-09-16T18:02:52.905Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14168</link>
      <description>The email client in Jira Server and Data Center before version 7.13.16, from 8.5.0 before 8.5.7, from 8.8.0 before 8.8.2, and from 8.9.0 before 8.9.1 allows remote attackers to access outgoing emails between a Jira instance and the SMTP server via man-in-the-middle (MITM) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14168|2024-09-16T18:02:52.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 01:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39114|2024-09-16T19:04:58.886Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39114</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center allow users with a valid account on a Confluence Data Center instance to execute arbitrary Java code or run arbitrary system commands by injecting an OGNL payload. The affected versions are before version 6.13.23, from version 6.14.0 before 7.4.11, from version 7.5.0 before 7.11.6, and from version 7.12.0 before 7.12.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39114|2024-09-16T19:04:58.886Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 04:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18041|2024-09-16T19:04:12.784Z -- atlassian -- bamboo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18041</link>
      <description>The viewDeploymentVersionJiraIssuesDialog resource in Atlassian Bamboo before version 6.2.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the name of a release.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18041|2024-09-16T19:04:12.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39117|2024-09-16T17:58:25.977Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39117</link>
      <description>The AssociateFieldToScreens page in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.18.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the name of a custom field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39117|2024-09-16T17:58:25.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 06:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18105|2024-09-16T20:42:15.439Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18105</link>
      <description>The console login resource in Atlassian Crowd before version 3.0.2 and from version 3.1.0 before version 3.1.1 allows remote attackers, who have previously obtained a user's JSESSIONID cookie, to gain access to some of the built-in and potentially third party rest resources via a session fixation vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18105|2024-09-16T20:42:15.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 14:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4028|2024-09-16T16:48:18.602Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4028</link>
      <description>Versions before 8.9.1, Various resources in Jira responded with a 404 instead of redirecting unauthenticated users to the login page, in some situations this may have allowed unauthorised attackers to determine if certain resources exist or not through an Information Disclosure vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4028|2024-09-16T16:48:18.602Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 12:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14586|2024-09-16T18:08:06.305Z -- atlassian -- hipchat%20for%20mac%20desktop%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14586</link>
      <description>The Hipchat for Mac desktop client is vulnerable to client-side remote code execution via video call link parsing. Hipchat for Mac desktop clients at or above version 4.0 and before version 4.30 are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14586|2024-09-16T18:08:06.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18096|2024-09-16T17:54:30.699Z -- atlassian -- atlassian%20application%20links
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18096</link>
      <description>The OAuth status rest resource in Atlassian Application Links before version 5.2.7, from 5.3.0 before 5.3.4 and from 5.4.0 before 5.4.3 allows remote attackers with administrative rights to access the content of internal network resources via a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) by creating an OAuth application link to a location they control and then redirecting access from the linked location's OAuth status rest resource to an internal location. When running in an environment like Amazon EC2, this flaw maybe used to access to a metadata resource that provides access credentials and other potentially confidential information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18096|2024-09-16T17:54:30.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36287|2024-09-16T16:39:12.728Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36287</link>
      <description>The dashboard gadgets preference resource of the Atlassian gadgets plugin used in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.1 allows remote anonymous attackers to obtain gadget related settings via a missing permissions check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36287|2024-09-16T16:39:12.728Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 02:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14181|2024-09-16T21:57:12.718Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14181</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow an unauthenticated user to enumerate users via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /ViewUserHover.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 7.13.6, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.7, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.12.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14181|2024-09-16T21:57:12.718Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13404|2024-09-16T17:28:16.895Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13404</link>
      <description>The VerifyPopServerConnection resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.10, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3, from version 7.11.0 before version 7.11.3, from version 7.12.0 before version 7.12.3, and from version 7.13.0 before version 7.13.1 allows remote attackers who have administrator rights to determine the existence of internal hosts &amp; open ports and in some cases obtain service information from internal network resources via a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13404|2024-09-16T17:28:16.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8442|2024-09-16T17:58:53.478Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8442</link>
      <description>The CachingResourceDownloadRewriteRule class in Jira before version 7.13.4, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.4, and from version 8.1.0 before version 8.1.1 allows remote attackers to access files in the Jira webroot under the META-INF directory via a lax path access check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8442|2024-09-16T17:58:53.478Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 17:39:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20413|2024-09-16T19:41:27.665Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20413</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability on the UserPickerBrowser.jspa page. The affected versions are before version 7.13.9, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20413|2024-09-16T19:41:27.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 06:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20237|2024-09-16T21:02:16.888Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20237</link>
      <description>Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center before version 6.13.1 allows an authenticated user to download a deleted page via the word export feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20237|2024-09-16T21:02:16.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36233|2024-09-16T19:30:12.974Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36233</link>
      <description>The Microsoft Windows Installer for Atlassian Bitbucket Server and Data Center before version 6.10.9, 7.x before 7.6.4, and from version 7.7.0 before 7.10.1 allows local attackers to escalate privileges because of weak permissions on the installation directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36233|2024-09-16T19:30:12.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 15:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36235|2024-09-16T16:24:07.752Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36235</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to view custom field and custom SLA names via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the mobile site view. The affected versions are before version 8.13.2, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.14.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36235|2024-09-16T16:24:07.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 23:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18040|2024-09-16T20:16:51.105Z -- atlassian -- bamboo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18040</link>
      <description>The viewDeploymentVersionCommits resource in Atlassian Bamboo before version 6.2.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the name of a release.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18040|2024-09-16T20:16:51.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14594|2024-09-16T17:14:01.826Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14594</link>
      <description>The printable searchrequest issue resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.2.12 and from version 7.3.0 before 7.6.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the jqlQuery query parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14594|2024-09-16T17:14:01.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5223|2024-09-16T19:56:55.062Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5223</link>
      <description>Fisheye and Crucible did not correctly check if a configured Mercurial repository URI contained values that the Windows operating system may consider argument parameters. An attacker who has permission to add a repository in Fisheye or Crucible can execute code of their choice on systems that run a vulnerable version of Fisheye or Crucible on the Windows operating system. All versions of Fisheye and Crucible before 4.4.6 (the fixed version for 4.4.x) and from 4.5.0 before 4.5.3 (the fixed version for 4.5.x) are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5223|2024-09-16T19:56:55.062Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14169|2024-09-16T20:28:10.550Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14169</link>
      <description>The quick search component in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before 8.9.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14169|2024-09-16T20:28:10.550Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 01:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14995|2024-09-16T18:24:24.535Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14995</link>
      <description>The /rest/api/1.0/render resource in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote anonymous attackers to determine if an attachment with a specific name exists and if an issue key is valid via a missing permissions check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14995|2024-09-16T18:24:24.535Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 13:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14166|2024-09-16T16:33:13.111Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20desk%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14166</link>
      <description>The /servicedesk/customer/portals resource in Jira Service Desk Server and Data Center before version 4.10.0 allows remote attackers with project administrator privileges to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript names via an Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability by uploading a html file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14166|2024-09-16T16:33:13.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 01:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20102|2024-09-16T16:57:45.935Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20102</link>
      <description>The attachment-uploading feature in Atlassian Confluence Server from version 6.14.0 through version 6.14.3, and version 6.15.0 before version 6.15.5 allows remote attackers to achieve stored cross-site- scripting (SXSS) via a malicious attachment with a modified `mimeType` parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20102|2024-09-16T16:57:45.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 03:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14189|2024-09-16T20:13:22.226Z -- atlassian -- gajira-comment
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14189</link>
      <description>The execute function in in the Atlassian gajira-comment GitHub Action before version 2.0.2 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a GitHub runner by creating a specially crafted GitHub issue comment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14189|2024-09-16T20:13:22.226Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 21:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14179|2024-09-16T16:17:53.447Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14179</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote, unauthenticated attackers to view custom field names and custom SLA names via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /secure/QueryComponent!Default.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.8, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.11.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14179|2024-09-16T16:17:53.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 00:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26133|2024-09-16T19:56:27.196Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26133</link>
      <description>SharedSecretClusterAuthenticator in Atlassian Bitbucket Data Center versions 5.14.0 and later before 7.6.14, 7.7.0 and later prior to 7.17.6, 7.18.0 and later prior to 7.18.4, 7.19.0 and later prior to 7.19.4, and 7.20.0 allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code via Java deserialization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26133|2024-09-16T19:56:27.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 18:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26070|2024-09-16T19:42:02.091Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26070</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to evade behind-the-firewall protection of app-linked resources via a Broken Authentication vulnerability in the `makeRequest` gadget resource. The affected versions are before version 8.13.3, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.14.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26070|2024-09-16T19:42:02.091Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 04:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3399|2024-09-16T17:48:24.295Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3399</link>
      <description>The BrowseProjects.jspa resource in Jira before version 7.13.2, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.2 allows remote attackers to see information for archived projects through a missing authorisation check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3399|2024-09-16T17:48:24.295Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 15:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26067|2024-09-16T18:34:10.127Z -- atlassian -- bamboo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26067</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Bamboo allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to view a stack trace that may reveal the path for the home directory in disk and if certain files exists on the tmp directory, via a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability in the /chart endpoint. The affected versions are before version 7.2.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26067|2024-09-16T18:34:10.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 01:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18036|2024-09-16T19:04:43.701Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18036</link>
      <description>The Github repository importer in Atlassian Bitbucket Server before version 5.3.0 allows remote attackers to determine if a service they could not otherwise reach has open ports via a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18036|2024-09-16T19:04:43.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18095|2024-09-16T17:28:59.763Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18095</link>
      <description>The SnippetRPCServiceImpl class in Atlassian Crucible before version 4.5.1 (the fixed version 4.5.x) and before 4.6.0 allows remote attackers to comment on snippets they do not have authorization to access via an improper authorization vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18095|2024-09-16T17:28:59.763Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8450|2024-09-16T19:50:40.011Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8450</link>
      <description>Various templates of the Optimization plugin in Jira before version 7.13.6, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.4.0 allow remote attackers who have permission to manage custom fields to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the name of a custom field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8450|2024-09-16T19:50:40.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 13:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39128|2024-09-16T17:23:08.218Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39128</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server or Data Center using the Jira Service Management addon allow remote attackers with JIRA Administrators access to execute arbitrary Java code via a server-side template injection vulnerability in the Email Template feature. The affected versions of Jira Server or Data Center are before version 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.19.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39128|2024-09-16T17:23:08.218Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 05:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26134|2024-09-16T18:55:17.016Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26134</link>
      <description>In affected versions of Confluence Server and Data Center, an OGNL injection vulnerability exists that would allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on a Confluence Server or Data Center instance. The affected versions are from 1.3.0 before 7.4.17, from 7.13.0 before 7.13.7, from 7.14.0 before 7.14.3, from 7.15.0 before 7.15.2, from 7.16.0 before 7.16.4, from 7.17.0 before 7.17.4, and from 7.18.0 before 7.18.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26134|2024-09-16T18:55:17.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4024|2024-09-16T17:15:19.346Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4024</link>
      <description>The attachment download resource in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before 8.5.5, and from 8.6.0 before 8.8.2, and from 8.9.0 before 8.9.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability issue attachments with a vnd.wap.xhtml+xml content type.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4024|2024-09-16T17:15:19.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 01:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39115|2024-09-16T19:46:22.797Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20desk%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39115</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow remote attackers with "Jira Administrators" access to execute arbitrary Java code or run arbitrary system commands via a Server_Side Template Injection vulnerability in the Email Template feature. The affected versions are before version 4.13.9, and from version 4.14.0 before 4.18.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39115|2024-09-16T19:46:22.797Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 23:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11580|2024-09-16T20:47:44.405Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11580</link>
      <description>Atlassian Crowd and Crowd Data Center had the pdkinstall development plugin incorrectly enabled in release builds. Attackers who can send unauthenticated or authenticated requests to a Crowd or Crowd Data Center instance can exploit this vulnerability to install arbitrary plugins, which permits remote code execution on systems running a vulnerable version of Crowd or Crowd Data Center. All versions of Crowd from version 2.1.0 before 3.0.5 (the fixed version for 3.0.x), from version 3.1.0 before 3.1.6 (the fixed version for 3.1.x), from version 3.2.0 before 3.2.8 (the fixed version for 3.2.x), from version 3.3.0 before 3.3.5 (the fixed version for 3.3.x), and from version 3.4.0 before 3.4.4 (the fixed version for 3.4.x) are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11580|2024-09-16T20:47:44.405Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 13:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14174|2024-09-16T20:31:56.101Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14174</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to view titles of a private project via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Administration Permission Helper. The affected versions are before version 7.13.6, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.7, from version 8.6.0 before 8.9.2, and from version 8.10.0 before 8.10.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14174|2024-09-16T20:31:56.101Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 04:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14192|2024-09-16T16:14:04.913Z -- atlassian -- fisheye
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14192</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible allow remote attackers to view a product's SEN via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the x-asen response header from Atlassian Analytics. The affected versions are before version 4.8.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14192|2024-09-16T16:14:04.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 23:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5226|2024-09-16T20:32:16.150Z -- atlassian -- sourcetree%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5226</link>
      <description>There was an argument injection vulnerability in Sourcetree for Windows via Mercurial repository tag name that is going to be deleted. An attacker with permission to create a tag on a Mercurial repository linked in Sourcetree for Windows is able to exploit this issue to gain code execution on the system. All versions of Sourcetree for Windows before 2.5.5.0 are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5226|2024-09-16T20:32:16.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4013|2024-09-16T20:36:58.765Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4013</link>
      <description>The review resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or Javascript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the review objectives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4013|2024-09-16T20:36:58.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 06:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18098|2024-09-16T18:38:34.469Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18098</link>
      <description>The searchrequest-xml resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through various fields.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18098|2024-09-16T18:38:34.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26086|2024-09-16T16:37:51.040Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26086</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to read particular files via a path traversal vulnerability in the /WEB-INF/web.xml endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.16.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26086|2024-09-16T16:37:51.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43940|2024-09-16T20:53:11.080Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43940</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center allow authenticated local attackers to achieve elevated privileges on the local system via a DLL Hijacking vulnerability in the Confluence installer. This vulnerability only affects installations of Confluence Server and Data Center on Windows. The affected versions are before version 7.4.10, and from version 7.5.0 before 7.12.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43940|2024-09-16T20:53:11.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 03:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14164|2024-09-16T16:59:07.646Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14164</link>
      <description>The WYSIWYG editor resource in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.8.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript names via an Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability by pasting javascript code into the editor field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14164|2024-09-16T16:59:07.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 01:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36290|2024-09-16T18:24:43.695Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36290</link>
      <description>The Livesearch macro in Confluence Server and Data Center before version 7.4.5, from version 7.5.0 before 7.6.3, and from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.4 allows remote attackers with permission to edit a page or blog to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the page excerpt functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36290|2024-09-16T18:24:43.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 04:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43958|2024-09-16T17:08:22.249Z -- atlassian -- fisheye
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43958</link>
      <description>Various rest resources in Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.9 allowed remote attackers to brute force user login credentials as rest resources did not check if users were beyond their max failed login limits and therefore required solving a CAPTCHA in addition to providing user credentials for authentication via a improper restriction of excess authentication attempts vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43958|2024-09-16T17:08:22.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11586|2024-09-16T17:18:14.250Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11586</link>
      <description>The AddResolution.jspa resource in Jira before version 7.13.6, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.2.3, and from version 8.3.0 before version 8.3.2 allows remote attackers to create new resolutions via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11586|2024-09-16T17:18:14.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 13:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39112|2024-09-16T16:53:16.614Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39112</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to redirect users to a malicious URL via a reverse tabnapping vulnerability in the Project Shortcuts feature. The affected versions are before version 8.5.15, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.7, from version 8.14.0 before 8.17.1, and from version 8.18.0 before 8.18.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39112|2024-09-16T16:53:16.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 02:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4019|2024-09-16T17:19:04.361Z -- atlassian -- companion%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4019</link>
      <description>The file editing functionality in the Atlassian Companion App before version 1.0.0 allows local attackers to have the app run a different executable in place of the app's cmd.exe via a untrusted search path vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4019|2024-09-16T17:19:04.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 06:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26076|2024-09-16T17:02:47.922Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26076</link>
      <description>The jira.editor.user.mode cookie set by the Jira Editor Plugin in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.12, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.4, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.0 allows remote anonymous attackers who can perform an attacker in the middle attack to learn which mode a user is editing in due to the cookie not being set with a secure attribute if Jira was configured to use https.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26076|2024-09-16T17:02:47.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 23:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20104|2024-09-16T17:04:16.877Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20104</link>
      <description>The OpenID client application in Atlassian Crowd before version 3.6.2, and from version 3.7.0 before 3.7.1 allows remote attackers to perform a Denial of Service attack via an XML Entity Expansion vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20104|2024-09-16T17:04:16.877Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 03:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36231|2024-09-16T17:14:09.087Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36231</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to view the metadata of boards they should not have access to via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 8.5.10, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36231|2024-09-16T17:14:09.087Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 23:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20101|2024-09-16T18:34:10.644Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20101</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view whitelist rules via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the /rest/whitelist/&lt;version&gt;/check endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.13.3, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.14.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20101|2024-09-16T18:34:10.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 05:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14585|2024-09-16T19:31:45.090Z -- atlassian -- hipchat%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14585</link>
      <description>A Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability could lead to remote code execution for authenticated administrators. This issue was introduced in version 2.2.0 of Hipchat Server and version 3.0.0 of Hipchat Data Center. Versions of Hipchat Server starting with 2.2.0 and before 2.2.6 are affected by this vulnerability. Versions of Hipchat Data Center starting with 3.0.0 and before 3.1.0 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14585|2024-09-16T19:31:45.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18109|2024-09-16T17:08:13.135Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18109</link>
      <description>The login resource of CrowdId in Atlassian Crowd before version 3.0.2 and from version 3.1.0 before version 3.1.1 allows remote attackers to redirect users to a different website which they may use as part of performing a phishing attack via an open redirect.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18109|2024-09-16T17:08:13.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 14:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13402|2024-09-16T17:52:50.468Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13402</link>
      <description>Many resources in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.9, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3, from version 7.11.0 before version 7.11.3, from version 7.12.0 before version 7.12.3, and before version 7.13.1 allow remote attackers to attack users, in some cases be able to obtain a user's Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) token, via a open redirect vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13402|2024-09-16T17:52:50.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20418|2024-09-16T18:19:35.652Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20418</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to prevent users from accessing the instance via an Application Denial of Service vulnerability in the /rendering/wiki endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20418|2024-09-16T18:19:35.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 01:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18110|2024-09-16T18:08:23.904Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18110</link>
      <description>The administration backup restore resource in Atlassian Crowd before version 3.0.2 and from version 3.1.0 before version 3.1.1 allows remote attackers to read files from the filesystem via a XXE vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18110|2024-09-16T18:08:23.904Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 14:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15005|2024-09-16T20:31:42.718Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15005</link>
      <description>The Atlassian Troubleshooting and Support Tools plugin prior to version 1.17.2 allows an unprivileged user to initiate periodic log scans and send the results to a user-specified email address due to a missing authorization check. The email message may contain configuration information about the application that the plugin is installed into. A vulnerable version of the plugin is included with Bitbucket Server / Data Center before 6.6.0, Confluence Server / Data Center before 7.0.1, Jira Server / Data Center before 8.3.2, Crowd / Crowd Data Center before 3.6.0, Fisheye before 4.7.2, Crucible before 4.7.2, and Bamboo before 6.10.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15005|2024-09-16T20:31:42.718Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 03:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-9506|2024-09-16T20:51:54.092Z -- atlassian -- atlassian%20oauth%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-9506</link>
      <description>The IconUriServlet of the Atlassian OAuth Plugin from version 1.3.0 before version 1.9.12 and from version 2.0.0 before version 2.0.4 allows remote attackers to access the content of internal network resources and/or perform an XSS attack via Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-9506|2024-09-16T20:51:54.092Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36804|2024-09-16T18:14:18.941Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36804</link>
      <description>Multiple API endpoints in Atlassian Bitbucket Server and Data Center 7.0.0 before version 7.6.17, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.17.10, from version 7.18.0 before version 7.21.4, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.3, from version 8.1.0 before version 8.1.3, and from version 8.2.0 before version 8.2.2, and from version 8.3.0 before 8.3.1 allows remote attackers with read permissions to a public or private Bitbucket repository to execute arbitrary code by sending a malicious HTTP request. This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty Program by TheGrandPew.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36804|2024-09-16T18:14:18.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 05:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39116|2024-09-16T20:11:28.456Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39116</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in the GIF Image Reader component. The affected versions are before version 8.13.14, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.19.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39116|2024-09-16T20:11:28.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11585|2024-09-16T20:32:20.365Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11585</link>
      <description>The startup.jsp resource in Jira before version 7.13.6, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.2.3, and from version 8.3.0 before version 8.3.2 allows remote attackers to redirect users to a different website which they may use as part of performing a phishing attack via an open redirect.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11585|2024-09-16T20:32:20.365Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 13:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43944|2024-09-16T18:28:35.601Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43944</link>
      <description>This issue exists to document that a security improvement in the way that Jira Server and Data Center use templates has been implemented. Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allowed remote attackers with system administrator permissions to execute arbitrary code via Template Injection leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE) in the Email Templates feature. The affected versions are before version 8.13.15, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43944|2024-09-16T18:28:35.601Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 02:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13399|2024-09-16T20:21:40.541Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13399</link>
      <description>The Microsoft Windows Installer for Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.6.1 allows local attackers to escalate privileges because of weak permissions on the installation directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13399|2024-09-16T20:21:40.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14173|2024-09-16T21:56:45.464Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14173</link>
      <description>The file upload feature in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center in affected versions allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 8.5.4, from version 8.6.0 before 8.6.2, and from version 8.7.0 before 8.7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14173|2024-09-16T21:56:45.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 01:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18111|2024-09-16T17:32:37.560Z -- atlassian -- application%20links
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18111</link>
      <description>The OAuthHelper in Atlassian Application Links before version 5.0.10, from version 5.1.0 before version 5.1.3, and from version 5.2.0 before version 5.2.6 used an XML document builder that was vulnerable to XXE when consuming a client OAuth request. This allowed malicious oauth application linked applications to probe internal network resources by requesting internal locations, read the contents of files and also cause an out of memory exception affecting availability via an XML External Entity vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18111|2024-09-16T17:32:37.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 14:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18084|2024-09-16T20:28:09.477Z -- atlassian -- confluence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18084</link>
      <description>The usermacros resource in Atlassian Confluence Server before version 6.3.4 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the description of a macro.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18084|2024-09-16T20:28:09.477Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14185|2024-09-16T16:24:13.539Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14185</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Jira Server allow remote unauthenticated attackers to enumerate issue keys via a missing permissions check in the ActionsAndOperations resource. The affected versions are before 7.13.18, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.9, and from version 8.6.0 before version 8.12.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14185|2024-09-16T16:24:13.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 21:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11583|2024-09-16T17:54:52.599Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11583</link>
      <description>The issue searching component in Jira before version 8.1.0 allows remote attackers to deny access to Jira service via denial of service vulnerability in issue search when ordering by "Epic Name".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11583|2024-09-16T17:54:52.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 15:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36234|2024-09-16T16:18:31.237Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36234</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Screens Modal view. The affected versions are before version 8.5.11, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.3, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.15.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36234|2024-09-16T16:18:31.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13396|2024-09-16T21:03:34.200Z -- atlassian -- sourcetree%20for%20macos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13396</link>
      <description>There was an argument injection vulnerability in Sourcetree for macOS from version 1.0b2 before version 3.0.0 via Git subrepositories in Mercurial repositories. An attacker with permission to commit to a Mercurial repository linked in Sourcetree for macOS is able to exploit this issue to gain code execution on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13396|2024-09-16T21:03:34.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3397|2024-09-16T17:47:59.258Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3397</link>
      <description>Atlassian Bitbucket Data Center licensed instances starting with version 5.13.0 before 5.13.6 (the fixed version for 5.13.x), from 5.14.0 before 5.14.4 (fixed version for 5.14.x), from 5.15.0 before 5.15.3 (fixed version for 5.15.x), from 5.16.0 before 5.16.3 (fixed version for 5.16.x), from 6.0.0 before 6.0.3 (fixed version for 6.0.x), and from 6.1.0 before 6.1.2 (the fixed version for 6.1.x) allow remote attackers who have admin permissions to achieve remote code execution on a Bitbucket server instance via path traversal through the Data Center migration tool.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3397|2024-09-16T17:47:59.258Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 13:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20105|2024-09-16T19:25:54.920Z -- atlassian -- application%20links
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20105</link>
      <description>The EditApplinkServlet resource in the Atlassian Application Links plugin before version 5.4.20, from version 6.0.0 before version 6.0.12, from version 6.1.0 before version 6.1.2, from version 7.0.0 before version 7.0.1, and from version 7.1.0 before version 7.1.3 allows remote attackers who have obtained access to administrator's session to access the EditApplinkServlet resource without needing to re-authenticate to pass "WebSudo" in products that support "WebSudo" through an improper access control vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20105|2024-09-16T19:25:54.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 02:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20097|2024-09-16T18:48:48.325Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20097</link>
      <description>Bitbucket Server and Bitbucket Data Center versions starting from 1.0.0 before 5.16.11, from version 6.0.0 before 6.0.11, from version 6.1.0 before 6.1.9, from version 6.2.0 before 6.2.7, from version 6.3.0 before 6.3.6, from version 6.4.0 before 6.4.4, from version 6.5.0 before 6.5.3, from version 6.6.0 before 6.6.3, from version 6.7.0 before 6.7.3, from version 6.8.0 before 6.8.2, from version 6.9.0 before 6.9.1 had a Remote Code Execution vulnerability via the post-receive hook. A remote attacker with permission to clone and push files to a repository on the victim's Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center instance, can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands on the Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center systems, using a file with specially crafted content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20097|2024-09-16T18:48:48.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 20:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18083|2024-09-16T18:09:18.179Z -- atlassian -- confluence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18083</link>
      <description>The editinword resource in Atlassian Confluence Server before version 6.4.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the contents of an uploaded file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18083|2024-09-16T18:09:18.179Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18039|2024-09-16T19:10:00.691Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18039</link>
      <description>The IncomingMailServers resource in Atlassian Jira from version 6.2.1 before version 7.4.4 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the messagesThreshold parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18039|2024-09-16T19:10:00.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5224|2024-09-16T18:04:23.118Z -- atlassian -- bamboo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5224</link>
      <description>Bamboo did not correctly check if a configured Mercurial repository URI contained values that the Windows operating system may consider argument parameters. An attacker who has permission to create a repository in Bamboo, edit an existing plan in Bamboo that has a non-linked Mercurial repository, or create a plan in Bamboo either globally or in a project using Bamboo Specs can can execute code of their choice on systems that run a vulnerable version of Bamboo on the Windows operating system. All versions of Bamboo starting with 2.7.0 before 6.3.3 (the fixed version for 6.3.x) and from version 6.4.0 before 6.4.1 (the fixed version for 6.4.x) running on the Windows operating system are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5224|2024-09-16T18:04:23.118Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39113|2024-09-16T17:57:48.308Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39113</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to continue to view cached content even after losing permissions, via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the allowlist feature. The affected versions are before version 8.13.9, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.18.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39113|2024-09-16T17:57:48.308Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 06:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20239|2024-09-16T20:01:43.685Z -- atlassian -- atlassian%20application%20links
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20239</link>
      <description>Application Links before version 5.0.11, from version 5.1.0 before 5.2.10, from version 5.3.0 before 5.3.6, from version 5.4.0 before 5.4.12, and from version 6.0.0 before 6.0.4 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the applinkStartingUrl parameter. The product is used as a plugin in various Atlassian products where the following are affected: Confluence before version 6.15.2, Crucible before version 4.7.0, Crowd before version 3.4.3, Fisheye before version 4.7.0, Jira before version 7.13.3 and 8.x before 8.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20239|2024-09-16T20:01:43.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 15:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4021|2024-09-16T16:47:43.937Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4021</link>
      <description>Affected versions are: Before 8.5.5, and from 8.6.0 before 8.8.1 of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the XML export view.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4021|2024-09-16T16:47:43.937Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 06:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36288|2024-09-16T18:34:20.368Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36288</link>
      <description>The issue navigation and search view in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.12, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.4, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a DOM Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability caused by parameter pollution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36288|2024-09-16T18:34:20.368Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 23:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20238|2024-09-16T20:41:48.136Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20238</link>
      <description>Various rest resources in Atlassian Crowd before version 3.2.7 and from version 3.3.0 before version 3.3.4 allow remote attackers to authenticate using an expired user session via an insufficient session expiration vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20238|2024-09-16T20:41:48.136Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3402|2024-09-16T18:59:29.908Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3402</link>
      <description>The ConfigurePortalPages.jspa resource in Jira before version 7.13.3 and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.1.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the searchOwnerUserName parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3402|2024-09-16T18:59:29.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 17:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43953|2024-09-16T16:18:22.052Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43953</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to toggle the Thread Contention and CPU monitoring settings via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the /secure/admin/ViewInstrumentation.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.13.16, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43953|2024-09-16T16:18:22.052Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 02:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20411|2024-09-16T17:43:47.805Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20411</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to modify Wallboard settings via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 7.13.9, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20411|2024-09-16T17:43:47.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 05:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8447|2024-09-16T21:02:48.300Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8447</link>
      <description>The ServiceExecutor resource in Jira before version 8.3.2 allows remote attackers to trigger the creation of export files via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8447|2024-09-16T21:02:48.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 13:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20236|2024-09-16T19:10:38.203Z -- atlassian -- sourcetree%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20236</link>
      <description>There was an command injection vulnerability in Sourcetree for Windows from version 0.5a before version 3.0.10 via URI handling. A remote attacker could send a malicious URI to a victim using Sourcetree for Windows to exploit this issue to gain code execution on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20236|2024-09-16T19:10:38.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15013|2024-09-16T16:57:38.126Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15013</link>
      <description>The WorkflowResource class removeStatus method in Jira before version 7.13.12, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.4.3, and from version 8.5.0 before version 8.5.2 allows authenticated remote attackers who do not have project administration access to remove a configured issue status from a project via a missing authorisation check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15013|2024-09-16T16:57:38.126Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 03:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39125|2024-09-16T18:59:59.640Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39125</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to discover the usernames of users via an enumeration vulnerability in the password reset page. The affected versions are before version 8.5.10, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39125|2024-09-16T18:59:59.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 06:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43941|2024-09-16T18:49:14.480Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43941</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to modify several resources (including CsvFieldMappingsPage.jspa and ImporterValueMappingsPage.jspa) via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the jira-importers-plugin. The affected versions are before version 8.13.15, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43941|2024-09-16T18:49:14.480Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 03:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18094|2024-09-16T18:28:38.668Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18094</link>
      <description>Various resources in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.4.3 (the fixed version for 4.4.x) and 4.5.0 allow remote attackers with administrative privileges to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the base path setting of a configured file system repository.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18094|2024-09-16T18:28:38.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20402|2024-09-16T18:29:43.223Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20402</link>
      <description>Support zip files in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.6.0 could be downloaded by a System Administrator user without requiring the user to re-enter their password via an improper authorization vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20402|2024-09-16T18:29:43.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 03:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39109|2024-09-16T19:05:26.944Z -- atlassian -- atlasboard
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39109</link>
      <description>The renderWidgetResource resource in Atlasian Atlasboard before version 1.1.9 allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files via a path traversal vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39109|2024-09-16T19:05:26.944Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 05:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11582|2024-09-16T19:25:35.218Z -- atlassian -- sourcetree%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11582</link>
      <description>An argument injection vulnerability in Atlassian Sourcetree for Windows's URI handlers, in all versions prior to 3.1.3, allows remote attackers to gain remote code execution through the use of a crafted URI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11582|2024-09-16T19:25:35.218Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 13:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39126|2024-09-16T17:08:23.201Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39126</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to modify various resources via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability, following an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the referrer headers which discloses a user's CSRF token. The affected versions are before version 8.5.10, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39126|2024-09-16T17:08:23.201Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 02:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36286|2024-09-16T19:24:29.543Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36286</link>
      <description>The membersOf JQL search function in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.13, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.1 allows remote anonymous attackers to determine if a group exists &amp; members of groups if they are assigned to publicly visible issue field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36286|2024-09-16T19:24:29.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 03:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-9507|2024-09-16T16:38:56.135Z -- atlassian -- atlassian%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-9507</link>
      <description>The review dashboard resource in Atlassian Crucible from version 4.1.0 before version 4.4.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the review filter title parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-9507|2024-09-16T16:38:56.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20408|2024-09-16T17:54:00.591Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20408</link>
      <description>The /plugins/servlet/gadgets/makeRequest resource in Jira before version 8.7.0 allows remote attackers to access the content of internal network resources via a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability due to a logic bug in the JiraWhitelist class.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20408|2024-09-16T17:54:00.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 01:35:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20897|2024-09-16T17:33:31.211Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20897</link>
      <description>The avatar upload feature in affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allows remote attackers to achieve Denial of Service via a crafted PNG file. The affected versions are before version 8.5.4, from version 8.6.0 before 8.6.2, and from version 8.7.0 before 8.7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20897|2024-09-16T17:33:31.211Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 00:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36237|2024-09-16T18:34:42.149Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36237</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to view custom field options via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /rest/api/2/customFieldOption/ endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.15.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36237|2024-09-16T18:34:42.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 23:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-9511|2024-09-16T20:58:59.782Z -- atlassian -- atlassian%20fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-9511</link>
      <description>The MultiPathResource class in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible, before version 4.4.1 allows anonymous remote attackers to read arbitrary files via a path traversal vulnerability when Fisheye or Crucible is running on the Microsoft Windows operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-9511|2024-09-16T20:58:59.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43952|2024-09-16T16:58:37.647Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43952</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to restore the default configuration of fields via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the /secure/admin/RestoreDefaults.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.21.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43952|2024-09-16T16:58:37.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 00:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20099|2024-09-16T20:03:50.700Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20099</link>
      <description>The VerifyPopServerConnection!add.jspa component in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.7.0 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery (CSRF). An attacker could exploit this by tricking an administrative user into making malicious HTTP requests, allowing the attacker to enumerate hosts and open ports on the internal network where Jira server is present.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20099|2024-09-16T20:03:50.700Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 14:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29450|2024-09-16T17:49:14.701Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29450</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in the avatar upload feature. The affected versions are before version 7.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29450|2024-09-16T17:49:14.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 00:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36239|2024-09-16T16:28:58.838Z -- atlassian -- jira%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36239</link>
      <description>Jira Data Center, Jira Core Data Center, Jira Software Data Center from version 6.3.0 before 8.5.16, from 8.6.0 before 8.13.8, from 8.14.0 before 8.17.0 and Jira Service Management Data Center from version 2.0.2 before 4.5.16, from version 4.6.0 before 4.13.8, and from version 4.14.0 before 4.17.0 exposed a Ehcache RMI network service which attackers, who can connect to the service, on port 40001 and potentially 40011[0][1], could execute arbitrary code of their choice in Jira through deserialization due to a missing authentication vulnerability. While Atlassian strongly suggests restricting access to the Ehcache ports to only Data Center instances, fixed versions of Jira will now require a shared secret in order to allow access to the Ehcache service. [0] In Jira Data Center, Jira Core Data Center, and Jira Software Data Center versions prior to 7.13.1, the Ehcache object port can be randomly allocated. [1] In Jira Service Management Data Center versions prior to 3.16.1, the Ehcache object port can be randomly allocated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36239|2024-09-16T16:28:58.838Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 10:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43942|2024-09-16T19:04:23.161Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43942</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /rest/collectors/1.0/template/custom endpoint. To exploit this issue, the attacker must trick a user into visiting a malicious website. The affected versions are before version 8.13.15, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43942|2024-09-16T19:04:23.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 02:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20401|2024-09-16T16:23:36.710Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20401</link>
      <description>Various installation setup resources in Jira before version 8.5.2 allow remote attackers to configure a Jira instance, which has not yet finished being installed, via Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20401|2024-09-16T16:23:36.710Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 03:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14175|2024-09-16T20:58:53.451Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14175</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in user macro parameters. The affected versions are before version 7.4.2, and from version 7.5.0 before 7.5.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14175|2024-09-16T20:58:53.451Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 07:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41310|2024-09-16T17:23:06.694Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41310</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Associated Projects feature (/secure/admin/AssociatedProjectsForCustomField.jspa). The affected versions are before version 8.5.19, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.11, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.19.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41310|2024-09-16T17:23:06.694Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 22:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18101|2024-09-16T17:19:13.139Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18101</link>
      <description>Various administrative external system import resources in Atlassian JIRA Server (including JIRA Core) before version 7.6.5, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.3, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.3 and before version 7.9.0 allow remote attackers to run import operations and to determine if an internal service exists through missing permission checks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18101|2024-09-16T17:19:13.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14996|2024-09-16T18:34:31.193Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14996</link>
      <description>The FilterPickerPopup.jspa resource in Jira before version 7.13.7, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.3.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the searchOwnerUserName parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14996|2024-09-16T18:34:31.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 13:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41306|2024-09-16T16:24:16.923Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41306</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view private project and filter names via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Average Time in Status Gadget. The affected versions are before version 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41306|2024-09-16T16:24:16.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 04:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39119|2024-09-16T21:07:31.339Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39119</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow users who have watched an issue to continue receiving updates on the issue even after their Jira account is revoked, via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the issue notification feature. The affected versions are before version 8.19.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39119|2024-09-16T21:07:31.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 22:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5231|2024-09-16T20:31:48.634Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5231</link>
      <description>The ForgotLoginDetails resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.6, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.4, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.4 and from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.2 allows remote attackers to perform a denial of service attack via sending requests to it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5231|2024-09-16T20:31:48.634Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41307|2024-09-16T17:07:40.841Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41307</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to view the names of private projects and private filters via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Workload Pie Chart Gadget. The affected versions are before version 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41307|2024-09-16T17:07:40.841Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 04:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14994|2024-09-16T18:08:34.171Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20desk%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14994</link>
      <description>The Customer Context Filter in Atlassian Jira Service Desk Server and Jira Service Desk Data Center before version 3.9.16, from version 3.10.0 before version 3.16.8, from version 4.0.0 before version 4.1.3, from version 4.2.0 before version 4.2.5, from version 4.3.0 before version 4.3.4, and version 4.4.0 allows remote attackers with portal access to view arbitrary issues in Jira Service Desk projects via a path traversal vulnerability. Note that when the 'Anyone can email the service desk or raise a request in the portal' setting is enabled, an attacker can grant themselves portal access, allowing them to exploit the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14994|2024-09-16T18:08:34.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 14:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15011|2024-09-16T19:50:47.187Z -- atlassian -- application%20links
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15011</link>
      <description>The ListEntityLinksServlet resource in Application Links before version 5.0.12, from version 5.1.0 before version 5.2.11, from version 5.3.0 before version 5.3.7, from version 5.4.0 before 5.4.13, and from version 6.0.0 before 6.0.5 disclosed application link information to non-admin users via a missing permissions check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15011|2024-09-16T19:50:47.187Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 03:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26082|2024-09-16T18:23:40.272Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26082</link>
      <description>The XML Export in Atlassian Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.17.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a stored cross site scripting vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26082|2024-09-16T18:23:40.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 03:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21690|2024-08-22T13:51:43.963Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21690</link>
      <description>This High severity Reflected XSS and CSRF (Cross-Site Request Forgery) vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.19.0, 7.20.0, 8.0.0, 8.1.0, 8.2.0, 8.3.0, 8.4.0, 8.5.0, 8.6.0, 8.7.1, 8.8.0, and 8.9.0 of Confluence Data Center and Server. 
	
	This Reflected XSS and CSRF (Cross-Site Request Forgery) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.1, allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser and force a end user to execute unwanted actions on a web application in which they're currently authenticated which has high impact to confidentiality, low impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		* Confluence Data Center and Server 7.19: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 7.19.26
		
		* Confluence Data Center and Server 8.5: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.5.14
		
		* Confluence Data Center and Server 9.0: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.0.1
		
		
	
	See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives). 
	
	This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21690|2024-08-22T13:51:43.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21689|2024-08-20T10:00:00.967Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21689</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability CVE-2024-21689 was introduced in versions 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0, and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.6, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
 Bamboo Data Center and Server 9.2: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.2.17

 Bamboo Data Center and Server 9.6: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.6.5

See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html]). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives]).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21689|2024-08-20T10:00:00.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T07:52:01.198Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T07:52:01.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21684|2024-07-24T18:45:23.880Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21684</link>
      <description>There is a low severity open redirect vulnerability within affected versions of Bitbucket Data Center. Versions of Bitbucket DC from 8.0.0 to 8.9.12 and 8.19.0 to 8.19.1 are affected by this vulnerability. It is patched in 8.9.13 and 8.19.2.

This open redirect vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 3.1 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect a victim user upon login to Bitbucket Data Center to any arbitrary site which can be utilized for further exploitation which has low impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center customers upgrade to the version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the  supported fixed versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21684|2024-07-24T18:45:23.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-17T15:27:45.652Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-17T15:27:45.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-26T17:43:55.994Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-26T17:43:55.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-18T17:00:02.531Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-18T17:00:02.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-06-10T17:30:00.572Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-06-10T17:30:00.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21686|2024-07-16T20:00:02.617Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21686</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.13 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.3, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21686|2024-07-16T20:00:02.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-16T20:30:00.385Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-16T20:30:00.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-20T03:55:33.558Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-20T03:55:33.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T06:47:39.038Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T06:47:39.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21684|2024-08-01T22:27:36.150Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21684</link>
      <description>There is a low severity open redirect vulnerability within affected versions of Bitbucket Data Center. Versions of Bitbucket DC from 8.0.0 to 8.9.12 and 8.19.0 to 8.19.1 are affected by this vulnerability. It is patched in 8.9.13 and 8.19.2.

This open redirect vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 3.1 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect a victim user upon login to Bitbucket Data Center to any arbitrary site which can be utilized for further exploitation which has low impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center customers upgrade to the version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the  supported fixed versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21684|2024-08-01T22:27:36.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-08-01T22:27:36.035Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-08-01T22:27:36.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-08-01T22:27:35.803Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-08-01T22:27:35.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-08-01T22:27:36.189Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-08-01T22:27:36.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21686|2024-08-01T22:27:36.033Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21686</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.13 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.3, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21686|2024-08-01T22:27:36.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21686|2024-08-07T14:53:10.328Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21686</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.13 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.3, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21686|2024-08-07T14:53:10.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21690|2024-08-21T17:00:02.995Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21690</link>
      <description>This High severity Reflected XSS and CSRF (Cross-Site Request Forgery) vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.19.0, 7.20.0, 8.0.0, 8.1.0, 8.2.0, 8.3.0, 8.4.0, 8.5.0, 8.6.0, 8.7.1, 8.8.0, and 8.9.0 of Confluence Data Center and Server. 
	
	This Reflected XSS and CSRF (Cross-Site Request Forgery) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.1, allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser and force a end user to execute unwanted actions on a web application in which they're currently authenticated which has high impact to confidentiality, low impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		* Confluence Data Center and Server 7.19: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 7.19.26
		
		* Confluence Data Center and Server 8.5: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.5.14
		
		* Confluence Data Center and Server 9.0: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.0.1
		
		
	
	See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives). 
	
	This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21690|2024-08-21T17:00:02.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21689|2024-08-27T13:37:29.036Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21689</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability CVE-2024-21689 was introduced in versions 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0, and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.6, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
 Bamboo Data Center and Server 9.2: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.2.17

 Bamboo Data Center and Server 9.6: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.6.5

See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html]). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives]).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21689|2024-08-27T13:37:29.036Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21689|2024-09-13T11:29:29.907Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21689</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability CVE-2024-21689 was introduced in versions 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0, and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.6, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
 Bamboo Data Center and Server 9.2: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.2.17

 Bamboo Data Center and Server 9.6: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.6.5

See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html]). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives]).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21689|2024-09-13T11:29:29.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
