<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 20:24:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26137|2024-10-03T17:10:16.886Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26137</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in multiple Atlassian products allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to cause additional Servlet Filters to be invoked when the application processes requests or responses. Atlassian has confirmed and fixed the only known security issue associated with this vulnerability: Cross-origin resource sharing (CORS) bypass. Sending a specially crafted HTTP request can invoke the Servlet Filter used to respond to CORS requests, resulting in a CORS bypass. An attacker that can trick a user into requesting a malicious URL can access the vulnerable application with the victim’s permissions. Atlassian Bamboo versions are affected before 8.0.9, from 8.1.0 before 8.1.8, and from 8.2.0 before 8.2.4. Atlassian Bitbucket versions are affected before 7.6.16, from 7.7.0 before 7.17.8, from 7.18.0 before 7.19.5, from 7.20.0 before 7.20.2, from 7.21.0 before 7.21.2, and versions 8.0.0 and 8.1.0. Atlassian Confluence versions are affected before 7.4.17, from 7.5.0 before 7.13.7, from 7.14.0 before 7.14.3, from 7.15.0 before 7.15.2, from 7.16.0 before 7.16.4, from 7.17.0 before 7.17.4, and version 7.21.0. Atlassian Crowd versions are affected before 4.3.8, from 4.4.0 before 4.4.2, and version 5.0.0. Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible versions before 4.8.10 are affected. Atlassian Jira versions are affected before 8.13.22, from 8.14.0 before 8.20.10, and from 8.21.0 before 8.22.4. Atlassian Jira Service Management versions are affected before 4.13.22, from 4.14.0 before 4.20.10, and from 4.21.0 before 4.22.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26137|2024-10-03T17:10:16.886Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 17:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36800|2024-10-03T18:37:53.494Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36800</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow remote attackers without the "Browse Users" permission to view groups via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the browsegroups.action endpoint. The affected versions are before version 4.22.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36800|2024-10-03T18:37:53.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 02:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43956|2024-10-03T14:32:50.447Z -- atlassian -- fisheye
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43956</link>
      <description>The jQuery deserialize library in Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.9 allowed remote attackers to to inject arbitrary HTML and/or JavaScript via a prototype pollution vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43956|2024-10-03T14:32:50.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26135|2024-10-03T15:18:56.225Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26135</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Mobile Plugin for Jira Data Center and Server allows a remote, authenticated user (including a user who joined via the sign-up feature) to perform a full read server-side request forgery via a batch endpoint. This affects Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center from version 8.0.0 before version 8.13.22, from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.10, from version 8.21.0 before 8.22.4. This also affects Jira Management Server and Data Center versions from version 4.0.0 before 4.13.22, from version 4.14.0 before 4.20.10 and from version 4.21.0 before 4.22.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26135|2024-10-03T15:18:56.225Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 05:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36799|2024-10-03T18:44:09.152Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36799</link>
      <description>This issue exists to document that a security improvement in the way that Jira Server and Data Center use templates has been implemented. Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allowed remote attackers with system administrator permissions to execute arbitrary code via Template Injection leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE) in the Email Templates feature. In this case the security improvement was to protect against using the XStream library to be able to execute arbitrary code in velocity templates. The affected versions are before version 8.13.19, from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.7, and from version 8.21.0 before 8.22.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36799|2024-10-03T18:44:09.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 01:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26136|2024-10-03T16:43:16.268Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26136</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in multiple Atlassian products allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to bypass Servlet Filters used by first and third party apps. The impact depends on which filters are used by each app, and how the filters are used. This vulnerability can result in authentication bypass and cross-site scripting. Atlassian has released updates that fix the root cause of this vulnerability, but has not exhaustively enumerated all potential consequences of this vulnerability. Atlassian Bamboo versions are affected before 8.0.9, from 8.1.0 before 8.1.8, and from 8.2.0 before 8.2.4. Atlassian Bitbucket versions are affected before 7.6.16, from 7.7.0 before 7.17.8, from 7.18.0 before 7.19.5, from 7.20.0 before 7.20.2, from 7.21.0 before 7.21.2, and versions 8.0.0 and 8.1.0. Atlassian Confluence versions are affected before 7.4.17, from 7.5.0 before 7.13.7, from 7.14.0 before 7.14.3, from 7.15.0 before 7.15.2, from 7.16.0 before 7.16.4, from 7.17.0 before 7.17.4, and version 7.21.0. Atlassian Crowd versions are affected before 4.3.8, from 4.4.0 before 4.4.2, and version 5.0.0. Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible versions before 4.8.10 are affected. Atlassian Jira versions are affected before 8.13.22, from 8.14.0 before 8.20.10, and from 8.21.0 before 8.22.4. Atlassian Jira Service Management versions are affected before 4.13.22, from 4.14.0 before 4.20.10, and from 4.21.0 before 4.22.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26136|2024-10-03T16:43:16.268Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 17:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43959|2024-10-03T18:37:02.582Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43959</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to access the content of internal network resources via a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the CSV importing feature of JSM Insight. When running in an environment like Amazon EC2, this flaw may be used to access to a metadata resource that provides access credentials and other potentially confidential information. The affected versions are before version 4.13.20, from version 4.14.0 before 4.20.8, and from version 4.21.0 before 4.22.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43959|2024-10-03T18:37:02.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 08:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36290|2024-10-03T18:36:30.272Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36290</link>
      <description>The Livesearch macro in Confluence Server and Data Center before version 7.4.5, from version 7.5.0 before 7.6.3, and from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.4 allows remote attackers with permission to edit a page or blog to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the page excerpt functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36290|2024-10-03T18:36:30.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 04:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26133|2024-10-03T14:55:36.962Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26133</link>
      <description>SharedSecretClusterAuthenticator in Atlassian Bitbucket Data Center versions 5.14.0 and later before 7.6.14, 7.7.0 and later prior to 7.17.6, 7.18.0 and later prior to 7.18.4, 7.19.0 and later prior to 7.19.4, and 7.20.0 allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code via Java deserialization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26133|2024-10-03T14:55:36.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 18:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43955|2024-10-03T14:32:10.648Z -- atlassian -- fisheye
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43955</link>
      <description>The /rest-service-fecru/server-v1 resource in Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.9 allowed authenticated remote attackers to obtain information about installation directories via information disclosure vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43955|2024-10-03T14:32:10.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21689|2024-09-13T11:29:29.907Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21689</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability CVE-2024-21689  was introduced in versions 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0, and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.6, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
 Bamboo Data Center and Server 9.2: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.2.17

 Bamboo Data Center and Server 9.6: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.6.5

See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html]). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives]).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21689|2024-09-13T11:29:29.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21689|2024-08-27T13:37:29.036Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21689</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability CVE-2024-21689  was introduced in versions 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0, and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.6, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
 Bamboo Data Center and Server 9.2: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.2.17

 Bamboo Data Center and Server 9.6: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.6.5

See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html]). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives]).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21689|2024-08-27T13:37:29.036Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21690|2024-08-21T17:00:02.995Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21690</link>
      <description>This High severity Reflected XSS and CSRF (Cross-Site Request Forgery) vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.19.0, 7.20.0, 8.0.0, 8.1.0, 8.2.0, 8.3.0, 8.4.0, 8.5.0, 8.6.0, 8.7.1, 8.8.0, and 8.9.0 of Confluence Data Center and Server. 
	
	This Reflected XSS and CSRF (Cross-Site Request Forgery) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.1, allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser and force a end user to execute unwanted actions on a web application in which they're currently authenticated which has high impact to confidentiality, low impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		* Confluence Data Center and Server 7.19: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 7.19.26
		
		* Confluence Data Center and Server 8.5: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.5.14
		
		* Confluence Data Center and Server 9.0: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.0.1
		
		
	
	See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives). 
	
	This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21690|2024-08-21T17:00:02.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21686|2024-08-07T14:53:10.328Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21686</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.13 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.3, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21686|2024-08-07T14:53:10.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21686|2024-08-01T22:27:36.033Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21686</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.13 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.3, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21686|2024-08-01T22:27:36.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-08-01T22:27:36.189Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-08-01T22:27:36.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-08-01T22:27:35.803Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-08-01T22:27:35.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-08-01T22:27:36.035Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-08-01T22:27:36.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21684|2024-08-01T22:27:36.150Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21684</link>
      <description>There is a low severity open redirect vulnerability within affected versions of Bitbucket Data Center. Versions of Bitbucket DC from 8.0.0 to 8.9.12 and 8.19.0 to 8.19.1 are affected by this vulnerability. It is patched in 8.9.13 and 8.19.2.

This open redirect vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 3.1 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect a victim user upon login to Bitbucket Data Center to any arbitrary site which can be utilized for further exploitation which has low impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center customers upgrade to the version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the  supported fixed versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21684|2024-08-01T22:27:36.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T06:47:39.038Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T06:47:39.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-20T03:55:33.558Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-20T03:55:33.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-16T20:30:00.385Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-16T20:30:00.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21686|2024-07-16T20:00:02.617Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21686</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.13 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.3, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21686|2024-07-16T20:00:02.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-06-10T17:30:00.572Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-06-10T17:30:00.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-18T17:00:02.531Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-18T17:00:02.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-26T17:43:55.994Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-26T17:43:55.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-17T15:27:45.652Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-17T15:27:45.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21684|2024-07-24T18:45:23.880Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21684</link>
      <description>There is a low severity open redirect vulnerability within affected versions of Bitbucket Data Center. Versions of Bitbucket DC from 8.0.0 to 8.9.12 and 8.19.0 to 8.19.1 are affected by this vulnerability. It is patched in 8.9.13 and 8.19.2.

This open redirect vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 3.1 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect a victim user upon login to Bitbucket Data Center to any arbitrary site which can be utilized for further exploitation which has low impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center customers upgrade to the version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the  supported fixed versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21684|2024-07-24T18:45:23.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T07:52:01.198Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T07:52:01.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21689|2024-08-20T10:00:00.967Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21689</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability CVE-2024-21689  was introduced in versions 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0, and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.6, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
 Bamboo Data Center and Server 9.2: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.2.17

 Bamboo Data Center and Server 9.6: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.6.5

See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html]). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives]).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21689|2024-08-20T10:00:00.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21690|2024-08-22T13:51:43.963Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21690</link>
      <description>This High severity Reflected XSS and CSRF (Cross-Site Request Forgery) vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.19.0, 7.20.0, 8.0.0, 8.1.0, 8.2.0, 8.3.0, 8.4.0, 8.5.0, 8.6.0, 8.7.1, 8.8.0, and 8.9.0 of Confluence Data Center and Server. 
	
	This Reflected XSS and CSRF (Cross-Site Request Forgery) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.1, allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser and force a end user to execute unwanted actions on a web application in which they're currently authenticated which has high impact to confidentiality, low impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		* Confluence Data Center and Server 7.19: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 7.19.26
		
		* Confluence Data Center and Server 8.5: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.5.14
		
		* Confluence Data Center and Server 9.0: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.0.1
		
		
	
	See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives). 
	
	This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21690|2024-08-22T13:51:43.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
