<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:24:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5230|2024-08-05T05:33:43.614Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5230</link>
      <description>The issue collector in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.6, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.4, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.4 and from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the error message of custom fields when an invalid value is specified.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5230|2024-08-05T05:33:43.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20098|2024-08-05T02:32:10.613Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20098</link>
      <description>The VerifySmtpServerConnection!add.jspa component in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.7.0 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery (CSRF). An attacker could exploit this by tricking an administrative user into making malicious HTTP requests, allowing the attacker to enumerate hosts and open ports on the internal network where Jira server is present.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20098|2024-08-05T02:32:10.613Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5224|2024-08-05T05:26:46.994Z -- atlassian -- bamboo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5224</link>
      <description>Bamboo did not correctly check if a configured Mercurial repository URI contained values that the Windows operating system may consider argument parameters. An attacker who has permission to create a repository in Bamboo, edit an existing plan in Bamboo that has a non-linked Mercurial repository, or create a plan in Bamboo either globally or in a project using Bamboo Specs can can execute code of their choice on systems that run a vulnerable version of Bamboo on the Windows operating system. All versions of Bamboo starting with 2.7.0 before 6.3.3 (the fixed version for 6.3.x) and from version 6.4.0 before 6.4.1 (the fixed version for 6.4.x) running on the Windows operating system are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5224|2024-08-05T05:26:46.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20105|2024-08-05T02:32:10.632Z -- atlassian -- application%20links
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20105</link>
      <description>The EditApplinkServlet resource in the Atlassian Application Links plugin before version 5.4.20, from version 6.0.0 before version 6.0.12, from version 6.1.0 before version 6.1.2, from version 7.0.0 before version 7.0.1, and from version 7.1.0 before version 7.1.3 allows remote attackers who have obtained access to administrator's session to access the EditApplinkServlet resource without needing to re-authenticate to pass "WebSudo" in products that support "WebSudo" through an improper access control vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20105|2024-08-05T02:32:10.632Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13392|2024-08-05T09:00:35.118Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13392</link>
      <description>Several resources in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.6.0 allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in linked issue keys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13392|2024-08-05T09:00:35.118Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5228|2024-08-05T05:33:42.718Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5228</link>
      <description>The /browse/~raw resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.5.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the handling of response headers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5228|2024-08-05T05:33:42.718Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20898|2024-08-05T02:53:09.498Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20898</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to access sensitive information without being authenticated in the Global permissions screen. The affected versions are before version 8.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20898|2024-08-05T02:53:09.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20101|2024-08-05T02:32:10.530Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20101</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view whitelist rules via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the /rest/whitelist/&lt;version&gt;/check endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.13.3, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.14.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20101|2024-08-05T02:32:10.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20418|2024-08-05T02:39:09.934Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20418</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to prevent users from accessing the instance via an Application Denial of Service vulnerability in the /rendering/wiki endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20418|2024-08-05T02:39:09.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13390|2024-08-05T09:00:35.117Z -- atlassian -- cloudtoken
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13390</link>
      <description>Unauthenticated access to cloudtoken daemon on Linux via network from version 0.1.1 before version 0.1.24 allows attackers on the same subnet to gain temporary AWS credentials for the users' roles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13390|2024-08-05T09:00:35.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20416|2024-08-05T02:39:10.084Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20416</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the project configuration feature. The affected versions are before version 8.3.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20416|2024-08-05T02:39:10.084Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13400|2024-08-05T09:00:35.135Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13400</link>
      <description>Several administrative resources in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.9, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3, from version 7.11.0 before version 7.11.3, from version 7.12.0 before version 7.12.3, and before version 7.13.1 allow remote attackers who have obtained access to administrator's session to access certain administrative resources without needing to re-authenticate to pass "WebSudo" through an improper access control vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13400|2024-08-05T09:00:35.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20235|2024-08-05T11:58:18.789Z -- atlassian -- sourcetree%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20235</link>
      <description>There was an argument injection vulnerability in Atlassian Sourcetree for Windows from version 0.5a before version 3.0.15 via filenames in Mercurial repositories. A remote attacker with permission to commit to a Mercurial repository linked in Sourcetree for Windows is able to exploit this issue to gain code execution on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20235|2024-08-05T11:58:18.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20899|2024-08-05T02:53:09.541Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20899</link>
      <description>The Gadget API in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center in affected versions allows remote attackers to make Jira unresponsive via repeated requests to a certain endpoint in the Gadget API. The affected versions are before version 8.5.4, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.6.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20899|2024-08-05T02:53:09.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13393|2024-08-05T09:00:35.145Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20questions
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13393</link>
      <description>The convertCommentToAnswer resource in Atlassian Confluence Questions before version 2.6.6, the bundled version of Confluence Questions was updated to a fixed version in Confluence version 6.9.0, allows remote attackers to modify a comment into an answer via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13393|2024-08-05T09:00:35.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20100|2024-08-05T02:32:10.519Z -- atlassian -- application%20links
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20100</link>
      <description>The Atlassian Application Links plugin is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery (CSRF). The following versions are affected: all versions prior to 5.4.21, from version 6.0.0 before version 6.0.12, from version 6.1.0 before version 6.1.2, from version 7.0.0 before version 7.0.2, and from version 7.1.0 before version 7.1.3. The vulnerable plugin is used by Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.7.0. An attacker could exploit this by tricking an administrative user into making malicious HTTP requests, allowing the attacker to enumerate hosts and open ports on the internal network where Jira server is present.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20100|2024-08-05T02:32:10.519Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13389|2024-08-05T09:00:35.138Z -- atlassian -- confluence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13389</link>
      <description>The attachment resource in Atlassian Confluence before version 6.6.1 allows remote attackers to spoof web content in the Mozilla Firefox Browser through attachments that have a content-type of application/rdf+xml.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13389|2024-08-05T09:00:35.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20104|2024-08-05T02:32:10.611Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20104</link>
      <description>The OpenID client application in Atlassian Crowd before version 3.6.2, and from version 3.7.0 before 3.7.1 allows remote attackers to perform a Denial of Service attack via an XML Entity Expansion vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20104|2024-08-05T02:32:10.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14997|2024-08-05T00:34:53.000Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14997</link>
      <description>The AccessLogFilter class in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote anonymous attackers to learn details about other users, including their username, via an information expose through caching vulnerability when Jira is configured with a reverse Proxy and or a load balancer with caching or a CDN.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14997|2024-08-05T00:34:53.000Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20411|2024-08-05T02:39:09.917Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20411</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to modify Wallboard settings via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 7.13.9, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20411|2024-08-05T02:39:09.917Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15013|2024-08-05T00:34:53.218Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15013</link>
      <description>The WorkflowResource class removeStatus method in Jira before version 7.13.12, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.4.3, and from version 8.5.0 before version 8.5.2 allows authenticated remote attackers who do not have project administration access to remove a configured issue status from a project via a missing authorisation check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15013|2024-08-05T00:34:53.218Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5223|2024-08-05T05:26:47.210Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5223</link>
      <description>Fisheye and Crucible did not correctly check if a configured Mercurial repository URI contained values that the Windows operating system may consider argument parameters. An attacker who has permission to add a repository in Fisheye or Crucible can execute code of their choice on systems that run a vulnerable version of Fisheye or Crucible on the Windows operating system. All versions of Fisheye and Crucible before 4.4.6 (the fixed version for 4.4.x) and from 4.5.0 before 4.5.3 (the fixed version for 4.5.x) are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5223|2024-08-05T05:26:47.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13399|2024-08-05T09:00:35.148Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13399</link>
      <description>The Microsoft Windows Installer for Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.6.1 allows local attackers to escalate privileges because of weak permissions on the installation directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13399|2024-08-05T09:00:35.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13388|2024-08-05T09:00:35.142Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13388</link>
      <description>The review attachment resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.5.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in attached files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13388|2024-08-05T09:00:35.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13398|2024-08-05T09:00:35.196Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13398</link>
      <description>The administrative smart-commits resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.5.4 allows remote attackers to modify smart-commit settings via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13398|2024-08-05T09:00:35.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5229|2024-08-05T05:33:42.777Z -- atlassian -- universal%20plugin%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5229</link>
      <description>The NotificationRepresentationFactoryImpl class in Atlassian Universal Plugin Manager before version 2.22.9 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the name of user submitted add-on names.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5229|2024-08-05T05:33:42.777Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20415|2024-08-05T02:39:09.853Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20415</link>
      <description>Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center in affected versions allows remote attackers to modify logging and profiling settings via a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 7.13.3, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20415|2024-08-05T02:39:09.853Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5232|2024-08-05T05:33:43.591Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5232</link>
      <description>The EditIssue.jspa resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.7 and from version 7.7.0 before version 7.10.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the issuetype parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5232|2024-08-05T05:33:43.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15005|2024-08-05T00:34:53.099Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15005</link>
      <description>The Atlassian Troubleshooting and Support Tools plugin prior to version 1.17.2 allows an unprivileged user to initiate periodic log scans and send the results to a user-specified email address due to a missing authorization check. The email message may contain configuration information about the application that the plugin is installed into. A vulnerable version of the plugin is included with Bitbucket Server / Data Center before 6.6.0, Confluence Server / Data Center before 7.0.1, Jira Server / Data Center before 8.3.2, Crowd / Crowd Data Center before 3.6.0, Fisheye before 4.7.2, Crucible before 4.7.2, and Bamboo before 6.10.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15005|2024-08-05T00:34:53.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20403|2024-08-05T02:39:09.831Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20403</link>
      <description>The API in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.6.0 allows remote attackers to determine if a Jira project key exists or not via an information disclosure vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20403|2024-08-05T02:39:09.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13395|2024-08-05T09:00:35.128Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13395</link>
      <description>Various resources in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.8, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3 and before version 7.11.1 allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the epic colour field of an issue while an issue is being moved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13395|2024-08-05T09:00:35.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13391|2024-08-05T09:00:35.137Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13391</link>
      <description>The ProfileLinkUserFormat component of Jira Server before version 7.6.8, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3 and from version 7.11.0 before version 7.11.2 allows remote attackers who can access &amp; view an issue to obtain the email address of the reporter and assignee user of an issue despite the configured email visibility setting being set to hidden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13391|2024-08-05T09:00:35.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15010|2024-08-05T00:34:53.027Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15010</link>
      <description>Bitbucket Server and Bitbucket Data Center versions starting from version 3.0.0 before version 5.16.11, from version 6.0.0 before 6.0.11, from version 6.1.0 before 6.1.9, from version 6.2.0 before 6.2.7, from version 6.3.0 before 6.3.6, from version 6.4.0 before 6.4.4, from version 6.5.0 before 6.5.3, from version 6.6.0 before 6.6.3, from version 6.7.0 before 6.7.3, from version 6.8.0 before 6.8.2, and from version 6.9.0 before 6.9.1 had a Remote Code Execution vulnerability via certain user input fields. A remote attacker with user level permissions can exploit this vulnerability to run arbitrary commands on the victim's systems. Using a specially crafted payload as user input, the attacker can execute arbitrary commands on the victim's Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15010|2024-08-05T00:34:53.027Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13404|2024-08-05T09:00:35.190Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13404</link>
      <description>The VerifyPopServerConnection resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.10, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3, from version 7.11.0 before version 7.11.3, from version 7.12.0 before version 7.12.3, and from version 7.13.0 before version 7.13.1 allows remote attackers who have administrator rights to determine the existence of internal hosts &amp; open ports and in some cases obtain service information from internal network resources via a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13404|2024-08-05T09:00:35.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13394|2024-08-05T09:00:35.143Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20questions
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13394</link>
      <description>The acceptAnswer resource in Atlassian Confluence Questions before version 2.6.6, the bundled version of Confluence Questions was updated to a fixed version in Confluence version 6.9.0, allows remote attackers to modify a comment into an answer via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13394|2024-08-05T09:00:35.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20099|2024-08-05T02:32:10.521Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20099</link>
      <description>The VerifyPopServerConnection!add.jspa component in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.7.0 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery (CSRF). An attacker could exploit this by tricking an administrative user into making malicious HTTP requests, allowing the attacker to enumerate hosts and open ports on the internal network where Jira server is present.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20099|2024-08-05T02:32:10.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20102|2024-08-05T02:32:10.529Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20102</link>
      <description>The attachment-uploading feature in Atlassian Confluence Server from version 6.14.0 through version 6.14.3, and version 6.15.0 before version 6.15.5 allows remote attackers to achieve stored cross-site- scripting (SXSS) via a malicious attachment with a modified `mimeType` parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20102|2024-08-05T02:32:10.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13402|2024-08-05T09:00:35.161Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13402</link>
      <description>Many resources in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.9, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3, from version 7.11.0 before version 7.11.3, from version 7.12.0 before version 7.12.3, and before version 7.13.1 allow remote attackers to attack users, in some cases be able to obtain a user's Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) token, via a open redirect vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13402|2024-08-05T09:00:35.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20408|2024-08-05T02:39:09.927Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20408</link>
      <description>The /plugins/servlet/gadgets/makeRequest resource in Jira before version 8.7.0 allows remote attackers to access the content of internal network resources via a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability due to a logic bug in the JiraWhitelist class.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20408|2024-08-05T02:39:09.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15008|2024-08-05T00:34:53.154Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15008</link>
      <description>The /plugins/servlet/branchreview resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.7.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the reviewedBranch parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15008|2024-08-05T00:34:53.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14995|2024-08-05T00:34:53.143Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14995</link>
      <description>The /rest/api/1.0/render resource in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote anonymous attackers to determine if an attachment with a specific name exists and if an issue key is valid via a missing permissions check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14995|2024-08-05T00:34:53.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20412|2024-08-05T02:39:09.869Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20412</link>
      <description>The Convert Sub-Task to Issue page in affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to enumerate the following information via an Improper Authentication vulnerability: Workflow names; Project Key, if it is part of the workflow name; Issue Keys; Issue Types; Status Types. The affected versions are before version 7.13.9, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20412|2024-08-05T02:39:09.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20233|2024-08-05T11:58:18.690Z -- atlassian -- universal%20plugin%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20233</link>
      <description>The Upload add-on resource in Atlassian Universal Plugin Manager before version 2.22.14 allows remote attackers who have system administrator privileges to read files, make network requests and perform a denial of service attack via an XML External Entity vulnerability in the parsing of atlassian plugin xml files in an uploaded JAR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20233|2024-08-05T11:58:18.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20234|2024-08-05T11:58:18.799Z -- atlassian -- sourcetree%20for%20macos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20234</link>
      <description>There was an argument injection vulnerability in Atlassian Sourcetree for macOS from version 1.2 before version 3.1.1 via filenames in Mercurial repositories. A remote attacker with permission to commit to a Mercurial repository linked in Sourcetree for macOS is able to exploit this issue to gain code execution on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20234|2024-08-05T11:58:18.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13385|2024-08-05T09:00:35.151Z -- atlassian -- sourcetree%20for%20macos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13385</link>
      <description>There was an argument injection vulnerability in Sourcetree for macOS via filenames in Mercurial repositories. An attacker with permission to commit to a Mercurial repository linked in Sourcetree for macOS is able to exploit this issue to gain code execution on the system. Versions of Sourcetree for macOS from 1.0b2 before 2.7.6 are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13385|2024-08-05T09:00:35.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20097|2024-08-05T02:32:10.612Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20097</link>
      <description>Bitbucket Server and Bitbucket Data Center versions starting from 1.0.0 before 5.16.11, from version 6.0.0 before 6.0.11, from version 6.1.0 before 6.1.9, from version 6.2.0 before 6.2.7, from version 6.3.0 before 6.3.6, from version 6.4.0 before 6.4.4, from version 6.5.0 before 6.5.3, from version 6.6.0 before 6.6.3, from version 6.7.0 before 6.7.3, from version 6.8.0 before 6.8.2, from version 6.9.0 before 6.9.1 had a Remote Code Execution vulnerability via the post-receive hook. A remote attacker with permission to clone and push files to a repository on the victim's Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center instance, can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands on the Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center systems, using a file with specially crafted content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20097|2024-08-05T02:32:10.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15007|2024-08-05T00:34:52.856Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15007</link>
      <description>The review resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.7.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the name of a missing branch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15007|2024-08-05T00:34:52.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14998|2024-08-05T00:34:53.105Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14998</link>
      <description>The Webwork action Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) protection implementation in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote attackers to bypass its protection via "cookie tossing" a CSRF cookie from a subdomain of a Jira instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14998|2024-08-05T00:34:53.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13403|2024-08-05T09:00:35.157Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13403</link>
      <description>The two-dimensional filter statistics gadget in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.10, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.12.4, and from version 7.13.0 before version 7.13.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the name of a saved filter when displayed on a Jira dashboard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13403|2024-08-05T09:00:35.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20413|2024-08-05T02:39:09.910Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20413</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability on the UserPickerBrowser.jspa page. The affected versions are before version 7.13.9, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20413|2024-08-05T02:39:09.910Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14999|2024-08-05T00:34:53.081Z -- atlassian -- universal%20plugin%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14999</link>
      <description>The Uninstall REST endpoint in Atlassian Universal Plugin Manager before version 2.22.19, from version 3.0.0 before version 3.0.3 and from version 4.0.0 before version 4.0.3 allows remote attackers to uninstall plugins using a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability on an authenticated administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14999|2024-08-05T00:34:53.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20901|2024-08-05T02:53:09.434Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20901</link>
      <description>The login.jsp resource in Jira before version 8.5.2, and from version 8.6.0 before version 8.6.1 allows remote attackers to redirect users to a different website which they may use as part of performing a phishing attack via an open redirect in the os_destination parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20901|2024-08-05T02:53:09.434Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13397|2024-08-05T09:00:35.170Z -- atlassian -- sourcetree%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13397</link>
      <description>There was an argument injection vulnerability in Sourcetree for Windows from version 0.5.1.0 before version 3.0.0 via Git subrepositories in Mercurial repositories. An attacker with permission to commit to a Mercurial repository linked in Sourcetree for Windows is able to exploit this issue to gain code execution on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13397|2024-08-05T09:00:35.170Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20400|2024-08-05T02:39:09.764Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20400</link>
      <description>The usage of Tomcat in Jira before version 8.5.2 allows local attackers with permission to write a dll file to a directory in the global path environmental variable can inject code into via a DLL hijacking vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20400|2024-08-05T02:39:09.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14996|2024-08-05T00:34:53.093Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14996</link>
      <description>The FilterPickerPopup.jspa resource in Jira before version 7.13.7, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.3.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the searchOwnerUserName parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14996|2024-08-05T00:34:53.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20106|2024-08-05T02:32:10.627Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20106</link>
      <description>Comment properties in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 7.13.12, from 8.0.0 before version 8.5.4, and 8.6.0 before version 8.6.1 allows remote attackers to make comments on a ticket to which they do not have commenting permissions via a broken access control bug.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20106|2024-08-05T02:32:10.627Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20902|2024-08-05T02:53:09.638Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20902</link>
      <description>Upgrading Crowd via XML Data Transfer can reactivate a disabled user from OpenLDAP. The affected versions are from before version 3.4.6 and from 3.5.0 before 3.5.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20902|2024-08-05T02:53:09.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15000|2024-08-05T00:34:52.974Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15000</link>
      <description>The commit diff rest endpoint in Bitbucket Server and Data Center before 5.16.10 (the fixed version for 5.16.x ), from 6.0.0 before 6.0.10 (the fixed version for 6.0.x), from 6.1.0 before 6.1.8 (the fixed version for 6.1.x), from 6.2.0 before 6.2.6 (the fixed version for 6.2.x), from 6.3.0 before 6.3.5 (the fixed version for 6.3.x), from 6.4.0 before 6.4.3 (the fixed version for 6.4.x), and from 6.5.0 before 6.5.2 (the fixed version for 6.5.x) allows remote attackers who have permission to access a repository, if public access is enabled for a project or repository then attackers are able to exploit this issue anonymously, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the system and execute commands via injecting additional arguments into git commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15000|2024-08-05T00:34:52.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20240|2024-08-05T11:58:18.812Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20240</link>
      <description>The administrative linker functionality in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.7.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the href parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20240|2024-08-05T11:58:18.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20405|2024-08-05T02:39:09.769Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20405</link>
      <description>The JMX monitoring flag in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.6.0 allows remote attackers to turn the JMX monitoring flag off or on via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20405|2024-08-05T02:39:09.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20406|2024-08-05T02:39:09.888Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20406</link>
      <description>The usage of Tomcat in Confluence on the Microsoft Windows operating system before version 7.0.5, and from version 7.1.0 before version 7.1.1 allows local system attackers who have permission to write a DLL file in a directory in the global path environmental variable variable to inject code &amp; escalate their privileges via a DLL hijacking vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20406|2024-08-05T02:39:09.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15003|2024-08-05T00:34:53.128Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20desk%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15003</link>
      <description>The Customer Context Filter in Atlassian Jira Service Desk Server and Jira Service Desk Data Center before 3.9.17, from 3.10.0 before 3.16.10, from 4.0.0 before 4.2.6, from 4.3.0 before 4.3.5, from 4.4.0 before 4.4.3, and from 4.5.0 before 4.5.1 allows remote attackers with portal access to view arbitrary issues in Jira Service Desk projects via authorization bypass. Note that when the 'Anyone can email the service desk or raise a request in the portal' setting is enabled, an attacker can grant themselves portal access, allowing them to exploit the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15003|2024-08-05T00:34:53.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20241|2024-08-05T11:58:18.849Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20241</link>
      <description>The Edit upload resource for a review in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.7.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the wbuser parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20241|2024-08-05T11:58:18.849Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20824|2024-08-05T12:12:27.311Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20824</link>
      <description>The WallboardServlet resource in Jira before version 7.13.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the cyclePeriod parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20824|2024-08-05T12:12:27.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20827|2024-08-05T12:12:27.271Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20827</link>
      <description>The activity stream gadget in Jira before version 7.13.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the country parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20827|2024-08-05T12:12:27.271Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20826|2024-08-05T12:12:28.703Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20826</link>
      <description>The inline-create rest resource in Jira before version 7.12.3 allows authenticated remote attackers to set the reporter in issues via a missing authorisation check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20826|2024-08-05T12:12:28.703Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20401|2024-08-05T02:39:09.809Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20401</link>
      <description>Various installation setup resources in Jira before version 8.5.2 allow remote attackers to configure a Jira instance, which has not yet finished being installed, via Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20401|2024-08-05T02:39:09.809Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13387|2024-08-05T09:00:35.141Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13387</link>
      <description>The IncomingMailServers resource in Atlassian JIRA Server before version 7.6.7, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3 and from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the messagesThreshold parameter as the fix for CVE-2017-18039 was incomplete.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13387|2024-08-05T09:00:35.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14994|2024-08-05T00:34:52.769Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20desk%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14994</link>
      <description>The Customer Context Filter in Atlassian Jira Service Desk Server and Jira Service Desk Data Center before version 3.9.16, from version 3.10.0 before version 3.16.8, from version 4.0.0 before version 4.1.3, from version 4.2.0 before version 4.2.5, from version 4.3.0 before version 4.3.4, and version 4.4.0 allows remote attackers with portal access to view arbitrary issues in Jira Service Desk projects via a path traversal vulnerability. Note that when the 'Anyone can email the service desk or raise a request in the portal' setting is enabled, an attacker can grant themselves portal access, allowing them to exploit the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14994|2024-08-05T00:34:52.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20238|2024-08-05T11:58:19.098Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20238</link>
      <description>Various rest resources in Atlassian Crowd before version 3.2.7 and from version 3.3.0 before version 3.3.4 allow remote attackers to authenticate using an expired user session via an insufficient session expiration vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20238|2024-08-05T11:58:19.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13401|2024-08-05T09:00:35.157Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13401</link>
      <description>The XsrfErrorAction resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.9, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3, from version 7.11.0 before version 7.11.3, from version 7.12.0 before version 7.12.3, and before version 7.13.1 allows remote attackers to obtain a user's Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) token through an open redirect vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13401|2024-08-05T09:00:35.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20402|2024-08-05T02:39:09.826Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20402</link>
      <description>Support zip files in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.6.0 could be downloaded by a System Administrator user without requiring the user to re-enter their password via an improper authorization vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20402|2024-08-05T02:39:09.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20239|2024-08-05T11:58:18.795Z -- atlassian -- atlassian%20application%20links
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20239</link>
      <description>Application Links before version 5.0.11, from version 5.1.0 before 5.2.10, from version 5.3.0 before 5.3.6, from version 5.4.0 before 5.4.12, and from version 6.0.0 before 6.0.4 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the applinkStartingUrl parameter. The product is used as a plugin in various Atlassian products where the following are affected: Confluence before version 6.15.2, Crucible before version 4.7.0, Crowd before version 3.4.3, Fisheye before version 4.7.0, Jira before version 7.13.3 and 8.x before 8.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20239|2024-08-05T11:58:18.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15012|2024-08-05T00:34:53.124Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15012</link>
      <description>Bitbucket Server and Bitbucket Data Center from version 4.13. before 5.16.11, from version 6.0.0 before 6.0.11, from version 6.1.0 before 6.1.9, from version 6.2.0 before 6.2.7, from version 6.3.0 before 6.3.6, from version 6.4.0 before 6.4.4, from version 6.5.0 before 6.5.3, from version 6.6.0 before 6.6.3, from version 6.7.0 before 6.7.3, from version 6.8.0 before 6.8.2, from version 6.9.0 before 6.9.1 had a Remote Code Execution vulnerability via the edit-file request. A remote attacker with write permission on a repository can write to any arbitrary file to the victims Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center instance using the edit-file endpoint, if the user has Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center running, and has the permission to write the file at that destination. In some cases, this can result in execution of arbitrary code by the victims Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15012|2024-08-05T00:34:53.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13396|2024-08-05T09:00:35.267Z -- atlassian -- sourcetree%20for%20macos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13396</link>
      <description>There was an argument injection vulnerability in Sourcetree for macOS from version 1.0b2 before version 3.0.0 via Git subrepositories in Mercurial repositories. An attacker with permission to commit to a Mercurial repository linked in Sourcetree for macOS is able to exploit this issue to gain code execution on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13396|2024-08-05T09:00:35.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20419|2024-08-05T02:39:09.910Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20419</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a DLL hijacking vulnerability in Tomcat. The affected versions are before version 8.5.5, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.7.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20419|2024-08-05T02:39:09.910Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15011|2024-08-05T00:34:53.139Z -- atlassian -- application%20links
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15011</link>
      <description>The ListEntityLinksServlet resource in Application Links before version 5.0.12, from version 5.1.0 before version 5.2.11, from version 5.3.0 before version 5.3.7, from version 5.4.0 before 5.4.13, and from version 6.0.0 before 6.0.5 disclosed application link information to non-admin users via a missing permissions check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15011|2024-08-05T00:34:53.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20903|2024-08-05T02:53:09.631Z -- atlassian -- %40atlaskit%2Feditor-core
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20903</link>
      <description>The hyperlinks functionality in atlaskit/editor-core in before version 113.1.5 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in link targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20903|2024-08-05T02:53:09.631Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20236|2024-08-05T11:58:19.094Z -- atlassian -- sourcetree%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20236</link>
      <description>There was an command injection vulnerability in Sourcetree for Windows from version 0.5a before version 3.0.10 via URI handling. A remote attacker could send a malicious URI to a victim using Sourcetree for Windows to exploit this issue to gain code execution on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20236|2024-08-05T11:58:19.094Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20232|2024-08-05T11:58:18.959Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20232</link>
      <description>The labels widget gadget in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.11 and from version 7.7.0 before version 7.13.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the rendering of retrieved content from a url location that could be manipulated by the up_projectid widget preference setting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20232|2024-08-05T11:58:18.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20237|2024-08-05T11:58:18.553Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20237</link>
      <description>Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center before version 6.13.1 allows an authenticated user to download a deleted page via the word export feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20237|2024-08-05T11:58:18.553Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20404|2024-08-05T02:39:09.915Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20404</link>
      <description>The API in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.6.0 allows authenticated remote attackers to determine project titles they do not have access to via an improper authorization vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20404|2024-08-05T02:39:09.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20407|2024-08-05T02:39:10.018Z -- atlassian -- jira%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20407</link>
      <description>The ConfigureBambooRelease resource in Jira Software and Jira Software Data Center before version 8.6.1 allows authenticated remote attackers to view release version information in projects that they do not have access to through an missing authorisation check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20407|2024-08-05T02:39:10.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15004|2024-08-05T00:34:52.994Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20desk%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15004</link>
      <description>The Customer Context Filter in Atlassian Jira Service Desk Server and Jira Service Desk Data Center before 3.9.17, from 3.10.0 before 3.16.10, from 4.0.0 before 4.2.6, from 4.3.0 before 4.3.5, from 4.4.0 before 4.4.3, and from 4.5.0 before 4.5.1 allows remote attackers with portal access to view arbitrary issues in Jira Service Desk projects via a path traversal vulnerability. Note that when the 'Anyone can email the service desk or raise a request in the portal' setting is enabled, an attacker can grant themselves portal access, allowing them to exploit the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15004|2024-08-05T00:34:52.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5226|2024-08-05T05:33:42.778Z -- atlassian -- sourcetree%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5226</link>
      <description>There was an argument injection vulnerability in Sourcetree for Windows via Mercurial repository tag name that is going to be deleted. An attacker with permission to create a tag on a Mercurial repository linked in Sourcetree for Windows is able to exploit this issue to gain code execution on the system. All versions of Sourcetree for Windows before 2.5.5.0 are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5226|2024-08-05T05:33:42.778Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20900|2024-08-05T02:53:09.616Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20900</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Add Field module. The affected versions are before version 8.7.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20900|2024-08-05T02:53:09.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20897|2024-08-05T02:53:09.487Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20897</link>
      <description>The avatar upload feature in affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allows remote attackers to achieve Denial of Service via a crafted PNG file. The affected versions are before version 8.5.4, from version 8.6.0 before 8.6.2, and from version 8.7.0 before 8.7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20897|2024-08-05T02:53:09.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5225|2024-08-05T05:33:42.723Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5225</link>
      <description>In browser editing in Atlassian Bitbucket Server from version 4.13.0 before 5.4.8 (the fixed version for 4.13.0 through 5.4.7), 5.5.0 before 5.5.8 (the fixed version for 5.5.x), 5.6.0 before 5.6.5 (the fixed version for 5.6.x), 5.7.0 before 5.7.3 (the fixed version for 5.7.x), and 5.8.0 before 5.8.2 (the fixed version for 5.8.x), allows authenticated users to gain remote code execution using the in browser editing feature via editing a symbolic link within a repository.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5225|2024-08-05T05:33:42.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20414|2024-08-05T02:39:09.865Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20414</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Issue Navigator Basic Search. The affected versions are before version 7.13.9, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20414|2024-08-05T02:39:09.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13386|2024-08-05T09:00:35.135Z -- atlassian -- sourcetree%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13386</link>
      <description>There was an argument injection vulnerability in Sourcetree for Windows via filenames in Mercurial repositories. An attacker with permission to commit to a Mercurial repository linked in Sourcetree for Windows is able to exploit this issue to gain code execution on the system. Versions of Sourcetree for Windows before version 2.6.9 are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13386|2024-08-05T09:00:35.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15006|2024-08-05T00:34:53.000Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15006</link>
      <description>There was a man-in-the-middle (MITM) vulnerability present in the Confluence Previews plugin in Confluence Server and Confluence Data Center. This plugin was used to facilitate communication with the Atlassian Companion application. The Confluence Previews plugin in Confluence Server and Confluence Data Center communicated with the Companion application via the atlassian-domain-for-localhost-connections-only.com domain name, the DNS A record of which points at 127.0.0.1. Additionally, a signed certificate for the domain was publicly distributed with the Companion application. An attacker in the position to control DNS resolution of their victim could carry out a man-in-the-middle (MITM) attack between Confluence Server (or Confluence Data Center) and the atlassian-domain-for-localhost-connections-only.com domain intended to be used with the Companion application. This certificate has been revoked, however, usage of the atlassian-domain-for-localhost-connections-only.com domain name was still present in Confluence Server and Confluence Data Center. An attacker could perform the described attack by denying their victim access to certificate revocation information, and carry out a man-in-the-middle (MITM) attack to observe files being edited using the Companion application and/or modify them, and access some limited user information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15006|2024-08-05T00:34:53.000Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20409|2024-08-05T02:39:09.850Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20409</link>
      <description>The way in which velocity templates were used in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center prior to version 8.8.0 allowed remote attackers to gain remote code execution if they were able to exploit a server side template injection vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20409|2024-08-05T02:39:09.850Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15009|2024-08-05T00:34:53.014Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15009</link>
      <description>The /json/profile/removeStarAjax.do resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.0 allows remote attackers to remove another user's favourite setting for a project via an improper authorization vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15009|2024-08-05T00:34:53.014Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15001|2024-08-05T00:34:52.905Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15001</link>
      <description>The Jira Importers Plugin in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Cente from version with 7.0.10 before 7.6.16, from 7.7.0 before 7.13.8, from 8.0.0 before 8.1.3, from 8.2.0 before 8.2.5, from 8.3.0 before 8.3.4 and from 8.4.0 before 8.4.1 allows remote attackers with Administrator permissions to gain remote code execution via a template injection vulnerability through the use of a crafted PUT request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15001|2024-08-05T00:34:52.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20410|2024-08-05T02:39:09.835Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20410</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the comment restriction feature. The affected versions are before version 7.6.17, from version 7.7.0 before 7.13.9, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20410|2024-08-05T02:39:09.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5227|2024-08-05T05:33:43.998Z -- atlassian -- atlassian%20application%20links
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5227</link>
      <description>Various administrative application link resources in Atlassian Application Links before version 5.4.4 allow remote attackers with administration rights to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the display url of a configured application link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5227|2024-08-05T05:33:43.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5231|2024-08-05T05:33:43.763Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5231</link>
      <description>The ForgotLoginDetails resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.6, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.4, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.4 and from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.2 allows remote attackers to perform a denial of service attack via sending requests to it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5231|2024-08-05T05:33:43.763Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21686|2024-08-01T22:27:36.033Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21686</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.13 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.3, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21686|2024-08-01T22:27:36.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-08-01T22:27:36.189Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-08-01T22:27:36.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21678|2024-08-01T22:27:35.810Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21678</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in version 2.7.0 of Confluence Data Center.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.5, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, low impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.
Data Center

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.7.0 to 8.7.1|8.8.0 recommended or 8.7.2|
|from 8.6.0 to 8.6.1|8.8.0 recommended|
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
Server

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:


||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|

See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html]). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives]).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21678|2024-08-01T22:27:35.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-08-01T22:27:35.803Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-08-01T22:27:35.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21677|2024-08-01T22:27:35.969Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21677</link>
      <description>This High severity Path Traversal vulnerability was introduced in version 6.13.0 of Confluence Data Center. This Path Traversal vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.3, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit an undefinable vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions: Data Center Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version and that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version.

If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives. 

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21677|2024-08-01T22:27:35.969Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21682|2024-08-01T22:27:35.986Z -- atlassian -- assets%20discovery%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21682</link>
      <description>This High severity Injection vulnerability was introduced in Assets Discovery 1.0 - 6.2.0 (all versions). 

Assets Discovery, which can be downloaded via Atlassian Marketplace, is a network scanning tool that can be used with or without an agent with Jira Service Management Cloud, Data Center or Server. It detects hardware and software that is connected to your local network and extracts detailed information about each asset. This data can then be imported into Assets in Jira Service Management to help you manage all of the devices and configuration items within your local network.

This Injection vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to modify the actions taken by a system call which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Assets Discovery customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/assetapps/assets-discovery-3-2-1-cloud-6-2-1-data_center-1333987182.html). You can download the latest version of Assets Discovery from the Atlassian Marketplace (https://marketplace.atlassian.com/apps/1214668/assets-discovery?hosting=datacenter&amp;amp;tab=installation).

This vulnerability was reported via our Penetration Testing program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21682|2024-08-01T22:27:35.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-08-01T22:27:36.035Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-08-01T22:27:36.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21684|2024-08-01T22:27:36.150Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21684</link>
      <description>There is a low severity open redirect vulnerability within affected versions of Bitbucket Data Center. Versions of Bitbucket DC from 8.0.0 to 8.9.12 and 8.19.0 to 8.19.1 are affected by this vulnerability. It is patched in 8.9.13 and 8.19.2.

This open redirect vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 3.1 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect a victim user upon login to Bitbucket Data Center to any arbitrary site which can be utilized for further exploitation which has low impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center customers upgrade to the version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the  supported fixed versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21684|2024-08-01T22:27:36.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T06:47:39.038Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T06:47:39.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-20T03:55:33.558Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-20T03:55:33.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-16T20:30:00.385Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-16T20:30:00.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21686|2024-07-16T20:00:02.617Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21686</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.13 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.3, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21686|2024-07-16T20:00:02.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21677|2024-06-21T18:07:46.098Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21677</link>
      <description>This High severity Path Traversal vulnerability was introduced in version 6.13.0 of Confluence Data Center. This Path Traversal vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.3, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit an undefinable vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions: Data Center Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version and that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version.

If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives. 

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21677|2024-06-21T18:07:46.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21678|2024-06-04T17:38:08.576Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21678</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in version 2.7.0 of Confluence Data Center.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.5, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, low impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.
Data Center

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.7.0 to 8.7.1|8.8.0 recommended or 8.7.2|
|from 8.6.0 to 8.6.1|8.8.0 recommended|
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
Server

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:


||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|

See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html]). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives]).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21678|2024-06-04T17:38:08.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21677|2024-03-19T17:30:00.500Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21677</link>
      <description>This High severity Path Traversal vulnerability was introduced in version 6.13.0 of Confluence Data Center. This Path Traversal vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.3, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit an undefinable vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions: Data Center Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version and that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version.

If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives. 

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21677|2024-03-19T17:30:00.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21682|2024-02-20T18:00:00.699Z -- atlassian -- assets%20discovery%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21682</link>
      <description>This High severity Injection vulnerability was introduced in Assets Discovery 1.0 - 6.2.0 (all versions). 

Assets Discovery, which can be downloaded via Atlassian Marketplace, is a network scanning tool that can be used with or without an agent with Jira Service Management Cloud, Data Center or Server. It detects hardware and software that is connected to your local network and extracts detailed information about each asset. This data can then be imported into Assets in Jira Service Management to help you manage all of the devices and configuration items within your local network.

This Injection vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to modify the actions taken by a system call which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Assets Discovery customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/assetapps/assets-discovery-3-2-1-cloud-6-2-1-data_center-1333987182.html). You can download the latest version of Assets Discovery from the Atlassian Marketplace (https://marketplace.atlassian.com/apps/1214668/assets-discovery?hosting=datacenter&amp;amp;tab=installation).

This vulnerability was reported via our Penetration Testing program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21682|2024-02-20T18:00:00.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-06-10T17:30:00.572Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-06-10T17:30:00.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-18T17:00:02.531Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-18T17:00:02.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-26T17:43:55.994Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-26T17:43:55.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-17T15:27:45.652Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-17T15:27:45.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21684|2024-07-24T18:45:23.880Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21684</link>
      <description>There is a low severity open redirect vulnerability within affected versions of Bitbucket Data Center. Versions of Bitbucket DC from 8.0.0 to 8.9.12 and 8.19.0 to 8.19.1 are affected by this vulnerability. It is patched in 8.9.13 and 8.19.2.

This open redirect vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 3.1 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect a victim user upon login to Bitbucket Data Center to any arbitrary site which can be utilized for further exploitation which has low impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center customers upgrade to the version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the  supported fixed versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21684|2024-07-24T18:45:23.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T07:52:01.198Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T07:52:01.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
