<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:22:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3397|2024-08-04T19:12:09.402Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3397</link>
      <description>Atlassian Bitbucket Data Center licensed instances starting with version 5.13.0 before 5.13.6 (the fixed version for 5.13.x), from 5.14.0 before 5.14.4 (fixed version for 5.14.x), from 5.15.0 before 5.15.3 (fixed version for 5.15.x), from 5.16.0 before 5.16.3 (fixed version for 5.16.x), from 6.0.0 before 6.0.3 (fixed version for 6.0.x), and from 6.1.0 before 6.1.2 (the fixed version for 6.1.x) allow remote attackers who have admin permissions to achieve remote code execution on a Bitbucket server instance via path traversal through the Data Center migration tool.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3397|2024-08-04T19:12:09.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39115|2024-08-04T01:58:17.709Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20desk%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39115</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow remote attackers with "Jira Administrators" access to execute arbitrary Java code or run arbitrary system commands via a Server_Side Template Injection vulnerability in the Email Template feature. The affected versions are before version 4.13.9, and from version 4.14.0 before 4.18.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39115|2024-08-04T01:58:17.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39123|2024-08-04T01:58:17.890Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39123</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in the /rest/gadget/1.0/createdVsResolved/generate endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.16.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39123|2024-08-04T01:58:17.890Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43947|2024-08-04T04:10:17.270Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43947</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers with administrator privileges to execute arbitrary code via a Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in the Email Templates feature. This issue bypasses the fix of https://jira.atlassian.com/browse/JSDSERVER-8665. The affected versions are before version 8.13.15, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43947|2024-08-04T04:10:17.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41306|2024-08-04T03:08:31.997Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41306</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view private project and filter names via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Average Time in Status Gadget. The affected versions are before version 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41306|2024-08-04T03:08:31.997Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29448|2024-08-04T16:55:09.777Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29448</link>
      <description>The ConfluenceResourceDownloadRewriteRule class in Confluence Server and Confluence Data Center before version 6.13.18, from 6.14.0 before 7.4.6, and from 7.5.0 before 7.8.3 allowed unauthenticated remote attackers to read arbitrary files within WEB-INF and META-INF directories via an incorrect path access check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29448|2024-08-04T16:55:09.777Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4015|2024-08-04T07:52:20.704Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4015</link>
      <description>The /json/fe/activeUserFinder.do resource in Altassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.1 allows remote attackers to view user user email addresses via a information disclosure vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4015|2024-08-04T07:52:20.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4014|2024-08-04T07:52:20.578Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4014</link>
      <description>The /profile/deleteWatch.do resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.1 allows remote attackers to remove another user's watching settings for a repository via an improper authorization vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4014|2024-08-04T07:52:20.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43952|2024-08-04T04:10:17.284Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43952</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to restore the default configuration of fields via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the /secure/admin/RestoreDefaults.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.21.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43952|2024-08-04T04:10:17.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29444|2024-08-04T16:55:09.765Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29444</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Team Calendar in Confluence Server before 7.11.0 allow attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or Javascript via a Cross Site Scripting Vulnerability in admin global setting parameters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29444|2024-08-04T16:55:09.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43942|2024-08-04T04:10:17.127Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43942</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /rest/collectors/1.0/template/custom endpoint. To exploit this issue, the attacker must trick a user into visiting a malicious website. The affected versions are before version 8.13.15, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43942|2024-08-04T04:10:17.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43945|2024-08-04T04:10:17.223Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43945</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers with Roadmaps Administrator permissions to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (SXSS) vulnerability in the /rest/jpo/1.0/hierarchyConfiguration endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43945|2024-08-04T04:10:17.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36236|2024-08-04T17:23:09.649Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36236</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the ViewWorkflowSchemes.jspa and ListWorkflows.jspa endpoints. The affected versions are before version 8.5.11, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.3, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.15.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36236|2024-08-04T17:23:09.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3402|2024-08-04T19:12:09.400Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3402</link>
      <description>The ConfigurePortalPages.jspa resource in Jira before version 7.13.3 and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.1.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the searchOwnerUserName parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3402|2024-08-04T19:12:09.400Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14184|2024-08-04T12:39:36.188Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14184</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Jira issue filter export files. The affected versions are before 8.5.9, from version 8.6.0 before 8.12.3, and from version 8.13.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14184|2024-08-04T12:39:36.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43940|2024-08-04T04:10:17.171Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43940</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center allow authenticated local attackers to achieve elevated privileges on the local system via a DLL Hijacking vulnerability in the Confluence installer. This vulnerability only affects installations of Confluence Server and Data Center on Windows. The affected versions are before version 7.4.10, and from version 7.5.0 before 7.12.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43940|2024-08-04T04:10:17.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36237|2024-08-04T17:23:09.806Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36237</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to view custom field options via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /rest/api/2/customFieldOption/ endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.15.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36237|2024-08-04T17:23:09.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39114|2024-08-04T01:58:17.751Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39114</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center allow users with a valid account on a Confluence Data Center instance to execute arbitrary Java code or run arbitrary system commands by injecting an OGNL payload. The affected versions are before version 6.13.23, from version 6.14.0 before 7.4.11, from version 7.5.0 before 7.11.6, and from version 7.12.0 before 7.12.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39114|2024-08-04T01:58:17.751Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4024|2024-08-04T07:52:20.795Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4024</link>
      <description>The attachment download resource in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before 8.5.5, and from 8.6.0 before 8.8.2, and from 8.9.0 before 8.9.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability issue attachments with a vnd.wap.xhtml+xml content type.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4024|2024-08-04T07:52:20.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14185|2024-08-04T12:39:36.046Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14185</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Jira Server allow remote unauthenticated attackers to enumerate issue keys via a missing permissions check in the ActionsAndOperations resource. The affected versions are before 7.13.18, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.9, and from version 8.6.0 before version 8.12.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14185|2024-08-04T12:39:36.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39109|2024-08-04T01:58:17.666Z -- atlassian -- atlasboard
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39109</link>
      <description>The renderWidgetResource resource in Atlasian Atlasboard before version 1.1.9 allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files via a path traversal vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39109|2024-08-04T01:58:17.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4026|2024-08-04T07:52:20.704Z -- atlassian -- navigator%20links
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4026</link>
      <description>The CustomAppsRestResource list resource in Atlassian Navigator Links before version 3.3.23, from version 4.0.0 before version 4.3.7, from version 5.0.0 before 5.0.1, and from version 5.1.0 before 5.1.1 allows remote attackers to enumerate all linked applications, including those that are restricted or otherwise hidden, through an incorrect authorization check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4026|2024-08-04T07:52:20.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39118|2024-08-04T01:58:18.114Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39118</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to discover the usernames and full names of users via an enumeration vulnerability in the /rest/api/1.0/render endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.19.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39118|2024-08-04T01:58:18.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43949|2024-08-04T04:10:16.282Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43949</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to view private objects via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the Custom Fields feature. The affected versions are before version 4.21.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43949|2024-08-04T04:10:16.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39112|2024-08-04T01:58:17.761Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39112</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to redirect users to a malicious URL via a reverse tabnapping vulnerability in the Project Shortcuts feature. The affected versions are before version 8.5.15, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.7, from version 8.14.0 before 8.17.1, and from version 8.18.0 before 8.18.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39112|2024-08-04T01:58:17.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41304|2024-08-04T03:08:31.934Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41304</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /secure/admin/ImporterFinishedPage.jspa error message. The affected versions are before version 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41304|2024-08-04T03:08:31.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3401|2024-08-04T19:12:09.256Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3401</link>
      <description>The ManageFilters.jspa resource in Jira before version 7.13.3 and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.1.1 allows remote attackers to enumerate usernames via an incorrect authorisation check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3401|2024-08-04T19:12:09.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14168|2024-08-04T12:39:36.072Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14168</link>
      <description>The email client in Jira Server and Data Center before version 7.13.16, from 8.5.0 before 8.5.7, from 8.8.0 before 8.8.2, and from 8.9.0 before 8.9.1 allows remote attackers to access outgoing emails between a Jira instance and the SMTP server via man-in-the-middle (MITM) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14168|2024-08-04T12:39:36.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36235|2024-08-04T17:23:09.655Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36235</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to view custom field and custom SLA names via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the mobile site view. The affected versions are before version 8.13.2, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.14.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36235|2024-08-04T17:23:09.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4017|2024-08-04T07:52:20.678Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4017</link>
      <description>The /rest/jira-ril/1.0/jira-rest/applinks resource in the crucible-jira-ril plugin in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.1 allows remote attackers to get information about any configured Jira application links via an information disclosure vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4017|2024-08-04T07:52:20.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41313|2024-08-04T03:08:31.977Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41313</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated but non-admin remote attackers to edit email batch configurations via an Improper Authorization vulnerability in the /secure/admin/ConfigureBatching!default.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.20.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41313|2024-08-04T03:08:31.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39124|2024-08-04T01:58:17.936Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39124</link>
      <description>The Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) failure retry feature of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.16.0 allows remote attackers who are able to trick a user into retrying a request to bypass CSRF protection and replay a crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39124|2024-08-04T01:58:17.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3396|2024-08-04T19:12:09.544Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3396</link>
      <description>The Widget Connector macro in Atlassian Confluence Server before version 6.6.12 (the fixed version for 6.6.x), from version 6.7.0 before 6.12.3 (the fixed version for 6.12.x), from version 6.13.0 before 6.13.3 (the fixed version for 6.13.x), and from version 6.14.0 before 6.14.2 (the fixed version for 6.14.x), allows remote attackers to achieve path traversal and remote code execution on a Confluence Server or Data Center instance via server-side template injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3396|2024-08-04T19:12:09.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41310|2024-08-04T03:08:31.865Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41310</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Associated Projects feature (/secure/admin/AssociatedProjectsForCustomField.jspa). The affected versions are before version 8.5.19, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.11, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.19.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41310|2024-08-04T03:08:31.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4016|2024-08-04T07:52:20.545Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4016</link>
      <description>The /plugins/servlet/jira-blockers/ resource in the crucible-jira-ril plugin in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.1 allows remote attackers to get the ID of configured Jira application links via an information disclosure vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4016|2024-08-04T07:52:20.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36290|2024-08-04T17:23:09.942Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36290</link>
      <description>The Livesearch macro in Confluence Server and Data Center before version 7.4.5, from version 7.5.0 before 7.6.3, and from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.4 allows remote attackers with permission to edit a page or blog to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the page excerpt functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36290|2024-08-04T17:23:09.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29451|2024-08-04T16:55:10.212Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29451</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to enumerate Jira projects via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the Jira Projects plugin report page. The affected versions are before version 8.5.11, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.3, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.14.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29451|2024-08-04T16:55:10.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36239|2024-08-04T17:23:09.858Z -- atlassian -- jira%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36239</link>
      <description>Jira Data Center, Jira Core Data Center, Jira Software Data Center from version 6.3.0 before 8.5.16, from 8.6.0 before 8.13.8, from 8.14.0 before 8.17.0 and Jira Service Management Data Center from version 2.0.2 before 4.5.16, from version 4.6.0 before 4.13.8, and from version 4.14.0 before 4.17.0 exposed a Ehcache RMI network service which attackers, who can connect to the service, on port 40001 and potentially 40011[0][1], could execute arbitrary code of their choice in Jira through deserialization due to a missing authentication vulnerability. While Atlassian strongly suggests restricting access to the Ehcache ports to only Data Center instances, fixed versions of Jira will now require a shared secret in order to allow access to the Ehcache service. [0] In Jira Data Center, Jira Core Data Center, and Jira Software Data Center versions prior to 7.13.1, the Ehcache object port can be randomly allocated. [1] In Jira Service Management Data Center versions prior to 3.16.1, the Ehcache object port can be randomly allocated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36239|2024-08-04T17:23:09.858Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14190|2024-08-04T12:39:36.199Z -- atlassian -- fisheye
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14190</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Fisheye/Crucible allow remote attackers to achieve Regex Denial of Service via user-supplied regex in EyeQL. The affected versions are before version 4.8.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14190|2024-08-04T12:39:36.199Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3399|2024-08-04T19:12:09.513Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3399</link>
      <description>The BrowseProjects.jspa resource in Jira before version 7.13.2, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.2 allows remote attackers to see information for archived projects through a missing authorisation check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3399|2024-08-04T19:12:09.513Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39119|2024-08-04T01:58:18.117Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39119</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow users who have watched an issue to continue receiving updates on the issue even after their Jira account is revoked, via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the issue notification feature. The affected versions are before version 8.19.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39119|2024-08-04T01:58:18.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4022|2024-08-04T07:52:20.721Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4022</link>
      <description>The attachment download resource in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before 8.5.5, and from 8.6.0 before 8.8.2, and from 8.9.0 before 8.9.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability issue attachments with a mixed multipart content type.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4022|2024-08-04T07:52:20.721Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3395|2024-08-04T19:12:08.548Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3395</link>
      <description>The WebDAV endpoint in Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center before version 6.6.7 (the fixed version for 6.6.x), from version 6.7.0 before 6.8.5 (the fixed version for 6.8.x), and from version 6.9.0 before 6.9.3 (the fixed version for 6.9.x) allows remote attackers to send arbitrary HTTP and WebDAV requests from a Confluence Server or Data Center instance via Server-Side Request Forgery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3395|2024-08-04T19:12:08.548Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43946|2024-08-04T04:10:17.348Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43946</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to add administrator groups to filter subscriptions via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the /secure/EditSubscription.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.13.21, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43946|2024-08-04T04:10:17.348Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39126|2024-08-04T01:58:17.682Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39126</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to modify various resources via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability, following an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the referrer headers which discloses a user's CSRF token. The affected versions are before version 8.5.10, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39126|2024-08-04T01:58:17.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29450|2024-08-04T16:55:09.661Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29450</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in the avatar upload feature. The affected versions are before version 7.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29450|2024-08-04T16:55:09.661Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14179|2024-08-04T12:39:36.221Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14179</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote, unauthenticated attackers to view custom field names and custom SLA names via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /secure/QueryComponent!Default.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.8, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.11.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14179|2024-08-04T12:39:36.221Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36234|2024-08-04T17:23:09.664Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36234</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Screens Modal view. The affected versions are before version 8.5.11, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.3, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.15.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36234|2024-08-04T17:23:09.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14166|2024-08-04T12:39:36.181Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20desk%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14166</link>
      <description>The /servicedesk/customer/portals resource in Jira Service Desk Server and Data Center before version 4.10.0 allows remote attackers with project administrator privileges to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript names via an Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability by uploading a html file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14166|2024-08-04T12:39:36.181Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36286|2024-08-04T17:23:10.354Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36286</link>
      <description>The membersOf JQL search function in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.13, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.1 allows remote anonymous attackers to determine if a group exists &amp; members of groups if they are assigned to publicly visible issue field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36286|2024-08-04T17:23:10.354Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43944|2024-08-04T04:10:17.165Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43944</link>
      <description>This issue exists to document that a security improvement in the way that Jira Server and Data Center use templates has been implemented. Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allowed remote attackers with system administrator permissions to execute arbitrary code via Template Injection leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE) in the Email Templates feature. The affected versions are before version 8.13.15, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43944|2024-08-04T04:10:17.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14180|2024-08-04T12:39:36.097Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20desk%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14180</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Desk Server and Data Center allow remote attackers authenticated as a non-administrator user to view Project Request-Types and Descriptions, via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the editform request-type-fields resource. The affected versions are before version 4.12.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14180|2024-08-04T12:39:36.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3403|2024-08-04T19:12:09.377Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3403</link>
      <description>The /rest/api/2/user/picker rest resource in Jira before version 7.13.3, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.4, and from version 8.1.0 before version 8.1.1 allows remote attackers to enumerate usernames via an incorrect authorisation check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3403|2024-08-04T19:12:09.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41305|2024-08-04T03:08:32.012Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41305</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view the names of private projects and filters via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Average Number of Times in Status Gadget. The affected versions are before version 8.13.12..</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41305|2024-08-04T03:08:32.012Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39121|2024-08-04T01:58:17.588Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39121</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to enumerate the keys of private Jira projects via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /rest/api/latest/projectvalidate/key endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.18, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.10, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.18.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39121|2024-08-04T01:58:17.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4028|2024-08-04T07:52:20.916Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4028</link>
      <description>Versions before 8.9.1, Various resources in Jira responded with a 404 instead of redirecting unauthenticated users to the login page, in some situations this may have allowed unauthorised attackers to determine if certain resources exist or not through an Information Disclosure vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4028|2024-08-04T07:52:20.916Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43948|2024-08-04T04:10:17.270Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43948</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to view the names of private objects via an Improper Authorization vulnerability in the "Move objects" feature. The affected versions are before version 4.21.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43948|2024-08-04T04:10:17.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39127|2024-08-04T01:58:17.643Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39127</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to the query component JQL endpoint via a Broken Access Control vulnerability (BAC) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 8.5.10, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39127|2024-08-04T01:58:17.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4020|2024-08-04T07:52:20.594Z -- atlassian -- companion%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4020</link>
      <description>The file downloading functionality in the Atlassian Companion App before version 1.0.0 allows remote attackers, who control a Confluence Server instance that the Companion App is connected to, execute arbitrary .exe files via a Protection Mechanism Failure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4020|2024-08-04T07:52:20.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14175|2024-08-04T12:39:36.159Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14175</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in user macro parameters. The affected versions are before version 7.4.2, and from version 7.5.0 before 7.5.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14175|2024-08-04T12:39:36.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4023|2024-08-04T07:52:20.579Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4023</link>
      <description>The review coverage resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or Javascript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the committerFilter parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4023|2024-08-04T07:52:20.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14177|2024-08-04T12:39:36.159Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14177</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Regex-based Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in JQL version searching. The affected versions are before version 7.13.16; from version 7.14.0 before 8.5.7; from version 8.6.0 before 8.10.2; and from version 8.11.0 before 8.11.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14177|2024-08-04T12:39:36.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36289|2024-08-04T17:23:09.943Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36289</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow an unauthenticated user to enumerate users via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the QueryComponentRendererValue!Default.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.13, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.15.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36289|2024-08-04T17:23:09.943Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4027|2024-08-04T07:52:20.854Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4027</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center allowed remote attackers with system administration permissions to bypass velocity template injection mitigations via an injection vulnerability in custom user macros. The affected versions are before version 7.4.5, and from version 7.5.0 before 7.5.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4027|2024-08-04T07:52:20.854Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29447|2024-08-04T16:55:09.671Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29447</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Crucible allow remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in the file upload request feature of code reviews. The affected versions are before version 4.7.4, and from version 4.8.0 before 4.8.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29447|2024-08-04T16:55:09.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4013|2024-08-04T07:52:20.435Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4013</link>
      <description>The review resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or Javascript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the review objectives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4013|2024-08-04T07:52:20.435Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29445|2024-08-04T16:55:10.375Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29445</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Confluence Server before 7.4.8, and versions from 7.5.0 before 7.11.0 allow attackers to identify internal hosts and ports via a blind server-side request forgery vulnerability in Team Calendars parameters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29445|2024-08-04T16:55:10.375Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4029|2024-08-04T07:52:20.799Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4029</link>
      <description>The /rest/project-templates/1.0/createshared resource in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.5, from 8.6.0 before 8.7.2, and from 8.8.0 before 8.8.1 allows remote attackers to enumerate project names via an improper authorization vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4029|2024-08-04T07:52:20.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36231|2024-08-04T17:23:09.962Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36231</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to view the metadata of boards they should not have access to via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 8.5.10, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36231|2024-08-04T17:23:09.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41307|2024-08-04T03:08:31.948Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41307</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to view the names of private projects and private filters via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Workload Pie Chart Gadget. The affected versions are before version 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41307|2024-08-04T03:08:31.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36240|2024-08-04T17:23:09.980Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36240</link>
      <description>The ResourceDownloadRewriteRule class in Crowd before version 4.0.4, and from version 4.1.0 before 4.1.2 allowed unauthenticated remote attackers to read arbitrary files within WEB-INF and META-INF directories via an incorrect path access check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36240|2024-08-04T17:23:09.980Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14183|2024-08-04T12:39:36.172Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14183</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Jira Server &amp; Data Center allow a remote attacker with limited (non-admin) privileges to view a Jira instance's Support Entitlement Number (SEN) via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the HTTP Response headers. The affected versions are before version 7.13.18, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.9, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.12.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14183|2024-08-04T12:39:36.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43957|2024-08-04T04:10:17.200Z -- atlassian -- fisheye
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43957</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Fisheye &amp; Crucible allowed remote attackers to browse local files via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the WEB-INF directory and bypass the fix for CVE-2020-29446 due to a lack of url decoding. The affected versions are before version 4.8.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43957|2024-08-04T04:10:17.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4025|2024-08-04T07:52:20.714Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4025</link>
      <description>The attachment download resource in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center The attachment download resource in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before 8.5.5, and from 8.6.0 before 8.8.2, and from 8.9.0 before 8.9.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability issue attachments with a rdf content type.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4025|2024-08-04T07:52:20.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39116|2024-08-04T01:58:17.981Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39116</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in the GIF Image Reader component. The affected versions are before version 8.13.14, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.19.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39116|2024-08-04T01:58:17.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43941|2024-08-04T04:10:17.147Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43941</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to modify several resources (including CsvFieldMappingsPage.jspa and ImporterValueMappingsPage.jspa) via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the jira-importers-plugin. The affected versions are before version 8.13.15, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43941|2024-08-04T04:10:17.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43943|2024-08-04T04:10:17.129Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43943</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow attackers with administrator privileges to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the "Object Schema" field of /secure/admin/InsightDefaultCustomFieldConfig.jspa. The affected versions are before version 4.21.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43943|2024-08-04T04:10:17.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43951|2024-08-04T04:10:17.200Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43951</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to view object import configuration details via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the Create Object type mapping feature. The affected versions are before version 4.21.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43951|2024-08-04T04:10:17.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14174|2024-08-04T12:39:36.196Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14174</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to view titles of a private project via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Administration Permission Helper. The affected versions are before version 7.13.6, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.7, from version 8.6.0 before 8.9.2, and from version 8.10.0 before 8.10.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14174|2024-08-04T12:39:36.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14181|2024-08-04T12:39:36.073Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14181</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow an unauthenticated user to enumerate users via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /ViewUserHover.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 7.13.6, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.7, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.12.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14181|2024-08-04T12:39:36.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39122|2024-08-04T01:58:17.788Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39122</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view users' emails via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /rest/api/2/search endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.13, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.15.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39122|2024-08-04T01:58:17.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14178|2024-08-04T12:39:36.164Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14178</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to enumerate project keys via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /browse.PROJECTKEY endpoint. The affected versions are before version 7.13.7, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.8, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.12.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14178|2024-08-04T12:39:36.164Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3394|2024-08-04T19:12:09.337Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3394</link>
      <description>There was a local file disclosure vulnerability in Confluence Server and Confluence Data Center via page exporting. An attacker with permission to editing a page is able to exploit this issue to read arbitrary file on the server under &lt;install-directory&gt;/confluence/WEB-INF directory, which may contain configuration files used for integrating with other services, which could potentially leak credentials or other sensitive information such as LDAP credentials. The LDAP credential will be potentially leaked only if the Confluence server is configured to use LDAP as user repository. All versions of Confluence Server from 6.1.0 before 6.6.16 (the fixed version for 6.6.x), from 6.7.0 before 6.13.7 (the fixed version for 6.13.x), and from 6.14.0 before 6.15.8 (the fixed version for 6.15.x) are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3394|2024-08-04T19:12:09.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36232|2024-08-04T17:23:09.655Z -- atlassian -- atlassian%20gadgets
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36232</link>
      <description>The MessageBundleWhiteList class of atlassian-gadgets before version 4.2.37, from version 4.3.0 before 4.3.14, from version 4.3.2.0 before 4.3.2.4, from version 4.4.0 before 4.4.12, and from version 5.0.0 before 5.0.1 allowed unexpected DNS lookups and requests to arbitrary services as it incorrectly obtained application base url information from the executing http request which could be attacker controlled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36232|2024-08-04T17:23:09.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14172|2024-08-04T12:39:36.159Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14172</link>
      <description>This issue exists to document that a security improvement in the way that Jira Server and Data Center use velocity templates has been implemented. The way in which velocity templates were used in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center in affected versions allowed remote attackers to achieve remote code execution via insecure deserialization, if they were able to exploit a server side template injection vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 7.13.0, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.0, and from version 8.6.0 before version 8.8.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14172|2024-08-04T12:39:36.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14189|2024-08-04T12:39:36.088Z -- atlassian -- gajira-comment
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14189</link>
      <description>The execute function in in the Atlassian gajira-comment GitHub Action before version 2.0.2 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a GitHub runner by creating a specially crafted GitHub issue comment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14189|2024-08-04T12:39:36.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41312|2024-08-04T03:08:31.935Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41312</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow a remote attacker who has had their access revoked from Jira Service Management to enable and disable Issue Collectors on Jira Service Management projects via an Improper Authentication vulnerability in the /secure/ViewCollectors endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.19.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41312|2024-08-04T03:08:31.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43955|2024-08-04T04:10:16.302Z -- atlassian -- fisheye
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43955</link>
      <description>The /rest-service-fecru/server-v1 resource in Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.9 allowed authenticated remote attackers to obtain information about installation directories via information disclosure vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43955|2024-08-04T04:10:16.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14191|2024-08-04T12:39:36.171Z -- atlassian -- fisheye
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14191</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Fisheye/Crucible allow remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in the MessageBundleResource within Atlassian Gadgets. The affected versions are before version 4.8.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14191|2024-08-04T12:39:36.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14171|2024-08-04T12:39:36.011Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14171</link>
      <description>Atlassian Bitbucket Server from version 4.9.0 before version 7.2.4 allows remote attackers to intercept unencrypted repository import requests via a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14171|2024-08-04T12:39:36.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36287|2024-08-04T17:23:10.174Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36287</link>
      <description>The dashboard gadgets preference resource of the Atlassian gadgets plugin used in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.1 allows remote anonymous attackers to obtain gadget related settings via a missing permissions check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36287|2024-08-04T17:23:10.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29453|2024-08-04T16:55:09.848Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29453</link>
      <description>The CachingResourceDownloadRewriteRule class in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.11, from 8.6.0 before 8.13.3, and from 8.14.0 before 8.15.0 allowed unauthenticated remote attackers to read arbitrary files within WEB-INF and META-INF directories via an incorrect path access check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29453|2024-08-04T16:55:09.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3400|2024-08-04T19:12:09.257Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3400</link>
      <description>The labels gadget in Jira before version 7.13.2, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the jql parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3400|2024-08-04T19:12:09.257Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14188|2024-08-04T12:39:36.163Z -- atlassian -- gajira-create
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14188</link>
      <description>The preprocessArgs function in the Atlassian gajira-create GitHub Action before version 2.0.1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a GitHub runner by creating a specially crafted GitHub issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14188|2024-08-04T12:39:36.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39113|2024-08-04T01:58:17.748Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39113</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to continue to view cached content even after losing permissions, via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the allowlist feature. The affected versions are before version 8.13.9, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.18.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39113|2024-08-04T01:58:17.748Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41308|2024-08-04T03:08:31.936Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41308</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated yet non-administrator remote attackers to edit the File Replication settings via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the `ReplicationSettings!default.jspa` endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.6.0, from version 8.7.0 before 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41308|2024-08-04T03:08:31.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14192|2024-08-04T12:39:36.127Z -- atlassian -- fisheye
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14192</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible allow remote attackers to view a product's SEN via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the x-asen response header from Atlassian Analytics. The affected versions are before version 4.8.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14192|2024-08-04T12:39:36.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4018|2024-08-04T07:52:20.588Z -- atlassian -- crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4018</link>
      <description>The setup resources in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.1 allows remote attackers to complete the setup process via a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4018|2024-08-04T07:52:20.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43959|2024-08-04T04:10:16.934Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43959</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to access the content of internal network resources via a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the CSV importing feature of JSM Insight. When running in an environment like Amazon EC2, this flaw may be used to access to a metadata resource that provides access credentials and other potentially confidential information. The affected versions are before version 4.13.20, from version 4.14.0 before 4.20.8, and from version 4.21.0 before 4.22.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43959|2024-08-04T04:10:16.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41309|2024-08-04T03:08:31.877Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41309</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow a user who has had their Jira Service Management access revoked to export audit logs of another user's Jira Service Management project via a Broken Authentication vulnerability in the /plugins/servlet/audit/resource endpoint. The affected versions of Jira Server and Data Center are before version 8.19.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41309|2024-08-04T03:08:31.877Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39117|2024-08-04T01:58:17.600Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39117</link>
      <description>The AssociateFieldToScreens page in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.18.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the name of a custom field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39117|2024-08-04T01:58:17.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4021|2024-08-04T07:52:20.541Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4021</link>
      <description>Affected versions are: Before 8.5.5, and from 8.6.0 before 8.8.1 of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the XML export view.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4021|2024-08-04T07:52:20.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39111|2024-08-04T01:58:17.957Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39111</link>
      <description>The Editor plugin in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.18, from 8.6.0 before 8.13.10, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.18.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the handling of supplied content such as from a PDF when pasted into a field such as the description field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39111|2024-08-04T01:58:17.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43954|2024-08-04T04:10:17.160Z -- atlassian -- fisheye
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43954</link>
      <description>The DefaultRepositoryAdminService class in Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.9 allowed remote attackers, who have 'can add repository permission', to enumerate the existence of internal network and filesystem resources via a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43954|2024-08-04T04:10:17.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14165|2024-08-04T12:39:36.024Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14165</link>
      <description>The UniversalAvatarResource.getAvatars resource in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.9.0 allows remote attackers to obtain information about custom project avatars names via an Improper authorization vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14165|2024-08-04T12:39:36.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36288|2024-08-04T17:23:10.175Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36288</link>
      <description>The issue navigation and search view in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.12, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.4, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a DOM Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability caused by parameter pollution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36288|2024-08-04T17:23:10.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14169|2024-08-04T12:39:36.191Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14169</link>
      <description>The quick search component in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before 8.9.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14169|2024-08-04T12:39:36.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41311|2024-08-04T03:08:31.998Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41311</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow attackers with access to an administrator account that has had its access revoked to modify projects' Users &amp; Roles settings, via a Broken Authentication vulnerability in the /plugins/servlet/project-config/PROJECT/roles endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.19.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41311|2024-08-04T03:08:31.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3398|2024-08-04T19:12:09.521Z -- atlassian -- confluence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3398</link>
      <description>Confluence Server and Data Center had a path traversal vulnerability in the downloadallattachments resource. A remote attacker who has permission to add attachments to pages and / or blogs or to create a new space or a personal space or who has 'Admin' permissions for a space can exploit this path traversal vulnerability to write files to arbitrary locations which can lead to remote code execution on systems that run a vulnerable version of Confluence Server or Data Center. All versions of Confluence Server from 2.0.0 before 6.6.13 (the fixed version for 6.6.x), from 6.7.0 before 6.12.4 (the fixed version for 6.12.x), from 6.13.0 before 6.13.4 (the fixed version for 6.13.x), from 6.14.0 before 6.14.3 (the fixed version for 6.14.x), and from 6.15.0 before 6.15.2 are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3398|2024-08-04T19:12:09.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14193|2024-08-04T12:39:36.167Z -- atlassian -- automation%20for%20jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14193</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Automation for Jira - Server allowed remote attackers to read and render files as mustache templates in files inside the WEB-INF/classes &amp; &lt;jira-installation&gt;/jira/bin directories via a template injection vulnerability in Jira smart values using mustache partials. The affected versions are those before version 7.1.15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14193|2024-08-04T12:39:36.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36233|2024-08-04T17:23:09.677Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36233</link>
      <description>The Microsoft Windows Installer for Atlassian Bitbucket Server and Data Center before version 6.10.9, 7.x before 7.6.4, and from version 7.7.0 before 7.10.1 allows local attackers to escalate privileges because of weak permissions on the installation directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36233|2024-08-04T17:23:09.677Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14170|2024-08-04T12:39:36.189Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14170</link>
      <description>Webhooks in Atlassian Bitbucket Server from version 5.4.0 before version 7.3.1 allow remote attackers to access the content of internal network resources via a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14170|2024-08-04T12:39:36.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36238|2024-08-04T17:23:09.934Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36238</link>
      <description>The /rest/api/1.0/render resource in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.13, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.1 allows remote anonymous attackers to determine if a username is valid or not via a missing permissions check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36238|2024-08-04T17:23:09.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43956|2024-08-04T04:10:17.026Z -- atlassian -- fisheye
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43956</link>
      <description>The jQuery deserialize library in Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.9 allowed remote attackers to to inject arbitrary HTML and/or JavaScript via a prototype pollution vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43956|2024-08-04T04:10:17.026Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29446|2024-08-04T16:55:10.407Z -- atlassian -- fisheye
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29446</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Fisheye &amp; Crucible allow remote attackers to browse local files via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the WEB-INF directory. The affected versions are before version 4.8.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29446|2024-08-04T16:55:10.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43953|2024-08-04T04:10:16.450Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43953</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to toggle the Thread Contention and CPU monitoring settings via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the /secure/admin/ViewInstrumentation.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.13.16, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43953|2024-08-04T04:10:16.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43950|2024-08-04T04:10:17.146Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43950</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to view import source configuration information via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the Insight Import Source feature. The affected versions are before version 4.21.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43950|2024-08-04T04:10:17.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14173|2024-08-04T12:39:36.158Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14173</link>
      <description>The file upload feature in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center in affected versions allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 8.5.4, from version 8.6.0 before 8.6.2, and from version 8.7.0 before 8.7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14173|2024-08-04T12:39:36.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14167|2024-08-04T12:39:35.976Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14167</link>
      <description>The MessageBundleResource resource in Jira Server and Data Center before version 7.13.4, from 8.5.0 before 8.5.5, from 8.8.0 before 8.8.2, and from 8.9.0 before 8.9.1 allows remote attackers to impact the application's availability via an Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14167|2024-08-04T12:39:35.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43958|2024-08-04T04:10:17.148Z -- atlassian -- fisheye
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43958</link>
      <description>Various rest resources in Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.8.9 allowed remote attackers to brute force user login credentials as rest resources did not check if users were beyond their max failed login limits and therefore required solving a CAPTCHA in addition to providing user credentials for authentication via a improper restriction of excess authentication attempts vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43958|2024-08-04T04:10:17.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4019|2024-08-04T07:52:20.834Z -- atlassian -- companion%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4019</link>
      <description>The file editing functionality in the Atlassian Companion App before version 1.0.0 allows local attackers to have the app run a different executable in place of the app's cmd.exe via a untrusted search path vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4019|2024-08-04T07:52:20.834Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39125|2024-08-04T01:58:17.940Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39125</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to discover the usernames of users via an enumeration vulnerability in the password reset page. The affected versions are before version 8.5.10, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39125|2024-08-04T01:58:17.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14164|2024-08-04T12:39:36.137Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server%20and%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14164</link>
      <description>The WYSIWYG editor resource in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.8.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript names via an Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability by pasting javascript code into the editor field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14164|2024-08-04T12:39:36.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39128|2024-08-04T01:58:17.980Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39128</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server or Data Center using the Jira Service Management addon allow remote attackers with JIRA Administrators access to execute arbitrary Java code via a server-side template injection vulnerability in the Email Template feature. The affected versions of Jira Server or Data Center are before version 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.19.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39128|2024-08-04T01:58:17.980Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T07:52:01.198Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T07:52:01.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21684|2024-07-24T18:45:23.880Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21684</link>
      <description>There is a low severity open redirect vulnerability within affected versions of Bitbucket Data Center. Versions of Bitbucket DC from 8.0.0 to 8.9.12 and 8.19.0 to 8.19.1 are affected by this vulnerability. It is patched in 8.9.13 and 8.19.2.

This open redirect vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 3.1 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect a victim user upon login to Bitbucket Data Center to any arbitrary site which can be utilized for further exploitation which has low impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center customers upgrade to the version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the  supported fixed versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21684|2024-07-24T18:45:23.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-17T15:27:45.652Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-17T15:27:45.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-26T17:43:55.994Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-26T17:43:55.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-18T17:00:02.531Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-18T17:00:02.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-06-10T17:30:00.572Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-06-10T17:30:00.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21682|2024-02-20T18:00:00.699Z -- atlassian -- assets%20discovery%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21682</link>
      <description>This High severity Injection vulnerability was introduced in Assets Discovery 1.0 - 6.2.0 (all versions). 

Assets Discovery, which can be downloaded via Atlassian Marketplace, is a network scanning tool that can be used with or without an agent with Jira Service Management Cloud, Data Center or Server. It detects hardware and software that is connected to your local network and extracts detailed information about each asset. This data can then be imported into Assets in Jira Service Management to help you manage all of the devices and configuration items within your local network.

This Injection vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to modify the actions taken by a system call which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Assets Discovery customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/assetapps/assets-discovery-3-2-1-cloud-6-2-1-data_center-1333987182.html). You can download the latest version of Assets Discovery from the Atlassian Marketplace (https://marketplace.atlassian.com/apps/1214668/assets-discovery?hosting=datacenter&amp;amp;tab=installation).

This vulnerability was reported via our Penetration Testing program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21682|2024-02-20T18:00:00.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21677|2024-03-19T17:30:00.500Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21677</link>
      <description>This High severity Path Traversal vulnerability was introduced in version 6.13.0 of Confluence Data Center. This Path Traversal vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.3, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit an undefinable vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions: Data Center Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version and that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version.

If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives. 

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21677|2024-03-19T17:30:00.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21678|2024-06-04T17:38:08.576Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21678</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in version 2.7.0 of Confluence Data Center.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.5, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, low impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.
Data Center

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.7.0 to 8.7.1|8.8.0 recommended or 8.7.2|
|from 8.6.0 to 8.6.1|8.8.0 recommended|
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
Server

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:


||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|

See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html]). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives]).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21678|2024-06-04T17:38:08.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21677|2024-06-21T18:07:46.098Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21677</link>
      <description>This High severity Path Traversal vulnerability was introduced in version 6.13.0 of Confluence Data Center. This Path Traversal vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.3, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit an undefinable vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions: Data Center Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version and that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version.

If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives. 

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21677|2024-06-21T18:07:46.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21686|2024-07-16T20:00:02.617Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21686</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.13 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.3, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21686|2024-07-16T20:00:02.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-16T20:30:00.385Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-16T20:30:00.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-20T03:55:33.558Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-20T03:55:33.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T06:47:39.038Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T06:47:39.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21684|2024-08-01T22:27:36.150Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21684</link>
      <description>There is a low severity open redirect vulnerability within affected versions of Bitbucket Data Center. Versions of Bitbucket DC from 8.0.0 to 8.9.12 and 8.19.0 to 8.19.1 are affected by this vulnerability. It is patched in 8.9.13 and 8.19.2.

This open redirect vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 3.1 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect a victim user upon login to Bitbucket Data Center to any arbitrary site which can be utilized for further exploitation which has low impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center customers upgrade to the version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the  supported fixed versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21684|2024-08-01T22:27:36.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-08-01T22:27:36.035Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-08-01T22:27:36.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21682|2024-08-01T22:27:35.986Z -- atlassian -- assets%20discovery%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21682</link>
      <description>This High severity Injection vulnerability was introduced in Assets Discovery 1.0 - 6.2.0 (all versions). 

Assets Discovery, which can be downloaded via Atlassian Marketplace, is a network scanning tool that can be used with or without an agent with Jira Service Management Cloud, Data Center or Server. It detects hardware and software that is connected to your local network and extracts detailed information about each asset. This data can then be imported into Assets in Jira Service Management to help you manage all of the devices and configuration items within your local network.

This Injection vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to modify the actions taken by a system call which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Assets Discovery customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/assetapps/assets-discovery-3-2-1-cloud-6-2-1-data_center-1333987182.html). You can download the latest version of Assets Discovery from the Atlassian Marketplace (https://marketplace.atlassian.com/apps/1214668/assets-discovery?hosting=datacenter&amp;amp;tab=installation).

This vulnerability was reported via our Penetration Testing program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21682|2024-08-01T22:27:35.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21677|2024-08-01T22:27:35.969Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21677</link>
      <description>This High severity Path Traversal vulnerability was introduced in version 6.13.0 of Confluence Data Center. This Path Traversal vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.3, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit an undefinable vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions: Data Center Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version and that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version.

If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives. 

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21677|2024-08-01T22:27:35.969Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-08-01T22:27:35.803Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-08-01T22:27:35.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21678|2024-08-01T22:27:35.810Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21678</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in version 2.7.0 of Confluence Data Center.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.5, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, low impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.
Data Center

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.7.0 to 8.7.1|8.8.0 recommended or 8.7.2|
|from 8.6.0 to 8.6.1|8.8.0 recommended|
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
Server

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:


||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|

See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html]). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives]).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21678|2024-08-01T22:27:35.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-08-01T22:27:36.189Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-08-01T22:27:36.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21686|2024-08-01T22:27:36.033Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21686</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.13 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.3, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21686|2024-08-01T22:27:36.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
