<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:23:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22518|2024-08-02T10:13:48.670Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22518</link>
      <description>All versions of Confluence Data Center and Server are affected by this unexploited vulnerability. This Improper Authorization vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to reset Confluence and create a Confluence instance administrator account. Using this account, an attacker can then perform all administrative actions that are available to Confluence instance administrator leading to - but not limited to - full loss of confidentiality, integrity and availability. 

Atlassian Cloud sites are not affected by this vulnerability. If your Confluence site is accessed via an atlassian.net domain, it is hosted by Atlassian and is not vulnerable to this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22518|2024-08-02T10:13:48.670Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22523|2024-08-02T10:13:48.923Z -- atlassian -- assets%20discovery%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22523</link>
      <description>This vulnerability, if exploited, allows an attacker to perform privileged RCE (Remote Code Execution) on machines with the Assets Discovery agent installed. The vulnerability exists between the Assets Discovery application (formerly known as Insight Discovery) and the Assets Discovery agent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22523|2024-08-02T10:13:48.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22503|2024-08-02T10:13:48.665Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22503</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view the names of attachments and labels in a private Confluence space. This occurs via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the macro preview feature.&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability was reported by Rojan Rijal of the Tinder Security Engineering team.&#13;
&#13;
The affected versions are before version 7.13.15, from version 7.14.0 before 7.19.7, and from version 7.20.0 before 8.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22503|2024-08-02T10:13:48.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 16:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22521|2024-08-02T10:13:48.932Z -- atlassian -- crowd%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22521</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 3.4.6 of Crowd Data Center and Server.&#13;
&#13;
This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.0, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.&#13;
&#13;
Atlassian recommends that Crowd Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:&#13;
 Crowd Data Center and Server 3.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 5.1.6&#13;
 Crowd Data Center and Server 5.2: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 5.2.1&#13;
&#13;
See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/crowd/crowd-release-notes-199094.html]). You can download the latest version of Crowd Data Center and Server from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/crowd/download-archive]).&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability was discovered by m1sn0w and reported via our Bug Bounty program</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22521|2024-08-02T10:13:48.932Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22524|2024-08-02T10:13:49.011Z -- atlassian -- companion%20for%20mac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22524</link>
      <description>Certain versions of the Atlassian Companion App for MacOS were affected by a remote code execution vulnerability. An attacker could utilize WebSockets to bypass Atlassian Companion’s blocklist and MacOS Gatekeeper to allow execution of code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22524|2024-08-02T10:13:49.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22508|2024-08-02T10:13:48.922Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22508</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability known as CVE-2023-22508 was introduced in version 6.1.0 of Confluence Data Center &amp; Server. This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.5, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and no user interaction. Atlassian recommends that you upgrade your instance to avoid this bug using the following options: * Upgrade to a Confluence feature release greater than or equal to 8.2.0 (ie: 8.2, 8.2, 8.4, etc...) * Upgrade to a Confluence 7.19 LTS bugfix release greater than or equal to 7.19.8 (ie: 7.19.8, 7.19.9, 7.19.10, 7.19.11, etc...) * Upgrade to a Confluence 7.13 LTS bugfix release greater than or equal to 7.13.20 (Release available early August) See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html ). You can download the latest version of Data Center &amp; Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives ). If you are unable to upgrade your instance please use the following guide to workaround the issue https://confluence.atlassian.com/confkb/how-to-disable-the-jmx-network-port-for-cve-2023-22508-1267761550.html This vulnerability was discovered by a private user and reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22508|2024-08-02T10:13:48.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22506|2024-08-02T10:13:48.523Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22506</link>
      <description>This High severity Injection and RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability known as CVE-2023-22506 was introduced in version 8.0.0 of Bamboo Data Center.
 

This Injection and RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.5, allows an authenticated attacker to
modify the actions taken by a system call and execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and no user interaction.
 
 
Atlassian recommends that you upgrade your instance to latest version. If you're unable to upgrade to latest, upgrade to one of these fixed versions: 9.2.3 and 9.3.1. See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html|https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html]). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Bamboo Server from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives|https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives]).
 

This vulnerability was reported via our Penetration Testing program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22506|2024-08-02T10:13:48.523Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22513|2024-08-02T10:13:48.688Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22513</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 8.0.0 of Bitbucket Data Center and Server. This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.5, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions: Bitbucket Data Center and Server 8.9: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.9.5 Bitbucket Data Center and Server 8.10: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.10.5 Bitbucket Data Center and Server 8.11: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.11.4 Bitbucket Data Center and Server 8.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.12.2 Bitbucket Data Center and Server 8.13: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.13.1 Bitbucket Data Center and Server 8.14: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.14.0 Bitbucket Data Center and Server version &gt;= 8.0 and &lt; 8.9: Upgrade to any of the listed fix versions. See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bitbucketserver/release-notes). You can download the latest version of Bitbucket Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bitbucket/download-archives). This vulnerability was discovered by a private user and reported via our Bug Bounty program</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22513|2024-08-02T10:13:48.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22526|2024-08-02T10:13:48.994Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22526</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 7.19.0 of Confluence Data Center.&#13;
&#13;
This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.&#13;
&#13;
Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:&#13;
 Confluence Data Center and Server 7.19: Upgrade to a release 7.19.17, or any higher 7.19.x release&#13;
 Confluence Data Center and Server 8.5: Upgrade to a release 8.5.5 or any higher 8.5.x release&#13;
 Confluence Data Center and Server 8.7: Upgrade to a release 8.7.2 or any higher release&#13;
&#13;
See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html]). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives]).&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability was discovered by m1sn0w and reported via our Bug Bounty program</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22526|2024-08-02T10:13:48.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22515|2024-08-02T10:13:48.693Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22515</link>
      <description>Atlassian has been made aware of an issue reported by a handful of customers where external attackers may have exploited a previously unknown vulnerability in publicly accessible Confluence Data Center and Server instances to create unauthorized Confluence administrator accounts and access Confluence instances. &#13;
&#13;
Atlassian Cloud sites are not affected by this vulnerability. If your Confluence site is accessed via an atlassian.net domain, it is hosted by Atlassian and is not vulnerable to this issue. </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22515|2024-08-02T10:13:48.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22516|2024-08-02T10:13:48.652Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22516</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in versions 8.1.0, 8.2.0, 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, and 9.3.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.&#13;
&#13;
This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.5, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.&#13;
&#13;
Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:&#13;
 Bamboo Data Center and Server 9.2: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.2.7.&#13;
  JDK 1.8u121+ should be used in case Java 8 used to run Bamboo Data Center and Server. See Bamboo 9.2 Upgrade notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-9-2-upgrade-notes-1207179212.html)&#13;
&#13;
 Bamboo Data Center and Server 9.3: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.3.4&#13;
&#13;
See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html]). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives]).&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability was discovered by a private user and reported via our Bug Bounty program</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22516|2024-08-02T10:13:48.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22505|2024-08-02T10:13:48.555Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22505</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability known as CVE-2023-22505 was introduced in version 8.0.0 of Confluence Data Center &amp; Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that you upgrade your instance to latest version. If you're unable to upgrade to latest, upgrade to one of these fixed versions: 8.3.2, 8.4.0. See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html).|https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html).]  You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center &amp; Server from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).|https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).] 

This vulnerability was discovered by a private user and reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22505|2024-08-02T10:13:48.555Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22522|2024-08-02T10:13:48.928Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22522</link>
      <description>This Template Injection vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker, including one with anonymous access, to inject unsafe user input into a Confluence page. Using this approach, an attacker is able to achieve Remote Code Execution (RCE) on an affected instance. Publicly accessible Confluence Data Center and Server versions as listed below are at risk and require immediate attention. See the advisory for additional details

Atlassian Cloud sites are not affected by this vulnerability. If your Confluence site is accessed via an atlassian.net domain, it is hosted by Atlassian and is not vulnerable to this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22522|2024-08-02T10:13:48.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22504|2024-08-02T10:13:48.544Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22504</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server allow remote attackers who have read permissions to a page, but not write permissions, to upload attachments via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the attachments feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22504|2024-08-02T10:13:48.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 14:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22501|2024-08-02T10:13:48.675Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20management%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22501</link>
      <description>An authentication vulnerability was discovered in Jira Service Management Server and Data Center which allows an attacker to impersonate another user and gain access to a Jira Service Management instance under certain circumstances_._ With write access to a User Directory and outgoing email enabled on a Jira Service Management instance, an attacker could gain access to signup tokens sent to users with accounts that have never been logged into. Access to these tokens can be obtained in two cases:

* If the attacker is included on Jira issues or requests with these users, or
* If the attacker is forwarded or otherwise gains access to emails containing a “View Request” link from these users.

Bot accounts are particularly susceptible to this scenario. On instances with single sign-on, external customer accounts can be affected in projects where anyone can create their own account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22501|2024-08-02T10:13:48.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 18:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22527|2024-08-02T10:13:49.010Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22527</link>
      <description>A template injection vulnerability on older versions of Confluence Data Center and Server allows an unauthenticated attacker to achieve RCE on an affected instance. Customers using an affected version must take immediate action.

Most recent supported versions of Confluence Data Center and Server are not affected by this vulnerability as it was ultimately mitigated during regular version updates. However, Atlassian recommends that customers take care to install the latest version to protect their instances from non-critical vulnerabilities outlined in Atlassian’s January Security Bulletin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22527|2024-08-02T10:13:49.010Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21686|2024-08-01T22:27:36.033Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21686</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.13 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.3, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21686|2024-08-01T22:27:36.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-08-01T22:27:36.189Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-08-01T22:27:36.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21678|2024-08-01T22:27:35.810Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21678</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in version 2.7.0 of Confluence Data Center.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.5, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, low impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.
Data Center

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.7.0 to 8.7.1|8.8.0 recommended or 8.7.2|
|from 8.6.0 to 8.6.1|8.8.0 recommended|
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
Server

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:

 
||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS recommended |
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|

See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html]). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives]).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21678|2024-08-01T22:27:35.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-08-01T22:27:35.803Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-08-01T22:27:35.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21677|2024-08-01T22:27:35.969Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21677</link>
      <description>This High severity Path Traversal vulnerability was introduced in version 6.13.0 of Confluence Data Center. This Path Traversal vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.3, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit an undefinable vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions: Data Center Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version and that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version.

If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives. 

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21677|2024-08-01T22:27:35.969Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21682|2024-08-01T22:27:35.986Z -- atlassian -- assets%20discovery%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21682</link>
      <description>This High severity Injection vulnerability was introduced in Assets Discovery 1.0 - 6.2.0 (all versions). 

Assets Discovery, which can be downloaded via Atlassian Marketplace, is a network scanning tool that can be used with or without an agent with Jira Service Management Cloud, Data Center or Server. It detects hardware and software that is connected to your local network and extracts detailed information about each asset. This data can then be imported into Assets in Jira Service Management to help you manage all of the devices and configuration items within your local network.

This Injection vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to modify the actions taken by a system call which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Assets Discovery customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/assetapps/assets-discovery-3-2-1-cloud-6-2-1-data_center-1333987182.html). You can download the latest version of Assets Discovery from the Atlassian Marketplace (https://marketplace.atlassian.com/apps/1214668/assets-discovery?hosting=datacenter&amp;amp;tab=installation).

This vulnerability was reported via our Penetration Testing program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21682|2024-08-01T22:27:35.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-08-01T22:27:36.035Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-08-01T22:27:36.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21684|2024-08-01T22:27:36.150Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21684</link>
      <description>There is a low severity open redirect vulnerability within affected versions of Bitbucket Data Center. Versions of Bitbucket DC from 8.0.0 to 8.9.12 and 8.19.0 to 8.19.1 are affected by this vulnerability. It is patched in 8.9.13 and 8.19.2.

This open redirect vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 3.1 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect a victim user upon login to Bitbucket Data Center to any arbitrary site which can be utilized for further exploitation which has low impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center customers upgrade to the version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the  supported fixed versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21684|2024-08-01T22:27:36.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T06:47:39.038Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T06:47:39.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-20T03:55:33.558Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-20T03:55:33.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-16T20:30:00.385Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-16T20:30:00.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21686|2024-07-16T20:00:02.617Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21686</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in versions 7.13 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.3, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21686|2024-07-16T20:00:02.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21677|2024-06-21T18:07:46.098Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21677</link>
      <description>This High severity Path Traversal vulnerability was introduced in version 6.13.0 of Confluence Data Center. This Path Traversal vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.3, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit an undefinable vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions: Data Center Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version and that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version.

If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives. 

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21677|2024-06-21T18:07:46.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21678|2024-06-04T17:38:08.576Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21678</link>
      <description>This High severity Stored XSS vulnerability was introduced in version 2.7.0 of Confluence Data Center.

This Stored XSS vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.5, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victims browser which has high impact to confidentiality, low impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.
Data Center

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.7.0 to 8.7.1|8.8.0 recommended or 8.7.2|
|from 8.6.0 to 8.6.1|8.8.0 recommended|
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.8.0 recommended or 8.5.6 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
Server

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:

 
||Affected versions||Fixed versions||
|from 8.5.0 to 8.5.4 LTS|8.5.5 LTS or 8.5.6 LTS recommended |
|from 8.4.0 to 8.4.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.3.0 to 8.3.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.2.0 to 8.2.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.1.0 to 8.1.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 8.0.0 to 8.0.4|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.20.0 to 7.20.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended|
|from 7.19.0 to 7.19.17 LTS|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.18 LTS or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.18.0 to 7.18.3|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|from 7.17.0 to 7.17.5|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|
|Any earlier versions|8.5.6 LTS recommended or 7.19.19 LTS|

See the release notes ([https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html]). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center from the download center ([https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives]).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21678|2024-06-04T17:38:08.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21677|2024-03-19T17:30:00.500Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21677</link>
      <description>This High severity Path Traversal vulnerability was introduced in version 6.13.0 of Confluence Data Center. This Path Traversal vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.3, allows an unauthenticated attacker to exploit an undefinable vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions: Data Center Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center customers upgrade to the latest version and that Confluence Server customers upgrade to the latest 8.5.x LTS version.

If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives. 

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21677|2024-03-19T17:30:00.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21682|2024-02-20T18:00:00.699Z -- atlassian -- assets%20discovery%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21682</link>
      <description>This High severity Injection vulnerability was introduced in Assets Discovery 1.0 - 6.2.0 (all versions). 

Assets Discovery, which can be downloaded via Atlassian Marketplace, is a network scanning tool that can be used with or without an agent with Jira Service Management Cloud, Data Center or Server. It detects hardware and software that is connected to your local network and extracts detailed information about each asset. This data can then be imported into Assets in Jira Service Management to help you manage all of the devices and configuration items within your local network.

This Injection vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to modify the actions taken by a system call which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Assets Discovery customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/assetapps/assets-discovery-3-2-1-cloud-6-2-1-data_center-1333987182.html). You can download the latest version of Assets Discovery from the Atlassian Marketplace (https://marketplace.atlassian.com/apps/1214668/assets-discovery?hosting=datacenter&amp;amp;tab=installation).

This vulnerability was reported via our Penetration Testing program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21682|2024-02-20T18:00:00.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-06-10T17:30:00.572Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-06-10T17:30:00.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-18T17:00:02.531Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-18T17:00:02.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-26T17:43:55.994Z -- atlassian -- jira%20core%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21685</link>
      <description>This High severity Information Disclosure vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.4.0, 9.12.0, and 9.15.0 of Jira Core Data Center. 
	
	This Information Disclosure vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.4, allows an unauthenticated attacker to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability which has high impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction. 
	
	Atlassian recommends that Jira Core Data Center customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.4: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.4.21
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.12.8
		
		Jira Core Data Center 9.16: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 9.16.0
		
		
	
	See the release notes. You can download the latest version of Jira Core Data Center from the download center. 
	
	This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21685|2024-06-26T17:43:55.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-17T15:27:45.652Z -- atlassian -- bamboo%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21687</link>
      <description>This High severity File Inclusion vulnerability was introduced in versions 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 9.2.0, 9.3.0, 9.4.0, 9.5.0 and 9.6.0 of Bamboo Data Center and Server.

This File Inclusion vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.1, allows an authenticated attacker to get the application to display the contents of a local file, or execute a different files already stored locally on the server which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires no user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bamboo Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions listed on this CVE

See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bambooreleases/bamboo-release-notes-1189793869.html). You can download the latest version of Bamboo Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bamboo/download-archives).

This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21687|2024-07-17T15:27:45.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21684|2024-07-24T18:45:23.880Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21684</link>
      <description>There is a low severity open redirect vulnerability within affected versions of Bitbucket Data Center. Versions of Bitbucket DC from 8.0.0 to 8.9.12 and 8.19.0 to 8.19.1 are affected by this vulnerability. It is patched in 8.9.13 and 8.19.2.

This open redirect vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 3.1 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect a victim user upon login to Bitbucket Data Center to any arbitrary site which can be utilized for further exploitation which has low impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center customers upgrade to the version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the  supported fixed versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21684|2024-07-24T18:45:23.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T07:52:01.198Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21683</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 5.2 of Confluence Data Center and Server.

This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 7.2, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. 

Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions. See the release notes https://confluence.atlassian.com/doc/confluence-release-notes-327.html

You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives.

This vulnerability was found internally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21683|2024-07-31T07:52:01.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
