<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Application Links</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/application%20links.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Application Links</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 08:24:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20105|2024-08-05T02:32:10.632Z -- atlassian -- application%20links
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20105</link>
      <description>The EditApplinkServlet resource in the Atlassian Application Links plugin before version 5.4.20, from version 6.0.0 before version 6.0.12, from version 6.1.0 before version 6.1.2, from version 7.0.0 before version 7.0.1, and from version 7.1.0 before version 7.1.3 allows remote attackers who have obtained access to administrator's session to access the EditApplinkServlet resource without needing to re-authenticate to pass "WebSudo" in products that support "WebSudo" through an improper access control vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20105|2024-08-05T02:32:10.632Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20100|2024-08-05T02:32:10.519Z -- atlassian -- application%20links
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20100</link>
      <description>The Atlassian Application Links plugin is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery (CSRF). The following versions are affected: all versions prior to 5.4.21, from version 6.0.0 before version 6.0.12, from version 6.1.0 before version 6.1.2, from version 7.0.0 before version 7.0.2, and from version 7.1.0 before version 7.1.3. The vulnerable plugin is used by Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.7.0. An attacker could exploit this by tricking an administrative user into making malicious HTTP requests, allowing the attacker to enumerate hosts and open ports on the internal network where Jira server is present.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20100|2024-08-05T02:32:10.519Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15011|2024-08-05T00:34:53.139Z -- atlassian -- application%20links
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15011</link>
      <description>The ListEntityLinksServlet resource in Application Links before version 5.0.12, from version 5.1.0 before version 5.2.11, from version 5.3.0 before version 5.3.7, from version 5.4.0 before 5.4.13, and from version 6.0.0 before 6.0.5 disclosed application link information to non-admin users via a missing permissions check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15011|2024-08-05T00:34:53.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
