<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Application Links</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/application%20links.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Application Links</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 22:23:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16860|2024-09-17T00:10:37.417Z -- atlassian -- application%20links
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16860</link>
      <description>The invalidRedirectUrl template in Atlassian Application Links before version 5.2.7, from version 5.3.0 before version 5.3.4 and from version 5.4.0 before version 5.4.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the redirectUrl parameter link in the redirect warning message.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16860|2024-09-17T00:10:37.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20100|2024-09-17T00:40:31.695Z -- atlassian -- application%20links
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20100</link>
      <description>The Atlassian Application Links plugin is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery (CSRF). The following versions are affected: all versions prior to 5.4.21, from version 6.0.0 before version 6.0.12, from version 6.1.0 before version 6.1.2, from version 7.0.0 before version 7.0.2, and from version 7.1.0 before version 7.1.3. The vulnerable plugin is used by Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.7.0. An attacker could exploit this by tricking an administrative user into making malicious HTTP requests, allowing the attacker to enumerate hosts and open ports on the internal network where Jira server is present.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20100|2024-09-17T00:40:31.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 14:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
