<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Bamboo</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/bamboo.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Bamboo</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:23:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18082|2024-09-16T18:38:32.846Z -- atlassian -- bamboo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18082</link>
      <description>The plan configure branches resource in Atlassian Bamboo before version 6.2.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the name of a branch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18082|2024-09-16T18:38:32.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14589|2024-09-16T19:10:55.831Z -- atlassian -- bamboo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14589</link>
      <description>It was possible for double OGNL evaluation in FreeMarker templates through Struts FreeMarker tags to occur. An attacker who has restricted administration rights to Bamboo or who hosts a website that a Bamboo administrator visits, is able to exploit this vulnerability to execute Java code of their choice on systems that run a vulnerable version of Bamboo. All versions of Bamboo before 6.1.6 (the fixed version for 6.1.x) and from 6.2.0 before 6.2.5 (the fixed version for 6.2.x) are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14589|2024-09-16T19:10:55.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18041|2024-09-16T19:04:12.784Z -- atlassian -- bamboo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18041</link>
      <description>The viewDeploymentVersionJiraIssuesDialog resource in Atlassian Bamboo before version 6.2.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the name of a release.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18041|2024-09-16T19:04:12.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26067|2024-09-16T18:34:10.127Z -- atlassian -- bamboo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26067</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Bamboo allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to view a stack trace that may reveal the path for the home directory in disk and if certain files exists on the tmp directory, via a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability in the /chart endpoint. The affected versions are before version 7.2.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26067|2024-09-16T18:34:10.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 01:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5224|2024-09-16T18:04:23.118Z -- atlassian -- bamboo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5224</link>
      <description>Bamboo did not correctly check if a configured Mercurial repository URI contained values that the Windows operating system may consider argument parameters. An attacker who has permission to create a repository in Bamboo, edit an existing plan in Bamboo that has a non-linked Mercurial repository, or create a plan in Bamboo either globally or in a project using Bamboo Specs can can execute code of their choice on systems that run a vulnerable version of Bamboo on the Windows operating system. All versions of Bamboo starting with 2.7.0 before 6.3.3 (the fixed version for 6.3.x) and from version 6.4.0 before 6.4.1 (the fixed version for 6.4.x) running on the Windows operating system are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5224|2024-09-16T18:04:23.118Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
