<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Bitbucket Data Center</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/bitbucket%20data%20center.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Bitbucket Data Center</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:20:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22513|2024-08-02T10:13:48.688Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22513</link>
      <description>This High severity RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability was introduced in version 8.0.0 of Bitbucket Data Center and Server. This RCE (Remote Code Execution) vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 8.5, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity, high impact to availability, and requires no user interaction. Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center and Server customers upgrade to latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions: Bitbucket Data Center and Server 8.9: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.9.5 Bitbucket Data Center and Server 8.10: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.10.5 Bitbucket Data Center and Server 8.11: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.11.4 Bitbucket Data Center and Server 8.12: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.12.2 Bitbucket Data Center and Server 8.13: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.13.1 Bitbucket Data Center and Server 8.14: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.14.0 Bitbucket Data Center and Server version &gt;= 8.0 and &lt; 8.9: Upgrade to any of the listed fix versions. See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/bitbucketserver/release-notes). You can download the latest version of Bitbucket Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/bitbucket/download-archives). This vulnerability was discovered by a private user and reported via our Bug Bounty program</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22513|2024-08-02T10:13:48.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21684|2024-07-24T18:45:23.880Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21684</link>
      <description>There is a low severity open redirect vulnerability within affected versions of Bitbucket Data Center. Versions of Bitbucket DC from 8.0.0 to 8.9.12 and 8.19.0 to 8.19.1 are affected by this vulnerability. It is patched in 8.9.13 and 8.19.2.

This open redirect vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 3.1 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect a victim user upon login to Bitbucket Data Center to any arbitrary site which can be utilized for further exploitation which has low impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center customers upgrade to the version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the  supported fixed versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21684|2024-07-24T18:45:23.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21684|2024-08-01T22:27:36.150Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20data%20center</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21684</link>
      <description>There is a low severity open redirect vulnerability within affected versions of Bitbucket Data Center. Versions of Bitbucket DC from 8.0.0 to 8.9.12 and 8.19.0 to 8.19.1 are affected by this vulnerability. It is patched in 8.9.13 and 8.19.2.

This open redirect vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 3.1 and a CVSS Vector of CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect a victim user upon login to Bitbucket Data Center to any arbitrary site which can be utilized for further exploitation which has low impact to confidentiality, no impact to integrity, no impact to availability, and requires user interaction.

Atlassian recommends that Bitbucket Data Center customers upgrade to the version. If you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the  supported fixed versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21684|2024-08-01T22:27:36.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
