<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Bitbucket Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/bitbucket%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Bitbucket Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 22:22:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18037|2024-09-16T20:27:24.181Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18037</link>
      <description>The git repository tag rest resource in Atlassian Bitbucket Server from version 3.7.0 before 4.14.11 (the fixed version for 4.14.x), from version 5.0.0 before 5.0.9 (the fixed version for 5.0.x), from version 5.1.0 before 5.1.8 (the fixed version for 5.1.x), from version 5.2.0 before 5.2.6 (the fixed version for 5.2.x), from version 5.3.0 before 5.3.4 (the fixed version for 5.3.x), from version 5.4.0 before 5.4.2 (the fixed version for 5.4.x), from version 5.5.0 before 5.5.1 (the fixed version for 5.5.x) and before 5.6.0 allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files via a path traversal vulnerability through the name of a git tag.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18037|2024-09-16T20:27:24.181Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5225|2024-09-16T18:49:04.214Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5225</link>
      <description>In browser editing in Atlassian Bitbucket Server from version 4.13.0 before 5.4.8 (the fixed version for 4.13.0 through 5.4.7), 5.5.0 before 5.5.8 (the fixed version for 5.5.x), 5.6.0 before 5.6.5 (the fixed version for 5.6.x), 5.7.0 before 5.7.3 (the fixed version for 5.7.x), and 5.8.0 before 5.8.2 (the fixed version for 5.8.x), allows authenticated users to gain remote code execution using the in browser editing feature via editing a symbolic link within a repository.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5225|2024-09-16T18:49:04.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36233|2024-09-16T19:30:12.974Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36233</link>
      <description>The Microsoft Windows Installer for Atlassian Bitbucket Server and Data Center before version 6.10.9, 7.x before 7.6.4, and from version 7.7.0 before 7.10.1 allows local attackers to escalate privileges because of weak permissions on the installation directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36233|2024-09-16T19:30:12.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 15:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18036|2024-09-16T19:04:43.701Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18036</link>
      <description>The Github repository importer in Atlassian Bitbucket Server before version 5.3.0 allows remote attackers to determine if a service they could not otherwise reach has open ports via a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18036|2024-09-16T19:04:43.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15005|2024-09-16T20:31:42.718Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15005</link>
      <description>The Atlassian Troubleshooting and Support Tools plugin prior to version 1.17.2 allows an unprivileged user to initiate periodic log scans and send the results to a user-specified email address due to a missing authorization check. The email message may contain configuration information about the application that the plugin is installed into. A vulnerable version of the plugin is included with Bitbucket Server / Data Center before 6.6.0, Confluence Server / Data Center before 7.0.1, Jira Server / Data Center before 8.3.2, Crowd / Crowd Data Center before 3.6.0, Fisheye before 4.7.2, Crucible before 4.7.2, and Bamboo before 6.10.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15005|2024-09-16T20:31:42.718Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 03:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36804|2024-09-16T18:14:18.941Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36804</link>
      <description>Multiple API endpoints in Atlassian Bitbucket Server and Data Center 7.0.0 before version 7.6.17, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.17.10, from version 7.18.0 before version 7.21.4, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.3, from version 8.1.0 before version 8.1.3, and from version 8.2.0 before version 8.2.2, and from version 8.3.0 before 8.3.1 allows remote attackers with read permissions to a public or private Bitbucket repository to execute arbitrary code by sending a malicious HTTP request. This vulnerability was reported via our Bug Bounty Program by TheGrandPew.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36804|2024-09-16T18:14:18.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 05:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20097|2024-09-16T18:48:48.325Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20097</link>
      <description>Bitbucket Server and Bitbucket Data Center versions starting from 1.0.0 before 5.16.11, from version 6.0.0 before 6.0.11, from version 6.1.0 before 6.1.9, from version 6.2.0 before 6.2.7, from version 6.3.0 before 6.3.6, from version 6.4.0 before 6.4.4, from version 6.5.0 before 6.5.3, from version 6.6.0 before 6.6.3, from version 6.7.0 before 6.7.3, from version 6.8.0 before 6.8.2, from version 6.9.0 before 6.9.1 had a Remote Code Execution vulnerability via the post-receive hook. A remote attacker with permission to clone and push files to a repository on the victim's Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center instance, can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands on the Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center systems, using a file with specially crafted content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20097|2024-09-16T18:48:48.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 20:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
