<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Bitbucket Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/bitbucket%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Bitbucket Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 11:21:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18087|2024-09-17T01:56:57.833Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18087</link>
      <description>The download commit resource in Atlassian Bitbucket Server from version 5.1.0 before version 5.1.7, from version 5.2.0 before version 5.2.5, from version 5.3.0 before version 5.3.3 and from version 5.4.0 before version 5.4.1 allows remote attackers to write files to disk potentially allowing them to gain code execution, exploit CVE-2017-1000117 if a vulnerable version of git is in use, and or determine if an internal service exists via an argument injection vulnerability in the at parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18087|2024-09-17T01:56:57.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15000|2024-09-17T01:41:56.351Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15000</link>
      <description>The commit diff rest endpoint in Bitbucket Server and Data Center before 5.16.10 (the fixed version for 5.16.x ), from 6.0.0 before 6.0.10 (the fixed version for 6.0.x), from 6.1.0 before 6.1.8 (the fixed version for 6.1.x), from 6.2.0 before 6.2.6 (the fixed version for 6.2.x), from 6.3.0 before 6.3.5 (the fixed version for 6.3.x), from 6.4.0 before 6.4.3 (the fixed version for 6.4.x), and from 6.5.0 before 6.5.2 (the fixed version for 6.5.x) allows remote attackers who have permission to access a repository, if public access is enabled for a project or repository then attackers are able to exploit this issue anonymously, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the system and execute commands via injecting additional arguments into git commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15000|2024-09-17T01:41:56.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 14:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15012|2024-09-17T04:24:12.976Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15012</link>
      <description>Bitbucket Server and Bitbucket Data Center from version 4.13. before 5.16.11, from version 6.0.0 before 6.0.11, from version 6.1.0 before 6.1.9, from version 6.2.0 before 6.2.7, from version 6.3.0 before 6.3.6, from version 6.4.0 before 6.4.4, from version 6.5.0 before 6.5.3, from version 6.6.0 before 6.6.3, from version 6.7.0 before 6.7.3, from version 6.8.0 before 6.8.2, from version 6.9.0 before 6.9.1 had a Remote Code Execution vulnerability via the edit-file request. A remote attacker with write permission on a repository can write to any arbitrary file to the victims Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center instance using the edit-file endpoint, if the user has Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center running, and has the permission to write the file at that destination. In some cases, this can result in execution of arbitrary code by the victims Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15012|2024-09-17T04:24:12.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 20:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14171|2024-09-17T02:01:36.709Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14171</link>
      <description>Atlassian Bitbucket Server from version 4.9.0 before version 7.2.4 allows remote attackers to intercept unencrypted repository import requests via a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14171|2024-09-17T02:01:36.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 17:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14170|2024-09-17T04:09:37.826Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14170</link>
      <description>Webhooks in Atlassian Bitbucket Server from version 5.4.0 before version 7.3.1 allow remote attackers to access the content of internal network resources via a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14170|2024-09-17T04:09:37.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 17:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18038|2024-09-17T04:04:47.652Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18038</link>
      <description>The repository settings resource in Atlassian Bitbucket Server before version 5.6.0 allows remote attackers to read the first line of arbitrary files via a path traversal vulnerability through the default branch name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18038|2024-09-17T04:04:47.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
