<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Bitbucket Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/bitbucket%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Bitbucket Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:23:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15005|2024-08-05T00:34:53.099Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15005</link>
      <description>The Atlassian Troubleshooting and Support Tools plugin prior to version 1.17.2 allows an unprivileged user to initiate periodic log scans and send the results to a user-specified email address due to a missing authorization check. The email message may contain configuration information about the application that the plugin is installed into. A vulnerable version of the plugin is included with Bitbucket Server / Data Center before 6.6.0, Confluence Server / Data Center before 7.0.1, Jira Server / Data Center before 8.3.2, Crowd / Crowd Data Center before 3.6.0, Fisheye before 4.7.2, Crucible before 4.7.2, and Bamboo before 6.10.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15005|2024-08-05T00:34:53.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15010|2024-08-05T00:34:53.027Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15010</link>
      <description>Bitbucket Server and Bitbucket Data Center versions starting from version 3.0.0 before version 5.16.11, from version 6.0.0 before 6.0.11, from version 6.1.0 before 6.1.9, from version 6.2.0 before 6.2.7, from version 6.3.0 before 6.3.6, from version 6.4.0 before 6.4.4, from version 6.5.0 before 6.5.3, from version 6.6.0 before 6.6.3, from version 6.7.0 before 6.7.3, from version 6.8.0 before 6.8.2, and from version 6.9.0 before 6.9.1 had a Remote Code Execution vulnerability via certain user input fields. A remote attacker with user level permissions can exploit this vulnerability to run arbitrary commands on the victim's systems. Using a specially crafted payload as user input, the attacker can execute arbitrary commands on the victim's Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15010|2024-08-05T00:34:53.027Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20097|2024-08-05T02:32:10.612Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20097</link>
      <description>Bitbucket Server and Bitbucket Data Center versions starting from 1.0.0 before 5.16.11, from version 6.0.0 before 6.0.11, from version 6.1.0 before 6.1.9, from version 6.2.0 before 6.2.7, from version 6.3.0 before 6.3.6, from version 6.4.0 before 6.4.4, from version 6.5.0 before 6.5.3, from version 6.6.0 before 6.6.3, from version 6.7.0 before 6.7.3, from version 6.8.0 before 6.8.2, from version 6.9.0 before 6.9.1 had a Remote Code Execution vulnerability via the post-receive hook. A remote attacker with permission to clone and push files to a repository on the victim's Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center instance, can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands on the Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center systems, using a file with specially crafted content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20097|2024-08-05T02:32:10.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15000|2024-08-05T00:34:52.974Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15000</link>
      <description>The commit diff rest endpoint in Bitbucket Server and Data Center before 5.16.10 (the fixed version for 5.16.x ), from 6.0.0 before 6.0.10 (the fixed version for 6.0.x), from 6.1.0 before 6.1.8 (the fixed version for 6.1.x), from 6.2.0 before 6.2.6 (the fixed version for 6.2.x), from 6.3.0 before 6.3.5 (the fixed version for 6.3.x), from 6.4.0 before 6.4.3 (the fixed version for 6.4.x), and from 6.5.0 before 6.5.2 (the fixed version for 6.5.x) allows remote attackers who have permission to access a repository, if public access is enabled for a project or repository then attackers are able to exploit this issue anonymously, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the system and execute commands via injecting additional arguments into git commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15000|2024-08-05T00:34:52.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15012|2024-08-05T00:34:53.124Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15012</link>
      <description>Bitbucket Server and Bitbucket Data Center from version 4.13. before 5.16.11, from version 6.0.0 before 6.0.11, from version 6.1.0 before 6.1.9, from version 6.2.0 before 6.2.7, from version 6.3.0 before 6.3.6, from version 6.4.0 before 6.4.4, from version 6.5.0 before 6.5.3, from version 6.6.0 before 6.6.3, from version 6.7.0 before 6.7.3, from version 6.8.0 before 6.8.2, from version 6.9.0 before 6.9.1 had a Remote Code Execution vulnerability via the edit-file request. A remote attacker with write permission on a repository can write to any arbitrary file to the victims Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center instance using the edit-file endpoint, if the user has Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center running, and has the permission to write the file at that destination. In some cases, this can result in execution of arbitrary code by the victims Bitbucket Server or Bitbucket Data Center instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15012|2024-08-05T00:34:53.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5225|2024-08-05T05:33:42.723Z -- atlassian -- bitbucket%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5225</link>
      <description>In browser editing in Atlassian Bitbucket Server from version 4.13.0 before 5.4.8 (the fixed version for 4.13.0 through 5.4.7), 5.5.0 before 5.5.8 (the fixed version for 5.5.x), 5.6.0 before 5.6.5 (the fixed version for 5.6.x), 5.7.0 before 5.7.3 (the fixed version for 5.7.x), and 5.8.0 before 5.8.2 (the fixed version for 5.8.x), allows authenticated users to gain remote code execution using the in browser editing feature via editing a symbolic link within a repository.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5225|2024-08-05T05:33:42.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
