<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Confluence Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/confluence%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Confluence Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 01:37:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15006|2024-09-17T01:15:47.661Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15006</link>
      <description>There was a man-in-the-middle (MITM) vulnerability present in the Confluence Previews plugin in Confluence Server and Confluence Data Center. This plugin was used to facilitate communication with the Atlassian Companion application. The Confluence Previews plugin in Confluence Server and Confluence Data Center communicated with the Companion application via the atlassian-domain-for-localhost-connections-only.com domain name, the DNS A record of which points at 127.0.0.1. Additionally, a signed certificate for the domain was publicly distributed with the Companion application. An attacker in the position to control DNS resolution of their victim could carry out a man-in-the-middle (MITM) attack between Confluence Server (or Confluence Data Center) and the atlassian-domain-for-localhost-connections-only.com domain intended to be used with the Companion application. This certificate has been revoked, however, usage of the atlassian-domain-for-localhost-connections-only.com domain name was still present in Confluence Server and Confluence Data Center. An attacker could perform the described attack by denying their victim access to certificate revocation information, and carry out a man-in-the-middle (MITM) attack to observe files being edited using the Companion application and/or modify them, and access some limited user information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15006|2024-09-17T01:15:47.661Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29445|2024-09-17T00:11:54.979Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29445</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Confluence Server before 7.4.8, and versions from 7.5.0 before 7.11.0 allow attackers to identify internal hosts and ports via a blind server-side request forgery vulnerability in Team Calendars parameters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29445|2024-09-17T00:11:54.979Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 06:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3395|2024-09-17T00:20:30.157Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3395</link>
      <description>The WebDAV endpoint in Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center before version 6.6.7 (the fixed version for 6.6.x), from version 6.7.0 before 6.8.5 (the fixed version for 6.8.x), and from version 6.9.0 before 6.9.3 (the fixed version for 6.9.x) allows remote attackers to send arbitrary HTTP and WebDAV requests from a Confluence Server or Data Center instance via Server-Side Request Forgery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3395|2024-09-17T00:20:30.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 18:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
