<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Confluence Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/confluence%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Confluence Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:23:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29448|2024-08-04T16:55:09.777Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29448</link>
      <description>The ConfluenceResourceDownloadRewriteRule class in Confluence Server and Confluence Data Center before version 6.13.18, from 6.14.0 before 7.4.6, and from 7.5.0 before 7.8.3 allowed unauthenticated remote attackers to read arbitrary files within WEB-INF and META-INF directories via an incorrect path access check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29448|2024-08-04T16:55:09.777Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29444|2024-08-04T16:55:09.765Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29444</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Team Calendar in Confluence Server before 7.11.0 allow attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or Javascript via a Cross Site Scripting Vulnerability in admin global setting parameters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29444|2024-08-04T16:55:09.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43940|2024-08-04T04:10:17.171Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43940</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center allow authenticated local attackers to achieve elevated privileges on the local system via a DLL Hijacking vulnerability in the Confluence installer. This vulnerability only affects installations of Confluence Server and Data Center on Windows. The affected versions are before version 7.4.10, and from version 7.5.0 before 7.12.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43940|2024-08-04T04:10:17.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39114|2024-08-04T01:58:17.751Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39114</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center allow users with a valid account on a Confluence Data Center instance to execute arbitrary Java code or run arbitrary system commands by injecting an OGNL payload. The affected versions are before version 6.13.23, from version 6.14.0 before 7.4.11, from version 7.5.0 before 7.11.6, and from version 7.12.0 before 7.12.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39114|2024-08-04T01:58:17.751Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3396|2024-08-04T19:12:09.544Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3396</link>
      <description>The Widget Connector macro in Atlassian Confluence Server before version 6.6.12 (the fixed version for 6.6.x), from version 6.7.0 before 6.12.3 (the fixed version for 6.12.x), from version 6.13.0 before 6.13.3 (the fixed version for 6.13.x), and from version 6.14.0 before 6.14.2 (the fixed version for 6.14.x), allows remote attackers to achieve path traversal and remote code execution on a Confluence Server or Data Center instance via server-side template injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3396|2024-08-04T19:12:09.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36290|2024-08-04T17:23:09.942Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36290</link>
      <description>The Livesearch macro in Confluence Server and Data Center before version 7.4.5, from version 7.5.0 before 7.6.3, and from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.4 allows remote attackers with permission to edit a page or blog to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the page excerpt functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36290|2024-08-04T17:23:09.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3395|2024-08-04T19:12:08.548Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3395</link>
      <description>The WebDAV endpoint in Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center before version 6.6.7 (the fixed version for 6.6.x), from version 6.7.0 before 6.8.5 (the fixed version for 6.8.x), and from version 6.9.0 before 6.9.3 (the fixed version for 6.9.x) allows remote attackers to send arbitrary HTTP and WebDAV requests from a Confluence Server or Data Center instance via Server-Side Request Forgery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3395|2024-08-04T19:12:08.548Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29450|2024-08-04T16:55:09.661Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29450</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in the avatar upload feature. The affected versions are before version 7.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29450|2024-08-04T16:55:09.661Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14175|2024-08-04T12:39:36.159Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14175</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in user macro parameters. The affected versions are before version 7.4.2, and from version 7.5.0 before 7.5.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14175|2024-08-04T12:39:36.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4027|2024-08-04T07:52:20.854Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4027</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Confluence Server and Data Center allowed remote attackers with system administration permissions to bypass velocity template injection mitigations via an injection vulnerability in custom user macros. The affected versions are before version 7.4.5, and from version 7.5.0 before 7.5.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4027|2024-08-04T07:52:20.854Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29445|2024-08-04T16:55:10.375Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29445</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Confluence Server before 7.4.8, and versions from 7.5.0 before 7.11.0 allow attackers to identify internal hosts and ports via a blind server-side request forgery vulnerability in Team Calendars parameters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29445|2024-08-04T16:55:10.375Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3394|2024-08-04T19:12:09.337Z -- atlassian -- confluence%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3394</link>
      <description>There was a local file disclosure vulnerability in Confluence Server and Confluence Data Center via page exporting. An attacker with permission to editing a page is able to exploit this issue to read arbitrary file on the server under &lt;install-directory&gt;/confluence/WEB-INF directory, which may contain configuration files used for integrating with other services, which could potentially leak credentials or other sensitive information such as LDAP credentials. The LDAP credential will be potentially leaked only if the Confluence server is configured to use LDAP as user repository. All versions of Confluence Server from 6.1.0 before 6.6.16 (the fixed version for 6.6.x), from 6.7.0 before 6.13.7 (the fixed version for 6.13.x), and from 6.14.0 before 6.15.8 (the fixed version for 6.15.x) are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3394|2024-08-04T19:12:09.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
