<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Crowd</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/crowd.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Crowd</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:22:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20104|2024-08-05T02:32:10.611Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20104</link>
      <description>The OpenID client application in Atlassian Crowd before version 3.6.2, and from version 3.7.0 before 3.7.1 allows remote attackers to perform a Denial of Service attack via an XML Entity Expansion vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20104|2024-08-05T02:32:10.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18110|2024-08-05T21:13:48.200Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18110</link>
      <description>The administration backup restore resource in Atlassian Crowd before version 3.0.2 and from version 3.1.0 before version 3.1.1 allows remote attackers to read files from the filesystem via a XXE vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18110|2024-08-05T21:13:48.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18107|2024-08-05T21:13:48.099Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18107</link>
      <description>Various resources in the Crowd Demo application of Atlassian Crowd before version 3.1.1 allow remote attackers to modify add, modify and delete users &amp; groups via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability. Please be aware that the Demo application is not enabled by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18107|2024-08-05T21:13:48.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18105|2024-08-05T21:13:48.142Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18105</link>
      <description>The console login resource in Atlassian Crowd before version 3.0.2 and from version 3.1.0 before version 3.1.1 allows remote attackers, who have previously obtained a user's JSESSIONID cookie, to gain access to some of the built-in and potentially third party rest resources via a session fixation vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18105|2024-08-05T21:13:48.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18106|2024-08-05T21:13:48.419Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18106</link>
      <description>The identifier_hash for a session token in Atlassian Crowd before version 2.9.1 could potentially collide with an identifier_hash for another user or a user in a different directory, this allows remote attackers who can authenticate to Crowd or an application using Crowd for authentication to gain access to another user's session provided they can make their identifier hash collide with another user's session identifier hash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18106|2024-08-05T21:13:48.419Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20902|2024-08-05T02:53:09.638Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20902</link>
      <description>Upgrading Crowd via XML Data Transfer can reactivate a disabled user from OpenLDAP. The affected versions are from before version 3.4.6 and from 3.5.0 before 3.5.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20902|2024-08-05T02:53:09.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18108|2024-08-05T21:13:48.822Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18108</link>
      <description>The administration SMTP configuration resource in Atlassian Crowd before version 2.10.2 allows remote attackers with administration rights to execute arbitrary code via a JNDI injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18108|2024-08-05T21:13:48.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20238|2024-08-05T11:58:19.098Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20238</link>
      <description>Various rest resources in Atlassian Crowd before version 3.2.7 and from version 3.3.0 before version 3.3.4 allow remote attackers to authenticate using an expired user session via an insufficient session expiration vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20238|2024-08-05T11:58:19.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18109|2024-08-05T21:13:48.570Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18109</link>
      <description>The login resource of CrowdId in Atlassian Crowd before version 3.0.2 and from version 3.1.0 before version 3.1.1 allows remote attackers to redirect users to a different website which they may use as part of performing a phishing attack via an open redirect.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18109|2024-08-05T21:13:48.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16858|2024-08-05T20:35:21.278Z -- atlassian -- crowd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16858</link>
      <description>The 'crowd-application' plugin module (notably used by the Google Apps plugin) in Atlassian Crowd from version 1.5.0 before version 3.1.2 allowed an attacker to impersonate a Crowd user in REST requests by being able to authenticate to a directory bound to an application using the feature. Given the following situation: the Crowd application is bound to directory 1 and has a user called admin and the Google Apps application is bound to directory 2, which also has a user called admin, it was possible to authenticate REST requests using the credentials of the user coming from directory 2 and impersonate the user from directory 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16858|2024-08-05T20:35:21.278Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
