<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Fisheye and Crucible</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/fisheye%20and%20crucible.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Fisheye and Crucible</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:23:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13392|2024-08-05T09:00:35.118Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13392</link>
      <description>Several resources in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.6.0 allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in linked issue keys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13392|2024-08-05T09:00:35.118Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5228|2024-08-05T05:33:42.718Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5228</link>
      <description>The /browse/~raw resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.5.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the handling of response headers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5228|2024-08-05T05:33:42.718Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5223|2024-08-05T05:26:47.210Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5223</link>
      <description>Fisheye and Crucible did not correctly check if a configured Mercurial repository URI contained values that the Windows operating system may consider argument parameters. An attacker who has permission to add a repository in Fisheye or Crucible can execute code of their choice on systems that run a vulnerable version of Fisheye or Crucible on the Windows operating system. All versions of Fisheye and Crucible before 4.4.6 (the fixed version for 4.4.x) and from 4.5.0 before 4.5.3 (the fixed version for 4.5.x) are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5223|2024-08-05T05:26:47.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13399|2024-08-05T09:00:35.148Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13399</link>
      <description>The Microsoft Windows Installer for Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.6.1 allows local attackers to escalate privileges because of weak permissions on the installation directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13399|2024-08-05T09:00:35.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13388|2024-08-05T09:00:35.142Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13388</link>
      <description>The review attachment resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.5.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in attached files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13388|2024-08-05T09:00:35.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13398|2024-08-05T09:00:35.196Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13398</link>
      <description>The administrative smart-commits resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.5.4 allows remote attackers to modify smart-commit settings via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13398|2024-08-05T09:00:35.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14591|2024-08-05T19:34:38.497Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14591</link>
      <description>Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible versions less than 4.4.3 and version 4.5.0 are vulnerable to argument injection through filenames in Mercurial repositories, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code on a system running the impacted software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14591|2024-08-05T19:34:38.497Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20240|2024-08-05T11:58:18.812Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20240</link>
      <description>The administrative linker functionality in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.7.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the href parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20240|2024-08-05T11:58:18.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20241|2024-08-05T11:58:18.849Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20241</link>
      <description>The Edit upload resource for a review in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.7.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the wbuser parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20241|2024-08-05T11:58:18.849Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16859|2024-08-05T20:35:21.222Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16859</link>
      <description>The review attachment resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.3.2, from version 4.4.0 before 4.4.3 and before version 4.5.0 allows remote attackers to read files contained within context path of the running application through a path traversal vulnerability in the command parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16859|2024-08-05T20:35:21.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16861|2024-08-05T20:35:21.220Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16861</link>
      <description>It was possible for double OGNL evaluation in certain redirect action and in WebWork URL and Anchor tags in JSP files to occur. An attacker who can access the web interface of Fisheye or Crucible or who hosts a website that a user who can access the web interface of Fisheye or Crucible visits, is able to exploit this vulnerability to execute Java code of their choice on systems that run a vulnerable version of Fisheye or Crucible. All versions of Fisheye and Crucible before 4.4.5 (the fixed version for 4.4.x) and from 4.5.0 before 4.5.2 (the fixed version for 4.5.x) are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16861|2024-08-05T20:35:21.220Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
