<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Fisheye and Crucible</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/fisheye%20and%20crucible.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Fisheye and Crucible</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 22:22:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16859|2024-09-16T17:15:00.298Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16859</link>
      <description>The review attachment resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.3.2, from version 4.4.0 before 4.4.3 and before version 4.5.0 allows remote attackers to read files contained within context path of the running application through a path traversal vulnerability in the command parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16859|2024-09-16T17:15:00.298Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14591|2024-09-16T20:46:54.683Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14591</link>
      <description>Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible versions less than 4.4.3 and version 4.5.0 are vulnerable to argument injection through filenames in Mercurial repositories, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code on a system running the impacted software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14591|2024-09-16T20:46:54.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13398|2024-09-16T18:34:54.617Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13398</link>
      <description>The administrative smart-commits resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.5.4 allows remote attackers to modify smart-commit settings via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13398|2024-09-16T18:34:54.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18091|2024-09-16T20:22:54.697Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18091</link>
      <description>The admin backupprogress action in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.4.3 (the fixed version for 4.4.x) and before 4.5.0 allows remote attackers with administrative privileges to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the filename of a backup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18091|2024-09-16T20:22:54.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18034|2024-09-16T17:38:29.337Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18034</link>
      <description>The source browse resource in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.5.1 and 4.6.0 allows allows remote attackers that have write access to an indexed repository to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in via a specially crafted repository branch name when trying to display deleted files of the branch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18034|2024-09-16T17:38:29.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5223|2024-09-16T19:56:55.062Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5223</link>
      <description>Fisheye and Crucible did not correctly check if a configured Mercurial repository URI contained values that the Windows operating system may consider argument parameters. An attacker who has permission to add a repository in Fisheye or Crucible can execute code of their choice on systems that run a vulnerable version of Fisheye or Crucible on the Windows operating system. All versions of Fisheye and Crucible before 4.4.6 (the fixed version for 4.4.x) and from 4.5.0 before 4.5.3 (the fixed version for 4.5.x) are affected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5223|2024-09-16T19:56:55.062Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13399|2024-09-16T20:21:40.541Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13399</link>
      <description>The Microsoft Windows Installer for Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.6.1 allows local attackers to escalate privileges because of weak permissions on the installation directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13399|2024-09-16T20:21:40.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18094|2024-09-16T18:28:38.668Z -- atlassian -- fisheye%20and%20crucible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18094</link>
      <description>Various resources in Atlassian Fisheye and Crucible before version 4.4.3 (the fixed version for 4.4.x) and 4.5.0 allow remote attackers with administrative privileges to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through the base path setting of a configured file system repository.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18094|2024-09-16T18:28:38.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
