<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Jira Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/jira%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Jira Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 23:22:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39119|2024-10-11T19:07:45.328Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39119</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow users who have watched an issue to continue receiving updates on the issue even after their Jira account is revoked, via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the issue notification feature. The affected versions are before version 8.19.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39119|2024-10-11T19:07:45.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 22:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39111|2024-10-11T17:20:26.330Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39111</link>
      <description>The Editor plugin in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.18, from 8.6.0 before 8.13.10, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.18.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the handling of supplied content such as from a PDF when pasted into a field such as the description field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39111|2024-10-11T17:20:26.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 06:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26081|2024-10-11T17:18:17.200Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26081</link>
      <description>REST API in Atlassian Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.16.1 allows remote attackers to enumerate usernames via a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability in the `/rest/api/latest/user/avatar/temporary` endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26081|2024-10-11T17:18:17.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 03:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39113|2024-10-11T19:09:34.976Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39113</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to continue to view cached content even after losing permissions, via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the allowlist feature. The affected versions are before version 8.13.9, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.18.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39113|2024-10-11T19:09:34.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 06:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39112|2024-10-11T17:19:59.439Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39112</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to redirect users to a malicious URL via a reverse tabnapping vulnerability in the Project Shortcuts feature. The affected versions are before version 8.5.15, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.7, from version 8.14.0 before 8.17.1, and from version 8.18.0 before 8.18.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39112|2024-10-11T17:19:59.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 02:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26086|2024-10-11T19:10:33.731Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26086</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to read particular files via a path traversal vulnerability in the /WEB-INF/web.xml endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.16.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26086|2024-10-11T19:10:33.731Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26082|2024-10-11T17:19:19.636Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26082</link>
      <description>The XML Export in Atlassian Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.17.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a stored cross site scripting vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26082|2024-10-11T17:19:19.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 03:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39117|2024-10-11T17:21:15.424Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39117</link>
      <description>The AssociateFieldToScreens page in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.18.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the name of a custom field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39117|2024-10-11T17:21:15.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 06:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
