<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Jira</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/jira.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Jira</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 17:22:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13395|2024-09-16T16:42:34.901Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13395</link>
      <description>Various resources in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.8, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3 and before version 7.11.1 allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the epic colour field of an issue while an issue is being moved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13395|2024-09-16T16:42:34.901Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8444|2024-09-16T16:33:26.240Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8444</link>
      <description>The wikirenderer component in Jira before version 7.13.6, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.3.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in image attribute specification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8444|2024-09-16T16:33:26.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 13:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11588|2024-09-16T16:57:57.828Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11588</link>
      <description>The ViewSystemInfo class doGarbageCollection method in Jira before version 7.13.6, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.2.3, and from version 8.3.0 before version 8.3.2 allows remote attackers to trigger garbage collection via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11588|2024-09-16T16:57:57.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 13:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3400|2024-09-16T16:54:02.769Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3400</link>
      <description>The labels gadget in Jira before version 7.13.2, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the jql parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3400|2024-09-16T16:54:02.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 19:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15013|2024-09-16T16:57:38.126Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15013</link>
      <description>The WorkflowResource class removeStatus method in Jira before version 7.13.12, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.4.3, and from version 8.5.0 before version 8.5.2 allows authenticated remote attackers who do not have project administration access to remove a configured issue status from a project via a missing authorisation check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15013|2024-09-16T16:57:38.126Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 03:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
