<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Jira</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/jira.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Jira</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:24:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5230|2024-08-05T05:33:43.614Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5230</link>
      <description>The issue collector in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.6, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.4, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.4 and from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the error message of custom fields when an invalid value is specified.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5230|2024-08-05T05:33:43.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13400|2024-08-05T09:00:35.135Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13400</link>
      <description>Several administrative resources in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.9, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3, from version 7.11.0 before version 7.11.3, from version 7.12.0 before version 7.12.3, and before version 7.13.1 allow remote attackers who have obtained access to administrator's session to access certain administrative resources without needing to re-authenticate to pass "WebSudo" through an improper access control vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13400|2024-08-05T09:00:35.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14997|2024-08-05T00:34:53.000Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14997</link>
      <description>The AccessLogFilter class in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote anonymous attackers to learn details about other users, including their username, via an information expose through caching vulnerability when Jira is configured with a reverse Proxy and or a load balancer with caching or a CDN.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14997|2024-08-05T00:34:53.000Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15013|2024-08-05T00:34:53.218Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15013</link>
      <description>The WorkflowResource class removeStatus method in Jira before version 7.13.12, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.4.3, and from version 8.5.0 before version 8.5.2 allows authenticated remote attackers who do not have project administration access to remove a configured issue status from a project via a missing authorisation check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15013|2024-08-05T00:34:53.218Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5232|2024-08-05T05:33:43.591Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5232</link>
      <description>The EditIssue.jspa resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.7 and from version 7.7.0 before version 7.10.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the issuetype parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5232|2024-08-05T05:33:43.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13395|2024-08-05T09:00:35.128Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13395</link>
      <description>Various resources in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.8, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3 and before version 7.11.1 allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the epic colour field of an issue while an issue is being moved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13395|2024-08-05T09:00:35.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13391|2024-08-05T09:00:35.137Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13391</link>
      <description>The ProfileLinkUserFormat component of Jira Server before version 7.6.8, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3 and from version 7.11.0 before version 7.11.2 allows remote attackers who can access &amp; view an issue to obtain the email address of the reporter and assignee user of an issue despite the configured email visibility setting being set to hidden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13391|2024-08-05T09:00:35.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13404|2024-08-05T09:00:35.190Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13404</link>
      <description>The VerifyPopServerConnection resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.10, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3, from version 7.11.0 before version 7.11.3, from version 7.12.0 before version 7.12.3, and from version 7.13.0 before version 7.13.1 allows remote attackers who have administrator rights to determine the existence of internal hosts &amp; open ports and in some cases obtain service information from internal network resources via a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13404|2024-08-05T09:00:35.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13402|2024-08-05T09:00:35.161Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13402</link>
      <description>Many resources in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.9, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3, from version 7.11.0 before version 7.11.3, from version 7.12.0 before version 7.12.3, and before version 7.13.1 allow remote attackers to attack users, in some cases be able to obtain a user's Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) token, via a open redirect vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13402|2024-08-05T09:00:35.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14995|2024-08-05T00:34:53.143Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14995</link>
      <description>The /rest/api/1.0/render resource in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote anonymous attackers to determine if an attachment with a specific name exists and if an issue key is valid via a missing permissions check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14995|2024-08-05T00:34:53.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14998|2024-08-05T00:34:53.105Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14998</link>
      <description>The Webwork action Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) protection implementation in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote attackers to bypass its protection via "cookie tossing" a CSRF cookie from a subdomain of a Jira instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14998|2024-08-05T00:34:53.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13403|2024-08-05T09:00:35.157Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13403</link>
      <description>The two-dimensional filter statistics gadget in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.10, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.12.4, and from version 7.13.0 before version 7.13.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the name of a saved filter when displayed on a Jira dashboard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13403|2024-08-05T09:00:35.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14996|2024-08-05T00:34:53.093Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14996</link>
      <description>The FilterPickerPopup.jspa resource in Jira before version 7.13.7, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.3.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the searchOwnerUserName parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14996|2024-08-05T00:34:53.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20824|2024-08-05T12:12:27.311Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20824</link>
      <description>The WallboardServlet resource in Jira before version 7.13.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the cyclePeriod parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20824|2024-08-05T12:12:27.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20827|2024-08-05T12:12:27.271Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20827</link>
      <description>The activity stream gadget in Jira before version 7.13.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the country parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20827|2024-08-05T12:12:27.271Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20826|2024-08-05T12:12:28.703Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20826</link>
      <description>The inline-create rest resource in Jira before version 7.12.3 allows authenticated remote attackers to set the reporter in issues via a missing authorisation check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20826|2024-08-05T12:12:28.703Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13387|2024-08-05T09:00:35.141Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13387</link>
      <description>The IncomingMailServers resource in Atlassian JIRA Server before version 7.6.7, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3 and from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the messagesThreshold parameter as the fix for CVE-2017-18039 was incomplete.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13387|2024-08-05T09:00:35.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13401|2024-08-05T09:00:35.157Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13401</link>
      <description>The XsrfErrorAction resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.9, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3, from version 7.11.0 before version 7.11.3, from version 7.12.0 before version 7.12.3, and before version 7.13.1 allows remote attackers to obtain a user's Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) token through an open redirect vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13401|2024-08-05T09:00:35.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20232|2024-08-05T11:58:18.959Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20232</link>
      <description>The labels widget gadget in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.11 and from version 7.7.0 before version 7.13.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the rendering of retrieved content from a url location that could be manipulated by the up_projectid widget preference setting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20232|2024-08-05T11:58:18.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5231|2024-08-05T05:33:43.763Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5231</link>
      <description>The ForgotLoginDetails resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.6, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.4, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.4 and from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.2 allows remote attackers to perform a denial of service attack via sending requests to it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5231|2024-08-05T05:33:43.763Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
