<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Jira Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/jira%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Jira Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 03:23:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20098|2024-08-05T02:32:10.613Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20098</link>
      <description>The VerifySmtpServerConnection!add.jspa component in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.7.0 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery (CSRF). An attacker could exploit this by tricking an administrative user into making malicious HTTP requests, allowing the attacker to enumerate hosts and open ports on the internal network where Jira server is present.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20098|2024-08-05T02:32:10.613Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20898|2024-08-05T02:53:09.498Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20898</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to access sensitive information without being authenticated in the Global permissions screen. The affected versions are before version 8.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20898|2024-08-05T02:53:09.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20101|2024-08-05T02:32:10.530Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20101</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view whitelist rules via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the /rest/whitelist/&lt;version&gt;/check endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.13.3, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.14.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20101|2024-08-05T02:32:10.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20418|2024-08-05T02:39:09.934Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20418</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to prevent users from accessing the instance via an Application Denial of Service vulnerability in the /rendering/wiki endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20418|2024-08-05T02:39:09.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20416|2024-08-05T02:39:10.084Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20416</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the project configuration feature. The affected versions are before version 8.3.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20416|2024-08-05T02:39:10.084Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20899|2024-08-05T02:53:09.541Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20899</link>
      <description>The Gadget API in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center in affected versions allows remote attackers to make Jira unresponsive via repeated requests to a certain endpoint in the Gadget API. The affected versions are before version 8.5.4, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.6.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20899|2024-08-05T02:53:09.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20411|2024-08-05T02:39:09.917Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20411</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to modify Wallboard settings via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 7.13.9, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20411|2024-08-05T02:39:09.917Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20415|2024-08-05T02:39:09.853Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20415</link>
      <description>Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center in affected versions allows remote attackers to modify logging and profiling settings via a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 7.13.3, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20415|2024-08-05T02:39:09.853Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20403|2024-08-05T02:39:09.831Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20403</link>
      <description>The API in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.6.0 allows remote attackers to determine if a Jira project key exists or not via an information disclosure vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20403|2024-08-05T02:39:09.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20099|2024-08-05T02:32:10.521Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20099</link>
      <description>The VerifyPopServerConnection!add.jspa component in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.7.0 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery (CSRF). An attacker could exploit this by tricking an administrative user into making malicious HTTP requests, allowing the attacker to enumerate hosts and open ports on the internal network where Jira server is present.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20099|2024-08-05T02:32:10.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20408|2024-08-05T02:39:09.927Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20408</link>
      <description>The /plugins/servlet/gadgets/makeRequest resource in Jira before version 8.7.0 allows remote attackers to access the content of internal network resources via a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability due to a logic bug in the JiraWhitelist class.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20408|2024-08-05T02:39:09.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20412|2024-08-05T02:39:09.869Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20412</link>
      <description>The Convert Sub-Task to Issue page in affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to enumerate the following information via an Improper Authentication vulnerability: Workflow names; Project Key, if it is part of the workflow name; Issue Keys; Issue Types; Status Types. The affected versions are before version 7.13.9, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20412|2024-08-05T02:39:09.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20413|2024-08-05T02:39:09.910Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20413</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability on the UserPickerBrowser.jspa page. The affected versions are before version 7.13.9, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20413|2024-08-05T02:39:09.910Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20901|2024-08-05T02:53:09.434Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20901</link>
      <description>The login.jsp resource in Jira before version 8.5.2, and from version 8.6.0 before version 8.6.1 allows remote attackers to redirect users to a different website which they may use as part of performing a phishing attack via an open redirect in the os_destination parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20901|2024-08-05T02:53:09.434Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20400|2024-08-05T02:39:09.764Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20400</link>
      <description>The usage of Tomcat in Jira before version 8.5.2 allows local attackers with permission to write a dll file to a directory in the global path environmental variable can inject code into via a DLL hijacking vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20400|2024-08-05T02:39:09.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20405|2024-08-05T02:39:09.769Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20405</link>
      <description>The JMX monitoring flag in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.6.0 allows remote attackers to turn the JMX monitoring flag off or on via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20405|2024-08-05T02:39:09.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20401|2024-08-05T02:39:09.809Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20401</link>
      <description>Various installation setup resources in Jira before version 8.5.2 allow remote attackers to configure a Jira instance, which has not yet finished being installed, via Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20401|2024-08-05T02:39:09.809Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20402|2024-08-05T02:39:09.826Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20402</link>
      <description>Support zip files in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.6.0 could be downloaded by a System Administrator user without requiring the user to re-enter their password via an improper authorization vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20402|2024-08-05T02:39:09.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20419|2024-08-05T02:39:09.910Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20419</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a DLL hijacking vulnerability in Tomcat. The affected versions are before version 8.5.5, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.7.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20419|2024-08-05T02:39:09.910Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20404|2024-08-05T02:39:09.915Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20404</link>
      <description>The API in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.6.0 allows authenticated remote attackers to determine project titles they do not have access to via an improper authorization vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20404|2024-08-05T02:39:09.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20900|2024-08-05T02:53:09.616Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20900</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Add Field module. The affected versions are before version 8.7.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20900|2024-08-05T02:53:09.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20897|2024-08-05T02:53:09.487Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20897</link>
      <description>The avatar upload feature in affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allows remote attackers to achieve Denial of Service via a crafted PNG file. The affected versions are before version 8.5.4, from version 8.6.0 before 8.6.2, and from version 8.7.0 before 8.7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20897|2024-08-05T02:53:09.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20414|2024-08-05T02:39:09.865Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20414</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Issue Navigator Basic Search. The affected versions are before version 7.13.9, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20414|2024-08-05T02:39:09.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20409|2024-08-05T02:39:09.850Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20409</link>
      <description>The way in which velocity templates were used in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center prior to version 8.8.0 allowed remote attackers to gain remote code execution if they were able to exploit a server side template injection vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20409|2024-08-05T02:39:09.850Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15001|2024-08-05T00:34:52.905Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15001</link>
      <description>The Jira Importers Plugin in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Cente from version with 7.0.10 before 7.6.16, from 7.7.0 before 7.13.8, from 8.0.0 before 8.1.3, from 8.2.0 before 8.2.5, from 8.3.0 before 8.3.4 and from 8.4.0 before 8.4.1 allows remote attackers with Administrator permissions to gain remote code execution via a template injection vulnerability through the use of a crafted PUT request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15001|2024-08-05T00:34:52.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20410|2024-08-05T02:39:09.835Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20410</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to view sensitive information via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the comment restriction feature. The affected versions are before version 7.6.17, from version 7.7.0 before 7.13.9, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20410|2024-08-05T02:39:09.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
