<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Jira</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/jira.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Jira</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 19:20:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13395|2024-09-16T16:42:34.901Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13395</link>
      <description>Various resources in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.8, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3 and before version 7.11.1 allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the epic colour field of an issue while an issue is being moved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13395|2024-09-16T16:42:34.901Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16862|2024-09-16T18:48:43.537Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16862</link>
      <description>The IncomingMailServers resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.2 allows remote attackers to modify the "incoming mail" whitelist setting via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16862|2024-09-16T18:48:43.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8444|2024-09-16T16:33:26.240Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8444</link>
      <description>The wikirenderer component in Jira before version 7.13.6, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.3.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in image attribute specification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8444|2024-09-16T16:33:26.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 13:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13403|2024-09-16T18:08:58.970Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13403</link>
      <description>The two-dimensional filter statistics gadget in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.10, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.12.4, and from version 7.13.0 before version 7.13.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the name of a saved filter when displayed on a Jira dashboard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13403|2024-09-16T18:08:58.970Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14997|2024-09-16T18:44:06.559Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14997</link>
      <description>The AccessLogFilter class in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote anonymous attackers to learn details about other users, including their username, via an information expose through caching vulnerability when Jira is configured with a reverse Proxy and or a load balancer with caching or a CDN.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14997|2024-09-16T18:44:06.559Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 13:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11588|2024-09-16T16:57:57.828Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11588</link>
      <description>The ViewSystemInfo class doGarbageCollection method in Jira before version 7.13.6, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.2.3, and from version 8.3.0 before version 8.3.2 allows remote attackers to trigger garbage collection via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11588|2024-09-16T16:57:57.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 13:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5232|2024-09-16T17:37:58.152Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5232</link>
      <description>The EditIssue.jspa resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.7 and from version 7.7.0 before version 7.10.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the issuetype parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5232|2024-09-16T17:37:58.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3400|2024-09-16T16:54:02.769Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3400</link>
      <description>The labels gadget in Jira before version 7.13.2, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the jql parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3400|2024-09-16T16:54:02.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 19:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13404|2024-09-16T17:28:16.895Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13404</link>
      <description>The VerifyPopServerConnection resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.10, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3, from version 7.11.0 before version 7.11.3, from version 7.12.0 before version 7.12.3, and from version 7.13.0 before version 7.13.1 allows remote attackers who have administrator rights to determine the existence of internal hosts &amp; open ports and in some cases obtain service information from internal network resources via a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13404|2024-09-16T17:28:16.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8442|2024-09-16T17:58:53.478Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8442</link>
      <description>The CachingResourceDownloadRewriteRule class in Jira before version 7.13.4, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.4, and from version 8.1.0 before version 8.1.1 allows remote attackers to access files in the Jira webroot under the META-INF directory via a lax path access check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8442|2024-09-16T17:58:53.478Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 17:39:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14594|2024-09-16T17:14:01.826Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14594</link>
      <description>The printable searchrequest issue resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.2.12 and from version 7.3.0 before 7.6.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the jqlQuery query parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14594|2024-09-16T17:14:01.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14995|2024-09-16T18:24:24.535Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14995</link>
      <description>The /rest/api/1.0/render resource in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote anonymous attackers to determine if an attachment with a specific name exists and if an issue key is valid via a missing permissions check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14995|2024-09-16T18:24:24.535Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 13:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3399|2024-09-16T17:48:24.295Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3399</link>
      <description>The BrowseProjects.jspa resource in Jira before version 7.13.2, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.2 allows remote attackers to see information for archived projects through a missing authorisation check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3399|2024-09-16T17:48:24.295Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 15:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18098|2024-09-16T18:38:34.469Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18098</link>
      <description>The searchrequest-xml resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability through various fields.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18098|2024-09-16T18:38:34.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11586|2024-09-16T17:18:14.250Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11586</link>
      <description>The AddResolution.jspa resource in Jira before version 7.13.6, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.2.3, and from version 8.3.0 before version 8.3.2 allows remote attackers to create new resolutions via a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11586|2024-09-16T17:18:14.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 13:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13402|2024-09-16T17:52:50.468Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13402</link>
      <description>Many resources in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.9, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3, from version 7.11.0 before version 7.11.3, from version 7.12.0 before version 7.12.3, and before version 7.13.1 allow remote attackers to attack users, in some cases be able to obtain a user's Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) token, via a open redirect vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13402|2024-09-16T17:52:50.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11583|2024-09-16T17:54:52.599Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11583</link>
      <description>The issue searching component in Jira before version 8.1.0 allows remote attackers to deny access to Jira service via denial of service vulnerability in issue search when ordering by "Epic Name".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11583|2024-09-16T17:54:52.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 15:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3402|2024-09-16T18:59:29.908Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3402</link>
      <description>The ConfigurePortalPages.jspa resource in Jira before version 7.13.3 and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.1.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the searchOwnerUserName parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3402|2024-09-16T18:59:29.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 17:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15013|2024-09-16T16:57:38.126Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15013</link>
      <description>The WorkflowResource class removeStatus method in Jira before version 7.13.12, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.4.3, and from version 8.5.0 before version 8.5.2 allows authenticated remote attackers who do not have project administration access to remove a configured issue status from a project via a missing authorisation check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15013|2024-09-16T16:57:38.126Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 03:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18101|2024-09-16T17:19:13.139Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18101</link>
      <description>Various administrative external system import resources in Atlassian JIRA Server (including JIRA Core) before version 7.6.5, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.3, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.3 and before version 7.9.0 allow remote attackers to run import operations and to determine if an internal service exists through missing permission checks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18101|2024-09-16T17:19:13.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14996|2024-09-16T18:34:31.193Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14996</link>
      <description>The FilterPickerPopup.jspa resource in Jira before version 7.13.7, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.3.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the searchOwnerUserName parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14996|2024-09-16T18:34:31.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 13:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
