<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Jira</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/jira.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Jira</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 07:21:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5230|2024-08-05T05:33:43.614Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5230</link>
      <description>The issue collector in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.6, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.4, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.4 and from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the error message of custom fields when an invalid value is specified.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5230|2024-08-05T05:33:43.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14997|2024-08-05T00:34:53.000Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14997</link>
      <description>The AccessLogFilter class in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote anonymous attackers to learn details about other users, including their username, via an information expose through caching vulnerability when Jira is configured with a reverse Proxy and or a load balancer with caching or a CDN.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14997|2024-08-05T00:34:53.000Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15013|2024-08-05T00:34:53.218Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15013</link>
      <description>The WorkflowResource class removeStatus method in Jira before version 7.13.12, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.4.3, and from version 8.5.0 before version 8.5.2 allows authenticated remote attackers who do not have project administration access to remove a configured issue status from a project via a missing authorisation check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15013|2024-08-05T00:34:53.218Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5232|2024-08-05T05:33:43.591Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5232</link>
      <description>The EditIssue.jspa resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.7 and from version 7.7.0 before version 7.10.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the issuetype parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5232|2024-08-05T05:33:43.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14995|2024-08-05T00:34:53.143Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14995</link>
      <description>The /rest/api/1.0/render resource in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote anonymous attackers to determine if an attachment with a specific name exists and if an issue key is valid via a missing permissions check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14995|2024-08-05T00:34:53.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14998|2024-08-05T00:34:53.105Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14998</link>
      <description>The Webwork action Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) protection implementation in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote attackers to bypass its protection via "cookie tossing" a CSRF cookie from a subdomain of a Jira instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14998|2024-08-05T00:34:53.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14996|2024-08-05T00:34:53.093Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14996</link>
      <description>The FilterPickerPopup.jspa resource in Jira before version 7.13.7, and from version 8.0.0 before version 8.3.3 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the searchOwnerUserName parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14996|2024-08-05T00:34:53.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5231|2024-08-05T05:33:43.763Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5231</link>
      <description>The ForgotLoginDetails resource in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.6, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.4, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.4 and from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.2 allows remote attackers to perform a denial of service attack via sending requests to it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5231|2024-08-05T05:33:43.763Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
