<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Jira Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/jira%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Jira Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 21:22:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43952|2024-10-04T18:11:59.302Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43952</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to restore the default configuration of fields via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the /secure/admin/RestoreDefaults.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.21.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43952|2024-10-04T18:11:59.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 00:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43945|2024-10-04T18:12:49.031Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43945</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers with Roadmaps Administrator permissions to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (SXSS) vulnerability in the /rest/jpo/1.0/hierarchyConfiguration endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43945|2024-10-04T18:12:49.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 00:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43944|2024-10-04T18:45:21.133Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43944</link>
      <description>This issue exists to document that a security improvement in the way that Jira Server and Data Center use templates has been implemented. Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allowed remote attackers with system administrator permissions to execute arbitrary code via Template Injection leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE) in the Email Templates feature. The affected versions are before version 8.13.15, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43944|2024-10-04T18:45:21.133Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 02:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
