<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Jira Service Management Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/jira%20service%20management%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Jira Service Management Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 07:20:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43949|2024-08-04T04:10:16.282Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43949</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to view private objects via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the Custom Fields feature. The affected versions are before version 4.21.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43949|2024-08-04T04:10:16.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43948|2024-08-04T04:10:17.270Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43948</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to view the names of private objects via an Improper Authorization vulnerability in the "Move objects" feature. The affected versions are before version 4.21.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43948|2024-08-04T04:10:17.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43943|2024-08-04T04:10:17.129Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43943</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow attackers with administrator privileges to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the "Object Schema" field of /secure/admin/InsightDefaultCustomFieldConfig.jspa. The affected versions are before version 4.21.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43943|2024-08-04T04:10:17.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43951|2024-08-04T04:10:17.200Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43951</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to view object import configuration details via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the Create Object type mapping feature. The affected versions are before version 4.21.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43951|2024-08-04T04:10:17.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43959|2024-08-04T04:10:16.934Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43959</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to access the content of internal network resources via a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the CSV importing feature of JSM Insight. When running in an environment like Amazon EC2, this flaw may be used to access to a metadata resource that provides access credentials and other potentially confidential information. The affected versions are before version 4.13.20, from version 4.14.0 before 4.20.8, and from version 4.21.0 before 4.22.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43959|2024-08-04T04:10:16.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43950|2024-08-04T04:10:17.146Z -- atlassian -- jira%20service%20management%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43950</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Service Management Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to view import source configuration information via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the Insight Import Source feature. The affected versions are before version 4.21.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43950|2024-08-04T04:10:17.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
