<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Jira Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/jira%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Jira Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 17:22:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29451|2024-09-16T16:33:16.867Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29451</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to enumerate Jira projects via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the Jira Projects plugin report page. The affected versions are before version 8.5.11, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.3, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.14.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29451|2024-09-16T16:33:16.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26078|2024-09-16T16:17:58.100Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26078</link>
      <description>The number range searcher component in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.16.1 allows remote attackers inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26078|2024-09-16T16:17:58.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 22:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18113|2024-09-16T16:43:26.413Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18113</link>
      <description>The DefaultOSWorkflowConfigurator class in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.18.1 allows remote attackers who can trick a system administrator to import their malicious workflow to execute arbitrary code via a Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability. The vulnerability allowed for various problematic OSWorkflow classes to be used as part of workflows. The fix for this issue blocks usage of unsafe conditions, validators, functions and registers that are build-in into OSWorkflow library and other Jira dependencies. Atlassian-made functions or functions provided by 3rd party plugins are not affected by this fix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18113|2024-09-16T16:43:26.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 02:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43945|2024-09-16T16:47:56.975Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43945</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers with Roadmaps Administrator permissions to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (SXSS) vulnerability in the /rest/jpo/1.0/hierarchyConfiguration endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43945|2024-09-16T16:47:56.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 00:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39121|2024-09-16T16:48:52.686Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39121</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to enumerate the keys of private Jira projects via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /rest/api/latest/projectvalidate/key endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.18, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.10, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.18.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39121|2024-09-16T16:48:52.686Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 01:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36799|2024-09-16T16:43:15.537Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36799</link>
      <description>This issue exists to document that a security improvement in the way that Jira Server and Data Center use templates has been implemented. Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allowed remote attackers with system administrator permissions to execute arbitrary code via Template Injection leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE) in the Email Templates feature. In this case the security improvement was to protect against using the XStream library to be able to execute arbitrary code in velocity templates. The affected versions are before version 8.13.19, from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.7, and from version 8.21.0 before 8.22.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36799|2024-09-16T16:43:15.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 01:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36287|2024-09-16T16:39:12.728Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36287</link>
      <description>The dashboard gadgets preference resource of the Atlassian gadgets plugin used in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.1 allows remote anonymous attackers to obtain gadget related settings via a missing permissions check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36287|2024-09-16T16:39:12.728Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 02:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36235|2024-09-16T16:24:07.752Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36235</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to view custom field and custom SLA names via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the mobile site view. The affected versions are before version 8.13.2, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.14.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36235|2024-09-16T16:24:07.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 23:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14179|2024-09-16T16:17:53.447Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14179</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote, unauthenticated attackers to view custom field names and custom SLA names via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /secure/QueryComponent!Default.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.8, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.11.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14179|2024-09-16T16:17:53.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 00:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26086|2024-09-16T16:37:51.040Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26086</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to read particular files via a path traversal vulnerability in the /WEB-INF/web.xml endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.16.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26086|2024-09-16T16:37:51.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39112|2024-09-16T16:53:16.614Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39112</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to redirect users to a malicious URL via a reverse tabnapping vulnerability in the Project Shortcuts feature. The affected versions are before version 8.5.15, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.7, from version 8.14.0 before 8.17.1, and from version 8.18.0 before 8.18.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39112|2024-09-16T16:53:16.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 02:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14185|2024-09-16T16:24:13.539Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14185</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Jira Server allow remote unauthenticated attackers to enumerate issue keys via a missing permissions check in the ActionsAndOperations resource. The affected versions are before 7.13.18, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.9, and from version 8.6.0 before version 8.12.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14185|2024-09-16T16:24:13.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 21:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36234|2024-09-16T16:18:31.237Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36234</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Screens Modal view. The affected versions are before version 8.5.11, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.3, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.15.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36234|2024-09-16T16:18:31.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43953|2024-09-16T16:18:22.052Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43953</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to toggle the Thread Contention and CPU monitoring settings via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the /secure/admin/ViewInstrumentation.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.13.16, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43953|2024-09-16T16:18:22.052Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 02:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43952|2024-09-16T16:58:37.647Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43952</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to restore the default configuration of fields via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the /secure/admin/RestoreDefaults.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.21.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43952|2024-09-16T16:58:37.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 00:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20401|2024-09-16T16:23:36.710Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20401</link>
      <description>Various installation setup resources in Jira before version 8.5.2 allow remote attackers to configure a Jira instance, which has not yet finished being installed, via Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20401|2024-09-16T16:23:36.710Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 03:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41306|2024-09-16T16:24:16.923Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41306</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view private project and filter names via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Average Time in Status Gadget. The affected versions are before version 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41306|2024-09-16T16:24:16.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 04:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
