<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Jira Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/jira%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Jira Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 21:23:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18113|2024-10-17T16:03:55.792Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18113</link>
      <description>The DefaultOSWorkflowConfigurator class in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.18.1 allows remote attackers who can trick a system administrator to import their malicious workflow to execute arbitrary code via a Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability. The vulnerability allowed for various problematic OSWorkflow classes to be used as part of workflows. The fix for this issue blocks usage of unsafe conditions, validators, functions and registers that are build-in into OSWorkflow library and other Jira dependencies. Atlassian-made functions or functions provided by 3rd party plugins are not affected by this fix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18113|2024-10-17T16:03:55.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 02:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36288|2024-10-17T14:02:56.389Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36288</link>
      <description>The issue navigation and search view in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.12, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.4, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a DOM Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability caused by parameter pollution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36288|2024-10-17T14:02:56.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 23:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26075|2024-10-17T14:03:25.665Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26075</link>
      <description>The Jira importers plugin AttachTemporaryFile rest resource in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.12, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.4, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.15.1 allowed remote authenticated attackers to obtain the full path of the Jira application data directory via an information disclosure vulnerability in the error message when presented with an invalid filename.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26075|2024-10-17T14:03:25.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 23:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26078|2024-10-17T14:27:52.463Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26078</link>
      <description>The number range searcher component in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.16.1 allows remote attackers inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26078|2024-10-17T14:27:52.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 22:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26083|2024-10-17T14:33:00.954Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26083</link>
      <description>Export HTML Report in Atlassian Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.16.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26083|2024-10-17T14:33:00.954Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 03:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26076|2024-10-17T14:12:32.765Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26076</link>
      <description>The jira.editor.user.mode cookie set by the Jira Editor Plugin in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.12, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.4, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.0 allows remote anonymous attackers who can perform an attacker in the middle attack to learn which mode a user is editing in due to the cookie not being set with a secure attribute if Jira was configured to use https.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26076|2024-10-17T14:12:32.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 23:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36289|2024-10-17T14:27:07.580Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36289</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow an unauthenticated user to enumerate users via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the QueryComponentRendererValue!Default.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.13, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.15.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36289|2024-10-17T14:27:07.580Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 03:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26080|2024-10-17T14:28:50.794Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26080</link>
      <description>EditworkflowScheme.jspa in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, and from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.6, and from 8.14.0 before 8.16.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26080|2024-10-17T14:28:50.794Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 22:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26079|2024-10-17T14:29:23.194Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26079</link>
      <description>The CardLayoutConfigTable component in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.15, and from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.7, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.17.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26079|2024-10-17T14:29:23.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 22:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
