<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Jira Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/jira%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Jira Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 03:23:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39123|2024-08-04T01:58:17.890Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39123</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in the /rest/gadget/1.0/createdVsResolved/generate endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.16.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39123|2024-08-04T01:58:17.890Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39118|2024-08-04T01:58:18.114Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39118</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to discover the usernames and full names of users via an enumeration vulnerability in the /rest/api/1.0/render endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.19.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39118|2024-08-04T01:58:18.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39112|2024-08-04T01:58:17.761Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39112</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to redirect users to a malicious URL via a reverse tabnapping vulnerability in the Project Shortcuts feature. The affected versions are before version 8.5.15, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.7, from version 8.14.0 before 8.17.1, and from version 8.18.0 before 8.18.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39112|2024-08-04T01:58:17.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39124|2024-08-04T01:58:17.936Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39124</link>
      <description>The Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) failure retry feature of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.16.0 allows remote attackers who are able to trick a user into retrying a request to bypass CSRF protection and replay a crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39124|2024-08-04T01:58:17.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39119|2024-08-04T01:58:18.117Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39119</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow users who have watched an issue to continue receiving updates on the issue even after their Jira account is revoked, via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the issue notification feature. The affected versions are before version 8.19.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39119|2024-08-04T01:58:18.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39126|2024-08-04T01:58:17.682Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39126</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to modify various resources via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability, following an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the referrer headers which discloses a user's CSRF token. The affected versions are before version 8.5.10, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39126|2024-08-04T01:58:17.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39121|2024-08-04T01:58:17.588Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39121</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to enumerate the keys of private Jira projects via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /rest/api/latest/projectvalidate/key endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.18, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.10, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.18.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39121|2024-08-04T01:58:17.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39127|2024-08-04T01:58:17.643Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39127</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to the query component JQL endpoint via a Broken Access Control vulnerability (BAC) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 8.5.10, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39127|2024-08-04T01:58:17.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39116|2024-08-04T01:58:17.981Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39116</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in the GIF Image Reader component. The affected versions are before version 8.13.14, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.19.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39116|2024-08-04T01:58:17.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39122|2024-08-04T01:58:17.788Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39122</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view users' emails via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /rest/api/2/search endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.13, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.15.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39122|2024-08-04T01:58:17.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39113|2024-08-04T01:58:17.748Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39113</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to continue to view cached content even after losing permissions, via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the allowlist feature. The affected versions are before version 8.13.9, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.18.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39113|2024-08-04T01:58:17.748Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39117|2024-08-04T01:58:17.600Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39117</link>
      <description>The AssociateFieldToScreens page in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.18.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the name of a custom field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39117|2024-08-04T01:58:17.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39111|2024-08-04T01:58:17.957Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39111</link>
      <description>The Editor plugin in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.18, from 8.6.0 before 8.13.10, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.18.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the handling of supplied content such as from a PDF when pasted into a field such as the description field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39111|2024-08-04T01:58:17.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39125|2024-08-04T01:58:17.940Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39125</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to discover the usernames of users via an enumeration vulnerability in the password reset page. The affected versions are before version 8.5.10, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39125|2024-08-04T01:58:17.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39128|2024-08-04T01:58:17.980Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39128</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server or Data Center using the Jira Service Management addon allow remote attackers with JIRA Administrators access to execute arbitrary Java code via a server-side template injection vulnerability in the Email Template feature. The affected versions of Jira Server or Data Center are before version 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.19.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39128|2024-08-04T01:58:17.980Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
