<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Jira Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/jira%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Jira Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26071|2024-08-03T20:19:19.784Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26071</link>
      <description>The SetFeatureEnabled.jspa resource in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.13, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.1 allows remote anonymous attackers to enable and disable Jira Software configuration via a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26071|2024-08-03T20:19:19.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26069|2024-08-03T20:19:19.353Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26069</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to download temporary files and enumerate project keys via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /rest/api/1.0/issues/{id}/ActionsAndOperations API endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.11, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.3, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.15.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26069|2024-08-03T20:19:19.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26080|2024-08-03T20:19:19.475Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26080</link>
      <description>EditworkflowScheme.jspa in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, and from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.6, and from 8.14.0 before 8.16.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26080|2024-08-03T20:19:19.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36799|2024-08-03T10:14:28.495Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36799</link>
      <description>This issue exists to document that a security improvement in the way that Jira Server and Data Center use templates has been implemented. Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allowed remote attackers with system administrator permissions to execute arbitrary code via Template Injection leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE) in the Email Templates feature. In this case the security improvement was to protect against using the XStream library to be able to execute arbitrary code in velocity templates. The affected versions are before version 8.13.19, from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.7, and from version 8.21.0 before 8.22.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36799|2024-08-03T10:14:28.495Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26082|2024-08-03T20:19:19.355Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26082</link>
      <description>The XML Export in Atlassian Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.17.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a stored cross site scripting vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26082|2024-08-03T20:19:19.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26076|2024-08-03T20:19:19.447Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26076</link>
      <description>The jira.editor.user.mode cookie set by the Jira Editor Plugin in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.12, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.4, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.0 allows remote anonymous attackers who can perform an attacker in the middle attack to learn which mode a user is editing in due to the cookie not being set with a secure attribute if Jira was configured to use https.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26076|2024-08-03T20:19:19.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26078|2024-08-03T20:19:19.491Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26078</link>
      <description>The number range searcher component in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.16.1 allows remote attackers inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26078|2024-08-03T20:19:19.491Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36801|2024-08-03T10:14:28.388Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36801</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (RXSS) vulnerability in the TeamManagement.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.20.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36801|2024-08-03T10:14:28.388Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26070|2024-08-03T20:19:19.598Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26070</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to evade behind-the-firewall protection of app-linked resources via a Broken Authentication vulnerability in the `makeRequest` gadget resource. The affected versions are before version 8.13.3, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.14.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26070|2024-08-03T20:19:19.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26075|2024-08-03T20:19:19.544Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26075</link>
      <description>The Jira importers plugin AttachTemporaryFile rest resource in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.12, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.4, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.15.1 allowed remote authenticated attackers to obtain the full path of the Jira application data directory via an information disclosure vulnerability in the error message when presented with an invalid filename.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26075|2024-08-03T20:19:19.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26083|2024-08-03T20:19:19.624Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26083</link>
      <description>Export HTML Report in Atlassian Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.16.1 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26083|2024-08-03T20:19:19.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26086|2024-08-03T20:19:19.569Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26086</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to read particular files via a path traversal vulnerability in the /WEB-INF/web.xml endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.16.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26086|2024-08-03T20:19:19.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26081|2024-08-03T20:19:19.588Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26081</link>
      <description>REST API in Atlassian Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.14, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.6, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.16.1 allows remote attackers to enumerate usernames via a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability in the `/rest/api/latest/user/avatar/temporary` endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26081|2024-08-03T20:19:19.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26079|2024-08-03T20:19:19.868Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26079</link>
      <description>The CardLayoutConfigTable component in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.15, and from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.7, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.17.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26079|2024-08-03T20:19:19.868Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
