<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Jira Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/jira%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Jira Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 22:23:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41306|2024-10-09T18:21:09.274Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41306</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view private project and filter names via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Average Time in Status Gadget. The affected versions are before version 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41306|2024-10-09T18:21:09.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 04:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41307|2024-10-09T19:20:41.686Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41307</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to view the names of private projects and private filters via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Workload Pie Chart Gadget. The affected versions are before version 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41307|2024-10-09T19:20:41.686Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 04:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39125|2024-10-09T16:42:05.731Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39125</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to discover the usernames of users via an enumeration vulnerability in the password reset page. The affected versions are before version 8.5.10, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39125|2024-10-09T16:42:05.731Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 06:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41305|2024-10-09T16:52:39.165Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41305</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view the names of private projects and filters via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Average Number of Times in Status Gadget. The affected versions are before version 8.13.12..</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41305|2024-10-09T16:52:39.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 04:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41308|2024-10-09T19:23:22.782Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41308</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated yet non-administrator remote attackers to edit the File Replication settings via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the `ReplicationSettings!default.jspa` endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.6.0, from version 8.7.0 before 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41308|2024-10-09T19:23:22.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 04:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20101|2024-10-09T16:22:27.184Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20101</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view whitelist rules via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the /rest/whitelist/&lt;version&gt;/check endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.13.3, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.14.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20101|2024-10-09T16:22:27.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 05:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41310|2024-10-09T20:25:50.011Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41310</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Associated Projects feature (/secure/admin/AssociatedProjectsForCustomField.jspa). The affected versions are before version 8.5.19, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.11, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.19.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41310|2024-10-09T20:25:50.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 22:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
