<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Jira Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/jira%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Jira Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 01:37:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26079|2024-09-17T01:21:56.570Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26079</link>
      <description>The CardLayoutConfigTable component in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.15, and from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.7, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.17.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26079|2024-09-17T01:21:56.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 22:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29453|2024-09-17T00:15:39.961Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29453</link>
      <description>The CachingResourceDownloadRewriteRule class in Jira Server and Jira Data Center before version 8.5.11, from 8.6.0 before 8.13.3, and from 8.14.0 before 8.15.0 allowed unauthenticated remote attackers to read arbitrary files within WEB-INF and META-INF directories via an incorrect path access check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29453|2024-09-17T00:15:39.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 15:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43947|2024-09-17T00:45:50.288Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43947</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers with administrator privileges to execute arbitrary code via a Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in the Email Templates feature. This issue bypasses the fix of https://jira.atlassian.com/browse/JSDSERVER-8665. The affected versions are before version 8.13.15, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43947|2024-09-17T00:45:50.288Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 01:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39123|2024-09-17T01:16:57.624Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39123</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in the /rest/gadget/1.0/createdVsResolved/generate endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.16.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39123|2024-09-17T01:16:57.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 04:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20415|2024-09-17T00:51:17.879Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20415</link>
      <description>Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center in affected versions allows remote attackers to modify logging and profiling settings via a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 7.13.3, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20415|2024-09-17T00:51:17.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 02:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41313|2024-09-17T00:56:59.263Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41313</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated but non-admin remote attackers to edit email batch configurations via an Improper Authorization vulnerability in the /secure/admin/ConfigureBatching!default.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.20.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41313|2024-09-17T00:56:59.263Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 03:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20899|2024-09-17T00:41:28.244Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20899</link>
      <description>The Gadget API in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center in affected versions allows remote attackers to make Jira unresponsive via repeated requests to a certain endpoint in the Gadget API. The affected versions are before version 8.5.4, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.6.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20899|2024-09-17T00:41:28.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 01:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39122|2024-09-17T00:26:05.764Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39122</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view users' emails via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /rest/api/2/search endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.13, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.15.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39122|2024-09-17T00:26:05.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 02:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14177|2024-09-17T01:00:48.724Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14177</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Regex-based Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in JQL version searching. The affected versions are before version 7.13.16; from version 7.14.0 before 8.5.7; from version 8.6.0 before 8.10.2; and from version 8.11.0 before 8.11.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14177|2024-09-17T01:00:48.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 01:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14184|2024-09-17T00:10:51.045Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14184</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Jira issue filter export files. The affected versions are before 8.5.9, from version 8.6.0 before 8.12.3, and from version 8.13.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14184|2024-09-17T00:10:51.045Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 03:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20412|2024-09-17T00:06:43.084Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20412</link>
      <description>The Convert Sub-Task to Issue page in affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to enumerate the following information via an Improper Authentication vulnerability: Workflow names; Project Key, if it is part of the workflow name; Issue Keys; Issue Types; Status Types. The affected versions are before version 7.13.9, and from version 8.0.0 before 8.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20412|2024-09-17T00:06:43.084Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 05:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39124|2024-09-17T00:15:26.444Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39124</link>
      <description>The Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) failure retry feature of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.16.0 allows remote attackers who are able to trick a user into retrying a request to bypass CSRF protection and replay a crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39124|2024-09-17T00:15:26.444Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 04:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41308|2024-09-17T00:25:53.684Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41308</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated yet non-administrator remote attackers to edit the File Replication settings via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the `ReplicationSettings!default.jspa` endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.6.0, from version 8.7.0 before 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41308|2024-09-17T00:25:53.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 04:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36238|2024-09-17T00:30:53.159Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36238</link>
      <description>The /rest/api/1.0/render resource in Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.13, from version 8.6.0 before version 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0 before version 8.15.1 allows remote anonymous attackers to determine if a username is valid or not via a missing permissions check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36238|2024-09-17T00:30:53.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 02:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
