<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Jira Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/jira%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Jira Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 14:22:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39123|2024-08-04T01:58:17.890Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39123</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in the /rest/gadget/1.0/createdVsResolved/generate endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.16.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39123|2024-08-04T01:58:17.890Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43947|2024-08-04T04:10:17.270Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43947</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers with administrator privileges to execute arbitrary code via a Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in the Email Templates feature. This issue bypasses the fix of https://jira.atlassian.com/browse/JSDSERVER-8665. The affected versions are before version 8.13.15, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43947|2024-08-04T04:10:17.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41306|2024-08-04T03:08:31.997Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41306</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view private project and filter names via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Average Time in Status Gadget. The affected versions are before version 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41306|2024-08-04T03:08:31.997Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43952|2024-08-04T04:10:17.284Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43952</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to restore the default configuration of fields via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the /secure/admin/RestoreDefaults.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.21.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43952|2024-08-04T04:10:17.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43942|2024-08-04T04:10:17.127Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43942</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /rest/collectors/1.0/template/custom endpoint. To exploit this issue, the attacker must trick a user into visiting a malicious website. The affected versions are before version 8.13.15, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43942|2024-08-04T04:10:17.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43945|2024-08-04T04:10:17.223Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43945</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers with Roadmaps Administrator permissions to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (SXSS) vulnerability in the /rest/jpo/1.0/hierarchyConfiguration endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43945|2024-08-04T04:10:17.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14184|2024-08-04T12:39:36.188Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14184</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Jira issue filter export files. The affected versions are before 8.5.9, from version 8.6.0 before 8.12.3, and from version 8.13.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14184|2024-08-04T12:39:36.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14185|2024-08-04T12:39:36.046Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14185</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Jira Server allow remote unauthenticated attackers to enumerate issue keys via a missing permissions check in the ActionsAndOperations resource. The affected versions are before 7.13.18, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.9, and from version 8.6.0 before version 8.12.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14185|2024-08-04T12:39:36.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39118|2024-08-04T01:58:18.114Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39118</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to discover the usernames and full names of users via an enumeration vulnerability in the /rest/api/1.0/render endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.19.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39118|2024-08-04T01:58:18.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39112|2024-08-04T01:58:17.761Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39112</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to redirect users to a malicious URL via a reverse tabnapping vulnerability in the Project Shortcuts feature. The affected versions are before version 8.5.15, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.7, from version 8.14.0 before 8.17.1, and from version 8.18.0 before 8.18.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39112|2024-08-04T01:58:17.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41304|2024-08-04T03:08:31.934Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41304</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /secure/admin/ImporterFinishedPage.jspa error message. The affected versions are before version 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41304|2024-08-04T03:08:31.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41313|2024-08-04T03:08:31.977Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41313</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated but non-admin remote attackers to edit email batch configurations via an Improper Authorization vulnerability in the /secure/admin/ConfigureBatching!default.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.20.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41313|2024-08-04T03:08:31.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39124|2024-08-04T01:58:17.936Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39124</link>
      <description>The Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) failure retry feature of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.16.0 allows remote attackers who are able to trick a user into retrying a request to bypass CSRF protection and replay a crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39124|2024-08-04T01:58:17.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41310|2024-08-04T03:08:31.865Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41310</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Associated Projects feature (/secure/admin/AssociatedProjectsForCustomField.jspa). The affected versions are before version 8.5.19, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.11, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.19.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41310|2024-08-04T03:08:31.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39119|2024-08-04T01:58:18.117Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39119</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow users who have watched an issue to continue receiving updates on the issue even after their Jira account is revoked, via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the issue notification feature. The affected versions are before version 8.19.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39119|2024-08-04T01:58:18.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43946|2024-08-04T04:10:17.348Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43946</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to add administrator groups to filter subscriptions via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the /secure/EditSubscription.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.13.21, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43946|2024-08-04T04:10:17.348Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39126|2024-08-04T01:58:17.682Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39126</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to modify various resources via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability, following an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the referrer headers which discloses a user's CSRF token. The affected versions are before version 8.5.10, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39126|2024-08-04T01:58:17.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14179|2024-08-04T12:39:36.221Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14179</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote, unauthenticated attackers to view custom field names and custom SLA names via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /secure/QueryComponent!Default.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.8, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.11.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14179|2024-08-04T12:39:36.221Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43944|2024-08-04T04:10:17.165Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43944</link>
      <description>This issue exists to document that a security improvement in the way that Jira Server and Data Center use templates has been implemented. Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allowed remote attackers with system administrator permissions to execute arbitrary code via Template Injection leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE) in the Email Templates feature. The affected versions are before version 8.13.15, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43944|2024-08-04T04:10:17.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41305|2024-08-04T03:08:32.012Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41305</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view the names of private projects and filters via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Average Number of Times in Status Gadget. The affected versions are before version 8.13.12..</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41305|2024-08-04T03:08:32.012Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39121|2024-08-04T01:58:17.588Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39121</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to enumerate the keys of private Jira projects via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /rest/api/latest/projectvalidate/key endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.18, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.10, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.18.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39121|2024-08-04T01:58:17.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39127|2024-08-04T01:58:17.643Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39127</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to the query component JQL endpoint via a Broken Access Control vulnerability (BAC) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 8.5.10, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39127|2024-08-04T01:58:17.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14177|2024-08-04T12:39:36.159Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14177</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Regex-based Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in JQL version searching. The affected versions are before version 7.13.16; from version 7.14.0 before 8.5.7; from version 8.6.0 before 8.10.2; and from version 8.11.0 before 8.11.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14177|2024-08-04T12:39:36.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41307|2024-08-04T03:08:31.948Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41307</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to view the names of private projects and private filters via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Workload Pie Chart Gadget. The affected versions are before version 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41307|2024-08-04T03:08:31.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14183|2024-08-04T12:39:36.172Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14183</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Jira Server &amp; Data Center allow a remote attacker with limited (non-admin) privileges to view a Jira instance's Support Entitlement Number (SEN) via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the HTTP Response headers. The affected versions are before version 7.13.18, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.9, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.12.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14183|2024-08-04T12:39:36.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39116|2024-08-04T01:58:17.981Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39116</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to impact the application's availability via a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in the GIF Image Reader component. The affected versions are before version 8.13.14, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.19.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39116|2024-08-04T01:58:17.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43941|2024-08-04T04:10:17.147Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43941</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to modify several resources (including CsvFieldMappingsPage.jspa and ImporterValueMappingsPage.jspa) via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the jira-importers-plugin. The affected versions are before version 8.13.15, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43941|2024-08-04T04:10:17.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14174|2024-08-04T12:39:36.196Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14174</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to view titles of a private project via an Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in the Administration Permission Helper. The affected versions are before version 7.13.6, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.7, from version 8.6.0 before 8.9.2, and from version 8.10.0 before 8.10.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14174|2024-08-04T12:39:36.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14181|2024-08-04T12:39:36.073Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14181</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow an unauthenticated user to enumerate users via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /ViewUserHover.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 7.13.6, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.7, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.12.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14181|2024-08-04T12:39:36.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39122|2024-08-04T01:58:17.788Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39122</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to view users' emails via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /rest/api/2/search endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.5.13, from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.5, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.15.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39122|2024-08-04T01:58:17.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14178|2024-08-04T12:39:36.164Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14178</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to enumerate project keys via an Information Disclosure vulnerability in the /browse.PROJECTKEY endpoint. The affected versions are before version 7.13.7, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.8, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.12.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14178|2024-08-04T12:39:36.164Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14172|2024-08-04T12:39:36.159Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14172</link>
      <description>This issue exists to document that a security improvement in the way that Jira Server and Data Center use velocity templates has been implemented. The way in which velocity templates were used in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center in affected versions allowed remote attackers to achieve remote code execution via insecure deserialization, if they were able to exploit a server side template injection vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 7.13.0, from version 8.0.0 before 8.5.0, and from version 8.6.0 before version 8.8.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14172|2024-08-04T12:39:36.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41312|2024-08-04T03:08:31.935Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41312</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow a remote attacker who has had their access revoked from Jira Service Management to enable and disable Issue Collectors on Jira Service Management projects via an Improper Authentication vulnerability in the /secure/ViewCollectors endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.19.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41312|2024-08-04T03:08:31.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39113|2024-08-04T01:58:17.748Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39113</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to continue to view cached content even after losing permissions, via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the allowlist feature. The affected versions are before version 8.13.9, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.18.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39113|2024-08-04T01:58:17.748Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41308|2024-08-04T03:08:31.936Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41308</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated yet non-administrator remote attackers to edit the File Replication settings via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the `ReplicationSettings!default.jspa` endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.6.0, from version 8.7.0 before 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41308|2024-08-04T03:08:31.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41309|2024-08-04T03:08:31.877Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41309</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow a user who has had their Jira Service Management access revoked to export audit logs of another user's Jira Service Management project via a Broken Authentication vulnerability in the /plugins/servlet/audit/resource endpoint. The affected versions of Jira Server and Data Center are before version 8.19.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41309|2024-08-04T03:08:31.877Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39117|2024-08-04T01:58:17.600Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39117</link>
      <description>The AssociateFieldToScreens page in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.18.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the name of a custom field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39117|2024-08-04T01:58:17.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39111|2024-08-04T01:58:17.957Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39111</link>
      <description>The Editor plugin in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center before version 8.5.18, from 8.6.0 before 8.13.10, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.18.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the handling of supplied content such as from a PDF when pasted into a field such as the description field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39111|2024-08-04T01:58:17.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41311|2024-08-04T03:08:31.998Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41311</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow attackers with access to an administrator account that has had its access revoked to modify projects' Users &amp; Roles settings, via a Broken Authentication vulnerability in the /plugins/servlet/project-config/PROJECT/roles endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.19.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41311|2024-08-04T03:08:31.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43953|2024-08-04T04:10:16.450Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43953</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to toggle the Thread Contention and CPU monitoring settings via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the /secure/admin/ViewInstrumentation.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.13.16, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43953|2024-08-04T04:10:16.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14173|2024-08-04T12:39:36.158Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14173</link>
      <description>The file upload feature in Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center in affected versions allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. The affected versions are before version 8.5.4, from version 8.6.0 before 8.6.2, and from version 8.7.0 before 8.7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14173|2024-08-04T12:39:36.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39125|2024-08-04T01:58:17.940Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39125</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow anonymous remote attackers to discover the usernames of users via an enumeration vulnerability in the password reset page. The affected versions are before version 8.5.10, and from version 8.6.0 before 8.13.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39125|2024-08-04T01:58:17.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39128|2024-08-04T01:58:17.980Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39128</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server or Data Center using the Jira Service Management addon allow remote attackers with JIRA Administrators access to execute arbitrary Java code via a server-side template injection vulnerability in the Email Template feature. The affected versions of Jira Server or Data Center are before version 8.13.12, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.19.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39128|2024-08-04T01:58:17.980Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
