<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Jira</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/jira.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Jira</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 02:24:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13387|2024-09-17T00:25:48.998Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13387</link>
      <description>The IncomingMailServers resource in Atlassian JIRA Server before version 7.6.7, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3 and from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.2 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the messagesThreshold parameter as the fix for CVE-2017-18039 was incomplete.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13387|2024-09-17T00:25:48.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8449|2024-09-17T01:01:03.580Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8449</link>
      <description>The /rest/api/latest/groupuserpicker resource in Jira before version 8.4.0 allows remote attackers to enumerate usernames via an information disclosure vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8449|2024-09-17T01:01:03.580Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 13:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16865|2024-09-17T01:30:44.872Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16865</link>
      <description>The Trello importer in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.1 allows remote attackers to access the content of internal network resources via a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF). When running in an environment like Amazon EC2, this flaw maybe used to access to a metadata resource that provides access credentials and other potentially confidential information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16865|2024-09-17T01:30:44.872Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13400|2024-09-17T01:12:10.955Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13400</link>
      <description>Several administrative resources in Atlassian Jira before version 7.6.9, from version 7.7.0 before version 7.7.5, from version 7.8.0 before version 7.8.5, from version 7.9.0 before version 7.9.3, from version 7.10.0 before version 7.10.3, from version 7.11.0 before version 7.11.3, from version 7.12.0 before version 7.12.3, and before version 7.13.1 allow remote attackers who have obtained access to administrator's session to access certain administrative resources without needing to re-authenticate to pass "WebSudo" through an improper access control vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13400|2024-09-17T01:12:10.955Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3403|2024-09-17T01:00:56.714Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3403</link>
      <description>The /rest/api/2/user/picker rest resource in Jira before version 7.13.3, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.0.4, and from version 8.1.0 before version 8.1.1 allows remote attackers to enumerate usernames via an incorrect authorisation check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3403|2024-09-17T01:00:56.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 17:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11587|2024-09-17T02:06:37.521Z -- atlassian -- jira
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11587</link>
      <description>Various exposed resources of the ViewLogging class in Jira before version 7.13.6, from version 8.0.0 before version 8.2.3, and from version 8.3.0 before version 8.3.2 allow remote attackers to modify various settings via Cross-site request forgery (CSRF).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11587|2024-09-17T02:06:37.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 13:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
