<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Atlassian -- Jira Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atlassian/jira%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Atlassian -- Jira Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 19:19:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43947|2024-10-08T14:34:08.233Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43947</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers with administrator privileges to execute arbitrary code via a Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in the Email Templates feature. This issue bypasses the fix of https://jira.atlassian.com/browse/JSDSERVER-8665. The affected versions are before version 8.13.15, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43947|2024-10-08T14:34:08.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 01:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43942|2024-10-08T14:23:31.116Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43942</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript via a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /rest/collectors/1.0/template/custom endpoint. To exploit this issue, the attacker must trick a user into visiting a malicious website. The affected versions are before version 8.13.15, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43942|2024-10-08T14:23:31.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 02:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41313|2024-10-08T14:22:21.571Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41313</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated but non-admin remote attackers to edit email batch configurations via an Improper Authorization vulnerability in the /secure/admin/ConfigureBatching!default.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.20.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41313|2024-10-08T14:22:21.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 03:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43941|2024-10-08T17:37:25.273Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43941</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow remote attackers to modify several resources (including CsvFieldMappingsPage.jspa and ImporterValueMappingsPage.jspa) via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the jira-importers-plugin. The affected versions are before version 8.13.15, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43941|2024-10-08T17:37:25.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 03:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43946|2024-10-08T14:24:15.786Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43946</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow authenticated remote attackers to add administrator groups to filter subscriptions via a Broken Access Control vulnerability in the /secure/EditSubscription.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.13.21, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43946|2024-10-08T14:24:15.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 03:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43953|2024-10-08T14:38:59.629Z -- atlassian -- jira%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43953</link>
      <description>Affected versions of Atlassian Jira Server and Data Center allow unauthenticated remote attackers to toggle the Thread Contention and CPU monitoring settings via a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the /secure/admin/ViewInstrumentation.jspa endpoint. The affected versions are before version 8.13.16, and from version 8.14.0 before 8.20.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43953|2024-10-08T14:38:59.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 02:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
