<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for istio -- istio</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/istio/istio.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for istio -- istio</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 04:23:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21679|2024-08-03T02:46:39.336Z -- istio -- istio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21679</link>
      <description>Istio is an open platform to connect, manage, and secure microservices. In Istio 1.12.0 and 1.12.1 The authorization policy with hosts and notHosts might be accidentally bypassed for ALLOW action or rejected unexpectedly for DENY action during the upgrade from 1.11 to 1.12.0/1.12.1. Istio 1.12 supports the hosts and notHosts fields in authorization policy with a new Envoy API shipped with the 1.12 data plane. A bug in the 1.12.0 and 1.12.1 incorrectly uses the new Envoy API with the 1.11 data plane. This will cause the hosts and notHosts fields to be always matched regardless of the actual value of the host header when mixing 1.12.0/1.12.1 control plane and 1.11 data plane. Users are advised to upgrade or to not mix the 1.12.0/1.12.1 control plane with 1.11 data plane if using hosts or notHosts field in authorization policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21679|2024-08-03T02:46:39.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 21:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21701|2024-08-03T02:53:34.796Z -- istio -- istio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21701</link>
      <description>Istio is an open platform to connect, manage, and secure microservices. In versions 1.12.0 and 1.12.1 Istio is vulnerable to a privilege escalation attack. Users who have `CREATE` permission for `gateways.gateway.networking.k8s.io` objects can escalate this privilege to create other resources that they may not have access to, such as `Pod`. This vulnerability impacts only an Alpha level feature, the Kubernetes Gateway API. This is not the same as the Istio Gateway type (gateways.networking.istio.io), which is not vulnerable. Users are advised to upgrade to resolve this issue. Users unable to upgrade should implement any of the following which will prevent this vulnerability: Remove the gateways.gateway.networking.k8s.io CustomResourceDefinition, set PILOT_ENABLE_GATEWAY_API_DEPLOYMENT_CONTROLLER=true environment variable in Istiod, or remove CREATE permissions for gateways.gateway.networking.k8s.io objects from untrusted users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21701|2024-08-03T02:53:34.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 21:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23635|2024-08-03T03:51:45.891Z -- istio -- istio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23635</link>
      <description>Istio is an open platform to connect, manage, and secure microservices. In affected versions the Istio control plane, `istiod`, is vulnerable to a request processing error, allowing a malicious attacker that sends a specially crafted message which results in the control plane crashing. This endpoint is served over TLS port 15012, but does not require any authentication from the attacker. For simple installations, Istiod is typically only reachable from within the cluster, limiting the blast radius. However, for some deployments, especially [multicluster](https://istio.io/latest/docs/setup/install/multicluster/primary-remote/) topologies, this port is exposed over the public internet. There are no effective workarounds, beyond upgrading. Limiting network access to Istiod to the minimal set of clients can help lessen the scope of the vulnerability to some extent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23635|2024-08-03T03:51:45.891Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 22:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
