<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for theonedev -- onedev</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/theonedev/onedev.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for theonedev -- onedev</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 14:22:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39205|2024-08-03T12:00:42.469Z -- theonedev -- onedev
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39205</link>
      <description>Onedev is an open source, self-hosted Git Server with CI/CD and Kanban. In versions of Onedev prior to 7.3.0 unauthenticated users can take over a OneDev instance if there is no properly configured reverse proxy. The /git-prereceive-callback endpoint is used by the pre-receive git hook on the server to check for branch protections during a push event. It is only intended to be accessed from localhost, but the check relies on the X-Forwarded-For header. Invoking this endpoint leads to the execution of one of various git commands. The environment variables of this command execution can be controlled via query parameters. This allows attackers to write to arbitrary files, which can in turn lead to the execution of arbitrary code. Such an attack would be very hard to detect, which increases the potential impact even more. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39205|2024-08-03T12:00:42.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 18:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39207|2024-08-03T12:00:42.570Z -- theonedev -- onedev
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39207</link>
      <description>Onedev is an open source, self-hosted Git Server with CI/CD and Kanban. During CI/CD builds, it is possible to save build artifacts for later retrieval. They can be accessed through OneDev's web UI after the successful run of a build. These artifact files are served by the webserver in the same context as the UI without any further restrictions. This leads to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) when a user creates a build artifact that contains HTML. When accessing the artifact, the content is rendered by the browser, including any JavaScript that it contains. Since all cookies (except for the rememberMe one) do not set the HttpOnly flag, an attacker could steal the session of a victim and use it to impersonate them. To exploit this issue, attackers need to be able to modify the content of artifacts, which usually means they need to be able to modify a project's build spec. The exploitation requires the victim to click on an attacker's link. It can be used to elevate privileges by targeting admins of a OneDev instance. In the worst case, this can lead to arbitrary code execution on the server, because admins can create Server Shell Executors and use them to run any command on the server. This issue has been patched in version 7.3.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39207|2024-08-03T12:00:42.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 18:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39206|2024-08-03T12:00:43.907Z -- theonedev -- onedev
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39206</link>
      <description>Onedev is an open source, self-hosted Git Server with CI/CD and Kanban. When using Docker-based job executors, the Docker socket (e.g. /var/run/docker.sock on Linux) is mounted into each Docker step. Users that can define and trigger CI/CD jobs on a project could use this to control the Docker daemon on the host machine. This is a known dangerous pattern, as it can be used to break out of Docker containers and, in most cases, gain root privileges on the host system. This issue allows regular (non-admin) users to potentially take over the build infrastructure of a OneDev instance. Attackers need to have an account (or be able to register one) and need permission to create a project. Since code.onedev.io has the right preconditions for this to be exploited by remote attackers, it could have been used to hijack builds of OneDev itself, e.g. by injecting malware into the docker images that are built and pushed to Docker Hub. The impact is increased by this as described before. Users are advised to upgrade to 7.3.0 or higher. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39206|2024-08-03T12:00:43.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 18:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39208|2024-08-03T12:00:42.363Z -- theonedev -- onedev
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39208</link>
      <description>Onedev is an open source, self-hosted Git Server with CI/CD and Kanban. All files in the /opt/onedev/sites/ directory are exposed and can be read by unauthenticated users. This directory contains all projects, including their bare git repos and build artifacts. This file disclosure vulnerability can be used by unauthenticated attackers to leak all project files of any project. Since project IDs are incremental, an attacker could iterate through them and leak all project data. This issue has been resolved in version 7.3.0 and users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39208|2024-08-03T12:00:42.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 18:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
