<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for fobybus -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/fobybus/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for fobybus -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:23:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39518|2024-08-02T18:10:21.451Z -- fobybus -- social-media-skeleton
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39518</link>
      <description>social-media-skeleton is an uncompleted social media project implemented using PHP, MySQL, CSS, JavaScript, and HTML. Versions 1.0.0 until 1.0.3 have a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability. The problem is patched in v1.0.3.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39518|2024-08-02T18:10:21.451Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 18:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39344|2024-08-02T18:02:06.867Z -- fobybus -- social-media-skeleton
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39344</link>
      <description>social-media-skeleton is an uncompleted social media project. A SQL injection vulnerability in the project allows UNION based injections, which indirectly leads to remote code execution. Commit 3cabdd35c3d874608883c9eaf9bf69b2014d25c1 contains a fix for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39344|2024-08-02T18:02:06.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 19:49:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40174|2024-08-02T18:24:55.684Z -- fobybus -- social-media-skeleton
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40174</link>
      <description>Social media skeleton is an uncompleted/framework social media project implemented using a php, css ,javascript and html. Insufficient session expiration is a web application security vulnerability that occurs when a web application does not properly manage the lifecycle of a user's session. Social media skeleton releases prior to 1.0.5 did not properly limit manage user session lifecycles. This issue has been addressed in version 1.0.5 and users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40174|2024-08-02T18:24:55.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 21:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40173|2024-08-02T18:24:55.634Z -- fobybus -- social-media-skeleton
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40173</link>
      <description>Social media skeleton is an uncompleted/framework social media project implemented using a php, css ,javascript and html. Prior to version 1.0.5 Social media skeleton did not properly salt passwords leaving user passwords susceptible to cracking should an attacker gain access to hashed passwords. This issue has been addressed in version 1.0.5 and users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40173|2024-08-02T18:24:55.634Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 21:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40172|2024-08-02T18:24:55.660Z -- fobybus -- social-media-skeleton
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40172</link>
      <description>Social media skeleton is an uncompleted/framework social media project implemented using a php, css ,javascript and html. A Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack is a type of malicious attack whereby an attacker tricks a victim into performing an action on a website that they do not intend to do. This can be done by sending the victim a malicious link or by exploiting a vulnerability in the website. Prior to version 1.0.5 Social media skeleton did not properly restrict CSRF attacks. This has been addressed in version 1.0.5 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40172|2024-08-02T18:24:55.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 21:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
