<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for mosbth -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mosbth/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for mosbth -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:23:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-15022|2024-08-06T03:47:34.960Z -- mosbth -- cimage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15022</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in mosbth cimage up to 0.7.18. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file check_system.php. The manipulation of the argument $_SERVER['SERVER_SOFTWARE'] leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. Upgrading to version 0.7.19 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 401478c8393989836beeddfeac5ce44570af162b. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-219715.
In mosbth cimage bis 0.7.18 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei check_system.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments $_SERVER['SERVER_SOFTWARE'] mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie gilt als schwierig ausnutzbar. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 0.7.19 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 401478c8393989836beeddfeac5ce44570af162b bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-15022|2024-08-06T03:47:34.960Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 18:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
