<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Arborator -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/arborator/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Arborator -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:23:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-25087|2024-08-05T12:33:48.363Z -- arborator -- server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25087</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Arborator Server. This vulnerability affects the function start of the file project.cgi. The manipulation of the argument project leads to denial of service. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The patch is identified as cdbdbcbd491db65e9d697ab4365605fdfab1a604. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-230662 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Arborator Server wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist die Funktion start der Datei project.cgi. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments project mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Dieses Produkt verzichtet auf eine Versionierung und verwendet stattdessen Rolling Releases. Deshalb sind keine Details zu betroffenen oder zu aktualisierende Versionen vorhanden. Der Patch wird als cdbdbcbd491db65e9d697ab4365605fdfab1a604 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-25087|2024-08-05T12:33:48.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 03:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
