<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Fujian -- mwcms</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/fujian/mwcms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Fujian -- mwcms</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 23:23:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7706|2024-08-12T22:31:05.721Z -- fujian -- mwcms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7706</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Fujian mwcms 1.0.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function uploadimage of the file /uploadfile.html. The manipulation of the argument upfile leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Fujian mwcms 1.0.0 ausgemacht. Hierbei geht es um die Funktion uploadimage der Datei /uploadfile.html. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments upfile mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7706|2024-08-12T22:31:05.721Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7705|2024-08-12T22:31:04.237Z -- fujian -- mwcms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7705</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Fujian mwcms 1.0.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function uploadeditor of the file /uploadeditor.html?action=uploadimage of the component Image Upload. The manipulation of the argument upfile leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Fujian mwcms 1.0.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Dabei geht es um die Funktion uploadeditor der Datei /uploadeditor.html?action=uploadimage der Komponente Image Upload. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments upfile mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7705|2024-08-12T22:31:04.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
