<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for psi-4ward -- psitransfer</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/psi-4ward/psitransfer.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for psi-4ward -- psitransfer</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:19:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31453|2024-07-31T18:11:26.167Z -- psi-4ward -- psitransfer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31453</link>
      <description>PsiTransfer is an open source, self-hosted file sharing solution. Prior to version 2.2.0, the absence of restrictions on the endpoint, which allows users to create a path for uploading a file in a file distribution, allows an attacker to add arbitrary files to the distribution. The vulnerability allows an attacker to influence those users who come to the file distribution after them and slip the victim files with a malicious or phishing signature. Version 2.2.0 contains a patch for the issue.

CVE-2024-31453 allows users to violate the integrity of a file bucket and upload new files there, while the vulnerability with the number CVE-2024-31454 allows users to violate the integrity of a single file that is uploaded by another user by writing data there and not allows you to upload new files to the bucket. Thus, vulnerabilities are reproduced differently, require different security recommendations and affect different objects of the application’s business logic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31453|2024-07-31T18:11:26.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 17:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31453|2024-04-09T17:12:49.408Z -- psi-4ward -- psitransfer</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31453</link>
      <description>PsiTransfer is an open source, self-hosted file sharing solution. Prior to version 2.2.0, the absence of restrictions on the endpoint, which allows users to create a path for uploading a file in a file distribution, allows an attacker to add arbitrary files to the distribution. The vulnerability allows an attacker to influence those users who come to the file distribution after them and slip the victim files with a malicious or phishing signature. Version 2.2.0 contains a patch for the issue.

CVE-2024-31453 allows users to violate the integrity of a file bucket and upload new files there, while the vulnerability with the number CVE-2024-31454 allows users to violate the integrity of a single file that is uploaded by another user by writing data there and not allows you to upload new files to the bucket. Thus, vulnerabilities are reproduced differently, require different security recommendations and affect different objects of the application’s business logic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31453|2024-04-09T17:12:49.408Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 17:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31454|2024-04-09T17:19:24.991Z -- psi-4ward -- psitransfer</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31454</link>
      <description>PsiTransfer is an open source, self-hosted file sharing solution. Prior to version 2.2.0, the absence of restrictions on the endpoint, which is designed for uploading files, allows an attacker who received the id of a file distribution to change the files that are in this distribution. The vulnerability allows an attacker to influence those users who come to the file distribution after them and slip the victim files with a malicious or phishing signature. Version 2.2.0 contains a patch for this issue.

CVE-2024-31454 allows users to violate the integrity of a file that is uploaded by another user. In this case, additional files are not loaded into the file bucket. Violation of integrity at the level of individual files. While the vulnerability with the number CVE-2024-31453 allows users to violate the integrity of a file bucket without violating the integrity of files uploaded by other users. Thus, vulnerabilities are reproduced differently, require different security recommendations and affect different objects of the application’s business logic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31454|2024-04-09T17:19:24.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 17:19:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
