<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for oFono -- oFono</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ofono/ofono.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for oFono -- oFono</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:21:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7545|2024-08-06T19:49:17.011Z -- ofono -- ofono
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7545</link>
      <description>oFono SimToolKit Heap-based Buffer Overflow Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of oFono. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target modem in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of STK command PDUs. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-23458.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7545|2024-08-06T19:49:17.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7538|2024-08-06T19:55:03.568Z -- ofono -- ofono
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7538</link>
      <description>oFono CUSD AT Command Stack-based Buffer Overflow Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of oFono. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target modem in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of responses from AT Commands. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-23190.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7538|2024-08-06T19:55:03.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7539|2024-08-06T13:48:46.835Z -- ofono -- ofono</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7539</link>
      <description>oFono CUSD Stack-based Buffer Overflow Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of oFono. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target modem in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of responses from AT+CUSD commands. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-23195.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7539|2024-08-06T13:48:46.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:53:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7537|2024-08-06T13:56:32.912Z -- ofono -- ofono</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7537</link>
      <description>oFono QMI SMS Handling Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of oFono. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of SMS message lists. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-23157.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7537|2024-08-06T13:56:32.912Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7541|2024-08-06T13:24:10.805Z -- ofono -- ofono</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7541</link>
      <description>oFono AT CMT Command Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of oFono. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target modem in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of responses from AT+CMT commands. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-23308.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7541|2024-08-06T13:24:10.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7544|2024-08-06T13:56:09.146Z -- ofono -- ofono</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7544</link>
      <description>oFono SimToolKit Heap-based Buffer Overflow Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of oFono. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target modem in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of STK command PDUs. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-23457.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7544|2024-08-06T13:56:09.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7546|2024-08-06T13:45:57.935Z -- ofono -- ofono</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7546</link>
      <description>oFono SimToolKit Heap-based Buffer Overflow Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of oFono. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target modem in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of STK command PDUs. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-23459.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7546|2024-08-06T13:45:57.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7543|2024-08-06T15:16:20.581Z -- ofono -- ofono</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7543</link>
      <description>oFono SimToolKit Heap-based Buffer Overflow Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of oFono. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute code on the target modem in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of STK command PDUs. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-23456.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7543|2024-08-06T15:16:20.581Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
