<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for GitHub  -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/github/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for GitHub  -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 18:25:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16765|2024-08-05T01:24:47.950Z -- github -- vscode-codeql
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16765</link>
      <description>If an attacker can get a user to open a specially prepared directory tree as a workspace in Visual Studio Code with the CodeQL extension active, arbitrary code of the attacker's choosing may be executed on the user's behalf. This is fixed in version 1.0.1 of the extension. Users should upgrade to this version using Visual Studio Code Marketplace's upgrade mechanism. After upgrading, the codeQL.cli.executablePath setting can only be set in the per-user settings, and not in the per-workspace settings. More information about VS Code settings can be found here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16765|2024-08-05T01:24:47.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 17:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1908|2024-08-05T15:06:12.570Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1908</link>
      <description>An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to use the Enterprise Actions GitHub Connect download token to fetch private repository data. An attacker would require an account on the server instance with non-default settings for GitHub Connect. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.8.16, 3.9.11, 3.10.8, and 3.11.6. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1908|2024-08-05T15:06:12.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 18:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2748|2024-08-02T19:20:10.085Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2748</link>
      <description>A Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to execute unauthorized actions on behalf of an unsuspecting user. A mitigating factor is that user interaction is required. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12.0 and was fixed in versions 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2748|2024-08-02T19:20:10.085Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 23:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3470|2024-08-01T20:12:07.311Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3470</link>
      <description>An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to use a deploy key pertaining to an organization to bypass an organization ruleset. An attacker would require access to a valid deploy key for a repository in the organization as well as repository administrator access. This vulnerability affected versions of GitHub Enterprise Server 3.11 to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.8 and 3.12.2. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3470|2024-08-01T20:12:07.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3646|2024-08-01T20:20:00.135Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3646</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the instance when configuring the chat integration. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.12.2, 3.11.8, 3.10.10, and 3.9.13. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3646|2024-08-01T20:20:00.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3684|2024-08-01T20:20:00.537Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3684</link>
      <description>A server side request forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin access to the appliance when configuring the Artifacts &amp; Logs and Migrations Storage. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.12.2, 3.11.8, 3.10.10, and 3.9.13. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3684|2024-08-01T20:20:00.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4985|2024-08-01T20:55:10.505Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4985</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass vulnerability was present in the GitHub Enterprise Server (GHES) when utilizing SAML single sign-on authentication with the optional encrypted assertions feature. This vulnerability allowed an attacker to forge a SAML response to provision and/or gain access to a user with site administrator privileges. Exploitation of this vulnerability would allow unauthorized access to the instance without requiring prior authentication. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13.0 and was fixed in versions 3.9.15, 3.10.12, 3.11.10 and 3.12.4. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4985|2024-08-01T20:55:10.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 21:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1908|2024-08-01T18:56:22.478Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1908</link>
      <description>An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to use the Enterprise Actions GitHub Connect download token to fetch private repository data. An attacker would require an account on the server instance with non-default settings for GitHub Connect. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.8.16, 3.9.11, 3.10.8, and 3.11.6. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1908|2024-08-01T18:56:22.478Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 18:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1482|2024-08-01T18:40:21.100Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1482</link>
      <description>An incorrect authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to create new branches in public repositories and run arbitrary GitHub Actions workflows with permissions from the GITHUB_TOKEN. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need access to the Enterprise Server. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server after 3.8 and prior to 3.12, and was fixed in versions 3.9.10, 3.10.7, 3.11.5. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1482|2024-08-01T18:40:21.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 20:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1359|2024-08-01T18:33:25.450Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1359</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when setting up an HTTP proxy. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1359|2024-08-01T18:33:25.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1374|2024-08-01T18:40:20.725Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1374</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via nomad templates when configuring audit log forwarding. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1374|2024-08-01T18:40:20.725Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1354|2024-08-01T18:33:25.592Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1354</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via the `syslog-ng` configuration file. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1354|2024-08-01T18:33:25.592Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1369|2024-08-01T18:40:19.977Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1369</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when setting the username and password for collectd configurations. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1369|2024-08-01T18:40:19.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1378|2024-08-01T18:40:19.974Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1378</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via nomad templates when configuring SMTP options. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1378|2024-08-01T18:40:19.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1084|2024-08-01T18:26:30.428Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1084</link>
      <description>Cross-site Scripting in the tag name pattern field in the tag protections UI in GitHub Enterprise Server allows a malicious website that requires user interaction and social engineering to make changes to a user account via CSP bypass with created CSRF tokens. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12  and was fixed in all versions of 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1084|2024-08-01T18:26:30.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1082|2024-08-01T18:26:30.498Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1082</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to gain unauthorized read permission to files by deploying arbitrary symbolic links to a GitHub Pages site with a specially crafted artifact tarball. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need permission to create and build a GitHub Pages site on the GitHub Enterprise Server instance. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.8.15, 3.9.10, 3.10.7, 3.11.5. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1082|2024-08-01T18:26:30.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1372|2024-08-01T18:40:19.978Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1372</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when configuring SAML settings. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1372|2024-08-01T18:40:19.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1355|2024-08-01T18:33:25.412Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1355</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via the actions-console docker container while setting a service URL. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1355|2024-08-01T18:33:25.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5815|2024-07-24T20:48:10.911Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5815</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed write operations on a victim-owned repository by exploiting incorrect request types. A mitigating factor is that the attacker would have to be a trusted GitHub Enterprise Server user, and the victim would have to visit a tag in the attacker's fork of their own repository. vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17.


 This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5815|2024-07-24T20:48:10.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5566|2024-07-22T19:47:55.185Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5566</link>
      <description>An improper privilege management vulnerability allowed users to migrate private repositories without having appropriate scopes defined on the related Personal Access Token. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5566|2024-07-22T19:47:55.185Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5816|2024-07-18T15:14:00.162Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5816</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed a suspended GitHub App to retain access to the repository via a scoped user access token. This was only exploitable in public repositories while private repositories were not impacted. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.9.17, 3.10.14, 3.11.12, 3.12.6, 3.13.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5816|2024-07-18T15:14:00.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5817|2024-07-17T19:31:17.566Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5817</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed read access to issue content via GitHub Projects. This was only exploitable in internal repositories and required the attacker to have access to the corresponding project board. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5817|2024-07-17T19:31:17.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6395|2024-07-17T14:16:58.488Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6395</link>
      <description>An exposure of sensitive information vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server would allow an attacker to enumerate the names of private repositories that utilize deploy keys. This vulnerability did not allow unauthorized access to any repository content besides the name. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6395|2024-07-17T14:16:58.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5746|2024-06-24T15:08:21.753Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5746</link>
      <description>A Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with the Site Administrator role to gain arbitrary code execution capability on the GitHub Enterprise Server instance. Exploitation required authenticated access to GitHub Enterprise Server as a user with the Site Administrator role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.12.5, 3.11.11, 3.10.13, and 3.9.16. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5746|2024-06-24T15:08:21.753Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 21:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1374|2024-02-28T15:42:21.060Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1374</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via nomad templates when configuring audit log forwarding. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1374|2024-02-28T15:42:21.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1378|2024-02-28T15:42:37.329Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1378</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via nomad templates when configuring SMTP options. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1378|2024-02-28T15:42:37.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1084|2024-06-04T18:00:12.161Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1084</link>
      <description>Cross-site Scripting in the tag name pattern field in the tag protections UI in GitHub Enterprise Server allows a malicious website that requires user interaction and social engineering to make changes to a user account via CSP bypass with created CSRF tokens. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12  and was fixed in all versions of 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1084|2024-06-04T18:00:12.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1354|2024-02-28T15:40:40.697Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1354</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via the `syslog-ng` configuration file. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1354|2024-02-28T15:40:40.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1355|2024-02-28T15:41:02.070Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1355</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via the actions-console docker container while setting a service URL. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1355|2024-02-28T15:41:02.070Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1482|2024-06-04T18:00:04.297Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1482</link>
      <description>An incorrect authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to create new branches in public repositories and run arbitrary GitHub Actions workflows with permissions from the GITHUB_TOKEN. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need access to the Enterprise Server. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server after 3.8 and prior to 3.12, and was fixed in versions 3.9.10, 3.10.7, 3.11.5. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1482|2024-06-04T18:00:04.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 20:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1359|2024-02-28T15:29:24.410Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1359</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when setting up an HTTP proxy. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1359|2024-02-28T15:29:24.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1908|2024-02-29T18:23:21.156Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1908</link>
      <description>An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to use the Enterprise Actions GitHub Connect download token to fetch private repository data. An attacker would require an account on the server instance with non-default settings for GitHub Connect. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.8.16, 3.9.11, 3.10.8, and 3.11.6. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1908|2024-02-29T18:23:21.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 18:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1082|2024-02-28T15:39:56.533Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1082</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to gain unauthorized read permission to files by deploying arbitrary symbolic links to a GitHub Pages site with a specially crafted artifact tarball. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need permission to create and build a GitHub Pages site on the GitHub Enterprise Server instance. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.8.15, 3.9.10, 3.10.7, 3.11.5. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1082|2024-02-28T15:39:56.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1372|2024-02-28T15:41:59.912Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1372</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when configuring SAML settings. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1372|2024-02-28T15:41:59.912Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1369|2024-02-28T15:41:40.053Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1369</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when setting the username and password for collectd configurations. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1369|2024-02-28T15:41:40.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4985|2024-06-04T17:54:09.964Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4985</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass vulnerability was present in the GitHub Enterprise Server (GHES) when utilizing SAML single sign-on authentication with the optional encrypted assertions feature. This vulnerability allowed an attacker to forge a SAML response to provision and/or gain access to a user with site administrator privileges. Exploitation of this vulnerability would allow unauthorized access to the instance without requiring prior authentication. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13.0 and was fixed in versions 3.9.15, 3.10.12, 3.11.10 and 3.12.4. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4985|2024-06-04T17:54:09.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 21:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25129|2024-06-04T17:35:28.209Z -- github -- codeql-cli-binaries</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25129</link>
      <description>The CodeQL CLI repo holds binaries for the CodeQL command line interface (CLI). Prior to version 2.16.3, an XML parser used by the CodeQL CLI to read various auxiliary files is vulnerable to an XML External Entity attack. If a vulnerable version of the CLI is used to process either a maliciously modified CodeQL database, or a specially prepared set of QL query sources, the CLI can be made to make an outgoing HTTP request to an URL that contains material read from a local file chosen by the attacker. This may result in a loss of privacy of exfiltration of secrets. Security researchers and QL authors who receive databases or QL source files from untrusted sources may be impacted. A single untrusted `.ql` or `.qll` file cannot be affected, but a zip archive or tarball containing QL sources may unpack auxiliary files that will trigger an attack when CodeQL sees them in the file system. Those using CodeQL for routine analysis of source trees with a preselected set of trusted queries are not affected. In particular, extracting XML files from a source tree into the CodeQL database does not make one vulnerable. The problem is fixed in release 2.16.3 of the CodeQL CLI. Other than upgrading, workarounds include not accepting CodeQL databases or queries from untrusted sources, or only processing such material on a machine without an Internet connection. Customers who use older releases of CodeQL for security scanning in an automated CI system and cannot upgrade for compliance reasons can continue using that version. That use case is safe. If such customers have a private query pack and use the `codeql pack create` command to precompile them before using them in the CI system, they should be using the production CodeQL release to run `codeql pack create`. That command is safe as long as the QL source it precompiled is trusted. All other development of the query pack should use an upgraded CLI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25129|2024-06-04T17:35:28.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 18:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3646|2024-04-19T14:21:47.779Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3646</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the instance when configuring the chat integration. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.12.2, 3.11.8, 3.10.10, and 3.9.13. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3646|2024-04-19T14:21:47.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3684|2024-06-04T17:31:50.524Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3684</link>
      <description>A server side request forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin access to the appliance when configuring the Artifacts &amp; Logs and Migrations Storage. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.12.2, 3.11.8, 3.10.10, and 3.9.13. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3684|2024-06-04T17:31:50.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3470|2024-06-04T17:31:36.420Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3470</link>
      <description>An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to use a deploy key pertaining to an organization to bypass an organization ruleset. An attacker would require access to a valid deploy key for a repository in the organization as well as repository administrator access. This vulnerability affected versions of GitHub Enterprise Server 3.11 to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.8 and 3.12.2. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3470|2024-06-04T17:31:36.420Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2443|2024-03-20T23:04:23.899Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2443</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when configuring GeoJSON settings. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.8.17, 3.9.12, 3.10.9, 3.11.7, and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2443|2024-03-20T23:04:23.899Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 23:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2469|2024-03-20T22:56:13.304Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2469</link>
      <description>An attacker with an Administrator role in GitHub Enterprise Server could gain SSH root access via remote code execution. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server version 3.8.0 and above and was fixed in version 3.8.17, 3.9.12, 3.10.9, 3.11.7 and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2469|2024-03-20T22:56:13.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 22:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2440|2024-04-19T17:02:35.368Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2440</link>
      <description>A race condition in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed an existing admin to maintain permissions on a detached repository by making a GraphQL mutation to alter repository permissions while the repository is detached. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.9.13, 3.10.10, 3.11.8 and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2440|2024-04-19T17:02:35.368Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2748|2024-03-20T23:09:46.922Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2748</link>
      <description>A Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to execute unauthorized actions on behalf of an unsuspecting user. A mitigating factor is that user interaction is required. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12.0 and was fixed in versions 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2748|2024-03-20T23:09:46.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 23:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5746|2024-06-20T21:31:37.111Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5746</link>
      <description>A Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with the Site Administrator role to gain arbitrary code execution capability on the GitHub Enterprise Server instance. Exploitation required authenticated access to GitHub Enterprise Server as a user with the Site Administrator role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.12.5, 3.11.11, 3.10.13, and 3.9.16. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5746|2024-06-20T21:31:37.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 21:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5816|2024-07-16T21:27:00.491Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5816</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed a suspended GitHub App to retain access to the repository via a scoped user access token. This was only exploitable in public repositories while private repositories were not impacted. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.9.17, 3.10.14, 3.11.12, 3.12.6, 3.13.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5816|2024-07-16T21:27:00.491Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5817|2024-07-16T21:27:03.820Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5817</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed read access to issue content via GitHub Projects. This was only exploitable in internal repositories and required the attacker to have access to the corresponding project board. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5817|2024-07-16T21:27:03.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6395|2024-07-16T21:27:10.901Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6395</link>
      <description>An exposure of sensitive information vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server would allow an attacker to enumerate the names of private repositories that utilize deploy keys. This vulnerability did not allow unauthorized access to any repository content besides the name. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6395|2024-07-16T21:27:10.901Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5795|2024-07-16T21:26:54.243Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5795</link>
      <description>A Denial of Service vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to cause unbounded resource exhaustion by sending a large payload to the Git server. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5795|2024-07-16T21:26:54.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6336|2024-07-16T21:27:07.393Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6336</link>
      <description>A Security Misconfiguration vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed sensitive information disclosure to unauthorized users in GitHub Enterprise Server by exploiting organization ruleset feature. This attack required an organization member to explicitly change the visibility of a dependent repository from private to public. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6336|2024-07-16T21:27:07.393Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5815|2024-07-16T21:26:57.404Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5815</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed write operations on a victim-owned repository by exploiting incorrect request types. A mitigating factor is that the attacker would have to be a trusted GitHub Enterprise Server user, and the victim would have to visit a tag in the attacker's fork of their own repository. vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17.


 This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5815|2024-07-16T21:26:57.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5566|2024-07-16T21:26:46.902Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5566</link>
      <description>An improper privilege management vulnerability allowed users to migrate private repositories without having appropriate scopes defined on the related Personal Access Token. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5566|2024-07-16T21:26:46.902Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6336|2024-07-17T15:39:07.466Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6336</link>
      <description>A Security Misconfiguration vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed sensitive information disclosure to unauthorized users in GitHub Enterprise Server by exploiting organization ruleset feature. This attack required an organization member to explicitly change the visibility of a dependent repository from private to public. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6336|2024-07-17T15:39:07.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2469|2024-07-18T14:43:40.941Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2469</link>
      <description>An attacker with an Administrator role in GitHub Enterprise Server could gain SSH root access via remote code execution. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server version 3.8.0 and above and was fixed in version 3.8.17, 3.9.12, 3.10.9, 3.11.7 and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2469|2024-07-18T14:43:40.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 22:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5795|2024-07-22T14:40:29.964Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5795</link>
      <description>A Denial of Service vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to cause unbounded resource exhaustion by sending a large payload to the Git server. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5795|2024-07-22T14:40:29.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2440|2024-07-24T19:46:49.638Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2440</link>
      <description>A race condition in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed an existing admin to maintain permissions on a detached repository by making a GraphQL mutation to alter repository permissions while the repository is detached. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.9.13, 3.10.10, 3.11.8 and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2440|2024-07-24T19:46:49.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3646|2024-07-24T19:44:58.895Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3646</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the instance when configuring the chat integration. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.12.2, 3.11.8, 3.10.10, and 3.9.13. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3646|2024-07-24T19:44:58.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2748|2024-08-01T19:25:41.753Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2748</link>
      <description>A Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to execute unauthorized actions on behalf of an unsuspecting user. A mitigating factor is that user interaction is required. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12.0 and was fixed in versions 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2748|2024-08-01T19:25:41.753Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 23:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2443|2024-08-01T19:11:53.575Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2443</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when configuring GeoJSON settings. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.8.17, 3.9.12, 3.10.9, 3.11.7, and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2443|2024-08-01T19:11:53.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 23:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2440|2024-08-01T19:11:53.576Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2440</link>
      <description>A race condition in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed an existing admin to maintain permissions on a detached repository by making a GraphQL mutation to alter repository permissions while the repository is detached. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.9.13, 3.10.10, 3.11.8 and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2440|2024-08-01T19:11:53.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2469|2024-08-01T19:11:53.713Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2469</link>
      <description>An attacker with an Administrator role in GitHub Enterprise Server could gain SSH root access via remote code execution. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server version 3.8.0 and above and was fixed in version 3.8.17, 3.9.12, 3.10.9, 3.11.7 and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2469|2024-08-01T19:11:53.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 22:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6395|2024-08-01T21:41:03.389Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6395</link>
      <description>An exposure of sensitive information vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server would allow an attacker to enumerate the names of private repositories that utilize deploy keys. This vulnerability did not allow unauthorized access to any repository content besides the name. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6395|2024-08-01T21:41:03.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5746|2024-08-01T21:18:07.077Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5746</link>
      <description>A Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with the Site Administrator role to gain arbitrary code execution capability on the GitHub Enterprise Server instance. Exploitation required authenticated access to GitHub Enterprise Server as a user with the Site Administrator role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.12.5, 3.11.11, 3.10.13, and 3.9.16. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5746|2024-08-01T21:18:07.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 21:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5817|2024-08-01T21:25:02.832Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5817</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed read access to issue content via GitHub Projects. This was only exploitable in internal repositories and required the attacker to have access to the corresponding project board. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5817|2024-08-01T21:25:02.832Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5566|2024-08-01T21:18:06.292Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5566</link>
      <description>An improper privilege management vulnerability allowed users to migrate private repositories without having appropriate scopes defined on the related Personal Access Token. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5566|2024-08-01T21:18:06.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6336|2024-08-01T21:33:05.420Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6336</link>
      <description>A Security Misconfiguration vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed sensitive information disclosure to unauthorized users in GitHub Enterprise Server by exploiting organization ruleset feature. This attack required an organization member to explicitly change the visibility of a dependent repository from private to public. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6336|2024-08-01T21:33:05.420Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5816|2024-08-01T21:25:02.923Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5816</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed a suspended GitHub App to retain access to the repository via a scoped user access token. This was only exploitable in public repositories while private repositories were not impacted. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.9.17, 3.10.14, 3.11.12, 3.12.6, 3.13.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5816|2024-08-01T21:25:02.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5815|2024-08-01T21:25:02.739Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5815</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed write operations on a victim-owned repository by exploiting incorrect request types. A mitigating factor is that the attacker would have to be a trusted GitHub Enterprise Server user, and the victim would have to visit a tag in the attacker's fork of their own repository. vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17.


 This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5815|2024-08-01T21:25:02.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5795|2024-08-01T21:25:01.600Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5795</link>
      <description>A Denial of Service vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to cause unbounded resource exhaustion by sending a large payload to the Git server. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5795|2024-08-01T21:25:01.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
