<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for GitHub  -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/github/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for GitHub  -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:23:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23762|2024-08-02T10:42:25.884Z -- github -- enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23762</link>
      <description>An incorrect comparison vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed commit smuggling by displaying an incorrect diff. To do so, an attacker would need write access to the repository and be able to correctly guess the target branch before it’s created by the code maintainer. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.9 and was fixed in versions 3.4.18, 3.5.15, 3.6.11, 3.7.8, and 3.8.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23762|2024-08-02T10:42:25.884Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 18:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22486|2024-08-02T10:13:48.528Z -- github -- cmark-gfm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22486</link>
      <description>cmark-gfm is GitHub's fork of cmark, a CommonMark parsing and rendering library and program in C. Versions prior to 0.29.0.gfm.7 contain a  polynomial time complexity issue in handle_close_bracket that may lead to unbounded resource exhaustion and subsequent denial of service. This vulnerability has been patched in 0.29.0.gfm.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22486|2024-08-02T10:13:48.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 02:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6847|2024-08-02T08:42:07.604Z -- github -- enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6847</link>
      <description>An improper authentication vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed a bypass of Private Mode by using a specially crafted API request. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need network access to the Enterprise Server appliance configured in Private Mode. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server since 3.9 and was fixed in version 3.9.7, 3.10.4, and 3.11.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6847|2024-08-02T08:42:07.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6804|2024-08-02T08:42:07.836Z -- github -- enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6804</link>
      <description>Improper privilege management allowed arbitrary workflows to be committed and run using an improperly scoped PAT. To exploit this, a workflow must have already existed in the target repo. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server since 3.8 and was fixed in version 3.8.12, 3.9.7, 3.10.4, and 3.11.1. 
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6804|2024-08-02T08:42:07.836Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23763|2024-08-02T10:42:25.864Z -- github -- enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23763</link>
      <description>An authorization/sensitive information disclosure vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed a fork to retain read access to an upstream repository after its visibility was changed to private. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.10.0 and was fixed in versions 3.9.4, 3.8.9, 3.7.16 and 3.6.18. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23763|2024-08-02T10:42:25.864Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 14:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22484|2024-08-02T10:13:48.528Z -- github -- cmark-gfm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22484</link>
      <description>cmark-gfm is GitHub's fork of cmark, a CommonMark parsing and rendering library and program in C. Versions prior to 0.29.0.gfm.7 are subject to a polynomial time complexity issue in cmark-gfm that may lead to unbounded resource exhaustion and subsequent denial of service. This vulnerability has been patched in 0.29.0.gfm.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22484|2024-08-02T10:13:48.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 22:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6803|2024-08-02T08:42:07.752Z -- github -- enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6803</link>
      <description>A race condition in GitHub Enterprise Server allows an outside collaborator to be added while a repository is being transferred. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server since 3.8 and was fixed in version 3.8.12, 3.9.7, 3.10.4, and 3.11.1. 
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6803|2024-08-02T08:42:07.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6690|2024-08-02T08:35:14.855Z -- github -- enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6690</link>
      <description>A race condition in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed an existing admin to maintain permissions on transferred repositories by making a GraphQL mutation to alter repository permissions during the transfer. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server version 3.8.0 and above and was fixed in version 3.8.12, 3.9.7, 3.10.4, and 3.11.1.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6690|2024-08-02T08:35:14.855Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23766|2024-08-02T10:42:25.887Z -- github -- enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23766</link>
      <description>An incorrect comparison vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed commit smuggling by displaying an incorrect diff in a re-opened Pull Request. To do so, an attacker would need write access to the repository. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server and was fixed in versions 3.6.17, 3.7.15, 3.8.8, 3.9.3, and 3.10.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23766|2024-08-02T10:42:25.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 14:18:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24824|2024-08-02T11:03:19.254Z -- github -- cmark-gfm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24824</link>
      <description>cmark-gfm is GitHub's fork of cmark, a CommonMark parsing and rendering library and program in C. A polynomial time complexity issue in cmark-gfm may lead to unbounded resource exhaustion and subsequent denial of service. This CVE covers quadratic complexity issues when parsing text which leads with either large numbers of `&gt;` or `-` characters. This issue has been addressed in version 0.29.0.gfm.10. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should validate that their input comes from trusted sources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24824|2024-08-02T11:03:19.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 22:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23765|2024-08-02T10:42:26.237Z -- github -- enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23765</link>
      <description>An incorrect comparison vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed commit smuggling by displaying an incorrect diff in a re-opened Pull Request. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need write access to the repository. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty Program https://bounty.github.com/ .
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23765|2024-08-02T10:42:26.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 22:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23764|2024-08-02T10:42:25.871Z -- github -- enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23764</link>
      <description>An incorrect comparison vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed commit smuggling by displaying an incorrect diff within the GitHub pull request UI. To do so, an attacker would need write access to the repository. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server versions 3.7.0 and above and was fixed in versions 3.7.9, 3.8.2, and 3.9.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23764|2024-08-02T10:42:25.871Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 20:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23761|2024-08-02T10:42:26.151Z -- github -- enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23761</link>
      <description>An improper authentication vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an unauthorized actor to modify other users' secret gists by authenticating through an SSH certificate authority. To do so, a user had to know the secret gist's URL. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.9 and was fixed in versions 3.4.18, 3.5.15, 3.6.11, 3.7.8, and 3.8.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23761|2024-08-02T10:42:26.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 18:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26485|2024-08-02T11:53:52.747Z -- github -- cmark-gfm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26485</link>
      <description>cmark-gfm is GitHub's fork of cmark, a CommonMark parsing and rendering library and program in C. A polynomial time complexity issue in cmark-gfm may lead to unbounded resource exhaustion and subsequent denial of service. This CVE covers quadratic complexity issues when parsing text which leads with either large numbers of `_` characters. This issue has been addressed in version 0.29.0.gfm.10. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should validate that their input comes from trusted sources.




### Impact

A polynomial time complexity issue in cmark-gfm may lead to unbounded resource exhaustion and subsequent denial of service.

### Proof of concept

```
$ ~/cmark-gfm$ python3 -c 'pad = "_" * 100000; print(pad + "." + pad, end="")' | time ./build/src/cmark-gfm --to plaintext
```

Increasing the number 10000 in the above commands causes the running time to increase quadratically.

### Patches

This vulnerability have been patched in 0.29.0.gfm.10.

### Note on cmark and cmark-gfm

XXX: TBD

[cmark-gfm](https://github.com/github/cmark-gfm) is a fork of [cmark](https://github.com/commonmark/cmark) that adds the GitHub Flavored Markdown extensions. The two codebases have diverged over time, but share a common core. These bugs affect both `cmark` and `cmark-gfm`. 

### Credit

We would like to thank @gravypod for reporting this vulnerability.

### References

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Time_complexity

### For more information

If you have any questions or comments about this advisory:

* Open an issue in [github/cmark-gfm](https://github.com/github/cmark-gfm)
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26485|2024-08-02T11:53:52.747Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 22:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23760|2024-08-02T10:42:25.940Z -- github -- enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23760</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed remote code execution when building a GitHub Pages site. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need permission to create and build a GitHub Pages site on the GitHub Enterprise Server instance. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to versions 3.8 and was fixed in versions 3.7.7, 3.6.10, 3.5.14, and 3.4.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.




</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23760|2024-08-02T10:42:25.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 18:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37463|2024-08-02T17:16:30.468Z -- github -- cmark-gfm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37463</link>
      <description>cmark-gfm is an extended version of the C reference implementation of CommonMark, a rationalized version of Markdown syntax with a spec. Three polynomial time complexity issues in cmark-gfm may lead to unbounded resource exhaustion and subsequent denial of service. These vulnerabilities have been patched in 0.29.0.gfm.12.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37463|2024-08-02T17:16:30.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 19:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22485|2024-08-02T10:13:48.514Z -- github -- cmark-gfm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22485</link>
      <description>cmark-gfm is GitHub's fork of cmark, a CommonMark parsing and rendering library and program in C. In versions prior 0.29.0.gfm.7, a crafted markdown document can trigger an out-of-bounds read in the `validate_protocol` function. We believe this bug is harmless in practice, because the out-of-bounds read accesses `malloc` metadata without causing any visible damage.This vulnerability has been patched in 0.29.0.gfm.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22485|2024-08-02T10:13:48.514Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22381|2024-08-02T10:07:06.540Z -- github -- enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22381</link>
      <description>A code injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed setting arbitrary environment variables from a single environment variable value in GitHub Actions when using a Windows based runner. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need existing permission to control the value of environment variables for use with GitHub Actions. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.8.0 and was fixed in versions 3.4.15, 3.5.12, 3.6.8, 3.7.5. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.




</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22381|2024-08-02T10:07:06.540Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 20:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22483|2024-08-02T10:13:48.482Z -- github -- cmark-gfm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22483</link>
      <description>cmark-gfm is GitHub's fork of cmark, a CommonMark parsing and rendering library and program in C. Versions prior to 0.29.0.gfm.7 are subject to several polynomial time complexity issues in cmark-gfm that may lead to unbounded resource exhaustion and subsequent denial of service. Various commands, when piped to cmark-gfm with large values, cause the running time to increase quadratically. These vulnerabilities have been patched in version 0.29.0.gfm.7.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22483|2024-08-02T10:13:48.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 22:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2748|2024-08-02T19:20:10.085Z -- github -- enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2748</link>
      <description>A Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to execute unauthorized actions on behalf of an unsuspecting user. A mitigating factor is that user interaction is required. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12.0 and was fixed in versions 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program. 
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2748|2024-08-02T19:20:10.085Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 23:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6746|2024-08-02T08:42:07.218Z -- github -- enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6746</link>
      <description>An insertion of sensitive information into log file vulnerability was identified in the log files for a GitHub Enterprise Server back-end service that could permit an `adversary in the middle attack` when combined with other phishing techniques. To exploit this, an attacker would need access to the log files for the GitHub Enterprise Server appliance, a backup archive created with GitHub Enterprise Server Backup Utilities, or a service which received streamed logs. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server since 3.7 and was fixed in version 3.7.19, 3.8.12, 3.9.7, 3.10.4, and 3.11.1. </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6746|2024-08-02T08:42:07.218Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6802|2024-08-02T08:42:07.457Z -- github -- enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6802</link>
      <description>An insertion of sensitive information into the log file in the audit log in GitHub Enterprise Server was identified that could allow an attacker to gain access to the management console. To exploit this, an attacker would need access to the log files for the GitHub Enterprise Server appliance, a backup archive created with GitHub Enterprise Server Backup Utilities, or a service which received streamed logs. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server since 3.8 and was fixed in version 3.8.12, 3.9.7, 3.10.4, and 3.11.1. </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6802|2024-08-02T08:42:07.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 20:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22380|2024-08-02T10:07:06.637Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22380</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed arbitrary file reading when building a GitHub Pages site. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need permission to create and build a GitHub Pages site on the GitHub Enterprise Server instance. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server since 3.7 and was fixed in version 3.7.6. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22380|2024-08-02T10:07:06.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3470|2024-08-01T20:12:07.311Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3470</link>
      <description>An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to use a deploy key pertaining to an organization to bypass an organization ruleset. An attacker would require access to a valid deploy key for a repository in the organization as well as repository administrator access. This vulnerability affected versions of GitHub Enterprise Server 3.11 to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.8 and 3.12.2. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3470|2024-08-01T20:12:07.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3646|2024-08-01T20:20:00.135Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3646</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the instance when configuring the chat integration. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.12.2, 3.11.8, 3.10.10, and 3.9.13. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3646|2024-08-01T20:20:00.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3684|2024-08-01T20:20:00.537Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3684</link>
      <description>A server side request forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin access to the appliance when configuring the Artifacts &amp; Logs and Migrations Storage. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.12.2, 3.11.8, 3.10.10, and 3.9.13. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3684|2024-08-01T20:20:00.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4985|2024-08-01T20:55:10.505Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4985</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass vulnerability was present in the GitHub Enterprise Server (GHES) when utilizing SAML single sign-on authentication with the optional encrypted assertions feature. This vulnerability allowed an attacker to forge a SAML response to provision and/or gain access to a user with site administrator privileges. Exploitation of this vulnerability would allow unauthorized access to the instance without requiring prior authentication. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13.0 and was fixed in versions 3.9.15, 3.10.12, 3.11.10 and 3.12.4. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4985|2024-08-01T20:55:10.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 21:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1908|2024-08-01T18:56:22.478Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1908</link>
      <description>An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to use the Enterprise Actions GitHub Connect download token to fetch private repository data. An attacker would require an account on the server instance with non-default settings for GitHub Connect. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.8.16, 3.9.11, 3.10.8, and 3.11.6. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1908|2024-08-01T18:56:22.478Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 18:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1482|2024-08-01T18:40:21.100Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1482</link>
      <description>An incorrect authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to create new branches in public repositories and run arbitrary GitHub Actions workflows with permissions from the GITHUB_TOKEN. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need access to the Enterprise Server. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server after 3.8 and prior to 3.12, and was fixed in versions 3.9.10, 3.10.7, 3.11.5. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1482|2024-08-01T18:40:21.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 20:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1359|2024-08-01T18:33:25.450Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1359</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when setting up an HTTP proxy. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1359|2024-08-01T18:33:25.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1374|2024-08-01T18:40:20.725Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1374</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via nomad templates when configuring audit log forwarding. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1374|2024-08-01T18:40:20.725Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1354|2024-08-01T18:33:25.592Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1354</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via the `syslog-ng` configuration file. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1354|2024-08-01T18:33:25.592Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1369|2024-08-01T18:40:19.977Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1369</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when setting the username and password for collectd configurations. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1369|2024-08-01T18:40:19.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1378|2024-08-01T18:40:19.974Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1378</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via nomad templates when configuring SMTP options. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1378|2024-08-01T18:40:19.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1084|2024-08-01T18:26:30.428Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1084</link>
      <description>Cross-site Scripting in the tag name pattern field in the tag protections UI in GitHub Enterprise Server allows a malicious website that requires user interaction and social engineering to make changes to a user account via CSP bypass with created CSRF tokens. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12  and was fixed in all versions of 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1084|2024-08-01T18:26:30.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1082|2024-08-01T18:26:30.498Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1082</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to gain unauthorized read permission to files by deploying arbitrary symbolic links to a GitHub Pages site with a specially crafted artifact tarball. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need permission to create and build a GitHub Pages site on the GitHub Enterprise Server instance. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.8.15, 3.9.10, 3.10.7, 3.11.5. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1082|2024-08-01T18:26:30.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1372|2024-08-01T18:40:19.978Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1372</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when configuring SAML settings. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1372|2024-08-01T18:40:19.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1355|2024-08-01T18:33:25.412Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1355</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via the actions-console docker container while setting a service URL. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1355|2024-08-01T18:33:25.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5815|2024-07-24T20:48:10.911Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5815</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed write operations on a victim-owned repository by exploiting incorrect request types. A mitigating factor is that the attacker would have to be a trusted GitHub Enterprise Server user, and the victim would have to visit a tag in the attacker's fork of their own repository. vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17.


 This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5815|2024-07-24T20:48:10.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5566|2024-07-22T19:47:55.185Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5566</link>
      <description>An improper privilege management vulnerability allowed users to migrate private repositories without having appropriate scopes defined on the related Personal Access Token. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5566|2024-07-22T19:47:55.185Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5816|2024-07-18T15:14:00.162Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5816</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed a suspended GitHub App to retain access to the repository via a scoped user access token. This was only exploitable in public repositories while private repositories were not impacted. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.9.17, 3.10.14, 3.11.12, 3.12.6, 3.13.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5816|2024-07-18T15:14:00.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5817|2024-07-17T19:31:17.566Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5817</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed read access to issue content via GitHub Projects. This was only exploitable in internal repositories and required the attacker to have access to the corresponding project board. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5817|2024-07-17T19:31:17.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6395|2024-07-17T14:16:58.488Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6395</link>
      <description>An exposure of sensitive information vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server would allow an attacker to enumerate the names of private repositories that utilize deploy keys. This vulnerability did not allow unauthorized access to any repository content besides the name. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6395|2024-07-17T14:16:58.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5746|2024-06-24T15:08:21.753Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5746</link>
      <description>A Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with the Site Administrator role to gain arbitrary code execution capability on the GitHub Enterprise Server instance. Exploitation required authenticated access to GitHub Enterprise Server as a user with the Site Administrator role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.12.5, 3.11.11, 3.10.13, and 3.9.16. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5746|2024-06-24T15:08:21.753Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 21:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1374|2024-02-28T15:42:21.060Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1374</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via nomad templates when configuring audit log forwarding. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1374|2024-02-28T15:42:21.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1378|2024-02-28T15:42:37.329Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1378</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via nomad templates when configuring SMTP options. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1378|2024-02-28T15:42:37.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1084|2024-06-04T18:00:12.161Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1084</link>
      <description>Cross-site Scripting in the tag name pattern field in the tag protections UI in GitHub Enterprise Server allows a malicious website that requires user interaction and social engineering to make changes to a user account via CSP bypass with created CSRF tokens. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12  and was fixed in all versions of 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1084|2024-06-04T18:00:12.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1354|2024-02-28T15:40:40.697Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1354</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via the `syslog-ng` configuration file. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1354|2024-02-28T15:40:40.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1355|2024-02-28T15:41:02.070Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1355</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance via the actions-console docker container while setting a service URL. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1355|2024-02-28T15:41:02.070Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1482|2024-06-04T18:00:04.297Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1482</link>
      <description>An incorrect authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to create new branches in public repositories and run arbitrary GitHub Actions workflows with permissions from the GITHUB_TOKEN. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need access to the Enterprise Server. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server after 3.8 and prior to 3.12, and was fixed in versions 3.9.10, 3.10.7, 3.11.5. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1482|2024-06-04T18:00:04.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 20:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1359|2024-02-28T15:29:24.410Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1359</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when setting up an HTTP proxy. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1359|2024-02-28T15:29:24.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1908|2024-02-29T18:23:21.156Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1908</link>
      <description>An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to use the Enterprise Actions GitHub Connect download token to fetch private repository data. An attacker would require an account on the server instance with non-default settings for GitHub Connect. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.8.16, 3.9.11, 3.10.8, and 3.11.6. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1908|2024-02-29T18:23:21.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 18:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1082|2024-02-28T15:39:56.533Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1082</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to gain unauthorized read permission to files by deploying arbitrary symbolic links to a GitHub Pages site with a specially crafted artifact tarball. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need permission to create and build a GitHub Pages site on the GitHub Enterprise Server instance. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.8.15, 3.9.10, 3.10.7, 3.11.5. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1082|2024-02-28T15:39:56.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1372|2024-02-28T15:41:59.912Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1372</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when configuring SAML settings. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1372|2024-02-28T15:41:59.912Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1369|2024-02-28T15:41:40.053Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1369</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when setting the username and password for collectd configurations. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.5, 3.10.7, 3.9.10, and 3.8.15. This vulnerability was reported via the  GitHub Bug Bounty program https://bounty.github.com .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1369|2024-02-28T15:41:40.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 18:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4985|2024-06-04T17:54:09.964Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4985</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass vulnerability was present in the GitHub Enterprise Server (GHES) when utilizing SAML single sign-on authentication with the optional encrypted assertions feature. This vulnerability allowed an attacker to forge a SAML response to provision and/or gain access to a user with site administrator privileges. Exploitation of this vulnerability would allow unauthorized access to the instance without requiring prior authentication. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13.0 and was fixed in versions 3.9.15, 3.10.12, 3.11.10 and 3.12.4. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4985|2024-06-04T17:54:09.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 21:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25129|2024-06-04T17:35:28.209Z -- github -- codeql-cli-binaries</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25129</link>
      <description>The CodeQL CLI repo holds binaries for the CodeQL command line interface (CLI). Prior to version 2.16.3, an XML parser used by the CodeQL CLI to read various auxiliary files is vulnerable to an XML External Entity attack. If a vulnerable version of the CLI is used to process either a maliciously modified CodeQL database, or a specially prepared set of QL query sources, the CLI can be made to make an outgoing HTTP request to an URL that contains material read from a local file chosen by the attacker. This may result in a loss of privacy of exfiltration of secrets. Security researchers and QL authors who receive databases or QL source files from untrusted sources may be impacted. A single untrusted `.ql` or `.qll` file cannot be affected, but a zip archive or tarball containing QL sources may unpack auxiliary files that will trigger an attack when CodeQL sees them in the file system. Those using CodeQL for routine analysis of source trees with a preselected set of trusted queries are not affected. In particular, extracting XML files from a source tree into the CodeQL database does not make one vulnerable. The problem is fixed in release 2.16.3 of the CodeQL CLI. Other than upgrading, workarounds include not accepting CodeQL databases or queries from untrusted sources, or only processing such material on a machine without an Internet connection. Customers who use older releases of CodeQL for security scanning in an automated CI system and cannot upgrade for compliance reasons can continue using that version. That use case is safe. If such customers have a private query pack and use the `codeql pack create` command to precompile them before using them in the CI system, they should be using the production CodeQL release to run `codeql pack create`. That command is safe as long as the QL source it precompiled is trusted. All other development of the query pack should use an upgraded CLI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25129|2024-06-04T17:35:28.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 18:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3646|2024-04-19T14:21:47.779Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3646</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the instance when configuring the chat integration. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.12.2, 3.11.8, 3.10.10, and 3.9.13. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3646|2024-04-19T14:21:47.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3684|2024-06-04T17:31:50.524Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3684</link>
      <description>A server side request forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin access to the appliance when configuring the Artifacts &amp; Logs and Migrations Storage. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.12.2, 3.11.8, 3.10.10, and 3.9.13. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3684|2024-06-04T17:31:50.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3470|2024-06-04T17:31:36.420Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3470</link>
      <description>An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to use a deploy key pertaining to an organization to bypass an organization ruleset. An attacker would require access to a valid deploy key for a repository in the organization as well as repository administrator access. This vulnerability affected versions of GitHub Enterprise Server 3.11 to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.11.8 and 3.12.2. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3470|2024-06-04T17:31:36.420Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2443|2024-03-20T23:04:23.899Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2443</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when configuring GeoJSON settings. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.8.17, 3.9.12, 3.10.9, 3.11.7, and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2443|2024-03-20T23:04:23.899Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 23:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2469|2024-03-20T22:56:13.304Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2469</link>
      <description>An attacker with an Administrator role in GitHub Enterprise Server could gain SSH root access via remote code execution. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server version 3.8.0 and above and was fixed in version 3.8.17, 3.9.12, 3.10.9, 3.11.7 and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2469|2024-03-20T22:56:13.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 22:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2440|2024-04-19T17:02:35.368Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2440</link>
      <description>A race condition in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed an existing admin to maintain permissions on a detached repository by making a GraphQL mutation to alter repository permissions while the repository is detached. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.9.13, 3.10.10, 3.11.8 and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2440|2024-04-19T17:02:35.368Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2748|2024-03-20T23:09:46.922Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2748</link>
      <description>A Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to execute unauthorized actions on behalf of an unsuspecting user. A mitigating factor is that user interaction is required. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12.0 and was fixed in versions 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2748|2024-03-20T23:09:46.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 23:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5746|2024-06-20T21:31:37.111Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5746</link>
      <description>A Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with the Site Administrator role to gain arbitrary code execution capability on the GitHub Enterprise Server instance. Exploitation required authenticated access to GitHub Enterprise Server as a user with the Site Administrator role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.12.5, 3.11.11, 3.10.13, and 3.9.16. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5746|2024-06-20T21:31:37.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 21:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5816|2024-07-16T21:27:00.491Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5816</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed a suspended GitHub App to retain access to the repository via a scoped user access token. This was only exploitable in public repositories while private repositories were not impacted. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.9.17, 3.10.14, 3.11.12, 3.12.6, 3.13.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5816|2024-07-16T21:27:00.491Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5817|2024-07-16T21:27:03.820Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5817</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed read access to issue content via GitHub Projects. This was only exploitable in internal repositories and required the attacker to have access to the corresponding project board. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5817|2024-07-16T21:27:03.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6395|2024-07-16T21:27:10.901Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6395</link>
      <description>An exposure of sensitive information vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server would allow an attacker to enumerate the names of private repositories that utilize deploy keys. This vulnerability did not allow unauthorized access to any repository content besides the name. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6395|2024-07-16T21:27:10.901Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5795|2024-07-16T21:26:54.243Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5795</link>
      <description>A Denial of Service vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to cause unbounded resource exhaustion by sending a large payload to the Git server. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5795|2024-07-16T21:26:54.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6336|2024-07-16T21:27:07.393Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6336</link>
      <description>A Security Misconfiguration vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed sensitive information disclosure to unauthorized users in GitHub Enterprise Server by exploiting organization ruleset feature. This attack required an organization member to explicitly change the visibility of a dependent repository from private to public. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6336|2024-07-16T21:27:07.393Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5815|2024-07-16T21:26:57.404Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5815</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed write operations on a victim-owned repository by exploiting incorrect request types. A mitigating factor is that the attacker would have to be a trusted GitHub Enterprise Server user, and the victim would have to visit a tag in the attacker's fork of their own repository. vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17.


 This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5815|2024-07-16T21:26:57.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5566|2024-07-16T21:26:46.902Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5566</link>
      <description>An improper privilege management vulnerability allowed users to migrate private repositories without having appropriate scopes defined on the related Personal Access Token. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5566|2024-07-16T21:26:46.902Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6336|2024-07-17T15:39:07.466Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6336</link>
      <description>A Security Misconfiguration vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed sensitive information disclosure to unauthorized users in GitHub Enterprise Server by exploiting organization ruleset feature. This attack required an organization member to explicitly change the visibility of a dependent repository from private to public. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6336|2024-07-17T15:39:07.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2469|2024-07-18T14:43:40.941Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2469</link>
      <description>An attacker with an Administrator role in GitHub Enterprise Server could gain SSH root access via remote code execution. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server version 3.8.0 and above and was fixed in version 3.8.17, 3.9.12, 3.10.9, 3.11.7 and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2469|2024-07-18T14:43:40.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 22:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5795|2024-07-22T14:40:29.964Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5795</link>
      <description>A Denial of Service vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to cause unbounded resource exhaustion by sending a large payload to the Git server. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5795|2024-07-22T14:40:29.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2440|2024-07-24T19:46:49.638Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2440</link>
      <description>A race condition in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed an existing admin to maintain permissions on a detached repository by making a GraphQL mutation to alter repository permissions while the repository is detached. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.9.13, 3.10.10, 3.11.8 and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2440|2024-07-24T19:46:49.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3646|2024-07-24T19:44:58.895Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3646</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the instance when configuring the chat integration. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.12 and was fixed in versions 3.12.2, 3.11.8, 3.10.10, and 3.9.13. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3646|2024-07-24T19:44:58.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2748|2024-08-01T19:25:41.753Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2748</link>
      <description>A Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to execute unauthorized actions on behalf of an unsuspecting user. A mitigating factor is that user interaction is required. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server 3.12.0 and was fixed in versions 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2748|2024-08-01T19:25:41.753Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 23:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2443|2024-08-01T19:11:53.575Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2443</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when configuring GeoJSON settings. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.8.17, 3.9.12, 3.10.9, 3.11.7, and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2443|2024-08-01T19:11:53.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 23:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2440|2024-08-01T19:11:53.576Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2440</link>
      <description>A race condition in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed an existing admin to maintain permissions on a detached repository by making a GraphQL mutation to alter repository permissions while the repository is detached. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.9.13, 3.10.10, 3.11.8 and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2440|2024-08-01T19:11:53.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2469|2024-08-01T19:11:53.713Z -- github -- enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2469</link>
      <description>An attacker with an Administrator role in GitHub Enterprise Server could gain SSH root access via remote code execution. This vulnerability affected GitHub Enterprise Server version 3.8.0 and above and was fixed in version 3.8.17, 3.9.12, 3.10.9, 3.11.7 and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2469|2024-08-01T19:11:53.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 22:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6395|2024-08-01T21:41:03.389Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6395</link>
      <description>An exposure of sensitive information vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server would allow an attacker to enumerate the names of private repositories that utilize deploy keys. This vulnerability did not allow unauthorized access to any repository content besides the name. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6395|2024-08-01T21:41:03.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5746|2024-08-01T21:18:07.077Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5746</link>
      <description>A Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with the Site Administrator role to gain arbitrary code execution capability on the GitHub Enterprise Server instance. Exploitation required authenticated access to GitHub Enterprise Server as a user with the Site Administrator role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.12.5, 3.11.11, 3.10.13, and 3.9.16. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5746|2024-08-01T21:18:07.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 21:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5817|2024-08-01T21:25:02.832Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5817</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed read access to issue content via GitHub Projects. This was only exploitable in internal repositories and required the attacker to have access to the corresponding project board. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5817|2024-08-01T21:25:02.832Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5566|2024-08-01T21:18:06.292Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5566</link>
      <description>An improper privilege management vulnerability allowed users to migrate private repositories without having appropriate scopes defined on the related Personal Access Token. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5566|2024-08-01T21:18:06.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6336|2024-08-01T21:33:05.420Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6336</link>
      <description>A Security Misconfiguration vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed sensitive information disclosure to unauthorized users in GitHub Enterprise Server by exploiting organization ruleset feature. This attack required an organization member to explicitly change the visibility of a dependent repository from private to public. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6336|2024-08-01T21:33:05.420Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5816|2024-08-01T21:25:02.923Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5816</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed a suspended GitHub App to retain access to the repository via a scoped user access token. This was only exploitable in public repositories while private repositories were not impacted. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.9.17, 3.10.14, 3.11.12, 3.12.6, 3.13.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5816|2024-08-01T21:25:02.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5815|2024-08-01T21:25:02.739Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5815</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed write operations on a victim-owned repository by exploiting incorrect request types. A mitigating factor is that the attacker would have to be a trusted GitHub Enterprise Server user, and the victim would have to visit a tag in the attacker's fork of their own repository. vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17.


 This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5815|2024-08-01T21:25:02.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5795|2024-08-01T21:25:01.600Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5795</link>
      <description>A Denial of Service vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to cause unbounded resource exhaustion by sending a large payload to the Git server. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5795|2024-08-01T21:25:01.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
