<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for GitHub -- GitHub Enterprise Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/github/github%20enterprise%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for GitHub -- GitHub Enterprise Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:23:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23732|2024-08-03T03:51:46.012Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23732</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server management console that allowed the bypass of CSRF protections. This could potentially lead to privilege escalation. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to target a user that was actively logged into the management console. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.5 and was fixed in versions 3.1.19, 3.2.11, 3.3.6, 3.4.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23732|2024-08-03T03:51:46.012Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 00:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23740|2024-08-03T03:51:46.104Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23740</link>
      <description>CRITICAL: An improper neutralization of argument delimiters in a command vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that enabled remote code execution. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need permission to create and build GitHub Pages using GitHub Actions. This vulnerability affected only version 3.7.0 of GitHub Enterprise Server and was fixed in version 3.7.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23740|2024-08-03T03:51:46.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23733|2024-08-03T03:51:45.926Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23733</link>
      <description>A stored XSS vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed the injection of arbitrary attributes. This injection was blocked by Github's Content Security Policy (CSP). This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.6 and was fixed in versions 3.3.11, 3.4.6 and 3.5.3. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23733|2024-08-03T03:51:45.926Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 16:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23737|2024-08-03T03:51:46.055Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23737</link>
      <description>An improper privilege management vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed users with improper privileges to create or delete pages via the API. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to be added to an organization's repo with write permissions. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.7 and was fixed in versions 3.2.20, 3.3.15, 3.4.10, 3.5.7, and 3.6.3. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23737|2024-08-03T03:51:46.055Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23734|2024-08-03T03:51:45.942Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23734</link>
      <description>A deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that could potentially lead to remote code execution on the SVNBridge. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to gain access via a server-side request forgery (SSRF) that would let an attacker control the data being deserialized. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to v3.6 and was fixed in versions 3.5.3, 3.4.6, 3.3.11, and 3.2.16. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23734|2024-08-03T03:51:45.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23739|2024-08-03T03:51:46.013Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23739</link>
      <description>An incorrect authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server, allowing for escalation of privileges in GraphQL API requests from GitHub Apps. This vulnerability allowed an app installed on an organization to gain access to and modify most organization-level resources that are not tied to a repository regardless of granted permissions, such as users and organization-wide projects. Resources associated with repositories were not impacted, such as repository file content, repository-specific projects, issues, or pull requests. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.7.1 and was fixed in versions 3.3.16, 3.4.11, 3.5.8, 3.6.4, 3.7.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23739|2024-08-03T03:51:46.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23741|2024-08-03T03:51:46.025Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23741</link>
      <description>An incorrect authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed a scoped user-to-server token to escalate to full admin/owner privileges. An attacker would require an account with admin access to install a malicious GitHub App. This vulnerability was fixed in versions 3.3.17, 3.4.12, 3.5.9, and 3.6.5. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23741|2024-08-03T03:51:46.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23738|2024-08-03T03:51:46.239Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23738</link>
      <description>An improper cache key vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an unauthorized actor to access private repository files through a public repository. To exploit this, an actor would need to already be authorized on the GitHub Enterprise Server instance, be able to create a public repository, and have a site administrator visit a specially crafted URL. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.6 and was fixed in versions 3.2.20, 3.3.15, 3.4.10, 3.5.7, 3.6.3. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23738|2024-08-03T03:51:46.239Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2443|2024-08-01T19:11:53.575Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2443</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when configuring GeoJSON settings. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.8.17, 3.9.12, 3.10.9, 3.11.7, and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2443|2024-08-01T19:11:53.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 23:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5566|2024-07-22T19:47:55.185Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5566</link>
      <description>An improper privilege management vulnerability allowed users to migrate private repositories without having appropriate scopes defined on the related Personal Access Token. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5566|2024-07-22T19:47:55.185Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5816|2024-07-18T15:14:00.162Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5816</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed a suspended GitHub App to retain access to the repository via a scoped user access token. This was only exploitable in public repositories while private repositories were not impacted. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.9.17, 3.10.14, 3.11.12, 3.12.6, 3.13.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5816|2024-07-18T15:14:00.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6336|2024-07-17T15:39:07.466Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6336</link>
      <description>A Security Misconfiguration vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed sensitive information disclosure to unauthorized users in GitHub Enterprise Server by exploiting organization ruleset feature. This attack required an organization member to explicitly change the visibility of a dependent repository from private to public. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6336|2024-07-17T15:39:07.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5566|2024-07-16T21:26:46.902Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5566</link>
      <description>An improper privilege management vulnerability allowed users to migrate private repositories without having appropriate scopes defined on the related Personal Access Token. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5566|2024-07-16T21:26:46.902Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5815|2024-07-16T21:26:57.404Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5815</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed write operations on a victim-owned repository by exploiting incorrect request types. A mitigating factor is that the attacker would have to be a trusted GitHub Enterprise Server user, and the victim would have to visit a tag in the attacker's fork of their own repository. vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17.


 This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5815|2024-07-16T21:26:57.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6336|2024-07-16T21:27:07.393Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6336</link>
      <description>A Security Misconfiguration vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed sensitive information disclosure to unauthorized users in GitHub Enterprise Server by exploiting organization ruleset feature. This attack required an organization member to explicitly change the visibility of a dependent repository from private to public. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6336|2024-07-16T21:27:07.393Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5795|2024-07-16T21:26:54.243Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5795</link>
      <description>A Denial of Service vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to cause unbounded resource exhaustion by sending a large payload to the Git server. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5795|2024-07-16T21:26:54.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6395|2024-07-16T21:27:10.901Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6395</link>
      <description>An exposure of sensitive information vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server would allow an attacker to enumerate the names of private repositories that utilize deploy keys. This vulnerability did not allow unauthorized access to any repository content besides the name. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6395|2024-07-16T21:27:10.901Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5817|2024-07-16T21:27:03.820Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5817</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed read access to issue content via GitHub Projects. This was only exploitable in internal repositories and required the attacker to have access to the corresponding project board. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5817|2024-07-16T21:27:03.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5816|2024-07-16T21:27:00.491Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5816</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed a suspended GitHub App to retain access to the repository via a scoped user access token. This was only exploitable in public repositories while private repositories were not impacted. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.9.17, 3.10.14, 3.11.12, 3.12.6, 3.13.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5816|2024-07-16T21:27:00.491Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5746|2024-06-20T21:31:37.111Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5746</link>
      <description>A Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with the Site Administrator role to gain arbitrary code execution capability on the GitHub Enterprise Server instance. Exploitation required authenticated access to GitHub Enterprise Server as a user with the Site Administrator role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.12.5, 3.11.11, 3.10.13, and 3.9.16. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5746|2024-06-20T21:31:37.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 21:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2443|2024-03-20T23:04:23.899Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2443</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with an editor role in the Management Console to gain admin SSH access to the appliance when configuring GeoJSON settings. Exploitation of this vulnerability required access to the GitHub Enterprise Server instance and access to the Management Console with the editor role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.8.17, 3.9.12, 3.10.9, 3.11.7, and 3.12.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2443|2024-03-20T23:04:23.899Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 23:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5746|2024-06-24T15:08:21.753Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5746</link>
      <description>A Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with the Site Administrator role to gain arbitrary code execution capability on the GitHub Enterprise Server instance. Exploitation required authenticated access to GitHub Enterprise Server as a user with the Site Administrator role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.12.5, 3.11.11, 3.10.13, and 3.9.16. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5746|2024-06-24T15:08:21.753Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 21:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6395|2024-07-17T14:16:58.488Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6395</link>
      <description>An exposure of sensitive information vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server would allow an attacker to enumerate the names of private repositories that utilize deploy keys. This vulnerability did not allow unauthorized access to any repository content besides the name. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6395|2024-07-17T14:16:58.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5817|2024-07-17T19:31:17.566Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5817</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed read access to issue content via GitHub Projects. This was only exploitable in internal repositories and required the attacker to have access to the corresponding project board. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5817|2024-07-17T19:31:17.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5795|2024-07-22T14:40:29.964Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5795</link>
      <description>A Denial of Service vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to cause unbounded resource exhaustion by sending a large payload to the Git server. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5795|2024-07-22T14:40:29.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5815|2024-07-24T20:48:10.911Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5815</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed write operations on a victim-owned repository by exploiting incorrect request types. A mitigating factor is that the attacker would have to be a trusted GitHub Enterprise Server user, and the victim would have to visit a tag in the attacker's fork of their own repository. vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17.


 This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5815|2024-07-24T20:48:10.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6395|2024-08-01T21:41:03.389Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6395</link>
      <description>An exposure of sensitive information vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server would allow an attacker to enumerate the names of private repositories that utilize deploy keys. This vulnerability did not allow unauthorized access to any repository content besides the name. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6395|2024-08-01T21:41:03.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5746|2024-08-01T21:18:07.077Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5746</link>
      <description>A Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker with the Site Administrator role to gain arbitrary code execution capability on the GitHub Enterprise Server instance. Exploitation required authenticated access to GitHub Enterprise Server as a user with the Site Administrator role. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.13 and was fixed in versions 3.12.5, 3.11.11, 3.10.13, and 3.9.16. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5746|2024-08-01T21:18:07.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 21:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5817|2024-08-01T21:25:02.832Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5817</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed read access to issue content via GitHub Projects. This was only exploitable in internal repositories and required the attacker to have access to the corresponding project board. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5817|2024-08-01T21:25:02.832Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5566|2024-08-01T21:18:06.292Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5566</link>
      <description>An improper privilege management vulnerability allowed users to migrate private repositories without having appropriate scopes defined on the related Personal Access Token. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5566|2024-08-01T21:18:06.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6336|2024-08-01T21:33:05.420Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6336</link>
      <description>A Security Misconfiguration vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed sensitive information disclosure to unauthorized users in GitHub Enterprise Server by exploiting organization ruleset feature. This attack required an organization member to explicitly change the visibility of a dependent repository from private to public. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6336|2024-08-01T21:33:05.420Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5816|2024-08-01T21:25:02.923Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5816</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed a suspended GitHub App to retain access to the repository via a scoped user access token. This was only exploitable in public repositories while private repositories were not impacted. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in versions 3.9.17, 3.10.14, 3.11.12, 3.12.6, 3.13.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5816|2024-08-01T21:25:02.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5815|2024-08-01T21:25:02.739Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5815</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed write operations on a victim-owned repository by exploiting incorrect request types. A mitigating factor is that the attacker would have to be a trusted GitHub Enterprise Server user, and the victim would have to visit a tag in the attacker's fork of their own repository. vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17.


 This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5815|2024-08-01T21:25:02.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5795|2024-08-01T21:25:01.600Z -- github -- github%20enterprise%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5795</link>
      <description>A Denial of Service vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to cause unbounded resource exhaustion by sending a large payload to the Git server. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.14 and was fixed in version 3.13.1, 3.12.6, 3.11.12, 3.10.14, and 3.9.17. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5795|2024-08-01T21:25:01.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
