<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for BMC -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bmc/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for BMC -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 22:23:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1604|2024-10-10T15:36:14.867Z -- bmc -- control-m
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1604</link>
      <description>Improper authorization in the report management and creation module of BMC Control-M branches 9.0.20 and 9.0.21 allows logged-in users to read and make unauthorized changes to any reports available within the application, even without proper permissions. The attacker must know the unique identifier of the report they want to manipulate.







Fix for 9.0.20 branch was released in version 9.0.20.238. Fix for 9.0.21 branch was released in version 9.0.21.201.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1604|2024-10-10T15:36:14.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 09:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1605|2024-10-10T15:36:16.283Z -- bmc -- control-m
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1605</link>
      <description>BMC Control-M  branches 9.0.20 and 9.0.21 upon user login load all Dynamic Link Libraries (DLL)  from a directory that grants Write and Read permissions to all users. Leveraging it leads to loading of a potentially malicious libraries, which will execute with the application's privileges. 





Fix for 9.0.20 branch was released in version 9.0.20.238. Fix for 9.0.21 branch was released in version 9.0.21.201.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1605|2024-10-10T15:36:16.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 09:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35001|2024-08-04T00:26:55.843Z -- bmc -- track-it%21</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35001</link>
      <description>BMC Track-It! GetData Missing Authorization Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of BMC Track-It!. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the GetData endpoint. The issue results from the lack of authorization prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-14527.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35001|2024-08-04T00:26:55.843Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35002|2024-08-04T00:26:55.723Z -- bmc -- track-it%21</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35002</link>
      <description>BMC Track-It! Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of BMC Track-It!. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of email attachments. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can allow the upload of arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-14122.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35002|2024-08-04T00:26:55.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
