<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for BMC -- Track-It!</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bmc/track-it%21.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for BMC -- Track-It!</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:22:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24047|2024-08-03T03:59:23.594Z -- bmc -- track-it%21
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24047</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of BMC Track-It! 20.21.01.102. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the authorization of HTTP requests. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-14618.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24047|2024-08-03T03:59:23.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 19:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35864|2024-08-03T09:44:22.081Z -- bmc -- track-it%21
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35864</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of BMC Track-It! 20.21.02.109. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the GetPopupSubQueryDetails endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-16690.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35864|2024-08-03T09:44:22.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 15:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35865|2024-08-03T09:44:22.099Z -- bmc -- track-it%21
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35865</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of BMC Track-It! 20.21.2.109. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the authorization of HTTP requests. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-16709.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35865|2024-08-03T09:44:22.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 15:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
