<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for ThemeNectar -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/themenectar/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for ThemeNectar -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-3812|2024-05-18T05:40:03.418Z -- ThemeNectar -- Salient Core
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3812</link><description>The Salient Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.7 via the 'nectar_icon' shortcode 'icon_linea' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level and above permissions, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where php file type can be uploaded and included.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3812|2024-05-18T05:40:03.418Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 05:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3810|2024-05-18T05:40:02.930Z -- ThemeNectar -- Salient Shortcodes
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3810</link><description>The Salient Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.3 via the 'icon' shortcode 'image' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level and above permissions, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where php file type can be uploaded and included.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3810|2024-05-18T05:40:02.930Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 05:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3811|2024-05-18T05:40:02.452Z -- ThemeNectar -- Salient Shortcodes
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3811</link><description>The Salient Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'icon' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3811|2024-05-18T05:40:02.452Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 05:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>