<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for imartinez -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/imartinez/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for imartinez -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-3403|2024-05-16T09:03:47.440Z -- imartinez -- imartinez/privategpt
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3403</link><description>imartinez/privategpt version 0.2.0 is vulnerable to a local file inclusion vulnerability that allows attackers to read arbitrary files from the filesystem. By manipulating file upload functionality to ingest arbitrary local files, attackers can exploit the 'Search in Docs' feature or query the AI to retrieve or disclose the contents of any file on the system. This vulnerability could lead to various impacts, including but not limited to remote code execution by obtaining private SSH keys, unauthorized access to private files, source code disclosure facilitating further attacks, and exposure of configuration files.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3403|2024-05-16T09:03:47.440Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:03:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3851|2024-05-16T09:03:44.053Z -- imartinez -- imartinez/privategpt
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3851</link><description>A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the 'imartinez/privategpt' repository due to improper validation of file uploads. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by uploading malicious HTML files, such as those containing JavaScript payloads, which are then executed in the context of the victim's session when accessed. This could lead to the execution of arbitrary JavaScript code in the context of the user's browser session, potentially resulting in phishing attacks or other malicious actions. The vulnerability affects the latest version of the repository.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3851|2024-05-16T09:03:44.053Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:03:44 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>