<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for UpThemes -- Theme DesignFolio Plus</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/upthemes/theme%20designfolio%20plus.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for UpThemes -- Theme DesignFolio Plus</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:24:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-10087|2024-08-06T08:58:26.441Z -- upthemes -- theme%20designfolio%20plus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10087</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability has been found in UpThemes Theme DesignFolio Plus 1.2 on WordPress and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is 53f6ae62878076f99718e5feb589928e83c879a9. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-221809 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.
In UpThemes Theme DesignFolio Plus 1.2 für WordPress wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode. Mittels dem Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Der Patch wird als 53f6ae62878076f99718e5feb589928e83c879a9 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-10087|2024-08-06T08:58:26.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 14:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
