<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for hap-wi -- roxy-wi</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/hap-wi/roxy-wi.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for hap-wi -- roxy-wi</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:22:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25803|2024-08-02T11:32:12.453Z -- hap-wi -- roxy-wi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25803</link>
      <description>Roxy-WI is a Web interface for managing Haproxy, Nginx, Apache, and Keepalived servers. Versions prior to 6.3.5.0 have a directory traversal vulnerability that allows the inclusion of server-side files. This issue is fixed in version 6.3.5.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25803|2024-08-02T11:32:12.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25802|2024-08-02T11:32:12.516Z -- hap-wi -- roxy-wi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25802</link>
      <description>Roxy-WI is a Web interface for managing Haproxy, Nginx, Apache, and Keepalived servers. Versions prior to 6.3.6.0 don't correctly neutralize `dir/../filename` sequences, such as `/etc/nginx/../passwd`, allowing an actor to gain information about a server. Version 6.3.6.0 has a patch for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25802|2024-08-02T11:32:12.516Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 19:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29004|2024-08-02T13:51:39.014Z -- hap-wi -- roxy-wi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29004</link>
      <description>hap-wi/roxy-wi is a web interface for managing Haproxy, Nginx, Apache and Keepalived servers. A Path Traversal vulnerability was found in the current version of Roxy-WI (6.3.9.0 at the moment of writing this report). The vulnerability can be exploited via an HTTP request to /app/options.py and the config_file_name parameter. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker with user level privileges to obtain the content of arbitrary files on the file server within the scope of what the server process has access to. The root-cause of the vulnerability lies in the get_config function of the /app/modules/config/config.py file, which only checks for relative path traversal, but still allows to read files from absolute locations passed via the config_file_name parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29004|2024-08-02T13:51:39.014Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 18:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25804|2024-08-02T11:32:12.457Z -- hap-wi -- roxy-wi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25804</link>
      <description>Roxy-WI is a Web interface for managing Haproxy, Nginx, Apache, and Keepalived servers. Versions prior to 6.3.5.0 have a limited path traversal vulnerability. An SSH key can be saved into an unintended location, for example the `/tmp` folder using a payload `../../../../../tmp/test111_dev`. This issue has been fixed in version 6.3.5.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25804|2024-08-02T11:32:12.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 17:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
