<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Medtronic -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/medtronic/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Medtronic -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6540|2024-08-04T20:23:21.563Z -- medtronic -- conexus%20radio%20frequency%20telemetry%20protocol
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6540</link>
      <description>The Conexus telemetry protocol utilized within Medtronic MyCareLink Monitor versions 24950 and 24952, CareLink Monitor version 2490C, CareLink 2090 Programmer, Amplia CRT-D, Claria CRT-D, Compia CRT-D, Concerto CRT-D, Concerto II CRT-D, Consulta CRT-D, Evera ICD, Maximo II CRT-D and ICD, Mirro ICD, Nayamed ND ICD, Primo ICD, Protecta ICD and CRT-D, Secura ICD, Virtuoso ICD, Virtuoso II ICD, Visia AF ICD, and Viva CRT-D does not implement encryption. An attacker with adjacent short-range access to a target product can listen to communications, including the transmission of sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6540|2024-08-04T20:23:21.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 17:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6538|2024-08-04T20:23:21.992Z -- medtronic -- medtronic%20conexus%20radio%20frequency%20telemetry%20protocol
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6538</link>
      <description>The Conexus telemetry protocol utilized within Medtronic MyCareLink Monitor versions 24950 and 24952, CareLink Monitor version 2490C, CareLink 2090 Programmer, Amplia CRT-D, Claria CRT-D, Compia CRT-D, Concerto CRT-D, Concerto II CRT-D, Consulta CRT-D, Evera ICD, Maximo II CRT-D and ICD, Mirro ICD, Nayamed ND ICD, Primo ICD, Protecta ICD and CRT-D, Secura ICD, Virtuoso ICD, Virtuoso II ICD, Visia AF ICD, and Viva CRT-D does not implement authentication or authorization. An attacker with adjacent short-range access to an affected product, in situations where the product’s radio is turned on, can inject, replay, modify, and/or intercept data within the telemetry communication. This communication protocol provides the ability to read and write memory values to affected implanted cardiac devices; therefore, an attacker could exploit this communication protocol to change memory in the implanted cardiac device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6538|2024-08-04T20:23:21.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 21:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
