<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for collizo4sky -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/collizo4sky/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for collizo4sky -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1409|2024-03-13T15:26:49.245Z -- collizo4sky -- Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1409</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's [reg-select-role] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.15.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1409|2024-03-13T15:26:49.245Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1408|2024-02-20T18:56:33.858Z -- collizo4sky -- Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1408</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's edit-profile-text-box shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.14.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as 'type'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1408|2024-02-20T18:56:33.858Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1570|2024-02-20T18:56:30.068Z -- collizo4sky -- Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1570</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's login-password shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.14.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1570|2024-02-20T18:56:30.068Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1046|2024-02-05T21:21:51.417Z -- collizo4sky -- Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1046</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin 'reg-number-field' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.14.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1046|2024-02-05T21:21:51.417Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1519|2024-02-20T18:56:30.987Z -- collizo4sky -- Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1519</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'name' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.14.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This requires a member listing page to be active and using the Gerbera theme.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1519|2024-02-20T18:56:30.987Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1535|2024-03-13T15:26:43.832Z -- collizo4sky -- Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1535</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 4.15.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1535|2024-03-13T15:26:43.832Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1806|2024-03-13T15:27:17.016Z -- collizo4sky -- Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1806</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 4.15.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1806|2024-03-13T15:27:17.016Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3210|2024-04-10T05:32:23.418Z -- collizo4sky -- Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3210</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'reg-single-checkbox' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.15.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3210|2024-04-10T05:32:23.418Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 05:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2867|2024-05-02T16:52:04.809Z -- collizo4sky -- Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2867</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘title’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.15.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2867|2024-05-02T16:52:04.809Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2861|2024-05-23T09:32:32.877Z -- collizo4sky -- Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2861</link><description>The ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ProfilePress User Panel widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.15.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2861|2024-05-23T09:32:32.877Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 09:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>