<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Xiamen Four Letter -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/xiamen%20four%20letter/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Xiamen Four Letter -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:26:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3805|2024-08-02T07:08:50.356Z -- xiamen%20four%20letter -- video%20surveillance%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3805</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Xiamen Four Letter Video Surveillance Management System up to 20230712. This issue affects some unknown processing in the library UserInfoAction.class of the component Login. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-235073 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Xiamen Four Letter Video Surveillance Management System bis 20230712 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess in der Bibliothek UserInfoAction.class der Komponente Login. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper authorization-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3805|2024-08-02T07:08:50.356Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 01:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
