<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dominion Voting Systems -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dominion%20voting%20systems/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dominion Voting Systems -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 11:20:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1740|2024-08-03T00:16:58.942Z -- dominion%20voting%20systems -- imagecast%20x%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1740</link>
      <description>The tested version of Dominion Voting Systems ImageCast X’s on-screen application hash display feature, audit log export, and application export functionality rely on self-attestation mechanisms. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to disguise malicious applications on a device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1740|2024-08-03T00:16:58.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1746|2024-08-03T00:16:59.794Z -- dominion%20voting%20systems -- imagecast%20x%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1746</link>
      <description>The authentication mechanism used by poll workers to administer voting using the tested version of Dominion Voting Systems ImageCast X can expose cryptographic secrets used to protect election information. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to gain access to sensitive information and perform privileged actions, potentially affecting other election equipment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1746|2024-08-03T00:16:59.794Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1747|2024-08-03T00:16:58.972Z -- dominion%20voting%20systems -- imagecast%20x%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1747</link>
      <description>The authentication mechanism used by voters to activate a voting session on the tested version of Dominion Voting Systems ImageCast X is susceptible to forgery. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to print an arbitrary number of ballots without authorization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1747|2024-08-03T00:16:58.972Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1745|2024-08-03T00:16:59.678Z -- dominion%20voting%20systems -- imagecast%20x%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1745</link>
      <description>The authentication mechanism used by technicians on the tested version of Dominion Voting Systems ImageCast X is susceptible to forgery. An attacker with physical access may use this to gain administrative privileges on a device and install malicious code or perform arbitrary administrative actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1745|2024-08-03T00:16:59.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1739|2024-08-03T00:16:58.894Z -- dominion%20voting%20systems -- imagecast%20x%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1739</link>
      <description>The tested version of Dominion Voting Systems ImageCast X does not validate application signatures to a trusted root certificate. Use of a trusted root certificate ensures software installed on a device is traceable to, or verifiable against, a cryptographic key provided by the manufacturer to detect tampering. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to install malicious code, which could also be spread to other vulnerable ImageCast X devices via removable media.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1739|2024-08-03T00:16:58.894Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1741|2024-08-03T00:16:59.822Z -- dominion%20voting%20systems -- imagecast%20x%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1741</link>
      <description>The tested version of Dominion Voting Systems ImageCast X has a Terminal Emulator application which could be leveraged by an attacker to gain elevated privileges on a device and/or install malicious code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1741|2024-08-03T00:16:59.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1742|2024-08-03T00:16:59.804Z -- dominion%20voting%20systems -- imagecast%20x%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1742</link>
      <description>The tested version of Dominion Voting Systems ImageCast X allows for rebooting into Android Safe Mode, which allows an attacker to directly access the operating system. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges on a device and/or install malicious code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1742|2024-08-03T00:16:59.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
