<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for KylinSoft -- kylin-software-properties</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/kylinsoft/kylin-software-properties.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for KylinSoft -- kylin-software-properties</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 14:22:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3096|2024-08-02T06:48:07.114Z -- kylinsoft -- kylin-software-properties
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3096</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in KylinSoft kylin-software-properties on KylinOS. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function changedSource. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 0.0.1-130 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-230686 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In KylinSoft kylin-software-properties für KylinOS wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft die Funktion changedSource. Mittels dem Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper access controls-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs hat dabei lokal zu erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 0.0.1-130 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3096|2024-08-02T06:48:07.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 05:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3097|2024-08-02T06:48:07.104Z -- kylinsoft -- kylin-software-properties
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3097</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in KylinSoft kylin-software-properties on KylinOS. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function setMainSource. The manipulation leads to os command injection. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 0.0.1-130 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-230687. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in KylinSoft kylin-software-properties für KylinOS ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion setMainSource. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden muss der Angriff lokal. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 0.0.1-130 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3097|2024-08-02T06:48:07.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 06:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
