<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for KylinSoft -- youker-assistant</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/kylinsoft/youker-assistant.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for KylinSoft -- youker-assistant</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 16:25:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2091|2024-08-02T06:12:20.331Z -- kylinsoft -- youker-assistant
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2091</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in KylinSoft youker-assistant on KylinOS. Affected by this vulnerability is the function adjust_cpufreq_scaling_governer. The manipulation leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.1.4.13 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-226099.
In KylinSoft youker-assistant für KylinOS wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion adjust_cpufreq_scaling_governer. Mittels dem Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 3.1.4.13 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2091|2024-08-02T06:12:20.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 08:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3098|2024-08-02T06:48:07.044Z -- kylinsoft -- youker-assistant
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3098</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in KylinSoft youker-assistant on KylinOS. Affected is the function restore_all_sound_file. The manipulation leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.0.2-0kylin6k70-23 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-230688. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in KylinSoft youker-assistant für KylinOS entdeckt. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion restore_all_sound_file. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine path traversal: '../filedir'-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff hat dabei lokal zu erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 3.0.2-0kylin6k70-23 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3098|2024-08-02T06:48:07.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 06:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3099|2024-08-02T06:48:07.170Z -- kylinsoft -- youker-assistant
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3099</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in KylinSoft youker-assistant on KylinOS. Affected by this vulnerability is the function delete_file in the library dbus.SystemBus of the component Arbitrary File Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.0.2-0kylin6k70-23 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-230689 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In KylinSoft youker-assistant für KylinOS wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion delete_file in der Bibliothek dbus.SystemBus der Komponente Arbitrary File Handler. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper access controls-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 3.0.2-0kylin6k70-23 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3099|2024-08-02T06:48:07.170Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 07:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
