<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for asterisk -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/asterisk/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for asterisk -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49294|2023-12-14T19:40:46.157Z -- asterisk -- asterisk
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-49294</link>
      <description>Asterisk is an open source private branch exchange and telephony toolkit. In Asterisk prior to versions 18.20.1, 20.5.1, and 21.0.1, as well as certified-asterisk prior to 18.9-cert6, it is possible to read any arbitrary file even when the `live_dangerously` is not enabled. This allows arbitrary files to be read. Asterisk versions 18.20.1, 20.5.1, and 21.0.1, as well as certified-asterisk prior to 18.9-cert6, contain a fix for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49294|2023-12-14T19:40:46.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 19:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49786|2023-12-14T19:47:46.306Z -- asterisk -- asterisk
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-49786</link>
      <description>Asterisk is an open source private branch exchange and telephony toolkit. In Asterisk prior to versions 18.20.1, 20.5.1, and 21.0.1; as well as certified-asterisk prior to 18.9-cert6; Asterisk is susceptible to a DoS due to a race condition in the hello handshake phase of the DTLS protocol when handling DTLS-SRTP for media setup. This attack can be done continuously, thus denying new DTLS-SRTP encrypted calls during the attack. Abuse of this vulnerability may lead to a massive Denial of Service on vulnerable Asterisk servers for calls that rely on DTLS-SRTP. Commit d7d7764cb07c8a1872804321302ef93bf62cba05 contains a fix, which is part of versions 18.20.1, 20.5.1, 21.0.1, amd 18.9-cert6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49786|2023-12-14T19:47:46.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 19:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37457|2023-12-14T19:43:30.945Z -- asterisk -- asterisk
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37457</link>
      <description>Asterisk is an open source private branch exchange and telephony toolkit. In Asterisk versions 18.20.0 and prior, 20.5.0 and prior, and 21.0.0; as well as ceritifed-asterisk 18.9-cert5 and prior, the 'update' functionality of the PJSIP_HEADER dialplan function can exceed the available buffer space for storing the new value of a header. By doing so this can overwrite memory or cause a crash. This is not externally exploitable, unless dialplan is explicitly written to update a header based on data from an outside source. If the 'update' functionality is not used the vulnerability does not occur. A patch is available at commit a1ca0268254374b515fa5992f01340f7717113fa.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37457|2023-12-14T19:43:30.945Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 19:43:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-35190|2024-05-17T16:55:41.346Z -- asterisk -- asterisk
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-35190</link>
      <description>Asterisk is an open source private branch exchange and telephony toolkit. After upgrade to 18.23.0, ALL unauthorized SIP requests are identified as PJSIP Endpoint of local asterisk server. This vulnerability is fixed in 18.23.1, 20.8.1, and 21.3.1.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-35190|2024-05-17T16:55:41.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 16:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
