<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Splunk -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/splunk/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Splunk -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 23:22:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22934|2024-06-18T18:36:23.394Z -- splunk -- splunk%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22934</link>
      <description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 8.1.13, 8.2.10, and 9.0.4, the ‘pivot’ search processing language (SPL) command lets a search bypass SPL safeguards for risky commands using a saved search job. The vulnerability requires an authenticated user to craft the saved job and a higher privileged user to initiate a request within their browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22934|2024-06-18T18:36:23.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 17:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23677|2024-04-10T00:52:52.398Z -- splunk -- splunk%20enterprise</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23677</link>
      <description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.0.8, the Splunk RapidDiag utility discloses server responses from external applications in a log file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23677|2024-04-10T00:52:52.398Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 20:37:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23676|2024-04-10T00:52:46.949Z -- splunk -- splunk%20enterprise</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23676</link>
      <description>In Splunk versions below 9.0.8 and 9.1.3, the “mrollup” SPL command lets a low-privileged user view metrics on an index that they do not have permission to view. This vulnerability requires user interaction from a high-privileged user to exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23676|2024-04-10T00:52:46.949Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 20:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23675|2024-04-10T00:52:46.277Z -- splunk -- splunk%20enterprise</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23675</link>
      <description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.0.8 and 9.1.3, Splunk app key value store (KV Store) improperly handles permissions for users that use the REST application programming interface (API). This can potentially result in the deletion of KV Store collections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23675|2024-04-10T00:52:46.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 20:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23678|2024-04-10T00:53:01.229Z -- splunk -- splunk%20enterprise</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23678</link>
      <description>In Splunk Enterprise for Windows versions below 9.0.8 and 9.1.3, Splunk Enterprise does not correctly sanitize path input data. This results in the unsafe deserialization of untrusted data from a separate disk partition on the machine. This vulnerability only affects Splunk Enterprise for Windows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23678|2024-04-10T00:53:01.229Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 20:37:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22164|2024-04-10T00:52:44.162Z -- splunk -- splunk%20enterprise%20security%20%28es%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22164</link>
      <description>In Splunk Enterprise Security (ES) versions below 7.1.2, an attacker can use investigation attachments to perform a denial of service (DoS) to the Investigation. The attachment endpoint does not properly limit the size of the request which lets an attacker cause the Investigation to become inaccessible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22164|2024-04-10T00:52:44.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 17:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22165|2024-06-04T17:52:31.592Z -- splunk -- splunk%20enterprise%20security%20%28es%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22165</link>
      <description>In Splunk Enterprise Security (ES) versions lower than 7.1.2, an attacker can create a malformed Investigation to perform a denial of service (DoS). The malformed investigation prevents the generation and rendering of the Investigations manager until it is deleted.&lt;br /&gt;The vulnerability requires an authenticated session and access to create an Investigation. It only affects the availability of the Investigations manager, but without the manager, the Investigations functionality becomes unusable for most users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22165|2024-06-04T17:52:31.592Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 17:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29945|2024-06-04T17:57:04.564Z -- splunk -- splunk%20enterprise</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29945</link>
      <description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.1, 9.1.4, and 9.0.9, the software potentially exposes authentication tokens during the token validation process. This exposure happens when either Splunk Enterprise runs in debug mode or the JsonWebToken component has been configured to log its activity at the DEBUG logging level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29945|2024-06-04T17:57:04.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29946|2024-04-10T00:52:43.370Z -- splunk -- splunk%20enterprise</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29946</link>
      <description>In Splunk Enterprise versions below 9.2.1, 9.1.4, and 9.0.9, the Dashboard Examples Hub lacks protections for risky SPL commands. This could let attackers bypass SPL safeguards for risky commands in the Hub. The vulnerability would require the attacker to phish the victim by tricking them into initiating a request within their browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29946|2024-04-10T00:52:43.370Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46230|2024-04-10T00:53:06.033Z -- splunk -- splunk%20add-on%20builder</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-46230</link>
      <description>In Splunk Add-on Builder versions below 4.1.4, the app writes sensitive information to internal log files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46230|2024-04-10T00:53:06.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46231|2024-04-10T00:52:45.608Z -- splunk -- splunk%20add-on%20builder</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-46231</link>
      <description>In Splunk Add-on Builder versions below 4.1.4, the application writes user session tokens to its internal log files when you visit the Splunk Add-on Builder or when you build or edit a custom app or add-on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46231|2024-04-10T00:52:45.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 17:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
