<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for aio-libs -- aiosmtpd</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/aio-libs/aiosmtpd.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for aio-libs -- aiosmtpd</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-27305|2024-03-12T20:29:54.592Z -- aio-libs -- aiosmtpd
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27305</link><description>aiosmtpd is a reimplementation of the Python stdlib smtpd.py based on asyncio. aiosmtpd is vulnerable to inbound SMTP smuggling. SMTP smuggling is a novel vulnerability based on not so novel interpretation differences of the SMTP protocol. By exploiting SMTP smuggling, an attacker may send smuggle/spoof e-mails with fake sender addresses, allowing advanced phishing attacks. This issue is also existed in other SMTP software like Postfix. With the right SMTP server constellation, an attacker can send spoofed e-mails to inbound/receiving aiosmtpd instances. This issue has been addressed in version 1.4.5. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27305|2024-03-12T20:29:54.592Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 20:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34083|2024-05-18T18:12:19.442Z -- aio-libs -- aiosmtpd
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34083</link><description>aiosmptd is  a reimplementation of the Python stdlib smtpd.py based on asyncio. Prior to version 1.4.6, servers based on aiosmtpd accept extra unencrypted commands after STARTTLS, treating them as if they came from inside the encrypted connection. This could be exploited by a man-in-the-middle attack. Version 1.4.6 contains a patch for the issue.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34083|2024-05-18T18:12:19.442Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 18:12:19 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>