<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Microsoft Corporation -- Browser</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/microsoft%20corporation/browser.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Microsoft Corporation -- Browser</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:22:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0133|2024-08-05T12:55:18.659Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0133</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way affected Microsoft scripting engines render when handling objects in memory in Microsoft browsers. These vulnerabilities could corrupt memory in such a way that an attacker could execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0010, CVE-2017-0015, CVE-2017-0032, CVE-2017-0035, CVE-2017-0067, CVE-2017-0070, CVE-2017-0071, CVE-2017-0094, CVE-2017-0131, CVE-2017-0132, CVE-2017-0134, CVE-2017-0136, CVE-2017-0137, CVE-2017-0138, CVE-2017-0141, CVE-2017-0150, and CVE-2017-0151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0133|2024-08-05T12:55:18.659Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0071|2024-08-05T12:55:17.627Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0071</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way affected Microsoft scripting engines render when handling objects in memory in Microsoft browsers. These vulnerabilities could corrupt memory in such a way that an attacker could execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0010, CVE-2017-0015, CVE-2017-0032, CVE-2017-0035, CVE-2017-0067, CVE-2017-0070, CVE-2017-0094, CVE-2017-0131, CVE-2017-0132, CVE-2017-0133, CVE-2017-0134, CVE-2017-0136, CVE-2017-0137, CVE-2017-0138, CVE-2017-0141, CVE-2017-0150, and CVE-2017-0151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0071|2024-08-05T12:55:17.627Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0033|2024-08-05T12:47:57.591Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0033</link>
      <description>Microsoft Internet Explorer 11 and Microsoft Edge allow remote attackers to spoof web content via a crafted web site, aka "Microsoft Browser Spoofing Vulnerability." This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0012 and CVE-2017-0069.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0033|2024-08-05T12:47:57.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0141|2024-08-05T12:55:18.336Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0141</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way affected Microsoft scripting engines render when handling objects in memory in Microsoft browsers. These vulnerabilities could corrupt memory in such a way that an attacker could execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0010, CVE-2017-0015, CVE-2017-0032, CVE-2017-0035, CVE-2017-0067, CVE-2017-0070, CVE-2017-0071, CVE-2017-0094, CVE-2017-0131, CVE-2017-0132, CVE-2017-0133, CVE-2017-0134, CVE-2017-0136, CVE-2017-0137, CVE-2017-0138, CVE-2017-0150, and CVE-2017-0151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0141|2024-08-05T12:55:18.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0094|2024-08-05T12:55:18.228Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0094</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way affected Microsoft scripting engines render when handling objects in memory in Microsoft browsers. These vulnerabilities could corrupt memory in such a way that an attacker could execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0010, CVE-2017-0015, CVE-2017-0032, CVE-2017-0035, CVE-2017-0067, CVE-2017-0070, CVE-2017-0071, CVE-2017-0094, CVE-2017-0131, CVE-2017-0132, CVE-2017-0133, CVE-2017-0134, CVE-2017-0136, CVE-2017-0137, CVE-2017-0138, CVE-2017-0141, CVE-2017-0150, and CVE-2017-0151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0094|2024-08-05T12:55:18.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0150|2024-08-05T12:55:18.862Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0150</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way affected Microsoft scripting engines render when handling objects in memory in Microsoft browsers. These vulnerabilities could corrupt memory in such a way that an attacker could execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0010, CVE-2017-0015, CVE-2017-0032, CVE-2017-0035, CVE-2017-0067, CVE-2017-0070, CVE-2017-0071, CVE-2017-0094, CVE-2017-0131, CVE-2017-0132, CVE-2017-0133, CVE-2017-0134, CVE-2017-0136, CVE-2017-0137, CVE-2017-0138, CVE-2017-0141, and CVE-2017-0151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0150|2024-08-05T12:55:18.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0067|2024-08-05T12:55:17.654Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0067</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way affected Microsoft scripting engines render when handling objects in memory in Microsoft browsers. These vulnerabilities could corrupt memory in such a way that an attacker could execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0010, CVE-2017-0015, CVE-2017-0032, CVE-2017-0035, CVE-2017-0070, CVE-2017-0071, CVE-2017-0094, CVE-2017-0131, CVE-2017-0132, CVE-2017-0133, CVE-2017-0134, CVE-2017-0136, CVE-2017-0137, CVE-2017-0138, CVE-2017-0141, CVE-2017-0150, and CVE-2017-0151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0067|2024-08-05T12:55:17.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0151|2024-08-05T12:55:18.679Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0151</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way affected Microsoft scripting engines render when handling objects in memory in Microsoft browsers. These vulnerabilities could corrupt memory in such a way that an attacker could execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0010, CVE-2017-0015, CVE-2017-0032, CVE-2017-0035, CVE-2017-0067, CVE-2017-0070, CVE-2017-0071, CVE-2017-0094, CVE-2017-0131, CVE-2017-0132, CVE-2017-0133, CVE-2017-0134, CVE-2017-0136, CVE-2017-0137, CVE-2017-0138, CVE-2017-0141, and CVE-2017-0150.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0151|2024-08-05T12:55:18.679Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0134|2024-08-05T12:55:18.708Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0134</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way affected Microsoft scripting engines render when handling objects in memory in Microsoft browsers. These vulnerabilities could corrupt memory in such a way that an attacker could execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0010, CVE-2017-0015, CVE-2017-0032, CVE-2017-0035, CVE-2017-0067, CVE-2017-0070, CVE-2017-0071, CVE-2017-0094, CVE-2017-0131, CVE-2017-0132, CVE-2017-0133, CVE-2017-0136, CVE-2017-0137, CVE-2017-0138, CVE-2017-0141, CVE-2017-0150, and CVE-2017-0151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0134|2024-08-05T12:55:18.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0131|2024-08-05T12:55:18.343Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0131</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way affected Microsoft scripting engines render when handling objects in memory in Microsoft browsers. These vulnerabilities could corrupt memory in such a way that an attacker could execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0010, CVE-2017-0015, CVE-2017-0032, CVE-2017-0035, CVE-2017-0067, CVE-2017-0070, CVE-2017-0071, CVE-2017-0094, CVE-2017-0132, CVE-2017-0133, CVE-2017-0134, CVE-2017-0136, CVE-2017-0137, CVE-2017-0138, CVE-2017-0141, CVE-2017-0150, and CVE-2017-0151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0131|2024-08-05T12:55:18.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0132|2024-08-05T12:55:18.302Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0132</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way affected Microsoft scripting engines render when handling objects in memory in Microsoft browsers. These vulnerabilities could corrupt memory in such a way that an attacker could execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0010, CVE-2017-0015, CVE-2017-0032, CVE-2017-0035, CVE-2017-0067, CVE-2017-0070, CVE-2017-0071, CVE-2017-0094, CVE-2017-0131, CVE-2017-0133, CVE-2017-0134, CVE-2017-0136, CVE-2017-0137, CVE-2017-0138, CVE-2017-0141, CVE-2017-0150, and CVE-2017-0151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0132|2024-08-05T12:55:18.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0009|2024-08-05T12:47:57.592Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0009</link>
      <description>Microsoft Internet Explorer 9 through 11 allow remote attackers to obtain sensitive information from process memory via a crafted web site, aka "Microsoft Browser Memory Corruption Vulnerability." This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0011, CVE-2017-0017, CVE-2017-0065, and CVE-2017-0068.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0009|2024-08-05T12:47:57.592Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0032|2024-08-05T12:47:57.599Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0032</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way affected Microsoft scripting engines render when handling objects in memory in Microsoft browsers. These vulnerabilities could corrupt memory in such a way that an attacker could execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0010, CVE-2017-0015, CVE-2017-0035, CVE-2017-0067, CVE-2017-0070, CVE-2017-0071, CVE-2017-0094, CVE-2017-0131, CVE-2017-0132, CVE-2017-0133, CVE-2017-0134, CVE-2017-0136, CVE-2017-0137, CVE-2017-0138, CVE-2017-0141, CVE-2017-0150, and CVE-2017-0151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0032|2024-08-05T12:47:57.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0015|2024-08-05T12:47:57.593Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0015</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way affected Microsoft scripting engines render when handling objects in memory in Microsoft browsers. These vulnerabilities could corrupt memory in such a way that an attacker could execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0010, CVE-2017-0032, CVE-2017-0035, CVE-2017-0067, CVE-2017-0070, CVE-2017-0071, CVE-2017-0094, CVE-2017-0131, CVE-2017-0132, CVE-2017-0133, CVE-2017-0134, CVE-2017-0136, CVE-2017-0137, CVE-2017-0138, CVE-2017-0141, CVE-2017-0150, and CVE-2017-0151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0015|2024-08-05T12:47:57.593Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0070|2024-08-05T12:55:17.689Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0070</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way affected Microsoft scripting engines render when handling objects in memory in Microsoft browsers. These vulnerabilities could corrupt memory in such a way that an attacker could execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0010, CVE-2017-0015, CVE-2017-0032, CVE-2017-0035, CVE-2017-0067, CVE-2017-0071, CVE-2017-0094, CVE-2017-0131, CVE-2017-0132, CVE-2017-0133, CVE-2017-0134, CVE-2017-0136, CVE-2017-0137, CVE-2017-0138, CVE-2017-0141, CVE-2017-0150, and CVE-2017-0151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0070|2024-08-05T12:55:17.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0137|2024-08-05T12:55:18.609Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0137</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way affected Microsoft scripting engines render when handling objects in memory in Microsoft browsers. These vulnerabilities could corrupt memory in such a way that an attacker could execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0010, CVE-2017-0015, CVE-2017-0032, CVE-2017-0035, CVE-2017-0067, CVE-2017-0070, CVE-2017-0071, CVE-2017-0094, CVE-2017-0131, CVE-2017-0132, CVE-2017-0133, CVE-2017-0134, CVE-2017-0136, CVE-2017-0138, CVE-2017-0141, CVE-2017-0150, and CVE-2017-0151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0137|2024-08-05T12:55:18.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0136|2024-08-05T12:55:18.569Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0136</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way affected Microsoft scripting engines render when handling objects in memory in Microsoft browsers. These vulnerabilities could corrupt memory in such a way that an attacker could execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0010, CVE-2017-0015, CVE-2017-0032, CVE-2017-0035, CVE-2017-0067, CVE-2017-0070, CVE-2017-0071, CVE-2017-0094, CVE-2017-0131, CVE-2017-0132, CVE-2017-0133, CVE-2017-0134, CVE-2017-0137, CVE-2017-0138, CVE-2017-0141, CVE-2017-0150, and CVE-2017-0151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0136|2024-08-05T12:55:18.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0138|2024-08-05T12:55:18.519Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0138</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way affected Microsoft scripting engines render when handling objects in memory in Microsoft browsers. These vulnerabilities could corrupt memory in such a way that an attacker could execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0010, CVE-2017-0015, CVE-2017-0032, CVE-2017-0035, CVE-2017-0067, CVE-2017-0070, CVE-2017-0071, CVE-2017-0094, CVE-2017-0131, CVE-2017-0132, CVE-2017-0133, CVE-2017-0134, CVE-2017-0136, CVE-2017-0137, CVE-2017-0141, CVE-2017-0150, and CVE-2017-0151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0138|2024-08-05T12:55:18.519Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0035|2024-08-05T12:47:57.706Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0035</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way affected Microsoft scripting engines render when handling objects in memory in Microsoft browsers. These vulnerabilities could corrupt memory in such a way that an attacker could execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0010, CVE-2017-0015, CVE-2017-0032, CVE-2017-0067, CVE-2017-0070, CVE-2017-0071, CVE-2017-0094, CVE-2017-0131, CVE-2017-0132, CVE-2017-0133, CVE-2017-0134, CVE-2017-0136, CVE-2017-0137, CVE-2017-0138, CVE-2017-0141, CVE-2017-0150, and CVE-2017-0151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0035|2024-08-05T12:47:57.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0010|2024-08-05T12:47:57.581Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0010</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the way affected Microsoft scripting engines render when handling objects in memory in Microsoft browsers. These vulnerabilities could corrupt memory in such a way that an attacker could execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could gain the same user rights as the current user. If the current user is logged on with administrative user rights, an attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could take control of an affected system. An attacker could then install programs; view, change, or delete data; or create new accounts with full user rights. This vulnerability is different from those described in CVE-2017-0015, CVE-2017-0032, CVE-2017-0035, CVE-2017-0067, CVE-2017-0070, CVE-2017-0071, CVE-2017-0094, CVE-2017-0131, CVE-2017-0132, CVE-2017-0133, CVE-2017-0134, CVE-2017-0136, CVE-2017-0137, CVE-2017-0138, CVE-2017-0141, CVE-2017-0150, and CVE-2017-0151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0010|2024-08-05T12:47:57.581Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
