<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Microsoft Corporation -- Microsoft Office</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/microsoft%20corporation/microsoft%20office.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Microsoft Corporation -- Microsoft Office</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 23:23:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8571|2024-09-17T01:27:01.271Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8571</link>
      <description>Microsoft Outlook 2007 SP3, Outlook 2010 SP2, Outlook 2013 SP1, Outlook 2013 RT SP1, and Outlook 2016 as packaged in Microsoft Office allows a security feature bypass vulnerability due to the way that it handles input, aka "Microsoft Office Outlook Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8571|2024-09-17T01:27:01.271Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8567|2024-09-17T02:37:14.596Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8567</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in Microsoft Excel for Mac 2011 when it fails to properly handle objects in memory, aka "Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8567|2024-09-17T02:37:14.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0852|2024-09-17T02:07:08.264Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0852</link>
      <description>Microsoft Outlook 2007 SP3, Microsoft Outlook 2010 SP2, Microsoft Outlook 2013 SP1 and RT SP1, Microsoft Outlook 2016, and Microsoft Office 2016 Click-to-Run (C2R) allow a remote code execution vulnerability, due to how Outlook handles objects in memory, aka "Microsoft Office Memory Corruption Vulnerability". This CVE is unique from CVE-2018-0851.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0852|2024-09-17T02:07:08.264Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8745|2024-09-17T00:16:20.906Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8745</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in Microsoft SharePoint Foundation 2013 Service Pack 1 when it does not properly sanitize a specially crafted web request to an affected SharePoint server, aka "Microsoft SharePoint Cross Site Scripting Vulnerability".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8745|2024-09-17T00:16:20.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8572|2024-09-17T03:17:51.767Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8572</link>
      <description>Microsoft Outlook 2007 SP3, Outlook 2010 SP2, Outlook 2013 SP1, Outlook 2013 RT SP1, and Outlook 2016 as packaged in Microsoft Office allows an information disclosure vulnerability due to the way that it discloses the contents of its memory, aka "Microsoft Office Outlook Information Disclosure Vulnerability".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8572|2024-09-17T03:17:51.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-11934|2024-09-17T01:45:53.284Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-11934</link>
      <description>Microsoft Office 2013 RT SP1, Microsoft Office 2013 SP1, and Microsoft Office 2016 allow an information disclosure vulnerability due to the way certain functions handle objects in memory, aka "Microsoft Office Information Disclosure Vulnerability".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-11934|2024-09-17T01:45:53.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0919|2024-09-17T00:41:29.189Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0919</link>
      <description>Microsoft Office 2010 SP2, 2013 SP1, and 2016, Microsoft Office 2016 Click-to-Run Microsoft Office 2016 for Mac, Microsoft Office Web Apps 2010 SP2, Microsoft Office Web Apps 2013 SP1, Microsoft SharePoint Enterprise Server 2013 SP1, Microsoft SharePoint Enterprise Server 2016, Microsoft SharePoint Server 2010 SP2, Microsoft Word 2010 SP2, Word 2013 SP1 and Microsoft Word 2016 allow an information disclosure vulnerability due to how variables are initialized, aka "Microsoft Office Information Disclosure Vulnerability".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0919|2024-09-17T00:41:29.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0853|2024-09-17T01:56:42.510Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0853</link>
      <description>Microsoft Office 2010 SP2, Microsoft Office 2013 SP1 and RT SP1, Microsoft Office 2016, and Microsoft Office 2016 Click-to-Run (C2R) allow an information disclosure vulnerability, due to how Office initializes the affected variable, aka "Microsoft Office Information Disclosure Vulnerability".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0853|2024-09-17T01:56:42.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8632|2024-09-17T04:20:07.139Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8632</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in Microsoft Excel 2010 Service Pack 2, Microsoft Excel 2013 Service Pack 1, Microsoft Excel 2013 RT Service Pack 1, Microsoft Excel 2016, Microsoft Office Web Apps 2013, Microsoft Excel for Mac 2011, Microsoft Excel 2016 for Mac, and Microsoft Office Compatibility Pack Service Pack 3, when they fail to properly handle objects in memory, aka "Microsoft Office Memory Corruption Vulnerability". This CVE ID is unique from CVE-2017-8630, CVE-2017-8631, and CVE-2017-8744.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8632|2024-09-17T04:20:07.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-11884|2024-09-17T01:25:49.834Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-11884</link>
      <description>Microsoft Excel 2016 Click-to-Run (C2R) allows an attacker to run arbitrary code in the context of the current user by failing to properly handle objects in memory, aka "Microsoft Office Memory Corruption Vulnerability". This CVE ID is unique from CVE-2017-11882.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-11884|2024-09-17T01:25:49.834Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8630|2024-09-17T04:09:51.106Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8630</link>
      <description>Microsoft Office 2016 allows a remote code execution vulnerability when it fails to properly handle objects in memory, aka "Microsoft Office Memory Corruption Vulnerability". This CVE ID is unique from CVE-2017-8631, CVE-2017-8632, and CVE-2017-8744.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8630|2024-09-17T04:09:51.106Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8743|2024-09-17T04:10:26.438Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8743</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in Microsoft PowerPoint 2016, Microsoft SharePoint Enterprise Server 2016, and Office Online Server when they fail to properly handle objects in memory, aka "PowerPoint Remote Code Execution Vulnerability". This CVE ID is unique from CVE-2017-8742.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8743|2024-09-17T04:10:26.438Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8742|2024-09-17T01:31:58.948Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8742</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in Microsoft PowerPoint 2007 Service Pack 3, Microsoft PowerPoint 2010 Service Pack 2, Microsoft PowerPoint 2013 Service Pack 1, Microsoft PowerPoint 2013 RT Service Pack 1, Microsoft PowerPoint 2016, Microsoft PowerPoint Viewer 2007, Microsoft SharePoint Server 2013 Service Pack 1, Microsoft SharePoint Enterprise Server 2016, Microsoft Office Web Apps 2010 Service Pack 2, and Microsoft Office Compatibility Pack Service Pack 3 when they fail to properly handle objects in memory, aka "PowerPoint Remote Code Execution Vulnerability". This CVE ID is unique from CVE-2017-8743.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8742|2024-09-17T01:31:58.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-11878|2024-09-17T04:05:13.407Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-11878</link>
      <description>Microsoft Excel 2007 Service Pack 3, Microsoft Excel 2010 Service Pack 2, Microsoft Excel 2013 Service Pack 1, Microsoft Excel 2013 RT Service Pack 1, Microsoft Excel 2016, Microsoft Office Compatibility Pack Service Pack 3, and Microsoft Excel Viewer 2007 Service Pack 3 allow an attacker to run arbitrary code in the context of the current user by failing to properly handle objects in memory, aka "Microsoft Excel Memory Corruption Vulnerability".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-11878|2024-09-17T04:05:13.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-11939|2024-09-17T00:20:35.710Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-11939</link>
      <description>Microsoft Office 2016 Click-to-Run (C2R) allows an information disclosure vulnerability due to the way Microsoft Office enforces DRM copy/paste permissions, aka "Microsoft Office Information Disclosure Vulnerability".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-11939|2024-09-17T00:20:35.710Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8744|2024-09-17T00:11:02.669Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8744</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in Excel Services, Microsoft Excel 2007 Service Pack 3, Microsoft Excel 2010 Service Pack 2, Microsoft Excel 2013 Service Pack 1, Microsoft Excel 2013 RT Service Pack 1, and Microsoft Excel 2016 when they fail to properly handle objects in memory, aka "Microsoft Office Memory Corruption Vulnerability". This CVE ID is unique from CVE-2017-8630, CVE-2017-8632, and CVE-2017-8731.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8744|2024-09-17T00:11:02.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8725|2024-09-17T02:51:37.810Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- microsoft%20office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8725</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in Microsoft Publisher 2007 Service Pack 3 and Microsoft Publisher 2010 Service Pack 2 when they fail to properly handle objects in memory, aka "Microsoft Office Publisher Remote Code Execution".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8725|2024-09-17T02:51:37.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
