<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Microsoft Corporation -- Windows Graphics Component</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/microsoft%20corporation/windows%20graphics%20component.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Microsoft Corporation -- Windows Graphics Component</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0038|2024-08-05T12:47:57.617Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- windows%20graphics%20component
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0038</link>
      <description>gdi32.dll in Graphics Device Interface (GDI) in Microsoft Windows Vista SP2, Windows Server 2008 SP2 and R2 SP1, Windows 7 SP1, Windows 8.1, Windows Server 2012 Gold and R2, Windows RT 8.1, and Windows 10 Gold, 1511, and 1607 allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information from process heap memory via a crafted EMF file, as demonstrated by an EMR_SETDIBITSTODEVICE record with modified Device Independent Bitmap (DIB) dimensions. NOTE: this vulnerability exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2016-3216, CVE-2016-3219, and/or CVE-2016-3220.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0038|2024-08-05T12:47:57.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0108|2024-08-05T12:55:18.713Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- windows%20graphics%20component
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0108</link>
      <description>The Windows Graphics Component in Microsoft Office 2007 SP3; 2010 SP2; and Word Viewer; Skype for Business 2016; Lync 2013 SP1; Lync 2010; Live Meeting 2007; Silverlight 5; Windows Vista SP2; Windows Server 2008 SP2 and R2 SP1; and Windows 7 SP1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted web site, aka "Graphics Component Remote Code Execution Vulnerability." This vulnerability is different from that described in CVE-2017-0014.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0108|2024-08-05T12:55:18.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0014|2024-08-05T12:47:57.574Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- windows%20graphics%20component
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0014</link>
      <description>The Windows Graphics Component in Microsoft Office 2010 SP2; Windows Server 2008 R2 SP1; Windows 7 SP1; Windows 8.1; Windows Server 2012 Gold and R2; Windows RT 8.1; Windows 10 Gold, 1511, and 1607; and Windows Server 2016 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted web site, aka "Windows Graphics Component Remote Code Execution Vulnerability." This vulnerability is different from that described in CVE-2017-0108.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0014|2024-08-05T12:47:57.574Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8720|2024-08-05T16:41:24.279Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- windows%20graphics%20component
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8720</link>
      <description>The Microsoft Windows graphics component on Microsoft Windows Server 2008 SP2 and R2 SP1, Windows 7 SP1, Windows 8.1, Windows Server 2012 Gold and R2, Windows RT 8.1, Windows 10 Gold, 1511, 1607, and 1703, and Windows Server 2016 allows an elevation of privilege vulnerability when the Win32k component fails to properly handle objects in memory, aka "Win32k Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability". This CVE ID is unique from CVE-2017-8675.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8720|2024-08-05T16:41:24.279Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0155|2024-08-05T12:55:19.127Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- windows%20graphics%20component
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0155</link>
      <description>The Graphics component in the kernel in Microsoft Windows Vista SP2; Windows Server 2008 SP2 and R2 SP1; and Windows 7 SP1 allows local users to gain privileges via a crafted application, aka "Windows Graphics Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0155|2024-08-05T12:55:19.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0156|2024-08-05T12:55:19.121Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- windows%20graphics%20component
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0156</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability exists in Windows 7, Windows 8.1, Windows RT 8.1, Windows 10, Windows Server 2008 R2, Windows Server 2012, Windows Server 2012 R2, and Windows Server 2016 when the Microsoft Graphics Component fails to properly handle objects in memory, aka "Windows Graphics Component Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0156|2024-08-05T12:55:19.121Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
