<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Microsoft Corporation -- Windows COM</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/microsoft%20corporation/windows%20com.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Microsoft Corporation -- Windows COM</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:22:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0298|2024-08-05T13:03:55.877Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- windows%20com
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0298</link>
      <description>A DCOM object in Helppane.exe in Microsoft Windows Server 2008 SP2 and R2 SP1, Windows 7 SP1, Windows 8.1, Windows Server 2012 Gold and R2, Windows RT 8.1, Windows 10 Gold, 1511, 1607, 1703, and Windows Server 2016, when configured to run as the interactive user, allows an authenticated attacker to run arbitrary code in another user's session, aka "Windows COM Session Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0298|2024-08-05T13:03:55.877Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0214|2024-08-05T12:55:19.132Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- windows%20com
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0214</link>
      <description>Windows COM in Microsoft Windows Server 2008 SP2 and R2 SP1, Windows 7 SP1, Windows 8.1, Windows Server 2012 Gold and R2, Windows RT 8.1, Windows 10 Gold, 1511, 1607, and 1703, and Windows Server 2016 allows an elevation privilege vulnerability when Windows fails to properly validate input before loading type libraries, aka "Windows COM Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability". This CVE ID is unique from CVE-2017-0213.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0214|2024-08-05T12:55:19.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0213|2024-08-05T12:55:19.290Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- windows%20com
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0213</link>
      <description>Windows COM Aggregate Marshaler in Microsoft Windows Server 2008 SP2 and R2 SP1, Windows 7 SP1, Windows 8.1, Windows Server 2012 Gold and R2, Windows RT 8.1, Windows 10 Gold, 1511, 1607, and 1703, and Windows Server 2016 allows an elevation privilege vulnerability when an attacker runs a specially crafted application, aka "Windows COM Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability". This CVE ID is unique from CVE-2017-0214.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0213|2024-08-05T12:55:19.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
