<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Microsoft Corporation -- Windows Hyper-V</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/microsoft%20corporation/windows%20hyper-v.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Microsoft Corporation -- Windows Hyper-V</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:23:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8707|2024-09-17T04:24:25.975Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- windows%20hyper-v
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8707</link>
      <description>The Windows Hyper-V component on Microsoft Windows Server 2008 SP2 and R2 SP1, Windows 8.1, Windows Server 2012 Gold and R2, Windows 10 Gold, 1511, 1607, and 1703, and Windows Server 2016 allows an information disclosure vulnerability when it fails to properly validate input from an authenticated user on a guest operating system, aka Hyper-V Information Disclosure Vulnerability". This CVE ID is unique from CVE-2017-8706, CVE-2017-8711, CVE-2017-8712, and CVE-2017-8713.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8707|2024-09-17T04:24:25.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8713|2024-09-17T00:25:55.527Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- windows%20hyper-v
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8713</link>
      <description>The Windows Hyper-V component on Microsoft Windows Windows 8.1, Windows Server 2012 Gold and R2, Windows 10 Gold, 1511, 1607, and 1703, and Windows Server 2016 allows an information disclosure vulnerability when it fails to properly validate input from an authenticated user on a guest operating system, aka "Hyper-V Information Disclosure Vulnerability". This CVE ID is unique from CVE-2017-8707, CVE-2017-8711, CVE-2017-8712, and CVE-2017-8706.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8713|2024-09-17T00:25:55.527Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8714|2024-09-17T02:27:09.932Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- windows%20hyper-v
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8714</link>
      <description>The Windows Hyper-V component on Microsoft Windows 8.1, Windows Server 2012 Gold and R2,, Windows 10 1607, and Windows Server 2016 allows a remote code execution vulnerability when it fails to properly validate input from an authenticated user on a guest operating system, aka "Remote Desktop Virtual Host Remote Code Execution Vulnerability".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8714|2024-09-17T02:27:09.932Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8712|2024-09-17T03:37:45.441Z -- microsoft%20corporation -- windows%20hyper-v
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8712</link>
      <description>The Windows Hyper-V component on Microsoft Windows 10 1607, 1703, and Windows Server 2016 allows an information disclosure vulnerability when it fails to properly validate input from an authenticated user on a guest operating system, aka "Hyper-V Information Disclosure Vulnerability". This CVE ID is unique from CVE-2017-8707, CVE-2017-8711, CVE-2017-8706, and CVE-2017-8713.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8712|2024-09-17T03:37:45.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
