<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for freescout-helpdesk -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/freescout-helpdesk/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for freescout-helpdesk -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28186|2024-06-04T18:03:28.062Z -- freescout-helpdesk -- freescout
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28186</link>
      <description>FreeScout is an open source help desk and shared inbox built with PHP.

A vulnerability has been identified in the Free Scout Application, which exposes SMTP server credentials used by an organization in the application to users of the application. This issue arises from the application storing complete stack traces of exceptions in its database. The sensitive information is then inadvertently disclosed to users via the `/conversation/ajax-html/send_log?folder_id=&amp;thread_id={id}` endpoint. The stack trace reveals value of parameters, including the username and password, passed to the `Swift_Transport_Esmtp_Auth_LoginAuthenticator-&gt;authenticate()` function. Exploiting this vulnerability allows an attacker to gain unauthorized access to SMTP server credentials. With this sensitive information in hand, the attacker can potentially send unauthorized emails from the compromised SMTP server, posing a severe threat to the confidentiality and integrity of email communications. This could lead to targeted attacks on both the application users and the organization itself, compromising the security of email exchange servers. This issue has been addressed in version 1.8.124. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should adopt the following measures: 1. Avoid Storing Complete Stack Traces, 2. Implement redaction mechanisms to filter and exclude sensitive information, and 3. Review and enhance the application's logging practices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28186|2024-06-04T18:03:28.062Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 19:36:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1932|2024-02-28T00:00:15.339Z -- freescout-helpdesk -- freescout-helpdesk%2Ffreescout
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1932</link>
      <description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type in freescout-helpdesk/freescout</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1932|2024-02-28T00:00:15.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29185|2024-03-22T17:03:56.508Z -- freescout-helpdesk -- freescout
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29185</link>
      <description>FreeScout is a self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Versions prior to 1.8.128 are vulnerable to OS Command Injection in the /public/tools.php source file. The value of the php_path parameter is being executed as an OS command by the shell_exec function, without validating it. This allows an adversary to execute malicious OS commands on the server. A practical demonstration of the successful command injection attack extracted the /etc/passwd file of the server. This represented the complete compromise of the server hosting the FreeScout application. This attack requires an attacker to know the `App_Key` of the application. This limitation makes the Attack Complexity to be High. If an attacker gets hold of the `App_Key`, the attacker can compromise the Complete server on which the application is deployed. Version 1.8.128 contains a patch for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29185|2024-03-22T17:03:56.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 17:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29184|2024-06-04T17:57:38.536Z -- freescout-helpdesk -- freescout
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29184</link>
      <description>FreeScout is a self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified within the Signature Input Field of the FreeScout Application prior to version 1.8.128. Stored XSS occurs when user input is not properly sanitized and is stored on the server, allowing an attacker to inject malicious scripts that will be executed when other users access the affected page. In this case, the Support Agent User can inject malicious scripts into their signature, which will then be executed when viewed by the Administrator.

The application protects users against XSS attacks by enforcing a CSP policy, the CSP Policy is:  `script-src 'self' 'nonce-abcd'  `. The CSP policy only allows the inclusion of JS files that are present on the application server and doesn't allow any inline script or script other than nonce-abcd. The CSP policy was bypassed by uploading a JS file to the server by a POST request to /conversation/upload endpoint. After this, a working XSS payload was crafted by including the uploaded JS file link as the src of the script. This bypassed the CSP policy and XSS attacks became possible.

The impact of this vulnerability is severe as it allows an attacker to compromise the FreeScout Application. By exploiting this vulnerability, the attacker can perform various malicious actions such as forcing the Administrator to execute actions without their knowledge or consent. For instance, the attacker can force the Administrator to add a new administrator controlled by the attacker, thereby giving the attacker full control over the application. Alternatively, the attacker can elevate the privileges of a low-privileged user to Administrator, further compromising the security of the application. Attackers can steal sensitive information such as login credentials, session tokens, personal identifiable information (PII), and financial data. The vulnerability can also lead to defacement of the Application.

Version 1.8.128 contains a patch for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29184|2024-06-04T17:57:38.536Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 17:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34698|2024-06-04T17:42:25.344Z -- freescout-helpdesk -- freescout
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34698</link>
      <description>FreeScout is a free, self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Versions of FreeScout prior to 1.8.139 contain a Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the `/public/js/main.js` source file. The Prototype Pollution arises because the `getQueryParam` Function recursively merges an object containing user-controllable properties into an existing object (For URL Query Parameters Parsing), without first sanitizing the keys. This can allow an attacker to inject a property with a key `__proto__`, along with arbitrarily nested properties. The merge operation assigns the nested properties to the `params` object's prototype instead of the target object itself. As a result, the attacker can pollute the prototype with properties containing harmful values, which are then inherited by user-defined objects and subsequently used by the application dangerously. The vulnerability lets an attacker control properties of objects that would otherwise be inaccessible. If the application subsequently handles an attacker-controlled property in an unsafe way, this can potentially be chained with other vulnerabilities like DOM-based XSS, Open Redirection, Cookie Manipulation, Link Manipulation, HTML Injection, etc. Version 1.8.139 contains a patch for the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34698|2024-06-04T17:42:25.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 15:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34697|2024-06-04T17:41:14.724Z -- freescout-helpdesk -- freescout
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34697</link>
      <description>FreeScout is a free, self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. A stored HTML Injection vulnerability has been identified in the Email Receival Module of the Freescout Application. The vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious HTML content into emails sent to the application's mailbox. This vulnerability arises from improper handling of HTML content within incoming emails, allowing attackers to embed malicious HTML code in the context of the application's domain. Unauthenticated attackers can exploit this vulnerability to inject malicious HTML content into emails. This could lead to various attacks such as form hijacking, application defacement, or data exfiltration via CSS injection. Although unauthenticated attackers are limited to HTML injection, the consequences can still be severe. Version 1.8.139 implements strict input validation and sanitization mechanisms to ensure that any HTML content received via emails is properly sanitized to prevent malicious HTML injections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34697|2024-06-04T17:41:14.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 15:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
