<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for OpenImageIO Project -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/openimageio%20project/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for OpenImageIO Project -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 13:22:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41794|2024-08-03T12:49:43.826Z -- openimageio%20project -- openimageio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41794</link>
      <description>A heap based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the PSD thumbnail resource parsing code of OpenImageIO 2.3.19.0. A specially-crafted PSD file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41794|2024-08-03T12:49:43.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38143|2024-08-03T10:45:52.688Z -- openimageio%20project -- openimageio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38143</link>
      <description>A heap out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the way OpenImageIO v2.3.19.0 processes RLE encoded BMP images. A specially-crafted bmp file can write to arbitrary out of bounds memory, which can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38143|2024-08-03T10:45:52.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41981|2024-08-03T12:56:39.192Z -- openimageio%20project -- openimageio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41981</link>
      <description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the TGA file format parser of OpenImageIO v2.3.19.0. A specially-crafted targa file can lead to out of bounds read and write on the process stack, which can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41981|2024-08-03T12:56:39.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41977|2024-08-03T12:56:39.117Z -- openimageio%20project -- openimageio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41977</link>
      <description>An out of bounds read vulnerability exists in the way OpenImageIO version v2.3.19.0 processes string fields in TIFF image files. A specially-crafted TIFF file can lead to information disclosure. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41977|2024-08-03T12:56:39.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41684|2024-08-03T12:49:43.987Z -- openimageio%20project -- openimageio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41684</link>
      <description>A heap out of bounds read vulnerability exists in the OpenImageIO master-branch-9aeece7a when parsing the image file directory part of a PSD image file. A specially-crafted .psd file can cause a read of arbitrary memory address which can lead to denial of service. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41684|2024-08-03T12:49:43.987Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41999|2024-08-03T12:56:39.233Z -- openimageio%20project -- openimageio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41999</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the DDS native tile reading functionality of OpenImageIO Project OpenImageIO v2.3.19.0 and v2.4.4.2. A specially-crafted .dds can lead to denial of service. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41999|2024-08-03T12:56:39.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41649|2024-08-03T12:49:43.708Z -- openimageio%20project -- openimageio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41649</link>
      <description>A heap out of bounds read vulnerability exists in the handling of IPTC data while parsing TIFF images in OpenImageIO v2.3.19.0. A specially-crafted TIFF file can cause a read of adjacent heap memory, which can leak sensitive process information. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41649|2024-08-03T12:49:43.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41838|2024-08-03T12:56:38.382Z -- openimageio%20project -- openimageio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41838</link>
      <description>A code execution vulnerability exists in the DDS scanline parsing functionality of OpenImageIO Project OpenImageIO v2.4.4.2. A specially-crafted .dds can lead to a heap buffer overflow. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41838|2024-08-03T12:56:38.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36354|2024-08-03T10:00:04.378Z -- openimageio%20project -- openimageio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36354</link>
      <description>A heap out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in the RLA format parser of OpenImageIO master-branch-9aeece7a and v2.3.19.0. More specifically, in the way run-length encoded byte spans are handled. A malformed RLA file can lead to an out-of-bounds read of heap metadata which can result in sensitive information leak. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36354|2024-08-03T10:00:04.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41988|2024-08-03T12:56:39.140Z -- openimageio%20project -- openimageio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41988</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in the OpenImageIO::decode_iptc_iim() functionality of OpenImageIO Project OpenImageIO v2.3.19.0. A specially-crafted TIFF file can lead to a disclosure of sensitive information. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41988|2024-08-03T12:56:39.140Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41837|2024-08-03T12:56:38.278Z -- openimageio%20project -- openimageio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41837</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the OpenImageIO::add_exif_item_to_spec functionality of OpenImageIO Project OpenImageIO v2.4.4.2. Specially-crafted exif metadata can lead to stack-based memory corruption. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41837|2024-08-03T12:56:38.278Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41639|2024-08-03T12:49:43.475Z -- openimageio%20project -- openimageio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41639</link>
      <description>A heap based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in tile decoding code of TIFF image parser in OpenImageIO master-branch-9aeece7a and v2.3.19.0. A specially-crafted TIFF file can lead to an out of bounds memory corruption, which can result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41639|2024-08-03T12:49:43.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
