<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for bookwyrm-social -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bookwyrm-social/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for bookwyrm-social -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23644|2024-08-03T03:51:45.648Z -- bookwyrm-social -- bookwyrm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23644</link>
      <description>BookWyrm is a decentralized social network for tracking reading habits and reviewing books. The functionality to load a cover via url is vulnerable to a server-side request forgery attack. Any BookWyrm instance running a version prior to v0.3.0 is susceptible to attack from a logged-in user. The problem has been patched and administrators should upgrade to version 0.3.0 As a workaround, BookWyrm instances can close registration and limit members to trusted individuals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23644|2024-08-03T03:51:45.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 18:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31136|2024-08-03T07:11:39.628Z -- bookwyrm-social -- bookwyrm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31136</link>
      <description>Bookwyrm is an open source social reading and reviewing program. Versions of Bookwyrm prior to 0.4.1 did not properly sanitize html being rendered to users. Unprivileged users are able to inject scripts into user profiles, book descriptions, and statuses. These vulnerabilities may be exploited as cross site scripting attacks on users viewing these fields. Users are advised to upgrade to version 0.4.1. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31136|2024-08-03T07:11:39.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 17:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35925|2024-08-03T09:51:59.095Z -- bookwyrm-social -- bookwyrm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35925</link>
      <description>BookWyrm is a social network for tracking reading. Versions prior to 0.4.5 were found to lack rate limiting on authentication views which allows brute-force attacks. This issue has been patched in version 0.4.5. Admins with existing instances will need to update their `nginx.conf` file that was created when the instance was set up. Users are advised advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may update their nginx.conf files with the changes manually.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35925|2024-08-03T09:51:59.095Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 20:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35953|2024-08-03T09:51:59.579Z -- bookwyrm-social -- bookwyrm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35953</link>
      <description>BookWyrm is a social network for tracking your reading, talking about books, writing reviews, and discovering what to read next. Some links in BookWyrm may be vulnerable to tabnabbing, a form of phishing that gives attackers an opportunity to redirect a user to a malicious site. The issue was patched in version 0.4.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35953|2024-08-03T09:51:59.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 20:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2651|2024-08-03T00:46:03.487Z -- bookwyrm-social -- bookwyrm-social%2Fbookwyrm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2651</link>
      <description>Authentication Bypass by Primary Weakness in GitHub repository bookwyrm-social/bookwyrm prior to 0.4.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2651|2024-08-03T00:46:03.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 09:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
