<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Esri -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/esri/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Esri -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:22:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38212|2024-08-03T10:45:52.959Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38212</link>
      <description>Protections against potential Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerabilities in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.8.1 and below were not fully honored and may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to forge requests to arbitrary URLs from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or reading from hosts inside the network perimeter, a different issue than CVE-2022-38211 and CVE-2022-38203.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38212|2024-08-03T10:45:52.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29108|2024-08-03T22:02:50.492Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29108</link>
      <description>There is an privilege escalation vulnerability in organization-specific logins in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.9 and below that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker who is able to intercept and modify a SAML assertion to impersonate another account (XML Signature Wrapping Attack). In addition patching, Esri also strongly recommends as best practice for SAML assertions to be signed and encrypted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29108|2024-08-03T22:02:50.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38201|2024-08-03T10:45:52.960Z -- esri -- arcgis%20%20quickcapture
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38201</link>
      <description>An unvalidated redirect vulnerability exists in Esri Portal for ArcGIS Quick Capture Web Designer versions 10.8.1 to 10.9.1. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can potentially induce an unsuspecting authenticated user to access an an attacker controlled domain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38201|2024-08-03T10:45:52.960Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38210|2024-08-03T10:45:53.092Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38210</link>
      <description>There is a reflected HTML injection vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.9.1 and below that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could render arbitrary HTML in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38210|2024-08-03T10:45:53.092Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29094|2024-08-03T22:02:50.341Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29094</link>
      <description>Multiple buffer overflow vulnerabilities when parsing a specially crafted file in Esri ArcGIS Server 10.8.1 (and earlier) allows an authenticated attacker with specialized permissions to achieve arbitrary code execution in the context of the service account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29094|2024-08-03T22:02:50.341Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38190|2024-08-03T10:45:52.963Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38190</link>
      <description>A stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS configurable apps may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to pass and store malicious strings via crafted queries which when accessed could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the user’s browser</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38190|2024-08-03T10:45:52.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38207|2024-08-03T10:45:53.078Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38207</link>
      <description>There is a reflected XSS vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.8.1 and 10.7.1 which may allow a remote remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked which could execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38207|2024-08-03T10:45:53.078Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29109|2024-08-03T22:02:50.876Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29109</link>
      <description>A reflected XSS vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS version 10.9 and below may allow a remote attacker able to convince a user to click on a crafted link which could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the user’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29109|2024-08-03T22:02:50.876Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38208|2024-08-03T10:45:52.950Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38208</link>
      <description>There is an unvalidated redirect vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11 and below that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL that could redirect a victim to an arbitrary website, simplifying phishing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38208|2024-08-03T10:45:52.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38204|2024-08-03T10:45:52.910Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38204</link>
      <description>There is a reflected XSS vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.8.1 and 10.7.1 which may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38204|2024-08-03T10:45:52.910Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29098|2024-08-03T22:02:50.333Z -- esri -- arcreader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29098</link>
      <description>Multiple uninitialized pointer vulnerabilities when parsing a specially crafted file in Esri ArcReader, ArcGIS Desktop, ArcGIS Engine 10.8.1 (and earlier) and ArcGIS Pro 2.7 (and earlier) allow an unauthenticated attacker to achieve arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29098|2024-08-03T22:02:50.333Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29105|2024-08-03T22:02:50.506Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29105</link>
      <description>A stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Esri ArcGIS Server Services Directory version 10.8.1 and below may allow a remote authenticated attacker to pass and store malicious strings in the ArcGIS Services Directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29105|2024-08-03T22:02:50.506Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29116|2024-08-03T22:02:51.085Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29116</link>
      <description>A stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Esri ArcGIS Server feature services versions 10.8.1 and 10.9 (only) feature services may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to pass and store malicious strings via crafted queries which when accessed could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the user’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29116|2024-08-03T22:02:51.085Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29100|2024-08-03T22:02:50.529Z -- esri -- arcgis%20earth
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29100</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in Esri ArcGIS Earth versions 1.11.0 and below which allows arbitrary file creation on an affected system through crafted input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to gain arbitrary code execution under security context of the user running ArcGIS Earth by inducing the user to upload a crafted file to an affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29100|2024-08-03T22:02:50.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38200|2024-08-03T10:45:52.917Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38200</link>
      <description>A cross site scripting vulnerability exists in some map service configurations of ArcGIS Server versions 10.8.1 and 10.7.1. Specifically crafted web requests can execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the victim's browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38200|2024-08-03T10:45:52.917Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29099|2024-08-03T22:02:50.919Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29099</link>
      <description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in some configurations of ArcGIS Server versions 10.8.1 and earlier. Specially crafted web requests can expose information that is not intended to be disclosed (not customer datasets). Web Services that use file based data sources (file Geodatabase or Shape Files or tile cached services) are unaffected by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29099|2024-08-03T22:02:50.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38198|2024-08-03T10:45:53.004Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38198</link>
      <description>There is a reflected cross site scripting issue in the Esri ArcGIS Server services directory versions 10.9.1 and below that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to convince a user to click on a crafted link which could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38198|2024-08-03T10:45:53.004Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29118|2024-08-03T22:02:51.305Z -- esri -- arcreader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29118</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists when parsing a specially crafted file in Esri ArcReader 10.8.1 (and earlier) which allow an unauthenticated attacker to induce an information disclosure issue in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29118|2024-08-03T22:02:51.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38186|2024-08-03T10:45:52.916Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38186</link>
      <description>There is a reflected XSS vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.8.1 and below which may allow a remote attacker able to convince a user to click on a crafted link which could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38186|2024-08-03T10:45:52.916Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29104|2024-08-03T22:02:50.330Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29104</link>
      <description>A stored Cross Site Scripting (XXS) vulnerability in ArcGIS Server Manager version 10.8.1 and below may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to pass and store malicious strings in the ArcGIS Server Manager application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29104|2024-08-03T22:02:50.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29117|2024-08-03T22:02:51.117Z -- esri -- arcreader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29117</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability when parsing a specially crafted file in Esri ArcReader 10.8.1 (and earlier) allows an unauthenticated attacker to achieve arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29117|2024-08-03T22:02:51.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38206|2024-08-03T10:45:52.934Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38206</link>
      <description>There is a reflected XSS vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.9.1 and below which may allow a remote remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38206|2024-08-03T10:45:52.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38193|2024-08-03T10:45:53.026Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38193</link>
      <description>There is a code injection vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.8.1 and below that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to pass strings which could potentially cause arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38193|2024-08-03T10:45:53.026Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38184|2024-08-03T10:45:52.936Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38184</link>
      <description>There is an improper access control vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.8.1 and below which could allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to access an API that may induce Esri Portal for ArcGIS to read arbitrary URLs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38184|2024-08-03T10:45:52.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29106|2024-08-03T22:02:50.862Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29106</link>
      <description>A reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Esri ArcGIS Server version 10.8.1 and below may allow a remote attacker able to convince a user to click on a crafted link which could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the user’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29106|2024-08-03T22:02:50.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29095|2024-08-03T22:02:50.344Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29095</link>
      <description>Multiple uninitialized pointer vulnerabilities when parsing a specially crafted file in Esri ArcGIS Server 10.8.1 (and earlier) allows an authenticated attacker with specialized permissions to achieve arbitrary code execution in the context of the service account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29095|2024-08-03T22:02:50.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38196|2024-08-03T10:45:52.994Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38196</link>
      <description>Esri ArcGIS Server versions 10.9.1 and prior have a path traversal vulnerability that may result in a denial of service by allowing a remote, authenticated attacker to overwrite internal ArcGIS Server directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38196|2024-08-03T10:45:52.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38199|2024-08-03T10:45:53.098Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38199</link>
      <description>A remote file download issue can occur in some capabilities of Esri ArcGIS Server web services that may in some edge cases allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to induce an unsuspecting victim to launch a process in the victim's PATH environment. Current browsers provide users with warnings against running unsigned executables downloaded from the internet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38199|2024-08-03T10:45:53.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38209|2024-08-03T10:45:52.975Z -- esri -- arcgis%20%20quickcapture
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38209</link>
      <description>There is a reflected XSS vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.9.1 and below which may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38209|2024-08-03T10:45:52.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38211|2024-08-03T10:45:52.936Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38211</link>
      <description>Protections against potential Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerabilities in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.9.1 and below were not fully honored and may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to forge requests to arbitrary URLs from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or reading from hosts inside the network perimeter, a different issue than CVE-2022-38211 and CVE-2022-38212.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38211|2024-08-03T10:45:52.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29115|2024-08-03T22:02:50.331Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29115</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in the ArcGIS Service Directory in Esri ArcGIS Enterprise versions 10.9.0 and below may allows a remote attacker to view hidden field names in feature layers. This issue may reveal field names, but not not disclose features.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29115|2024-08-03T22:02:50.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38189|2024-08-03T10:45:53.003Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38189</link>
      <description>A stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to pass and store malicious strings via crafted queries which when accessed could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the user’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38189|2024-08-03T10:45:53.003Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38197|2024-08-03T10:45:52.892Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38197</link>
      <description>Esri ArcGIS Server versions 10.9.1 and below have an unvalidated redirect issue that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to phish a user into accessing an attacker controlled website via a crafted query parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38197|2024-08-03T10:45:52.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38195|2024-08-03T10:45:52.896Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38195</link>
      <description>There is as reflected cross site scripting issue in Esri ArcGIS Server versions 10.9.1 and below which may allow a remote unauthorized attacker able to convince a user to click on a crafted link which could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38195|2024-08-03T10:45:52.896Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29096|2024-08-03T22:02:50.577Z -- esri -- arcreader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29096</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability when parsing a specially crafted file in Esri ArcReader, ArcGIS Desktop, ArcGIS Engine 10.8.1 (and earlier) and ArcGIS Pro 2.7 (and earlier) allows an unauthenticated attacker to achieve arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29096|2024-08-03T22:02:50.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29112|2024-08-03T22:02:50.541Z -- esri -- arcreader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29112</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists when parsing a specially crafted file in Esri ArcReader 10.8.1 (and earlier) which allow an unauthenticated attacker to induce an information disclosure issue in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29112|2024-08-03T22:02:50.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29114|2024-08-03T22:02:50.515Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29114</link>
      <description>A SQL injection vulnerability in feature services provided by Esri ArcGIS Server 10.9 and below allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to impact the confidentiality, integrity and availability of targeted services via specifically crafted queries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29114|2024-08-03T22:02:50.515Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29113|2024-08-03T22:02:50.538Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29113</link>
      <description>A remote file inclusion vulnerability in the ArcGIS Server help documentation may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to inject attacker supplied html into a page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29113|2024-08-03T22:02:50.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29103|2024-08-03T22:02:51.334Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29103</link>
      <description>A reflected Cross Site Scripting (XXS) vulnerability in ArcGIS Server version 10.8.1 and below may allow a remote attacker able to convince a user to click on a crafted link which could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the user’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29103|2024-08-03T22:02:51.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38187|2024-08-03T10:45:52.961Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38187</link>
      <description>Prior to version 10.9.0, the sharing/rest/content/features/analyze endpoint is always accessible to anonymous users, which could allow an unauthenticated attacker to induce Esri Portal for ArcGIS to read arbitrary URLs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38187|2024-08-03T10:45:52.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29101|2024-08-03T22:02:50.541Z -- esri -- arcgis%20geoevent%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29101</link>
      <description>ArcGIS GeoEvent Server versions 10.8.1 and below has a read-only directory path traversal vulnerability that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to perform directory traversal attacks and read arbitrary files on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29101|2024-08-03T22:02:50.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38191|2024-08-03T10:45:52.996Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38191</link>
      <description>There is an HTML injection issue in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.9.0 and below which may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to inject HTML into some locations in the home application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38191|2024-08-03T10:45:52.996Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38192|2024-08-03T10:45:52.936Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38192</link>
      <description>A stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to pass and store malicious strings via crafted queries which when accessed could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the user’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38192|2024-08-03T10:45:52.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29110|2024-08-03T22:02:50.615Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29110</link>
      <description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) issue in Esri Portal for ArcGIS may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to pass and store malicious strings in the home application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29110|2024-08-03T22:02:50.615Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29107|2024-08-03T22:02:50.603Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29107</link>
      <description>A stored Cross Site Scripting (XXS) vulnerability in ArcGIS Server Manager version 10.8.1 and below may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to pass and store malicious strings in the ArcGIS Server Manager application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29107|2024-08-03T22:02:50.603Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38194|2024-08-03T10:45:52.947Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38194</link>
      <description>In Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.8.1, a system property is not properly encrypted. This may lead to a local user reading sensitive information from a properties file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38194|2024-08-03T10:45:52.947Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38202|2024-08-03T10:45:52.952Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38202</link>
      <description>There is a path traversal vulnerability in Esri ArcGIS Server versions 10.9.1 and below. Successful exploitation may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker traverse the file system to access files outside of the intended directory on ArcGIS Server. This could lead to the disclosure of sensitive site configuration information (not user datasets).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38202|2024-08-03T10:45:52.952Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38203|2024-08-03T10:45:53.061Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38203</link>
      <description>Protections against potential Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerabilities in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.8.1 and below were not fully honored and may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to forge requests to arbitrary URLs from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or reading from hosts inside the network perimeter, a different issue than CVE-2022-38211 and CVE-2022-38212.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38203|2024-08-03T10:45:53.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38205|2024-08-03T10:45:52.919Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38205</link>
      <description>In some non-default installations of Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.9.1 and below, a directory traversal issue may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to traverse the file system and lead to the disclosure of sensitive data (not customer-published content).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38205|2024-08-03T10:45:52.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29097|2024-08-03T22:02:50.311Z -- esri -- arcreader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29097</link>
      <description>Multiple buffer overflow vulnerabilities when parsing a specially crafted file in Esri ArcReader, ArcGIS Desktop, ArcGIS Engine 10.8.1 (and earlier) and ArcGIS Pro 2.7 (and earlier) allow an unauthenticated attacker to achieve arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29097|2024-08-03T22:02:50.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29093|2024-08-03T22:02:50.342Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29093</link>
      <description>A use-after-free vulnerability when parsing a specially crafted file in Esri ArcGIS Server 10.8.1 (and earlier) allows an authenticated attacker with specialized permissions to achieve arbitrary code execution in the context of the service account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29093|2024-08-03T22:02:50.342Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38188|2024-08-03T10:45:52.934Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38188</link>
      <description>There is a reflected XSS vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.9.1 which may allow a remote attacker able to convince a user to click on a crafted link which could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38188|2024-08-03T10:45:52.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29102|2024-08-03T22:02:50.565Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29102</link>
      <description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in ArcGIS Server Manager version 10.8.1 and below may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to forge GET requests to arbitrary URLs from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or facilitating other attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29102|2024-08-03T22:02:50.565Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25690|2024-07-05T17:22:31.573Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise%20web%20app%20builder</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25690</link>
      <description>There is an HTML injection vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 11.1 and below that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could render arbitrary HTML in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25690|2024-07-05T17:22:31.573Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25708|2024-07-05T17:21:28.406Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise%20web%20app%20builder</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25708</link>
      <description>There is a stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS Enterprise Web App Builder versions 10.8.1 – 10.9.1 that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.  The privileges required to execute this attack are high.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25708|2024-07-05T17:21:28.406Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25699|2024-07-05T17:21:33.510Z -- esri -- portal</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25699</link>
      <description>There is a difficult to exploit improper authentication issue in the Home application for Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.8.1 through 11.2 on Windows and Linux, and ArcGIS Enterprise 11.1 and below on Kubernetes which, under unique circumstances, could potentially allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to compromise the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25699|2024-07-05T17:21:33.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25692|2024-07-05T17:21:28.537Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25692</link>
      <description>There is a cross-site-request forgery vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS Versions 11.1 and below that may in some cases allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to trick an authorized user into executing unwanted actions via a crafted form. The impact to Confidentiality and Integrity vectors is limited and of low severity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25692|2024-07-05T17:21:28.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25697|2024-06-06T19:08:25.228Z -- esri -- portal</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25697</link>
      <description>There is a Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS in versions &lt;=11.1 that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when opening an authenticated users bio page will render an image in the victims browser.  The privileges required to execute this attack are low.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25697|2024-06-06T19:08:25.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:53:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25696|2024-06-04T17:35:06.198Z -- esri -- portal</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25696</link>
      <description>There is a Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS in versions &lt;=11.0 that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when accessing the page editor an image will render in the victim’s browser.  The privileges required to execute this attack are high.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25696|2024-06-04T17:35:06.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25690|2024-04-19T22:28:54.508Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise%20web%20app%20builder</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25690</link>
      <description>There is an HTML injection vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 11.1 and below that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could render arbitrary HTML in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25690|2024-04-19T22:28:54.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25693|2024-04-19T22:30:03.677Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25693</link>
      <description>There is a path traversal in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions &lt;= 11.2.  Successful exploitation may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to traverse the file system to access files or execute code outside of the intended directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25693|2024-04-19T22:30:03.677Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25692|2024-04-19T22:28:02.403Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25692</link>
      <description>There is a cross-site-request forgery vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS Versions 11.1 and below that may in some cases allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to trick an authorized user into executing unwanted actions via a crafted form. The impact to Confidentiality and Integrity vectors is limited and of low severity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25692|2024-04-19T22:28:02.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25699|2024-04-19T22:30:59.132Z -- esri -- portal</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25699</link>
      <description>There is a difficult to exploit improper authentication issue in the Home application for Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.8.1 through 11.2 on Windows and Linux, and ArcGIS Enterprise 11.1 and below on Kubernetes which, under unique circumstances, could potentially allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to compromise the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25699|2024-04-19T22:30:59.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25695|2024-06-04T17:35:42.120Z -- esri -- portal</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25695</link>
      <description>There is a Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS in versions &lt;= 11.2 that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to provide input that is not sanitized properly and is rendered in error messages.  The are no privileges required to execute this attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25695|2024-06-04T17:35:42.120Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25708|2024-04-19T22:28:32.554Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise%20web%20app%20builder</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25708</link>
      <description>There is a stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS Enterprise Web App Builder versions 10.8.1 – 10.9.1 that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.  The privileges required to execute this attack are high.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25708|2024-04-19T22:28:32.554Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25698|2024-06-04T17:35:54.799Z -- esri -- portal</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25698</link>
      <description>There is a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in the home application in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.1 and below on Windows and Linux that allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25698|2024-06-04T17:35:54.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25693|2024-07-31T20:00:27.790Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25693</link>
      <description>There is a path traversal in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions &lt;= 11.2.  Successful exploitation may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to traverse the file system to access files or execute code outside of the intended directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25693|2024-07-31T20:00:27.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
