<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Esri -- ArcGIS Enterprise</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/esri/arcgis%20enterprise.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Esri -- ArcGIS Enterprise</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38212|2024-08-03T10:45:52.959Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38212</link>
      <description>Protections against potential Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerabilities in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.8.1 and below were not fully honored and may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to forge requests to arbitrary URLs from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or reading from hosts inside the network perimeter, a different issue than CVE-2022-38211 and CVE-2022-38203.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38212|2024-08-03T10:45:52.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38210|2024-08-03T10:45:53.092Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38210</link>
      <description>There is a reflected HTML injection vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.9.1 and below that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could render arbitrary HTML in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38210|2024-08-03T10:45:53.092Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38207|2024-08-03T10:45:53.078Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38207</link>
      <description>There is a reflected XSS vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.8.1 and 10.7.1 which may allow a remote remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked which could execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38207|2024-08-03T10:45:53.078Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38208|2024-08-03T10:45:52.950Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38208</link>
      <description>There is an unvalidated redirect vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11 and below that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL that could redirect a victim to an arbitrary website, simplifying phishing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38208|2024-08-03T10:45:52.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38204|2024-08-03T10:45:52.910Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38204</link>
      <description>There is a reflected XSS vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.8.1 and 10.7.1 which may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38204|2024-08-03T10:45:52.910Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38206|2024-08-03T10:45:52.934Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38206</link>
      <description>There is a reflected XSS vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.9.1 and below which may allow a remote remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38206|2024-08-03T10:45:52.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38211|2024-08-03T10:45:52.936Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38211</link>
      <description>Protections against potential Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerabilities in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.9.1 and below were not fully honored and may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to forge requests to arbitrary URLs from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or reading from hosts inside the network perimeter, a different issue than CVE-2022-38211 and CVE-2022-38212.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38211|2024-08-03T10:45:52.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38205|2024-08-03T10:45:52.919Z -- esri -- arcgis%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38205</link>
      <description>In some non-default installations of Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.9.1 and below, a directory traversal issue may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to traverse the file system and lead to the disclosure of sensitive data (not customer-published content).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38205|2024-08-03T10:45:52.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
