<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Esri -- ArcGIS Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/esri/arcgis%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Esri -- ArcGIS Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 11:20:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38200|2024-08-03T10:45:52.917Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38200</link>
      <description>A cross site scripting vulnerability exists in some map service configurations of ArcGIS Server versions 10.8.1 and 10.7.1. Specifically crafted web requests can execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the victim's browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38200|2024-08-03T10:45:52.917Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38198|2024-08-03T10:45:53.004Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38198</link>
      <description>There is a reflected cross site scripting issue in the Esri ArcGIS Server services directory versions 10.9.1 and below that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to convince a user to click on a crafted link which could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38198|2024-08-03T10:45:53.004Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38196|2024-08-03T10:45:52.994Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38196</link>
      <description>Esri ArcGIS Server versions 10.9.1 and prior have a path traversal vulnerability that may result in a denial of service by allowing a remote, authenticated attacker to overwrite internal ArcGIS Server directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38196|2024-08-03T10:45:52.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38199|2024-08-03T10:45:53.098Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38199</link>
      <description>A remote file download issue can occur in some capabilities of Esri ArcGIS Server web services that may in some edge cases allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to induce an unsuspecting victim to launch a process in the victim's PATH environment. Current browsers provide users with warnings against running unsigned executables downloaded from the internet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38199|2024-08-03T10:45:53.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38197|2024-08-03T10:45:52.892Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38197</link>
      <description>Esri ArcGIS Server versions 10.9.1 and below have an unvalidated redirect issue that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to phish a user into accessing an attacker controlled website via a crafted query parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38197|2024-08-03T10:45:52.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38195|2024-08-03T10:45:52.896Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38195</link>
      <description>There is as reflected cross site scripting issue in Esri ArcGIS Server versions 10.9.1 and below which may allow a remote unauthorized attacker able to convince a user to click on a crafted link which could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38195|2024-08-03T10:45:52.896Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38202|2024-08-03T10:45:52.952Z -- esri -- arcgis%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38202</link>
      <description>There is a path traversal vulnerability in Esri ArcGIS Server versions 10.9.1 and below. Successful exploitation may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker traverse the file system to access files outside of the intended directory on ArcGIS Server. This could lead to the disclosure of sensitive site configuration information (not user datasets).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38202|2024-08-03T10:45:52.952Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
