<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Esri -- Portal for ArcGIS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/esri/portal%20for%20arcgis.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Esri -- Portal for ArcGIS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 21:23:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25699|2024-10-08T16:40:43.713Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25699</link>
      <description>There is a difficult to exploit improper authentication issue in the Home application for Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.8.1 through 11.2 on Windows and Linux, and ArcGIS Enterprise 11.1 and below on Kubernetes which, under unique circumstances, could potentially allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to compromise the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25699|2024-10-08T16:40:43.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25705|2024-10-08T16:41:32.453Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25705</link>
      <description>There is a cross site scripting vulnerability in the Esri Portal for ArcGIS Experience Builder 11.1 and below on Windows and Linux that allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser. The privileges required to execute this attack are low.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25705|2024-10-08T16:41:32.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25696|2024-10-08T16:38:59.045Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25696</link>
      <description>There is a Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS in versions &lt;=11.0 that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when accessing the page editor an image will render in the victim’s browser.  The privileges required to execute this attack are high.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25696|2024-10-08T16:38:59.045Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25697|2024-10-08T16:39:18.624Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25697</link>
      <description>There is a Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS in versions &lt;=11.1 that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when opening an authenticated users bio page will render an image in the victims browser.  The privileges required to execute this attack are low.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25697|2024-10-08T16:39:18.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:53:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25698|2024-10-08T16:40:10.850Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25698</link>
      <description>There is a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in the home application in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.1 and below on Windows and Linux that allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25698|2024-10-08T16:40:10.850Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25706|2024-10-08T16:41:51.121Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25706</link>
      <description>There is an HTML injection vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS &lt;=11.0 that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL which, when clicked, could potentially generate a message that may entice an unsuspecting victim to visit an arbitrary website. This could simplify phishing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25706|2024-10-08T16:41:51.121Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25695|2024-10-08T16:38:33.749Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25695</link>
      <description>There is a Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS in versions &lt;= 11.2 that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to provide input that is not sanitized properly and is rendered in error messages.  The are no privileges required to execute this attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25695|2024-10-08T16:38:33.749Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25709|2024-10-08T16:42:22.921Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25709</link>
      <description>There is a stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.8.1 – 1121 that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to create a crafted link that can be saved as a new location when moving an existing item which will potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.  The privileges required to execute this attack are high.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25709|2024-10-08T16:42:22.921Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38038|2024-10-08T16:43:02.451Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38038</link>
      <description>There is a reflected XSS vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 10.9.1, 10.8.1 and 10.7.1 which may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38038|2024-10-08T16:43:02.451Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 17:19:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25707|2024-10-08T16:42:03.491Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25707</link>
      <description>There is a reflected cross site scripting in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.1 and below on Windows and Linux x64 allows a remote authenticated attacker with administrative access to supply a crafted string which could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the their own browser (Self XSS). A user cannot be phished into clicking a link to execute code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25707|2024-10-08T16:42:03.491Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 17:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25691|2024-10-08T16:36:49.161Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25691</link>
      <description>There is a reflected XSS vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 11.1, 10.9.1 and 10.8.1 which may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25691|2024-10-08T16:36:49.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 17:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38037|2024-10-08T16:42:45.494Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38037</link>
      <description>There is an unvalidated redirect vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.0 and 10.9.1 that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL that could redirect a victim to an arbitrary website, simplifying phishing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38037|2024-10-08T16:42:45.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 17:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38039|2024-10-08T16:43:18.350Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38039</link>
      <description>There is an HTML injection vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 11.0 and below that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could render arbitrary HTML in the victim’s browser (no stateful change made or customer data rendered).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38039|2024-10-08T16:43:18.350Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 17:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8148|2024-10-08T16:35:04.123Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8148</link>
      <description>There is an unvalidated redirect vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 10.8.1 - 11.2 that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL that could redirect a victim to an arbitrary website, simplifying phishing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8148|2024-10-08T16:35:04.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 17:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8149|2024-10-08T16:36:22.657Z -- esri -- portal%20for%20arcgis</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8149</link>
      <description>There is a reflected XSS vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS versions 11.1 and 11.2 which may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to create a crafted link which when clicked could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8149|2024-10-08T16:36:22.657Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 17:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
