<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for wpzoom -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/wpzoom/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for wpzoom -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:23:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5686|2024-07-02T19:34:11.406Z -- wpzoom -- wpzoom%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%28templates%2C%20widgets%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5686</link>
      <description>The WPZOOM Addons for Elementor (Templates, Widgets) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ attribute within the plugin's Team Members widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.38 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5686|2024-07-02T19:34:11.406Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 03:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5147|2024-06-04T18:01:55.868Z -- wpzoom -- wpzoom%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%28templates%2C%20widgets%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5147</link>
      <description>The WPZOOM Addons for Elementor (Templates, Widgets) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.37 via the 'grid_style' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5147|2024-06-04T18:01:55.868Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 07:37:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4370|2024-06-06T19:49:13.482Z -- wpzoom -- wpzoom%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%28templates%2C%20widgets%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4370</link>
      <description>The WPZOOM Addons for Elementor (Templates, Widgets) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widget Image Box in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.36 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4370|2024-06-06T19:49:13.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 23:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22162|2024-01-31T18:00:09.781Z -- wpzoom -- wpzoom%20shortcodes</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22162</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPZOOM Shortcodes allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WPZOOM Shortcodes: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22162|2024-01-31T18:00:09.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 18:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33539|2024-04-29T05:23:30.661Z -- wpzoom -- wpzoom%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%28templates%2C%20widgets%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33539</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPZOOM WPZOOM Addons for Elementor (Templates, Widgets) allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WPZOOM Addons for Elementor (Templates, Widgets): from n/a through 1.1.35.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33539|2024-04-29T05:23:30.661Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30464|2024-06-10T13:33:21.137Z -- wpzoom -- social%20icons%20widget%20%26%20block%20by%20wpzoom</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30464</link>
      <description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPZOOM Social Icons Widget &amp; Block by WPZOOM.This issue affects Social Icons Widget &amp; Block by WPZOOM: from n/a through 4.2.15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30464|2024-06-10T13:33:21.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 10:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3662|2024-06-06T18:28:29.195Z -- wpzoom -- wpzoom%20social%20feed%20widget%20%26%20block</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3662</link>
      <description>The WPZOOM Social Feed Widget &amp; Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the wpzoom_instagram_clear_data() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to delete all Instagram images installed on the site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3662|2024-06-06T18:28:29.195Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 08:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2183|2024-06-04T17:30:31.437Z -- wpzoom -- beaver%20builder%20addons%20by%20wpzoom</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2183</link>
      <description>The Beaver Builder Addons by WPZOOM plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Heading widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. CVE-2024-30424 is likely a duplicate of this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2183|2024-06-04T17:30:31.437Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2185|2024-06-04T17:30:07.888Z -- wpzoom -- beaver%20builder%20addons%20by%20wpzoom</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2185</link>
      <description>The Beaver Builder Addons by WPZOOM plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Box widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2185|2024-06-04T17:30:07.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2186|2024-04-09T18:58:57.763Z -- wpzoom -- beaver%20builder%20addons%20by%20wpzoom</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2186</link>
      <description>The Beaver Builder Addons by WPZOOM plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Team Members widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2186|2024-04-09T18:58:57.763Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2187|2024-06-04T17:29:42.371Z -- wpzoom -- beaver%20builder%20addons%20by%20wpzoom</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2187</link>
      <description>The Beaver Builder Addons by WPZOOM plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Testimonials widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2187|2024-06-04T17:29:42.371Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2181|2024-06-04T17:29:04.296Z -- wpzoom -- beaver%20builder%20addons%20by%20wpzoom</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2181</link>
      <description>The Beaver Builder Addons by WPZOOM plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Button widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2181|2024-06-04T17:29:04.296Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5686|2024-06-20T03:37:23.231Z -- wpzoom -- wpzoom%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%28templates%2C%20widgets%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5686</link>
      <description>The WPZOOM Addons for Elementor (Templates, Widgets) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ attribute within the plugin's Team Members widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.38 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5686|2024-06-20T03:37:23.231Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 03:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
