<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for MMDeveloper -- A Forms Plugin</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mmdeveloper/a%20forms%20plugin.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for MMDeveloper -- A Forms Plugin</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 21:21:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2013-10020|2024-08-06T18:09:16.991Z -- mmdeveloper -- a%20forms%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10020</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in MMDeveloper A Forms Plugin up to 1.4.2 on WordPress. This affects an unknown part of the file a-forms.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 1.4.3 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 3e693197bd69b7173cc16d8d2e0a7d501a2a0b06. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-222609 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in MMDeveloper A Forms Plugin bis 1.4.2 für WordPress gefunden. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei a-forms.php. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.4.3 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 3e693197bd69b7173cc16d8d2e0a7d501a2a0b06 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2013-10020|2024-08-06T18:09:16.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 01:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
