<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for DaSchTour -- matomo-mediawiki-extension</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/daschtour/matomo-mediawiki-extension.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for DaSchTour -- matomo-mediawiki-extension</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20175|2024-08-05T21:45:25.969Z -- daschtour -- matomo-mediawiki-extension
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20175</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in DaSchTour matomo-mediawiki-extension up to 2.4.2 on MediaWiki. This affects an unknown part of the file Piwik.hooks.php of the component Username Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.4.3 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 681324e4f518a8af4bd1f93867074c728eb9923d. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-220203.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in DaSchTour matomo-mediawiki-extension bis 2.4.2 für MediaWiki entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei Piwik.hooks.php der Komponente Username Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie ist schwierig auszunutzen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 2.4.3 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 681324e4f518a8af4bd1f93867074c728eb9923d bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20175|2024-08-05T21:45:25.969Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 19:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
