<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for HP Inc. -- HP DeskJet 2600 All-in-One Printer series</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/hp%20inc./hp%20deskjet%202600%20all-in-one%20printer%20series.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for HP Inc. -- HP DeskJet 2600 All-in-One Printer series</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6332|2024-08-04T20:16:24.804Z -- hp%20inc. -- hp%20deskjet%202600%20all-in-one%20printer%20series
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6332</link>
      <description>A potential security vulnerability has been identified with certain HP InkJet printers. The vulnerability could be exploited to allow cross-site scripting (XSS). Affected products and versions include: HP DeskJet 2600 All-in-One Printer series model numbers 4UJ28B, V1N01A - V1N08A, Y5H60A - Y5H80A; HP DeskJet Ink Advantage 2600 All-in-One Printer series model numbers V1N02A - V1N02B, Y5Z00A - Y5Z04B; HP DeskJet Ink Advantage 5000 All-in-One Printer series model numbers M2U86A - M2U89B; HP DeskJet Ink Advantage 5200 All-in-One Printer series model numbers M2U76A - M2U78B; HP ENVY 5000 All-in-One Printer series model numbers M2U85A - M2U85B, M2U91A - M2U94B, Z4A54A - Z4A74A; HP ENVY Photo 6200 All-in-One Printer series model numbers K7G18A-K7G26B, K7S21B, Y0K13D - Y0K15A; HP ENVY Photo 7100 All-in-One Printer series model numbers 3XD89A, K7G93A-K7G99A, Z3M37A - Z3M52A; HP ENVY Photo 7800 All-in-One Printer series model numbers K7R96A, K7S00A - K7S10D, Y0G42D - Y0G52B; HP Ink Tank Wireless 410 series model numbers Z4B53A - Z4B55A, Z6Z95A - Z6Z99A, 4DX94A - 4DX95A, 4YF79A, Z7A01A; HP OfficeJet 5200 All-in-One Printer series model numbers M2U75A, M2U81A-M2U84B, Z4B12A - Z4B14A, Z4B27A - Z4B29A; HP Smart Tank Wireless 450 series model numbers Z4B56A, Z6Z96A - Z6Z98A.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6332|2024-08-04T20:16:24.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 18:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
