<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for InHand Networks -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/inhand%20networks/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for InHand Networks -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22598|2023-01-12T22:30:33.090Z -- inhand%20networks -- inrouter%20302
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22598</link>
      <description>
InHand Networks InRouter 302, prior to version IR302 V3.5.56, and InRouter 615, prior to version InRouter6XX-S-V2.3.0.r5542, contain vulnerability CWE-78:  Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection'). 

An unauthorized user with privileged access to the local web interface or the cloud account managing the affected devices could push a specially crafted configuration update file to gain root access. This could lead to remote code execution with root privileges. 

 

 

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22598|2023-01-12T22:30:33.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 22:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22599|2023-01-12T22:31:55.394Z -- inhand%20networks -- inrouter%20302
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22599</link>
      <description>
InHand Networks InRouter 302, prior to version IR302 V3.5.56, and InRouter 615, prior to version InRouter6XX-S-V2.3.0.r5542, contain vulnerability CWE-760: Use of a One-way Hash with a Predictable Salt. They 

send MQTT credentials in response to HTTP/HTTPS requests from the cloud platform. These credentials are encoded using a hardcoded string into an MD5 hash. This string could be easily calculated by an unauthorized user who spoofed sending an HTTP/HTTPS request to the devices. This could result in the affected devices being temporarily disconnected from the cloud platform and allow the user to receive MQTT commands with potentially sensitive information. 

 

 

 

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22599|2023-01-12T22:31:55.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 22:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22597|2023-01-12T22:27:53.790Z -- inhand%20networks -- inrouter%20302
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22597</link>
      <description>
InHand Networks InRouter 302, prior to version IR302 V3.5.56, and InRouter 615, prior to version InRouter6XX-S-V2.3.0.r5542, contain vulnerability CWE-319: Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information. They use an unsecured channel to communicate with the cloud platform by default. An unauthorized user could intercept this communication and steal sensitive information such as configuration information and MQTT credentials; this could allow MQTT command injection. 

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22597|2023-01-12T22:27:53.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 22:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22601|2023-01-12T22:34:14.532Z -- inhand%20networks -- inrouter%20302
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22601</link>
      <description>
InHand Networks InRouter 302, prior to version IR302 V3.5.56, and InRouter 615, prior to version InRouter6XX-S-V2.3.0.r5542, contain vulnerability CWE-330: Use of Insufficiently Random Values. They do not properly randomize MQTT ClientID parameters. An unauthorized user could calculate this parameter and use it to gather additional information about other InHand devices managed on the same cloud platform. 

 

 

 

 

 

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22601|2023-01-12T22:34:14.532Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 22:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22600|2023-01-12T22:33:16.337Z -- inhand%20networks -- inrouter%20302
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22600</link>
      <description>
InHand Networks InRouter 302, prior to version IR302 V3.5.56, and InRouter 615, prior to version InRouter6XX-S-V2.3.0.r5542, contain vulnerability CWE-284: Improper Access Control. They allow unauthenticated devices to subscribe to MQTT topics on the same network as the device manager. An unauthorized user who knows of an existing topic name could send and receive messages to and from that topic. This includes the ability to send GET/SET configuration commands, reboot commands, and push firmware updates. 

 

 

 

 

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22600|2023-01-12T22:33:16.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 22:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
