<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Siemens -- Cerberus PRO EN Engineering Tool</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/siemens/cerberus%20pro%20en%20engineering%20tool.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Siemens -- Cerberus PRO EN Engineering Tool</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 23:21:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-22039|2024-05-15T07:23:51.702Z -- Siemens -- Cerberus PRO EN Engineering Tool</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22039</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Cerberus PRO EN Engineering Tool (All versions &lt; IP8), Cerberus PRO EN Fire Panel FC72x IP6 (All versions &lt; IP6 SR3), Cerberus PRO EN Fire Panel FC72x IP7 (All versions &lt; IP7 SR5), Cerberus PRO EN X200 Cloud Distribution IP7 (All versions &lt; V3.0.6602), Cerberus PRO EN X200 Cloud Distribution IP8 (All versions &lt; V4.0.5016), Cerberus PRO EN X300 Cloud Distribution IP7 (All versions &lt; V3.2.6601), Cerberus PRO EN X300 Cloud Distribution IP8 (All versions &lt; V4.2.5015), Cerberus PRO UL Compact Panel FC922/924 (All versions &lt; MP4), Cerberus PRO UL Engineering Tool (All versions &lt; MP4), Cerberus PRO UL X300 Cloud Distribution (All versions &lt; V4.3.0001), Desigo Fire Safety UL Compact Panel FC2025/2050 (All versions &lt; MP4), Desigo Fire Safety UL Engineering Tool (All versions &lt; MP4), Desigo Fire Safety UL X300 Cloud Distribution (All versions &lt; V4.3.0001), Sinteso FS20 EN Engineering Tool (All versions &lt; MP8), Sinteso FS20 EN Fire Panel FC20 MP6 (All versions &lt; MP6 SR3), Sinteso FS20 EN Fire Panel FC20 MP7 (All versions &lt; MP7 SR5), Sinteso FS20 EN X200 Cloud Distribution MP7 (All versions &lt; V3.0.6602), Sinteso FS20 EN X200 Cloud Distribution MP8 (All versions &lt; V4.0.5016), Sinteso FS20 EN X300 Cloud Distribution MP7 (All versions &lt; V3.2.6601), Sinteso FS20 EN X300 Cloud Distribution MP8 (All versions &lt; V4.2.5015), Sinteso Mobile (All versions &lt; V3.0.0). The network communication library in affected systems does not validate the length of certain X.509 certificate attributes which might result in a stack-based buffer overflow.
This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute code on the underlying operating system with root privileges.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22039|2024-05-15T07:23:51.702Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 10:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22041|2024-05-15T07:23:54.480Z -- Siemens -- Cerberus PRO EN Engineering Tool</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22041</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Cerberus PRO EN Engineering Tool (All versions), Cerberus PRO EN Fire Panel FC72x IP6 (All versions), Cerberus PRO EN Fire Panel FC72x IP7 (All versions), Cerberus PRO EN Fire Panel FC72x IP8 (All versions &lt; IP8 SR4), Cerberus PRO EN X200 Cloud Distribution IP7 (All versions), Cerberus PRO EN X200 Cloud Distribution IP8 (All versions &lt; V4.3.5618), Cerberus PRO EN X300 Cloud Distribution IP7 (All versions), Cerberus PRO EN X300 Cloud Distribution IP8 (All versions &lt; V4.3.5617), Cerberus PRO UL Compact Panel FC922/924 (All versions &lt; MP4), Cerberus PRO UL Engineering Tool (All versions &lt; MP4), Cerberus PRO UL X300 Cloud Distribution (All versions &lt; V4.3.0001), Desigo Fire Safety UL Compact Panel FC2025/2050 (All versions &lt; MP4), Desigo Fire Safety UL Engineering Tool (All versions &lt; MP4), Desigo Fire Safety UL X300 Cloud Distribution (All versions &lt; V4.3.0001), Sinteso FS20 EN Engineering Tool (All versions), Sinteso FS20 EN Fire Panel FC20 MP6 (All versions), Sinteso FS20 EN Fire Panel FC20 MP7 (All versions), Sinteso FS20 EN Fire Panel FC20 MP8 (All versions &lt; MP8 SR4), Sinteso FS20 EN X200 Cloud Distribution MP7 (All versions), Sinteso FS20 EN X200 Cloud Distribution MP8 (All versions &lt; V4.3.5618), Sinteso FS20 EN X300 Cloud Distribution MP7 (All versions), Sinteso FS20 EN X300 Cloud Distribution MP8 (All versions &lt; V4.3.5617), Sinteso Mobile (All versions). The network communication library in affected systems improperly handles memory buffers when parsing X.509 certificates.
This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to crash the network service.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22041|2024-05-15T07:23:54.480Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 10:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22040|2024-05-15T07:23:53.096Z -- Siemens -- Cerberus PRO EN Engineering Tool</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22040</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Cerberus PRO EN Engineering Tool (All versions), Cerberus PRO EN Fire Panel FC72x IP6 (All versions), Cerberus PRO EN Fire Panel FC72x IP7 (All versions), Cerberus PRO EN Fire Panel FC72x IP8 (All versions &lt; IP8 SR4), Cerberus PRO EN X200 Cloud Distribution IP7 (All versions), Cerberus PRO EN X200 Cloud Distribution IP8 (All versions &lt; V4.3.5618), Cerberus PRO EN X300 Cloud Distribution IP7 (All versions), Cerberus PRO EN X300 Cloud Distribution IP8 (All versions &lt; V4.3.5617), Cerberus PRO UL Compact Panel FC922/924 (All versions &lt; MP4), Cerberus PRO UL Engineering Tool (All versions &lt; MP4), Cerberus PRO UL X300 Cloud Distribution (All versions &lt; V4.3.0001), Desigo Fire Safety UL Compact Panel FC2025/2050 (All versions &lt; MP4), Desigo Fire Safety UL Engineering Tool (All versions &lt; MP4), Desigo Fire Safety UL X300 Cloud Distribution (All versions &lt; V4.3.0001), Sinteso FS20 EN Engineering Tool (All versions), Sinteso FS20 EN Fire Panel FC20 MP6 (All versions), Sinteso FS20 EN Fire Panel FC20 MP7 (All versions), Sinteso FS20 EN Fire Panel FC20 MP8 (All versions &lt; MP8 SR4), Sinteso FS20 EN X200 Cloud Distribution MP7 (All versions), Sinteso FS20 EN X200 Cloud Distribution MP8 (All versions &lt; V4.3.5618), Sinteso FS20 EN X300 Cloud Distribution MP7 (All versions), Sinteso FS20 EN X300 Cloud Distribution MP8 (All versions &lt; V4.3.5617), Sinteso Mobile (All versions). The network communication library in affected systems insufficiently validates HMAC values which might result in a buffer overread.
This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to crash the network service.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22040|2024-05-15T07:23:53.096Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 10:21:54 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>