<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Siemens -- RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) EU</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/siemens/ruggedcom%20rm1224%20lte%284g%29%20eu.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Siemens -- RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) EU</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:22:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44318|2024-08-02T19:59:51.959Z -- siemens -- ruggedcom%20rm1224%20lte%284g%29%20eu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44318</link>
      <description>Affected devices use a hardcoded key to obfuscate the configuration backup that an administrator can export from the device. This could allow an authenticated attacker with administrative privileges or an attacker that obtains a configuration backup to extract configuration information from the exported file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44318|2024-08-02T19:59:51.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44374|2024-08-02T20:07:33.316Z -- siemens -- ruggedcom%20rm1224%20lte%284g%29%20eu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44374</link>
      <description>Affected devices allow to change the password, but insufficiently check which password is to be changed. With this  an authenticated attacker could, under certain conditions, be able to change the password of another, potential admin user allowing her to escalate her privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44374|2024-08-02T20:07:33.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44322|2024-08-02T19:59:52.069Z -- siemens -- ruggedcom%20rm1224%20lte%284g%29%20eu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44322</link>
      <description>Affected devices can be configured to send emails when certain events occur on the device. When presented with an invalid response from the SMTP server, the device triggers an error that disrupts email sending. An attacker with access to the network can use this to do disable notification of users when certain events occur.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44322|2024-08-02T19:59:52.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44319|2024-08-02T19:59:52.078Z -- siemens -- ruggedcom%20rm1224%20lte%284g%29%20eu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44319</link>
      <description>Affected devices use a weak checksum algorithm to protect the configuration backup that an administrator can export from the device. This could allow an authenticated attacker with administrative privileges or an attacker that tricks a legitimate administrator to upload a modified configuration file to change the configuration of an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44319|2024-08-02T19:59:52.078Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44321|2024-08-02T19:59:51.947Z -- siemens -- ruggedcom%20rm1224%20lte%284g%29%20eu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44321</link>
      <description>Affected devices do not properly validate the length of inputs when performing certain configuration changes in the web interface allowing an authenticated attacker to cause a denial of service condition. The device needs to be restarted for the web interface to become available again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44321|2024-08-02T19:59:51.947Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44320|2024-08-02T19:59:52.158Z -- siemens -- ruggedcom%20rm1224%20lte%284g%29%20eu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44320</link>
      <description>Affected devices do not properly validate the authentication when performing certain modifications in the web interface allowing an authenticated attacker to influence the user interface configured by an administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44320|2024-08-02T19:59:52.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44317|2024-08-02T19:59:52.114Z -- siemens -- ruggedcom%20rm1224%20lte%284g%29%20eu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44317</link>
      <description>Affected products do not properly validate the content of uploaded X509 certificates which could allow an attacker with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary code on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44317|2024-08-02T19:59:52.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44373|2024-08-02T20:07:32.915Z -- siemens -- ruggedcom%20rm1224%20lte%284g%29%20eu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44373</link>
      <description>Affected devices do not properly sanitize an input field.  This could allow an authenticated remote attacker with administrative privileges to inject code or spawn a system root shell. Follow-up of CVE-2022-36323.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44373|2024-08-02T20:07:32.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
