<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Siemens -- SICAM PAS/PQS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/siemens/sicam%20pas%2Fpqs.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Siemens -- SICAM PAS/PQS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:22:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43722|2024-08-03T13:40:06.158Z -- siemens -- sicam%20pas%2Fpqs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43722</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SICAM PAS/PQS (All versions &lt; V7.0). Affected software does not properly secure a folder containing library files. This could allow an attacker to place a custom malicious DLL in this folder which is then run with SYSTEM rights when a service is started that requires this DLL. At the time of assigning the CVE, the affected firmware version of the component has already been superseded by succeeding mainline versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43722|2024-08-03T13:40:06.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43723|2024-08-03T13:40:06.444Z -- siemens -- sicam%20pas%2Fpqs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43723</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SICAM PAS/PQS (All versions &lt; V7.0), SICAM PAS/PQS (All versions &gt;= 7.0 &lt; V8.06). Affected software does not properly validate the input for a certain parameter in the s7ontcp.dll. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to send messages and create a denial of service condition as the application crashes. At the time of assigning the CVE, the affected firmware version of the component has already been superseded by succeeding mainline versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43723|2024-08-03T13:40:06.444Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43724|2024-08-03T13:40:06.447Z -- siemens -- sicam%20pas%2Fpqs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43724</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SICAM PAS/PQS (All versions &lt; V7.0). Affected software transmits the database credentials for the inbuilt SQL server in cleartext. In combination with the by default enabled xp_cmdshell feature unauthenticated remote attackers could execute custom OS commands. At the time of assigning the CVE, the affected firmware version of the component has already been superseded by succeeding mainline versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43724|2024-08-03T13:40:06.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
