<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Siemens -- SIMATIC S7-PLCSIM V5.4</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/siemens/simatic%20s7-plcsim%20v5.4.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Siemens -- SIMATIC S7-PLCSIM V5.4</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25675|2024-08-03T20:11:28.318Z -- siemens -- simatic%20s7-plcsim%20v5.4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25675</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC S7-PLCSIM V5.4 (All versions). An attacker with local access to the system could cause a Denial-of-Service condition in the application when it is used to open a specially crafted file. As a consequence, a divide by zero operation could occur and cause the application to terminate unexpectedly and must be restarted to restore the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25675|2024-08-03T20:11:28.318Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 17:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25673|2024-08-03T20:11:28.393Z -- siemens -- simatic%20s7-plcsim%20v5.4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25673</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC S7-PLCSIM V5.4 (All versions). An attacker with local access to the system could cause a Denial-of-Service condition in the application when it is used to open a specially crafted file. As a consequence, the application could enter an infinite loop, become unresponsive and must be restarted to restore the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25673|2024-08-03T20:11:28.393Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 17:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25674|2024-08-03T20:11:27.880Z -- siemens -- simatic%20s7-plcsim%20v5.4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25674</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC S7-PLCSIM V5.4 (All versions). An attacker with local access to the system could cause a Denial-of-Service condition in the application when it is used to open a specially crafted file. As a consequence, a NULL pointer deference condition could cause the application to terminate unexpectedly and must be restarted to restore the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25674|2024-08-03T20:11:27.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 17:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
