<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Siemens -- SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/siemens/sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Siemens -- SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 10:23:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18329|2024-08-05T01:54:13.454Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18329</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server can cause a Denial-of-Service condition and potentially gain remote code execution by sending specifically crafted packets to 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18323, CVE-2019-18324, CVE-2019-18325, CVE-2019-18326, CVE-2019-18327, CVE-2019-18328, and CVE-2019-18330. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18329|2024-08-05T01:54:13.454Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18292|2024-08-05T01:47:14.122Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18292</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could trigger a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18290, CVE-2019-18291, CVE-2019-18294, CVE-2019-18298, CVE-2019-18299, CVE-2019-18300, CVE-2019-18301, CVE-2019-18302, CVE-2019-18303, CVE-2019-18304, CVE-2019-18305, CVE-2019-18306, and CVE-2019-18307. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18292|2024-08-05T01:47:14.122Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18307|2024-08-05T01:47:14.140Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18307</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could trigger a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18290, CVE-2019-18291, CVE-2019-18292, CVE-2019-18294, CVE-2019-18298, CVE-2019-18299, CVE-2019-18300, CVE-2019-18301, CVE-2019-18302, CVE-2019-18303, CVE-2019-18304, CVE-2019-18305, and CVE-2019-18306. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18307|2024-08-05T01:47:14.140Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18323|2024-08-05T01:54:14.271Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18323</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could cause a Denial-of-Service condition and potentially gain remote code execution by sending specifically crafted packets to 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18324, CVE-2019-18325, CVE-2019-18326, CVE-2019-18327, CVE-2019-18328, CVE-2019-18329, and CVE-2019-18330. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18323|2024-08-05T01:54:14.271Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18295|2024-08-05T01:47:14.164Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18295</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could trigger a Denial-of-Service condition and potentially gain remote code execution by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18289, CVE-2019-18293, and CVE-2019-18296. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18295|2024-08-05T01:47:14.164Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18325|2024-08-05T01:54:12.854Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18325</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server can cause a Denial-of-Service condition and potentially gain remote code execution by sending specifically crafted packets to 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18323, CVE-2019-18324, CVE-2019-18326, CVE-2019-18327, CVE-2019-18328, CVE-2019-18329, and CVE-2019-18330. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18325|2024-08-05T01:54:12.854Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18326|2024-08-05T01:54:14.095Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18326</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server can cause a Denial-of-Service condition and potentially gain remote code execution by sending specifically crafted packets to 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18323, CVE-2019-18324, CVE-2019-18325, CVE-2019-18327, CVE-2019-18328, CVE-2019-18329, and CVE-2019-18330. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18326|2024-08-05T01:54:14.095Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18300|2024-08-05T01:47:14.212Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18300</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server can trigger a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18290, CVE-2019-18291, CVE-2019-18292, CVE-2019-18294, CVE-2019-18298, CVE-2019-18299, CVE-2019-18301, CVE-2019-18302, CVE-2019-18303, CVE-2019-18304, CVE-2019-18305, CVE-2019-18306, and CVE-2019-18307. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18300|2024-08-05T01:47:14.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18291|2024-08-05T01:47:14.216Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18291</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could trigger a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18290, CVE-2019-18292, CVE-2019-18294, CVE-2019-18298, CVE-2019-18299, CVE-2019-18300, CVE-2019-18301, CVE-2019-18302, CVE-2019-18303, CVE-2019-18304, CVE-2019-18305, CVE-2019-18306, and CVE-2019-18307. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18291|2024-08-05T01:47:14.216Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18302|2024-08-05T01:47:14.167Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18302</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server can trigger a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18290, CVE-2019-18291, CVE-2019-18292, CVE-2019-18294, CVE-2019-18298, CVE-2019-18299, CVE-2019-18300, CVE-2019-18301, CVE-2019-18303, CVE-2019-18304, CVE-2019-18305, CVE-2019-18306, and CVE-2019-18307. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18302|2024-08-05T01:47:14.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18304|2024-08-05T01:47:14.161Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18304</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server can trigger a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18290, CVE-2019-18291, CVE-2019-18292, CVE-2019-18294, CVE-2019-18298, CVE-2019-18299, CVE-2019-18300, CVE-2019-18301, CVE-2019-18302, CVE-2019-18303, CVE-2019-18305, CVE-2019-18306, and CVE-2019-18307. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18304|2024-08-05T01:47:14.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18308|2024-08-05T01:54:13.307Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18308</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with local access to the MS3000 Server and a low privileged user account could gain root privileges by manipulating specific files in the local file system. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18309. Please note that an attacker needs to have local access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18308|2024-08-05T01:54:13.307Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18297|2024-08-05T01:47:14.109Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18297</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with local access to the MS3000 Server and low privileges could gain root privileges by sending specifically crafted packets to a named pipe. Please note that an attacker needs to have local access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18297|2024-08-05T01:47:14.109Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18301|2024-08-05T01:47:14.190Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18301</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server can trigger a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18290, CVE-2019-18291, CVE-2019-18292, CVE-2019-18294, CVE-2019-18298, CVE-2019-18299, CVE-2019-18300, CVE-2019-18302, CVE-2019-18303, CVE-2019-18304, CVE-2019-18305, CVE-2019-18306, and CVE-2019-18307. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18301|2024-08-05T01:47:14.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18328|2024-08-05T01:54:13.301Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18328</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server can cause a Denial-of-Service condition and potentially gain remote code execution by sending specifically crafted packets to 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18323, CVE-2019-18324, CVE-2019-18325, CVE-2019-18326, CVE-2019-18327, CVE-2019-18329, and CVE-2019-18330. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18328|2024-08-05T01:54:13.301Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18330|2024-08-05T01:54:13.278Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18330</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could cause a Denial-of-Service condition and potentially gain remote code execution by sending specifically crafted packets to 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18323, CVE-2019-18324, CVE-2019-18325, CVE-2019-18326, CVE-2019-18327, CVE-2019-18328, and CVE-2019-18329. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18330|2024-08-05T01:54:13.278Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18290|2024-08-05T01:47:14.161Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18290</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could trigger a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18291, CVE-2019-18292, CVE-2019-18294, CVE-2019-18298, CVE-2019-18299, CVE-2019-18300, CVE-2019-18301, CVE-2019-18302, CVE-2019-18303, CVE-2019-18304, CVE-2019-18305, CVE-2019-18306, and CVE-2019-18307. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18290|2024-08-05T01:47:14.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18322|2024-08-05T01:54:12.859Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18322</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could be able to read and write arbitrary files on the local file system by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18321. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18322|2024-08-05T01:54:12.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18327|2024-08-05T01:54:13.389Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18327</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server can cause a Denial-of-Service condition and potentially gain remote code execution by sending specifically crafted packets to 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18323, CVE-2019-18324, CVE-2019-18325, CVE-2019-18326, CVE-2019-18328, CVE-2019-18329, and CVE-2019-18330. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18327|2024-08-05T01:54:13.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18298|2024-08-05T01:47:14.157Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18298</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could trigger a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18290, CVE-2019-18291, CVE-2019-18292, CVE-2019-18294, CVE-2019-18299, CVE-2019-18300, CVE-2019-18301, CVE-2019-18302, CVE-2019-18303, CVE-2019-18304, CVE-2019-18305, CVE-2019-18306, and CVE-2019-18307. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18298|2024-08-05T01:47:14.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18311|2024-08-05T01:54:12.839Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18311</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could trigger a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specifically crafted packets to port 7061/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18310. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18311|2024-08-05T01:54:12.839Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18294|2024-08-05T01:47:14.156Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18294</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could trigger a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18290, CVE-2019-18291, CVE-2019-18292, CVE-2019-18298, CVE-2019-18299, CVE-2019-18300, CVE-2019-18301, CVE-2019-18302, CVE-2019-18303, CVE-2019-18304, CVE-2019-18305, CVE-2019-18306, and CVE-2019-18307. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18294|2024-08-05T01:47:14.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18306|2024-08-05T01:47:14.163Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could trigger a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18290, CVE-2019-18291, CVE-2019-18292, CVE-2019-18294, CVE-2019-18298, CVE-2019-18299, CVE-2019-18300, CVE-2019-18301, CVE-2019-18302, CVE-2019-18303, CVE-2019-18304, CVE-2019-18305, and CVE-2019-18307. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18306|2024-08-05T01:47:14.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18293|2024-08-05T01:47:14.161Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could trigger a Denial-of-Service condition and potentially gain remote code execution by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18289, CVE-2019-18295, and CVE-2019-18296. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18293|2024-08-05T01:47:14.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18324|2024-08-05T01:54:13.588Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18324</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server can cause a Denial-of-Service condition and potentially gain remote code execution by sending specifically crafted packets to 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18323, CVE-2019-18325, CVE-2019-18326, CVE-2019-18327, CVE-2019-18328, CVE-2019-18329, and CVE-2019-18330. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18324|2024-08-05T01:54:13.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18313|2024-08-05T01:54:13.298Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18313</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could gain remote code execution by sending specifically crafted objects to one of the RPC services. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18313|2024-08-05T01:54:13.298Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18296|2024-08-05T01:47:14.139Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18296</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could trigger a Denial-of-Service condition and potentially gain remote code execution by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18289, CVE-2019-18293, and CVE-2019-18295. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18296|2024-08-05T01:47:14.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18303|2024-08-05T01:47:14.192Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18303</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server can trigger a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18290, CVE-2019-18291, CVE-2019-18292, CVE-2019-18294, CVE-2019-18298, CVE-2019-18299, CVE-2019-18300, CVE-2019-18301, CVE-2019-18302, CVE-2019-18304, CVE-2019-18305, CVE-2019-18306, and CVE-2019-18307. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18303|2024-08-05T01:47:14.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18321|2024-08-05T01:54:13.332Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18321</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could be able to read and write arbitrary files on the local file system by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18322. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18321|2024-08-05T01:54:13.332Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18289|2024-08-05T01:47:14.164Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18289</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could trigger a Denial-of-Service condition and potentially gain remote code execution by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18293, CVE-2019-18295, and CVE-2019-18296. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18289|2024-08-05T01:47:14.164Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18305|2024-08-05T01:47:14.168Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18305</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could trigger a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18290, CVE-2019-18291, CVE-2019-18292, CVE-2019-18294, CVE-2019-18298, CVE-2019-18299, CVE-2019-18300, CVE-2019-18301, CVE-2019-18302, CVE-2019-18303, CVE-2019-18304, CVE-2019-18306, and CVE-2019-18307. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18305|2024-08-05T01:47:14.168Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18299|2024-08-05T01:47:14.155Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18299</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server can trigger a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specifically crafted packets to port 5010/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18290, CVE-2019-18291, CVE-2019-18292, CVE-2019-18294, CVE-2019-18298, CVE-2019-18300, CVE-2019-18301, CVE-2019-18302, CVE-2019-18303, CVE-2019-18304, CVE-2019-18305, CVE-2019-18306, and CVE-2019-18307. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18299|2024-08-05T01:47:14.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18310|2024-08-05T01:54:12.814Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could trigger a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specifically crafted packets to port 7061/tcp. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18311. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18310|2024-08-05T01:54:12.814Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18309|2024-08-05T01:54:12.833Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with local access to the MS3000 Server and a low privileged user account could gain root privileges by manipulating specific files in the local file system. This vulnerability is independent from CVE-2019-18308. Please note that an attacker needs to have local access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18309|2024-08-05T01:54:12.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18312|2024-08-05T01:54:12.859Z -- siemens -- sppa-t3000%20ms3000%20migration%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18312</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SPPA-T3000 MS3000 Migration Server (All versions). An attacker with network access to the MS3000 Server could be able to enumerate running RPC services. Please note that an attacker needs to have network access to the MS3000 in order to exploit this vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18312|2024-08-05T01:54:12.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
