<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for HID Mercury -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/hid%20mercury/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for HID Mercury -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:43:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31486|2024-09-16T18:03:16.897Z -- hid%20mercury -- lp1501
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31486</link>
      <description>An authenticated attacker can send a specially crafted route to the “edit_route.cgi” binary and have it execute shell commands. This vulnerability impacts products based on HID Mercury Intelligent Controllers LP1501, LP1502, LP2500, LP4502, and EP4502 which contain firmware versions prior to 1.303 for the LP series and 1.297 for the EP series. An attacker with this level of access on the device can monitor all communications sent to and from this device, modify onboard relays, change configuration files, or cause the device to become unstable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31486|2024-09-16T18:03:16.897Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 16:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31483|2024-09-16T18:55:31.907Z -- hid%20mercury -- lp1501
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31483</link>
      <description>An authenticated attacker can upload a file with a filename including “..” and “/” to achieve the ability to upload the desired file anywhere on the filesystem. This vulnerability impacts products based on HID Mercury Intelligent Controllers LP1501, LP1502, LP2500, LP4502, and EP4502 which contain firmware versions prior to 1.271. This allows a malicious actor to overwrite sensitive system files and install a startup service to gain remote access to the underlaying Linux operating system with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31483|2024-09-16T18:55:31.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 16:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31481|2024-09-16T16:12:27.210Z -- hid%20mercury -- lp1501
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31481</link>
      <description>An unauthenticated attacker can send a specially crafted update file to the device that can overflow a buffer. This vulnerability impacts products based on HID Mercury Intelligent Controllers LP1501, LP1502, LP2500, LP4502, and EP4502 which contain firmware versions prior to 1.302 for the LP series and 1.296 for the EP series. The overflowed data can allow the attacker to manipulate the “normal” code execution to that of their choosing. An attacker with this level of access on the device can monitor all communications sent to and from this device, modify onboard relays, change configuration files, or cause the device to become unstable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31481|2024-09-16T16:12:27.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 16:38:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
