<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Ashlar-Vellum -- Cobalt</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ashlar-vellum/cobalt.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Ashlar-Vellum -- Cobalt</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:21:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34311|2024-07-24T20:44:40.024Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34311</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt Untrusted Pointer Dereference Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied value prior to dereferencing it as a pointer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19879.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34311|2024-07-24T20:44:40.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35711|2024-07-23T17:18:24.455Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35711</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt XE File Parsing Untrusted Pointer Dereference Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XE files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied value prior to dereferencing it as a pointer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20189.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35711|2024-07-23T17:18:24.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35709|2024-07-23T17:18:42.080Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35709</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19928.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35709|2024-07-23T17:18:42.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42101|2024-06-04T17:25:24.776Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42101</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of AR files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20418.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42101|2024-06-04T17:25:24.776Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42102|2024-06-04T17:25:17.742Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42102</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of AR files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20409.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42102|2024-06-04T17:25:17.742Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42103|2024-06-04T17:25:13.816Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42103</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of AR files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20660.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42103|2024-06-04T17:25:13.816Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42104|2024-06-04T17:25:10.751Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42104</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of AR files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20630.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42104|2024-06-04T17:25:10.751Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42105|2024-05-03T02:13:15.779Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42105</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of AR files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20562.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42105|2024-05-03T02:13:15.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34305|2024-06-04T17:21:21.346Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34305</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of X_B or X_T files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18637.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34305|2024-06-04T17:21:21.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34309|2024-06-04T17:21:20.132Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34309</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt Untrusted Pointer Dereference Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied value prior to dereferencing it as a pointer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19876.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34309|2024-06-04T17:21:20.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34299|2024-06-04T17:21:19.295Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34299</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17910.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34299|2024-06-04T17:21:19.295Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34304|2024-06-04T17:21:16.347Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34304</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt Out-Of-Bounds Access Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of IGS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory access past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18006.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34304|2024-06-04T17:21:16.347Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34289|2024-06-04T17:21:15.930Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34289</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of AR files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17985.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34289|2024-06-04T17:21:15.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34303|2024-06-04T17:21:15.497Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34303</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of VC6 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17987.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34303|2024-06-04T17:21:15.497Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34293|2024-06-04T17:21:14.636Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34293</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of X_B or X_T files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18636.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34293|2024-06-04T17:21:14.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34292|2024-06-04T17:21:14.218Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34292</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of X_B or X_T files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write before the start of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18552.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34292|2024-06-04T17:21:14.218Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34302|2024-06-04T17:21:13.807Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34302</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17865.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34302|2024-06-04T17:21:13.807Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34288|2024-06-04T17:21:12.978Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34288</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt XE File Parsing Uninitialized Pointer Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XE files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of a pointer prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17966.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34288|2024-06-04T17:21:12.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34291|2024-06-04T17:21:11.725Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34291</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of X_B or X_T files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18401.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34291|2024-06-04T17:21:11.725Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34287|2024-06-04T17:21:11.322Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34287</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17892.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34287|2024-06-04T17:21:11.322Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34301|2024-05-03T01:57:24.319Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34301</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Untrusted Pointer Dereference Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied value prior to dereferencing it as a pointer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17909.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34301|2024-05-03T01:57:24.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34300|2024-06-04T17:21:10.462Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34300</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt XE File Parsing Untrusted Pointer Dereference Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XE files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied value prior to dereferencing it as a pointer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17948.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34300|2024-06-04T17:21:10.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34286|2024-06-04T17:21:09.621Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34286</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17891.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34286|2024-06-04T17:21:09.621Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34290|2024-06-04T17:21:09.220Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34290</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of 3DS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18007.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34290|2024-06-04T17:21:09.220Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34311|2024-05-03T01:57:31.856Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34311</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt Untrusted Pointer Dereference Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied value prior to dereferencing it as a pointer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19879.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34311|2024-05-03T01:57:31.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34310|2024-06-04T17:21:06.141Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34310</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt Uninitialized Memory Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19878.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34310|2024-06-04T17:21:06.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44437|2024-06-04T17:19:38.457Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44437</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt Uncontrolled Search Path Element Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of various file types. The process loads a library from an unsecured location. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21540.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44437|2024-06-04T17:19:38.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35715|2024-06-04T17:18:39.898Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35715</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Uninitialized Memory Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of AR files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20408.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35715|2024-06-04T17:18:39.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35714|2024-06-04T17:18:34.091Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35714</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt IGS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of IGS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read before the start of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18005.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35714|2024-06-04T17:18:34.091Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35709|2024-05-03T01:57:32.608Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35709</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19928.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35709|2024-05-03T01:57:32.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35713|2024-06-04T17:18:25.658Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35713</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt XE File Parsing Uninitialized Memory Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XE files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20201.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35713|2024-06-04T17:18:25.658Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35712|2024-06-04T17:18:25.222Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35712</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt XE File Parsing Uninitialized Memory Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XE files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20200.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35712|2024-06-04T17:18:25.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35711|2024-05-03T01:57:34.139Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35711</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt XE File Parsing Untrusted Pointer Dereference Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XE files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied value prior to dereferencing it as a pointer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20189.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35711|2024-05-03T01:57:34.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35710|2024-06-04T17:18:14.600Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35710</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19956.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35710|2024-06-04T17:18:14.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35716|2024-06-04T17:18:09.099Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35716</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of AR files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20417.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35716|2024-06-04T17:18:09.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42105|2024-07-23T16:33:20.528Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42105</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of AR files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20562.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42105|2024-07-23T16:33:20.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34301|2024-07-24T17:41:24.961Z -- ashlar-vellum -- cobalt</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34301</link>
      <description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Untrusted Pointer Dereference Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied value prior to dereferencing it as a pointer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17909.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34301|2024-07-24T17:41:24.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
