<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for rickardw -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/rickardw/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for rickardw -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:19:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3568|2024-08-03T01:14:02.525Z -- rickardw -- imagemagick%20engine
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3568</link>
      <description>The ImageMagick Engine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to deserialization of untrusted input via the 'cli_path' parameter in versions up to, and including 1.7.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated users to call files using a PHAR wrapper, granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link, that will deserialize and call arbitrary PHP Objects that can be used to perform a variety of malicious actions granted a POP chain is also present. It also requires that the attacker is successful in uploading a file with the serialized payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3568|2024-08-03T01:14:02.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 23:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2441|2024-08-03T00:39:06.412Z -- rickardw -- imagemagick%20engine
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2441</link>
      <description>The ImageMagick Engine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to remote code execution via the 'cli_path' parameter in versions up to, and including 1.7.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated users to run arbitrary commands leading to remote command execution, granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. This makes it possible for an attacker to create and or modify files hosted on the server which can easily grant attackers backdoor access to the affected server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2441|2024-08-03T00:39:06.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 07:29:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
