<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Ragentek -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ragentek/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Ragentek -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 04:23:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6564|2024-08-06T01:36:28.064Z -- ragentek -- android%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6564</link>
      <description>Android devices with code from Ragentek contain a privileged binary that performs over-the-air (OTA) update checks. Additionally, there are multiple techniques used to hide the execution of this binary. This behavior could be described as a rootkit. This binary, which resides as /system/bin/debugs, runs with root privileges and does not communicate over an encrypted channel. The binary has been shown to communicate with three hosts via HTTP: oyag[.]lhzbdvm[.]com oyag[.]prugskh[.]net oyag[.]prugskh[.]com Server responses to requests sent by the debugs binary include functionalities to execute arbitrary commands as root, install applications, or update configurations. Examples of a request sent by the client binary: POST /pagt/agent?data={"name":"c_regist","details":{...}} HTTP/1. 1 Host: 114.80.68.223 Connection: Close An example response from the server could be: HTTP/1.1 200 OK {"code": "01", "name": "push_commands", "details": {"server_id": "1" , "title": "Test Command", "comments": "Test", "commands": "touch /tmp/test"}} This binary is reported to be present in the following devices: BLU Studio G BLU Studio G Plus BLU Studio 6.0 HD BLU Studio X BLU Studio X Plus BLU Studio C HD Infinix Hot X507 Infinix Hot 2 X510 Infinix Zero X506 Infinix Zero 2 X509 DOOGEE Voyager 2 DG310 LEAGOO Lead 5 LEAGOO Lead 6 LEAGOO Lead 3i LEAGOO Lead 2S LEAGOO Alfa 6 IKU Colorful K45i Beeline Pro 2 XOLO Cube 5.0</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6564|2024-08-06T01:36:28.064Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
