<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for wireapp -- wire-server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/wireapp/wire-server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for wireapp -- wire-server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31122|2024-08-03T07:11:39.209Z -- wireapp -- wire-server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31122</link>
      <description>Wire is an encrypted communication and collaboration platform. Versions prior to 2022-07-12/Chart 4.19.0 are subject to Token Recipient Confusion. If an attacker has certain details of SAML IdP metadata, and configures their own SAML on the same backend, the attacker can delete all SAML authenticated accounts of a targeted team, Authenticate as a user of the attacked team and create arbitrary accounts in the context of the team if it is not managed by SCIM. This issue is fixed in wire-server 2022-07-12 and is already deployed on all Wire managed services. On-premise instances of wire-server need to be updated to 2022-07-12/Chart 4.19.0, so that their backends are no longer affected. As a workaround, the risk of an attack can be reduced by disabling SAML configuration for teams (galley.config.settings.featureFlags.sso). Helm overrides are located in `values/wire-server/values.yaml` Note that the ability to configure SAML SSO as a team is disabled by default for on-premise installations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31122|2024-08-03T07:11:39.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21396|2024-08-03T18:09:16.005Z -- wireapp -- wire-server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21396</link>
      <description>wire-server is an open-source back end for Wire, a secure collaboration platform. In wire-server from version 2021-02-16 and before version 2021-03-02, the client metadata of all users was exposed in the `GET /users/list-clients` endpoint. The endpoint could be used by any logged in user who could request client details of any other user (no connection required) as far as they can find their User ID. The exposed metadata included id, class, type, location, time, and cookie. A user on a Wire backend could use this endpoint to find registration time and location for each device for a given list of users. As a workaround, remove `/list-clients` from nginx config. This has been fixed in version 2021-03-02.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21396|2024-08-03T18:09:16.005Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 21:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23610|2024-08-03T03:43:46.981Z -- wireapp -- wire-server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23610</link>
      <description>wire-server provides back end services for Wire, an open source messenger. In versions of wire-server prior to the 2022-01-27 release, it was possible to craft DSA Signatures to bypass SAML SSO and impersonate any Wire user with SAML credentials. In teams with SAML, but without SCIM, it was possible to create new accounts with fake SAML credentials. Under certain conditions that can be established by an attacker, an upstream library for parsing, rendering, signing, and validating SAML XML data was accepting public keys as trusted that were provided by the attacker in the signature. As a consequence, the attacker could login as any user in any Wire team with SAML SSO enabled. If SCIM was not enabled, the attacker could also create new users with new SAML NameIDs. In order to exploit this vulnerability, the attacker needs to know the SSO login code (distributed to all team members with SAML credentials and visible in the Team Management app), the SAML EntityID identifying the IdP (a URL not considered sensitive, but usually hard to guess, also visible in Team Management), and the SAML NameID of the user (usually an email address or a nick). The issue has been fixed in wire-server `2022-01-27` and is already deployed on all Wire managed services. On premise instances of wire-server need to be updated to `2022-01-27`, so that their backends are no longer affected. There are currently no known workarounds. More detailed information about how to reproduce the vulnerability and mitigation strategies is available in the GitHub Security Advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23610|2024-08-03T03:43:46.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 17:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
