<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for code-projects -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/code-projects/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for code-projects -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 22:22:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3060|2024-07-19T18:54:01.593Z -- code-projects -- agro-school%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3060</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Agro-School Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function doAddQuestion of the file btn_functions.php. The manipulation of the argument Question leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. VDB-230566 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In code-projects Agro-School Management System 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Das betrifft die Funktion doAddQuestion der Datei btn_functions.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments Question mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3060|2024-07-19T18:54:01.593Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 13:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0462|2024-07-19T17:54:18.456Z -- code-projects -- online%20faculty%20clearance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0462</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Faculty Clearance 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /production/designee_view_status.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument haydi leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250567.
In code-projects Online Faculty Clearance 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /production/designee_view_status.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments haydi mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0462|2024-07-19T17:54:18.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 17:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5829|2024-07-19T17:32:55.206Z -- code-projects -- admission%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5829</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Admission Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file student_avatar.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243728.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Admission Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei student_avatar.php. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5829|2024-07-19T17:32:55.206Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6745|2024-07-15T11:00:06.332Z -- code-projects -- simple%20ticket%20booking</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6745</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Simple Ticket Booking 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file adminauthenticate.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument email/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271476.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in code-projects Simple Ticket Booking 1.0 entdeckt. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei adminauthenticate.php der Komponente Login. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments email/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6745|2024-07-15T11:00:06.332Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6653|2024-07-11T12:17:31.649Z -- code-projects -- simple%20task%20list</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6653</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Task List 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file loginForm.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271060.
In code-projects Simple Task List 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei loginForm.php der Komponente Login. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6653|2024-07-11T12:17:31.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1829|2024-07-05T17:21:59.300Z -- code-projects -- library%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1829</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Library System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file Source/librarian/user/student/registration.php. The manipulation of the argument email/regno/phone/username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254617 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In code-projects Library System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei Source/librarian/user/student/registration.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments email/regno/phone/username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1829|2024-07-05T17:21:59.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 18:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2927|2024-03-26T23:00:08.667Z -- code-projects -- mobile%20shop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2927</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Mobile Shop 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file Details.php of the component Login Page. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258000.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in code-projects Mobile Shop 1.0 ausgemacht. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei Details.php der Komponente Login Page. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2927|2024-03-26T23:00:08.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 23:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3000|2024-03-27T21:31:04.286Z -- code-projects -- online%20book%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3000</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Online Book System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password/login_username/login_password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-258202 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In code-projects Online Book System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /index.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments username/password/login_username/login_password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3000|2024-03-27T21:31:04.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3369|2024-04-06T11:00:05.805Z -- code-projects -- car%20rental</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3369</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Car Rental 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file add-vehicle.php. The manipulation of the argument Upload Image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259490 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Car Rental 1.0 entdeckt. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei add-vehicle.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments Upload Image mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3369|2024-04-06T11:00:05.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3001|2024-03-27T21:31:05.664Z -- code-projects -- online%20book%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3001</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Online Book System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Product.php. The manipulation of the argument value leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258203.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Online Book System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /Product.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments value mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3001|2024-03-27T21:31:05.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3002|2024-03-27T22:00:05.365Z -- code-projects -- online%20book%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3002</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Online Book System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /description.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258204.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in code-projects Online Book System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /description.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments ID mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3002|2024-03-27T22:00:05.365Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 22:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3003|2024-03-27T22:00:06.795Z -- code-projects -- online%20book%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3003</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Online Book System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /cart.php. The manipulation of the argument quantity/remove leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-258205 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In code-projects Online Book System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /cart.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments quantity/remove mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3003|2024-03-27T22:00:06.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 22:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3004|2024-03-27T22:31:03.985Z -- code-projects -- online%20book%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3004</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Book System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Product.php. The manipulation of the argument value leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-258206 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Online Book System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /Product.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments value mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3004|2024-03-27T22:31:03.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 22:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4972|2024-06-04T17:54:59.072Z -- code-projects -- simple%20chat%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4972</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Simple Chat System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument email/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-264537 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in code-projects Simple Chat System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /login.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments email/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4972|2024-06-04T17:54:59.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4973|2024-06-04T17:55:39.190Z -- code-projects -- simple%20chat%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4973</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Simple Chat System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /register.php. The manipulation of the argument name/number/address leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-264538 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In code-projects Simple Chat System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /register.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments name/number/address mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4973|2024-06-04T17:55:39.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4974|2024-06-04T17:56:09.974Z -- code-projects -- simple%20chat%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4974</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in code-projects Simple Chat System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /register.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-264540.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in code-projects Simple Chat System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /register.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4974|2024-06-04T17:56:09.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4975|2024-06-04T17:56:18.779Z -- code-projects -- simple%20chat%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4975</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Simple Chat System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Message Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-264539.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Simple Chat System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Komponente Message Handler. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4975|2024-06-04T17:56:18.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 10:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1826|2024-03-04T18:25:04.483Z -- code-projects -- library%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1826</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Library System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file Source/librarian/user/student/login.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-254614 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In code-projects Library System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei Source/librarian/user/student/login.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments username/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1826|2024-03-04T18:25:04.483Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1830|2024-03-04T18:25:06.518Z -- code-projects -- library%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1830</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Library System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file Source/librarian/user/student/lost-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-254618 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Library System 1.0 ausgemacht. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei Source/librarian/user/student/lost-password.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments email mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1830|2024-03-04T18:25:06.518Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 18:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1827|2024-03-04T18:25:26.738Z -- code-projects -- library%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1827</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Library System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file Source/librarian/user/teacher/login.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254615.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Library System 1.0 gefunden. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei Source/librarian/user/teacher/login.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments username/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1827|2024-03-04T18:25:26.738Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1820|2024-03-04T18:25:00.730Z -- code-projects -- crime%20reporting%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1820</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Crime Reporting System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file inchargelogin.php. The manipulation of the argument email/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254608.
In code-projects Crime Reporting System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei inchargelogin.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments email/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1820|2024-03-04T18:25:00.730Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1821|2024-03-04T18:24:58.698Z -- code-projects -- crime%20reporting%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1821</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Crime Reporting System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file police_add.php. The manipulation of the argument police_name/police_id/police_spec/password leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254609 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Crime Reporting System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei police_add.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments police_name/police_id/police_spec/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1821|2024-03-04T18:24:58.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1828|2024-03-04T18:25:24.567Z -- code-projects -- library%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1828</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Library System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file Source/librarian/user/teacher/registration.php. The manipulation of the argument email/idno/phone/username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254616.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in code-projects Library System 1.0 ausgemacht. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei Source/librarian/user/teacher/registration.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments email/idno/phone/username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1828|2024-03-04T18:25:24.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 18:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1829|2024-03-04T18:25:21.797Z -- code-projects -- library%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1829</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Library System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file Source/librarian/user/student/registration.php. The manipulation of the argument email/regno/phone/username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254617 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In code-projects Library System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei Source/librarian/user/student/registration.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments email/regno/phone/username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1829|2024-03-04T18:25:21.797Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 18:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5048|2024-06-04T18:02:01.338Z -- code-projects -- budget%20management</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5048</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Budget Management 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument edit leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-264745 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In code-projects Budget Management 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /index.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments edit mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5048|2024-06-04T18:02:01.338Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6653|2024-07-11T13:38:36.522Z -- code-projects -- simple%20task%20list</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6653</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Task List 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file loginForm.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271060.
In code-projects Simple Task List 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei loginForm.php der Komponente Login. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6653|2024-07-11T13:38:36.522Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6653|2024-07-15T12:48:11.272Z -- code-projects -- simple%20task%20list</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6653</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Task List 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file loginForm.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271060.
In code-projects Simple Task List 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei loginForm.php der Komponente Login. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6653|2024-07-15T12:48:11.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1830|2024-07-19T18:04:10.431Z -- code-projects -- library%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1830</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Library System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file Source/librarian/user/student/lost-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-254618 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Library System 1.0 ausgemacht. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei Source/librarian/user/student/lost-password.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments email mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1830|2024-07-19T18:04:10.431Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 18:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
