<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for code-projects -- Crime Reporting System</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/code-projects/crime%20reporting%20system.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for code-projects -- Crime Reporting System</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1821|2024-03-04T18:24:58.698Z -- code-projects -- Crime Reporting System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1821</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Crime Reporting System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file police_add.php. The manipulation of the argument police_name/police_id/police_spec/password leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254609 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Crime Reporting System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei police_add.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments police_name/police_id/police_spec/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1821|2024-03-04T18:24:58.698Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1820|2024-03-04T18:25:00.730Z -- code-projects -- Crime Reporting System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1820</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Crime Reporting System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file inchargelogin.php. The manipulation of the argument email/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-254608.
In code-projects Crime Reporting System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei inchargelogin.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments email/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1820|2024-03-04T18:25:00.730Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>