<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for code-projects -- Dormitory Management System</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/code-projects/dormitory%20management%20system.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for code-projects -- Dormitory Management System</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-0473|2024-02-09T19:10:15.838Z -- code-projects -- Dormitory Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0473</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Dormitory Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file comment.php. The manipulation of the argument com leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250578 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in code-projects Dormitory Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei comment.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments com mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0473|2024-02-09T19:10:15.838Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 21:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0472|2024-02-09T19:10:12.170Z -- code-projects -- Dormitory Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0472</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Dormitory Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file modifyuser.php. The manipulation of the argument mname leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250577 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Dormitory Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei modifyuser.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments mname mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0472|2024-02-09T19:10:12.170Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 21:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0475|2024-02-09T19:10:17.067Z -- code-projects -- Dormitory Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0475</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Dormitory Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file modifyuser.php. The manipulation of the argument user_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250580.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Dormitory Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei modifyuser.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments user_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0475|2024-02-09T19:10:17.067Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0474|2024-02-09T19:10:14.618Z -- code-projects -- Dormitory Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0474</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Dormitory Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250579.
In code-projects Dormitory Management System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei login.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0474|2024-02-09T19:10:14.618Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 22:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>