<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for code-projects -- Fighting Cock Information System</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/code-projects/fighting%20cock%20information%20system.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for code-projects -- Fighting Cock Information System</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-0486|2024-02-09T19:10:53.723Z -- code-projects -- Fighting Cock Information System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0486</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/action/add_con.php. The manipulation of the argument chicken leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250591.
In code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /admin/action/add_con.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments chicken mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0486|2024-02-09T19:10:53.723Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0468|2024-02-09T19:10:09.692Z -- code-projects -- Fighting Cock Information System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0468</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/action/new-father.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250573 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /admin/action/new-father.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments image mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0468|2024-02-09T19:10:09.692Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0487|2024-02-09T19:10:57.375Z -- code-projects -- Fighting Cock Information System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0487</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/action/delete-vaccine.php. The manipulation of the argument ref leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250592.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /admin/action/delete-vaccine.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments ref mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0487|2024-02-09T19:10:57.375Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 12:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0478|2024-02-09T19:10:26.345Z -- code-projects -- Fighting Cock Information System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0478</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/pages/edit_chicken.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250583.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 gefunden. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /admin/pages/edit_chicken.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0478|2024-02-09T19:10:26.345Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 06:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0477|2024-02-09T19:10:25.133Z -- code-projects -- Fighting Cock Information System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0477</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/action/update-deworm.php. The manipulation of the argument usage_deworm leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250582 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /admin/action/update-deworm.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments usage_deworm mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0477|2024-02-09T19:10:25.133Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 06:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0484|2024-02-09T19:10:45.727Z -- code-projects -- Fighting Cock Information System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0484</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/action/update_mother.php. The manipulation of the argument age_mother leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250589 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei admin/action/update_mother.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments age_mother mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0484|2024-02-09T19:10:45.727Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 10:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0488|2024-02-09T19:10:54.966Z -- code-projects -- Fighting Cock Information System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0488</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/action/new-feed.php. The manipulation of the argument type_feed leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250593 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /admin/action/new-feed.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments type_feed mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0488|2024-02-09T19:10:54.966Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 13:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0489|2024-02-09T19:11:02.154Z -- code-projects -- Fighting Cock Information System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0489</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/action/edit_chicken.php. The manipulation of the argument ref leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250594 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /admin/action/edit_chicken.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments ref mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0489|2024-02-09T19:11:02.154Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 13:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0485|2024-02-09T19:10:44.529Z -- code-projects -- Fighting Cock Information System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0485</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin/pages/tables/add_con.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250590 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei admin/pages/tables/add_con.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0485|2024-02-09T19:10:44.529Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>