<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for code-projects -- Online Faculty Clearance</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/code-projects/online%20faculty%20clearance.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for code-projects -- Online Faculty Clearance</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-0464|2024-02-09T19:10:01.165Z -- code-projects -- Online Faculty Clearance
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0464</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Online Faculty Clearance 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file delete_faculty.php of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250569 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in code-projects Online Faculty Clearance 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei delete_faculty.php der Komponente HTTP GET Request Handler. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0464|2024-02-09T19:10:01.165Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0463|2024-02-09T19:09:59.947Z -- code-projects -- Online Faculty Clearance
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0463</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Faculty Clearance 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /production/admin_view_info.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument haydi leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250568.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Online Faculty Clearance 1.0 ausgemacht. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /production/admin_view_info.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments haydi mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0463|2024-02-09T19:09:59.947Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0462|2024-02-09T19:09:43.526Z -- code-projects -- Online Faculty Clearance
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0462</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Faculty Clearance 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /production/designee_view_status.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument haydi leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250567.
In code-projects Online Faculty Clearance 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /production/designee_view_status.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments haydi mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0462|2024-02-09T19:09:43.526Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 17:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0461|2024-02-09T19:09:42.354Z -- code-projects -- Online Faculty Clearance
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0461</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Faculty Clearance 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file deactivate.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument haydi leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250566 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in code-projects Online Faculty Clearance 1.0 ausgemacht. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei deactivate.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments haydi mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0461|2024-02-09T19:09:42.354Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>