<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for code-projects -- Point of Sales and Inventory Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/code-projects/point%20of%20sales%20and%20inventory%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for code-projects -- Point of Sales and Inventory Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:25:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7075|2024-08-02T08:50:07.948Z -- code-projects -- point%20of%20sales%20and%20inventory%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7075</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /main/checkout.php. The manipulation of the argument pt leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-248846 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /main/checkout.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments pt mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7075|2024-08-02T08:50:07.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 12:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
