<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for code-projects -- Restaurant Reservation System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/code-projects/restaurant%20reservation%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for code-projects -- Restaurant Reservation System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 22:22:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-9086|2024-09-22T21:00:07.667Z -- code-projects -- restaurant%20reservation%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9086</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Restaurant Reservation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /filter.php. The manipulation of the argument from/to leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "from" to be affected. But it must be assumed that parameter "to" is affected as well.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in code-projects Restaurant Reservation System 1.0 entdeckt. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /filter.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments from/to mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-9086|2024-09-22T21:00:07.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 21:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-9085|2024-09-22T07:47:57.895Z -- code-projects -- restaurant%20reservation%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9085</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Restaurant Reservation System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument date leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions sid as affected paramater which is incorrect.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Restaurant Reservation System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei index.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments date mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-9085|2024-09-22T07:47:57.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 07:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
