<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for code-projects -- Simple Art Gallery</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/code-projects/simple%20art%20gallery.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for code-projects -- Simple Art Gallery</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 07:22:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1499|2024-08-02T05:49:11.674Z -- code-projects -- simple%20art%20gallery
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1499</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Simple Art Gallery 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file adminHome.php. The manipulation of the argument reach_city leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223399.
In code-projects Simple Art Gallery 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei adminHome.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments reach_city mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1499|2024-08-02T05:49:11.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 19:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1500|2024-08-02T05:49:11.672Z -- code-projects -- simple%20art%20gallery
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1500</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Simple Art Gallery 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file adminHome.php. The manipulation of the argument about_info leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223400.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in code-projects Simple Art Gallery 1.0 entdeckt. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei adminHome.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments about_info mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1500|2024-08-02T05:49:11.672Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
