<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Shandong Star Measurement and Control Equipment -- Heating Network Wireless Monitoring System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/shandong%20star%20measurement%20and%20control%20equipment/heating%20network%20wireless%20monitoring%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Shandong Star Measurement and Control Equipment -- Heating Network Wireless Monitoring System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 23:23:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8705|2024-09-11T22:31:24.919Z -- shandong%20star%20measurement%20and%20control%20equipment -- heating%20network%20wireless%20monitoring%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8705</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Shandong Star Measurement and Control Equipment Heating Network Wireless Monitoring System 5.6.2 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function GetDataKindByType of the file /DataSrvs/UCCGSrv.asmx. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Shandong Star Measurement and Control Equipment Heating Network Wireless Monitoring System 5.6.2 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um die Funktion GetDataKindByType der Datei /DataSrvs/UCCGSrv.asmx. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8705|2024-09-11T22:31:24.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 22:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
