<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- DataGear</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/datagear.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- DataGear</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1571|2024-02-13T07:57:29.440Z -- n%2Fa -- datagear
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1571</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in DataGear up to 4.5.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /analysisProject/pagingQueryData. The manipulation of the argument queryOrder leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.5.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223563.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in DataGear bis 4.5.0 gefunden. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /analysisProject/pagingQueryData. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments queryOrder mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 4.5.1 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1571|2024-02-13T07:57:29.440Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 15:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1772|2024-02-13T07:49:03.905Z -- n%2Fa -- datagear
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1772</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in DataGear up to 4.5.1. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the component Diagram Type Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-224673 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in DataGear bis 4.5.1 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Komponente Diagram Type Handler. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1772|2024-02-13T07:49:03.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 11:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1573|2024-02-13T07:48:34.200Z -- n%2Fa -- datagear
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1573</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in DataGear up to 1.11.1 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Graph Dataset Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.12.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-223565 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in DataGear bis 1.11.1 gefunden. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Komponente Graph Dataset Handler. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.12.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1573|2024-02-13T07:48:34.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 15:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1572|2024-02-13T07:48:23.378Z -- n%2Fa -- datagear
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1572</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in DataGear up to 1.11.1 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Plugin Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.12.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223564.
In DataGear bis 1.11.1 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Komponente Plugin Handler. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs hat dabei lokal zu erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.12.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1572|2024-02-13T07:48:23.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 12:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2042|2024-02-13T07:24:32.796Z -- n%2Fa -- datagear
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2042</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in DataGear up to 4.5.1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component JDBC Server Handler. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-225920. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in DataGear bis 4.5.1 entdeckt. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Komponente JDBC Server Handler. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine deserialization-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2042|2024-02-13T07:24:32.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 09:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
