<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for n/a -- DeepFaceLab</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/deepfacelab.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- DeepFaceLab</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1432|2024-02-13T13:41:31.741Z -- n/a -- DeepFaceLab
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1432</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in DeepFaceLab pretrained DF.wf.288res.384.92.72.22 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function apply_xseg of the file main.py. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-253391. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in DeepFaceLab pretrained DF.wf.288res.384.92.72.22 gefunden. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion apply_xseg der Datei main.py. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine deserialization-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Die Ausnutzbarkeit gilt als schwierig. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1432|2024-02-13T13:41:31.741Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 03:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0654|2024-02-09T19:12:11.048Z -- n/a -- DeepFaceLab
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0654</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in DeepFaceLab pretrained DF.wf.288res.384.92.72.22. Affected is an unknown function of the file mainscripts/Util.py. The manipulation leads to deserialization. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-251382 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in DeepFaceLab pretrained DF.wf.288res.384.92.72.22 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei mainscripts/Util.py. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine deserialization-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff hat dabei lokal zu erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0654|2024-02-09T19:12:11.048Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 01:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>