<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- Dreamer CMS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/dreamer%20cms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- Dreamer CMS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1746|2023-10-21T14:14:50.480Z -- n%2Fa -- dreamer%20cms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1746</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Dreamer CMS up to 3.5.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component File Upload Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. VDB-224634 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Dreamer CMS bis 3.5.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Komponente File Upload Handler. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1746|2023-10-21T14:14:50.480Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 23:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2473|2023-10-23T05:13:48.158Z -- n%2Fa -- dreamer%20cms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2473</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Dreamer CMS up to 4.1.3. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function updatePwd of the file UserController.java of the component Password Hash Calculation. The manipulation leads to inefficient algorithmic complexity. The attack can be initiated remotely. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227860.
In Dreamer CMS bis 4.1.3 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht um die Funktion updatePwd der Datei UserController.java der Komponente Password Hash Calculation. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine inefficient algorithmic complexity-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2473|2023-10-23T05:13:48.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 12:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
