<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- DriverGenius</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/drivergenius.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- DriverGenius</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1678|2023-10-21T13:44:21.341Z -- n%2Fa -- drivergenius
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1678</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in DriverGenius 9.70.0.346. This affects the function 0x9C40A0D8/0x9C40A0DC/0x9C40A0E0 in the library mydrivers64.sys of the component IOCTL Handler. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-224235.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in DriverGenius 9.70.0.346 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft die Funktion 0x9C40A0D8/0x9C40A0DC/0x9C40A0E0 in der Bibliothek mydrivers64.sys der Komponente IOCTL Handler. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine memory corruption-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1678|2023-10-21T13:44:21.341Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 22:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1679|2023-10-21T13:45:34.484Z -- n%2Fa -- drivergenius
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1679</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in DriverGenius 9.70.0.346. This vulnerability affects the function 0x9C406104/0x9C40A108 in the library mydrivers64.sys of the component IOCTL Handler. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-224236.
In DriverGenius 9.70.0.346 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft die Funktion 0x9C406104/0x9C40A108 in der Bibliothek mydrivers64.sys der Komponente IOCTL Handler. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine memory corruption-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs hat dabei lokal zu erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1679|2023-10-21T13:45:34.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 22:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1676|2023-10-21T13:41:55.073Z -- n%2Fa -- drivergenius
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1676</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in DriverGenius 9.70.0.346. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function 0x9C402088 in the library mydrivers64.sys of the component IOCTL Handler. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-224233 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In DriverGenius 9.70.0.346 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Dabei geht es um die Funktion 0x9C402088 in der Bibliothek mydrivers64.sys der Komponente IOCTL Handler. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine memory corruption-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1676|2023-10-21T13:41:55.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 21:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1677|2023-10-21T13:43:08.210Z -- n%2Fa -- drivergenius
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1677</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in DriverGenius 9.70.0.346. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function 0x9c40a0c8/0x9c40a0dc/0x9c40a0e0/0x9c40a0d8/0x9c4060d4/0x9c402004/0x9c402088/0x9c40208c/0x9c4060d0/0x9c4060cc/0x9c4060c4/0x9c402084 in the library mydrivers64.sys of the component IOCTL Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-224234 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in DriverGenius 9.70.0.346 ausgemacht. Hierbei geht es um die Funktion 0x9c40a0c8/0x9c40a0dc/0x9c40a0e0/0x9c40a0d8/0x9c4060d4/0x9c402004/0x9c402088/0x9c40208c/0x9c4060d0/0x9c4060cc/0x9c4060c4/0x9c402084 in der Bibliothek mydrivers64.sys der Komponente IOCTL Handler. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1677|2023-10-21T13:43:08.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 21:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
