<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- ECshop</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/ecshop.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- ECshop</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5293|2023-10-25T04:52:05.131Z -- n%2Fa -- ecshop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in ECshop 4.1.5. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/leancloud.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-240924.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in ECshop 4.1.5 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /admin/leancloud.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5293|2023-10-25T04:52:05.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 20:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5294|2023-10-25T04:53:18.293Z -- n%2Fa -- ecshop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5294</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in ECshop 4.1.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/order.php. The manipulation of the argument goods_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-240925 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In ECshop 4.1.1 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /admin/order.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments goods_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5294|2023-10-25T04:53:18.293Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 21:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1185|2024-02-13T07:55:17.159Z -- n%2Fa -- ecshop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1185</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in ECshop up to 4.1.8. This affects an unknown part of the component New Product Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-222357 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in ECshop bis 4.1.8 gefunden. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Komponente New Product Handler. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1185|2024-02-13T07:55:17.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 07:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1184|2024-02-13T07:53:57.547Z -- n%2Fa -- ecshop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1184</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in ECshop up to 4.1.8. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/database.php of the component Backup Database Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-222356.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in ECshop bis 4.1.8 entdeckt. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei admin/database.php der Komponente Backup Database Handler. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1184|2024-02-13T07:53:57.547Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 07:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0783|2023-10-20T20:59:19.814Z -- n%2Fa -- ecshop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0783</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in EcShop 4.1.5. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /ecshop/admin/template.php of the component PHP File Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-220641 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in EcShop 4.1.5 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /ecshop/admin/template.php der Komponente PHP File Handler. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0783|2023-10-20T20:59:19.814Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 17:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1530|2024-02-15T12:46:26.788Z -- n%2Fa -- ecshop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1530</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in ECshop 4.1.8. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/view_sendlist.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250562 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in ECshop 4.1.8 entdeckt. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /admin/view_sendlist.php. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1530|2024-02-15T12:46:26.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
