<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for n/a -- github.com/greenpau/caddy-security</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/github.com%2Fgreenpau%2Fcaddy-security.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- github.com/greenpau/caddy-security</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-21497|2024-03-06T14:09:46.603Z -- n/a -- github.com/greenpau/caddy-security
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21497</link><description>All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Open Redirect via the redirect_url parameter. An attacker could perform a phishing attack and trick users into visiting a malicious website by crafting a convincing URL with this parameter. To exploit this vulnerability, the user must take an action, such as clicking on a portal button or using the browser’s back button, to trigger the redirection.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21497|2024-03-06T14:09:46.603Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21496|2024-03-06T14:09:46.106Z -- n/a -- github.com/greenpau/caddy-security
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21496</link><description>All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via the Referer header, due to improper input sanitization. Although the Referer header is sanitized by escaping some characters that can allow XSS (e.g., [&amp;], [&lt;], [&gt;], ["], [']), it does not account for the attack based on the JavaScript URL scheme (e.g., javascript:alert(document.domain)// payload). Exploiting this vulnerability may not be trivial, but it could lead to the execution of malicious scripts in the context of the target user’s browser, compromising user sessions.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21496|2024-03-06T14:09:46.106Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21500|2024-03-06T14:09:47.438Z -- n/a -- github.com/greenpau/caddy-security
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21500</link><description>All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts via the two-factor authentication (2FA). Although the application blocks the user after several failed attempts to provide 2FA codes, attackers can bypass this blocking mechanism by automating the application’s full multistep 2FA process.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21500|2024-03-06T14:09:47.438Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21493|2024-03-06T14:09:47.512Z -- n/a -- github.com/greenpau/caddy-security
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21493</link><description>All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Improper Validation of Array Index when parsing a Caddyfile. Multiple parsing functions in the affected library do not validate whether their input values are nil before attempting to access elements, which can lead to a panic (index out of range). Panics during the parsing of a configuration file may introduce ambiguity and vulnerabilities, hindering the correct interpretation and configuration of the web server.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21493|2024-03-06T14:09:47.512Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21492|2024-03-06T14:09:46.602Z -- n/a -- github.com/greenpau/caddy-security
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21492</link><description>All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Insufficient Session Expiration due to improper user session invalidation upon clicking the "Sign Out" button. User sessions remain valid even after requests are sent to /logout and /oauth2/google/logout. Attackers who gain access to an active but supposedly logged-out session can perform unauthorized actions on behalf of the user.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21492|2024-03-06T14:09:46.602Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21499|2024-03-06T14:09:47.106Z -- n/a -- github.com/greenpau/caddy-security
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21499</link><description>All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to HTTP Header Injection via the X-Forwarded-Proto header due to redirecting to the injected protocol.Exploiting this vulnerability could lead to bypass of security mechanisms or confusion in handling TLS.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21499|2024-03-06T14:09:47.106Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21495|2024-03-06T14:09:47.539Z -- n/a -- github.com/greenpau/caddy-security
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21495</link><description>Versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security before 1.0.42 are vulnerable to Insecure Randomness due to using an insecure random number generation library which could possibly be predicted via a brute-force search. Attackers could use the potentially predictable nonce value used for authentication purposes in the OAuth flow to conduct OAuth replay attacks. In addition, insecure randomness is used while generating multifactor authentication (MFA) secrets and creating API keys in the database package.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21495|2024-03-06T14:09:47.539Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21494|2024-03-06T14:09:47.391Z -- n/a -- github.com/greenpau/caddy-security
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21494</link><description>All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Authentication Bypass by Spoofing via the X-Forwarded-For header due to improper input sanitization. An attacker can spoof an IP address used in the user identity module (/whoami API endpoint). This could lead to unauthorized access if the system trusts this spoofed IP address.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21494|2024-03-06T14:09:47.391Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21498|2024-03-06T14:09:46.968Z -- n/a -- github.com/greenpau/caddy-security
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21498</link><description>All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Server-side Request Forgery (SSRF) via X-Forwarded-Host header manipulation. An attacker can expose sensitive information, interact with internal services, or exploit other vulnerabilities within the network by exploiting this vulnerability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21498|2024-03-06T14:09:46.968Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>