<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- glibc</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/glibc.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- glibc</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6779|2024-02-15T06:57:30.291Z -- n%2Fa -- glibc
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6779</link>
      <description>An off-by-one heap-based buffer overflow was found in the __vsyslog_internal function of the glibc library. This function is called by the syslog and vsyslog functions. This issue occurs when these functions are called with a message bigger than INT_MAX bytes, leading to an incorrect calculation of the buffer size to store the message, resulting in an application crash. This issue affects glibc 2.37 and newer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6779|2024-02-15T06:57:30.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 14:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6780|2024-03-26T15:30:47.720Z -- n%2Fa -- glibc
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6780</link>
      <description>An integer overflow was found in the __vsyslog_internal function of the glibc library. This function is called by the syslog and vsyslog functions. This issue occurs when these functions are called with a very long message, leading to an incorrect calculation of the buffer size to store the message, resulting in undefined behavior. This issue affects glibc 2.37 and newer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6780|2024-03-26T15:30:47.720Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 14:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6246|2024-02-15T06:56:44.724Z -- n%2Fa -- glibc
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6246</link>
      <description>A heap-based buffer overflow was found in the __vsyslog_internal function of the glibc library. This function is called by the syslog and vsyslog functions. This issue occurs when the openlog function was not called, or called with the ident argument set to NULL, and the program name (the basename of argv[0]) is bigger than 1024 bytes, resulting in an application crash or local privilege escalation. This issue affects glibc 2.36 and newer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6246|2024-02-15T06:56:44.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 14:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
