<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- GPAC</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/gpac.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- GPAC</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1449|2023-10-21T08:58:39.054Z -- n%2Fa -- gpac
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1449</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev35-gbbca86917-master and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function gf_av1_reset_state of the file media_tools/av_parsers.c. The manipulation leads to double free. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-223294 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev35-gbbca86917-master wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion gf_av1_reset_state der Datei media_tools/av_parsers.c. Mittels dem Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine double free-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs hat dabei lokal zu erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1449|2023-10-21T08:58:39.054Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 06:44:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1452|2023-10-21T09:02:18.715Z -- n%2Fa -- gpac
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1452</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev35-gbbca86917-master. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file filters/load_text.c. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-223297 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev35-gbbca86917-master wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei filters/load_text.c. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1452|2023-10-21T09:02:18.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 06:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1448|2023-10-21T08:57:25.810Z -- n%2Fa -- gpac
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1448</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev35-gbbca86917-master. This affects the function gf_m2ts_process_sdt of the file media_tools/mpegts.c. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-223293 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev35-gbbca86917-master gefunden. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion gf_m2ts_process_sdt der Datei media_tools/mpegts.c. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine heap-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1448|2023-10-21T08:57:25.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 06:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0841|2023-10-20T21:06:38.955Z -- n%2Fa -- gpac
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0841</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev40-g3602a5ded. This issue affects the function mp3_dmx_process of the file filters/reframe_mp3.c. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-221087.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in GPAC 2.3-DEV-rev40-g3602a5ded entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion mp3_dmx_process der Datei filters/reframe_mp3.c. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine heap-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0841|2023-10-20T21:06:38.955Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 13:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
