<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- https://github.com/rails/rails</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/https%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2Frails%2Frails.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- https://github.com/rails/rails</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22792|2024-02-02T14:06:17.486014 -- n%2Fa -- https%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2Frails%2Frails
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22792</link>
      <description>A regular expression based DoS vulnerability in Action Dispatch &lt;6.0.6.1,&lt; 6.1.7.1, and &lt;7.0.4.1. Specially crafted cookies, in combination with a specially crafted X_FORWARDED_HOST header can cause the regular expression engine to enter a state of catastrophic backtracking. This can cause the process to use large amounts of CPU and memory, leading to a possible DoS vulnerability All users running an affected release should either upgrade or use one of the workarounds immediately.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22792|2024-02-02T14:06:17.486014</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22795|2024-02-02T14:06:23.429831 -- n%2Fa -- https%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2Frails%2Frails
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22795</link>
      <description>A regular expression based DoS vulnerability in Action Dispatch &lt;6.1.7.1 and &lt;7.0.4.1 related to the If-None-Match header. A specially crafted HTTP If-None-Match header can cause the regular expression engine to enter a state of catastrophic backtracking, when on a version of Ruby below 3.2.0. This can cause the process to use large amounts of CPU and memory, leading to a possible DoS vulnerability All users running an affected release should either upgrade or use one of the workarounds immediately.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22795|2024-02-02T14:06:23.429831</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22794|2024-02-02T14:06:11.892247 -- n%2Fa -- https%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2Frails%2Frails
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22794</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in ActiveRecord &lt;6.0.6.1, v6.1.7.1 and v7.0.4.1 related to the sanitization of comments. If malicious user input is passed to either the `annotate` query method, the `optimizer_hints` query method, or through the QueryLogs interface which automatically adds annotations, it may be sent to the database withinsufficient sanitization and be able to inject SQL outside of the comment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22794|2024-02-02T14:06:11.892247</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22797|2023-02-09T00:00:00 -- n%2Fa -- https%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2Frails%2Frails
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22797</link>
      <description>An open redirect vulnerability is fixed in Rails 7.0.4.1 with the new protection against open redirects from calling redirect_to with untrusted user input. In prior versions the developer was fully responsible for only providing trusted input. However the check introduced could allow an attacker to bypass with a carefully crafted URL resulting in an open redirect vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22797|2023-02-09T00:00:00</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22796|2024-02-02T14:06:29.581100 -- n%2Fa -- https%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2Frails%2Frails
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22796</link>
      <description>A regular expression based DoS vulnerability in Active Support &lt;6.1.7.1 and &lt;7.0.4.1. A specially crafted string passed to the underscore method can cause the regular expression engine to enter a state of catastrophic backtracking. This can cause the process to use large amounts of CPU and memory, leading to a possible DoS vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22796|2024-02-02T14:06:29.581100</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
