<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- jeecg-boot</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/jeecg-boot.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- jeecg-boot</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1454|2024-02-13T07:56:27.604Z -- n%2Fa -- jeecg-boot
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1454</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in jeecg-boot 3.5.0. This affects an unknown part of the file jmreport/qurestSql. The manipulation of the argument apiSelectId leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223299.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in jeecg-boot 3.5.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei jmreport/qurestSql. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments apiSelectId mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1454|2024-02-13T07:56:27.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 06:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1784|2023-10-21T14:23:22.793Z -- n%2Fa -- jeecg-boot
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1784</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in jeecg-boot 3.5.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component API Documentation. The manipulation leads to improper authentication. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-224699.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in jeecg-boot 3.5.0 gefunden. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Komponente API Documentation. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper authentication-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1784|2023-10-21T14:23:22.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1741|2024-02-13T07:54:20.161Z -- n%2Fa -- jeecg-boot
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1741</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in jeecg-boot 3.5.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file SysDictMapper.java of the component Sleep Command Handler. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-224629 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In jeecg-boot 3.5.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei SysDictMapper.java der Komponente Sleep Command Handler. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1741|2024-02-13T07:54:20.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 21:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
