<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for n/a -- Jspxcms</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/jspxcms.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- Jspxcms</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1256|2024-02-06T19:31:04.009Z -- n/a -- Jspxcms
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1256</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Jspxcms 10.2.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ext/collect/filter_text.do. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252995.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Jspxcms 10.2.0 gefunden. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /ext/collect/filter_text.do. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1256|2024-02-06T19:31:04.009Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 19:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1200|2024-02-03T02:00:06.276Z -- n/a -- Jspxcms
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1200</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Jspxcms 10.2.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /template/1/default/. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252698 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Jspxcms 10.2.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /template/1/default/. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1200|2024-02-03T02:00:06.276Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 02:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1257|2024-02-06T20:00:06.539Z -- n/a -- Jspxcms
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1257</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Jspxcms 10.2.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /ext/collect/find_text.do. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252996.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Jspxcms 10.2.0 ausgemacht. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /ext/collect/find_text.do. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1257|2024-02-06T20:00:06.539Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0721|2024-01-19T16:00:07.534Z -- n/a -- Jspxcms
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0721</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Jspxcms 10.2.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Survey Label Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-251545 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Jspxcms 10.2.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Komponente Survey Label Handler. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0721|2024-01-19T16:00:07.534Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 16:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0599|2024-01-16T20:00:05.381Z -- n/a -- Jspxcms
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0599</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Jspxcms 10.2.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file src\main\java\com\jspxcms\core\web\back\InfoController.java of the component Document Management Page. The manipulation of the argument title leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250837 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Jspxcms 10.2.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei src\main\java\com\jspxcms\core\web\back\InfoController.java der Komponente Document Management Page. Durch Manipulation des Arguments title mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0599|2024-01-16T20:00:05.381Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>