<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- libssh</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/libssh.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- libssh</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1667|2023-12-22T10:06:17.929046 -- n%2Fa -- libssh
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1667</link>
      <description>A NULL pointer dereference was found In libssh during re-keying with algorithm guessing. This issue may allow an authenticated client to cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1667|2023-12-22T10:06:17.929046</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3603|2024-01-23T00:58:36.996Z -- n%2Fa -- libssh
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3603</link>
      <description>A missing allocation check in sftp server processing read requests may cause a NULL dereference on low-memory conditions. The malicious client can request up to 4GB SFTP reads, causing allocation of up to 4GB buffers, which was not being checked for failure. This will likely crash the authenticated user's sftp server connection (if implemented as forking as recommended). For thread-based servers, this might also cause DoS for legitimate users.&#13;
&#13;
Given this code is not in any released versions, no security releases have been issued.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3603|2024-01-23T00:58:36.996Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 19:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2283|2024-02-01T17:06:59.699395 -- n%2Fa -- libssh
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2283</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in libssh, where the authentication check of the connecting client can be bypassed in the`pki_verify_data_signature` function in memory allocation problems. This issue may happen if there is insufficient memory or the memory usage is limited. The problem is caused by the return value `rc,` which is initialized to SSH_ERROR and later rewritten to save the return value of the function call `pki_key_check_hash_compatible.` The value of the variable is not changed between this point and the cryptographic verification. Therefore any error between them calls `goto error` returning SSH_OK.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2283|2024-02-01T17:06:59.699395</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
