<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- lmxcms</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/lmxcms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- lmxcms</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5017|2024-06-05T20:26:31.297Z -- n%2Fa -- lmxcms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5017</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in lmxcms up to 1.41. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin.php. The manipulation of the argument lid leads to sql injection. VDB-239858 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in lmxcms bis 1.41 ausgemacht. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei admin.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments lid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5017|2024-06-05T20:26:31.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 03:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1321|2023-10-21T08:04:57.610Z -- n%2Fa -- lmxcms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1321</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in lmxcms 1.41 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function update of the file AcquisiAction.class.php. The manipulation of the argument id with the input -1 and updatexml(0,concat(0x7e,user()),1)# leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-222727.
In lmxcms 1.41 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist die Funktion update der Datei AcquisiAction.class.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments id mit der Eingabe -1 and updatexml(0,concat(0x7e,user()),1)# mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1321|2023-10-21T08:04:57.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 15:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1322|2023-10-21T08:06:10.793Z -- n%2Fa -- lmxcms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1322</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in lmxcms 1.41 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function reply of the file BookAction.class.php. The manipulation of the argument id with the input 1) and updatexml(0,concat(0x7e,user()),1)# leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-222728.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in lmxcms 1.41 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion reply der Datei BookAction.class.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments id mit der Eingabe 1) and updatexml(0,concat(0x7e,user()),1)# mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1322|2023-10-21T08:06:10.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 15:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
