<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- MailCleaner</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/mailcleaner.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- MailCleaner</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3195|2024-06-04T17:33:16.869Z -- n%2Fa -- mailcleaner
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3195</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in MailCleaner up to 2023.03.14. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the component Admin Endpoints. The manipulation leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262311.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in MailCleaner bis 2023.03.14 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Komponente Admin Endpoints. Mittels dem Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine path traversal-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3195|2024-06-04T17:33:16.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:22:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3194|2024-06-04T17:32:57.070Z -- n%2Fa -- mailcleaner
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3194</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in MailCleaner up to 2023.03.14 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Log File Endpoint. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-262310 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in MailCleaner bis 2023.03.14 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Komponente Log File Endpoint. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3194|2024-06-04T17:32:57.070Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3193|2024-06-04T17:32:33.010Z -- n%2Fa -- mailcleaner
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3193</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in MailCleaner up to 2023.03.14 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Admin Endpoints. The manipulation leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-262309 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In MailCleaner bis 2023.03.14 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Komponente Admin Endpoints. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3193|2024-06-04T17:32:33.010Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3192|2024-06-04T17:32:27.728Z -- n%2Fa -- mailcleaner
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3192</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in MailCleaner up to 2023.03.14. Affected is an unknown function of the component Admin Interface. The manipulation as part of Mail Message leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262308.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in MailCleaner bis 2023.03.14 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Komponente Admin Interface. Mit der Manipulation durch Mail Message kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3192|2024-06-04T17:32:27.728Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3191|2024-04-29T06:21:47.288Z -- n%2Fa -- mailcleaner
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3191</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in MailCleaner up to 2023.03.14. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Email Handler. The manipulation leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262307.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in MailCleaner bis 2023.03.14 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Komponente Email Handler. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3191|2024-04-29T06:21:47.288Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3196|2024-06-04T17:30:58.900Z -- n%2Fa -- mailcleaner
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3196</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in MailCleaner up to 2023.03.14. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function getStats/Services_silentDump/Services_stopStartMTA/Config_saveDateTime/Config_hostid/Logs_StartGetStat/dumpConfiguration of the component SOAP Service. The manipulation leads to os command injection. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262312.
In MailCleaner bis 2023.03.14 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist die Funktion getStats/Services_silentDump/Services_stopStartMTA/Config_saveDateTime/Config_hostid/Logs_StartGetStat/dumpConfiguration der Komponente SOAP Service. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs hat dabei lokal zu erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3196|2024-06-04T17:30:58.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
