<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- PeaZip</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/peazip.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- PeaZip</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6891|2023-12-17T03:31:03.908Z -- n%2Fa -- peazip
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6891</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in PeaZip 9.4.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality in the library dragdropfilesdll.dll of the component Library Handler. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. An attack has to be approached locally. Upgrading to version 9.6.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248251. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early, confirmed the existence of the flaw and immediately worked on a patched release.
In PeaZip 9.4.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität in der Bibliothek dragdropfilesdll.dll der Komponente Library Handler. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine uncontrolled search path-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal angegangen werden. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 9.6.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6891|2023-12-17T03:31:03.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 03:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
