<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- PHPEMS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/phpems.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- PHPEMS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6654|2024-02-13T07:26:05.925Z -- n%2Fa -- phpems
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6654</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPEMS 6.x/7.x/8.x/9.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality in the library lib/session.cls.php of the component Session Data Handler. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-247357 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In PHPEMS 6.x/7.x/8.x/9.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung in der Bibliothek lib/session.cls.php der Komponente Session Data Handler. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine deserialization-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6654|2024-02-13T07:26:05.925Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 15:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6472|2023-12-02T18:31:03.772Z -- n%2Fa -- phpems
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6472</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in PHPEMS 7.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file app\content\cls\api.cls.php of the component Content Section Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-246629 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in PHPEMS 7.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei app\content\cls\api.cls.php der Komponente Content Section Handler. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6472|2023-12-02T18:31:03.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 18:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1353|2024-02-09T00:31:06.389Z -- n%2Fa -- phpems
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1353</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPEMS up to 1.0. Affected by this issue is the function index of the file app/weixin/controller/index.api.php. The manipulation of the argument picurl leads to deserialization. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-253226 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in PHPEMS bis 1.0 entdeckt. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion index der Datei app/weixin/controller/index.api.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments picurl mit unbekannten Daten kann eine deserialization-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1353|2024-02-09T00:31:06.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
