<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- playSMS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/playsms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- playSMS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5851|2024-06-11T18:48:52.880Z -- n%2Fa -- playsms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5851</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in playSMS up to 1.4.7. Affected is an unknown function of the file /index.php?app=main&amp;inc=feature_schedule&amp;op=list of the component SMS Schedule Handler. The manipulation of the argument name/message leads to basic cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 1.4.8 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 7a88920f6b536c6a91512e739bcb4e8adefeed2b. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-267912. NOTE: The code maintainer was contacted early about this disclosure and was eager to prepare a fix as quickly as possible.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in playSMS bis 1.4.7 entdeckt. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /index.php?app=main&amp;inc=feature_schedule&amp;op=list der Komponente SMS Schedule Handler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments name/message mit unbekannten Daten kann eine basic cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.4.8 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 7a88920f6b536c6a91512e739bcb4e8adefeed2b bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5851|2024-06-11T18:48:52.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 17:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
