<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- PopojiCMS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/popojicms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- PopojiCMS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5910|2024-02-13T07:58:53.491Z -- n%2Fa -- popojicms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5910</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PopojiCMS 2.0.1 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file install.php of the component Web Config. The manipulation of the argument Site Title with the input &lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-244229 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in PopojiCMS 2.0.1 gefunden. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei install.php der Komponente Web Config. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments Site Title mit der Eingabe &lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt; mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Die Ausnutzbarkeit gilt als schwierig. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5910|2024-02-13T07:58:53.491Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 23:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
