<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for n/a -- PostgreSQL</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/postgresql.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- PostgreSQL</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-0985|2024-02-08T13:00:02.411Z -- n/a -- PostgreSQL
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0985</link><description>Late privilege drop in REFRESH MATERIALIZED VIEW CONCURRENTLY in PostgreSQL allows an object creator to execute arbitrary SQL functions as the command issuer. The command intends to run SQL functions as the owner of the materialized view, enabling safe refresh of untrusted materialized views. The victim is a superuser or member of one of the attacker's roles. The attack requires luring the victim into running REFRESH MATERIALIZED VIEW CONCURRENTLY on the attacker's materialized view. As part of exploiting this vulnerability, the attacker creates functions that use CREATE RULE to convert the internally-built temporary table to a view. Versions before PostgreSQL 15.6, 14.11, 13.14, and 12.18 are affected. The only known exploit does not work in PostgreSQL 16 and later. For defense in depth, PostgreSQL 16.2 adds the protections that older branches are using to fix their vulnerability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0985|2024-02-08T13:00:02.411Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4317|2024-05-09T13:00:01.285Z -- n/a -- PostgreSQL
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4317</link><description>Missing authorization in PostgreSQL built-in views pg_stats_ext and pg_stats_ext_exprs allows an unprivileged database user to read most common values and other statistics from CREATE STATISTICS commands of other users. The most common values may reveal column values the eavesdropper could not otherwise read or results of functions they cannot execute. Installing an unaffected version only fixes fresh PostgreSQL installations, namely those that are created with the initdb utility after installing that version. Current PostgreSQL installations will remain vulnerable until they follow the instructions in the release notes. Within major versions 14-16, minor versions before PostgreSQL 16.3, 15.7, and 14.12 are affected. Versions before PostgreSQL 14 are unaffected.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4317|2024-05-09T13:00:01.285Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>