<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- qemu</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/qemu.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- qemu</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1386|2024-04-17T17:34:27.317Z -- n%2Fa -- qemu
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1386</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the 9p passthrough filesystem (9pfs) implementation in QEMU. When a local user in the guest writes an executable file with SUID or SGID, none of these privileged bits are correctly dropped. As a result, in rare circumstances, this flaw could be used by malicious users in the guest to elevate their privileges within the guest and help a host local user to elevate privileges on the host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1386|2024-04-17T17:34:27.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0664|2023-08-29T02:06:24.520899 -- n%2Fa -- qemu
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0664</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the QEMU Guest Agent service for Windows. A local unprivileged user may be able to manipulate the QEMU Guest Agent's Windows installer via repair custom actions to elevate their privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0664|2023-08-29T02:06:24.520899</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3301|2023-09-13T16:09:36.861Z -- n%2Fa -- qemu
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3301</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in QEMU. The async nature of hot-unplug enables a race scenario where the net device backend is cleared before the virtio-net pci frontend has been unplugged. A malicious guest could use this time window to trigger an assertion and cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3301|2023-09-13T16:09:36.861Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 16:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3180|2024-01-23T02:29:25.701Z -- n%2Fa -- qemu
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3180</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the QEMU virtual crypto device while handling data encryption/decryption requests in virtio_crypto_handle_sym_req. There is no check for the value of `src_len` and `dst_len` in virtio_crypto_sym_op_helper, potentially leading to a heap buffer overflow when the two values differ.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3180|2024-01-23T02:29:25.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3354|2023-07-11T16:16:56.294Z -- n%2Fa -- qemu
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3354</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the QEMU built-in VNC server. When a client connects to the VNC server, QEMU checks whether the current number of connections crosses a certain threshold and if so, cleans up the previous connection. If the previous connection happens to be in the handshake phase and fails, QEMU cleans up the connection again, resulting in a NULL pointer dereference issue. This could allow a remote unauthenticated client to cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3354|2023-07-11T16:16:56.294Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 16:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2680|2023-09-13T16:50:53.532Z -- n%2Fa -- qemu
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2680</link>
      <description>This CVE exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2021-3750. More specifically, the qemu-kvm package as released for Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9.1 via RHSA-2022:7967 included a version of qemu-kvm that was actually missing the fix for CVE-2021-3750.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2680|2023-09-13T16:50:53.532Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 16:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
