<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for n/a -- Rebuild</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/rebuild.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- Rebuild</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1098|2024-01-31T11:31:04.316Z -- n/a -- Rebuild
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1098</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Rebuild up to 3.5.5 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function QiniuCloud.getStorageFile of the file /filex/proxy-download. The manipulation of the argument url leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252455.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Rebuild bis 3.5.5 gefunden. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion QiniuCloud.getStorageFile der Datei /filex/proxy-download. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1098|2024-01-31T11:31:04.316Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 11:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1020|2024-01-29T21:31:04.591Z -- n/a -- Rebuild
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1020</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Rebuild up to 3.5.5. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getStorageFile of the file /filex/proxy-download. The manipulation of the argument url leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252289 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Rebuild bis 3.5.5 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion getStorageFile der Datei /filex/proxy-download. Durch Manipulation des Arguments url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1020|2024-01-29T21:31:04.591Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1021|2024-01-29T22:00:08.338Z -- n/a -- Rebuild
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1021</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Rebuild up to 3.5.5. Affected by this issue is the function readRawText of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument url leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252290 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Rebuild bis 3.5.5 entdeckt. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion readRawText der Komponente HTTP Request Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine server-side request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1021|2024-01-29T22:00:08.338Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 22:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1099|2024-01-31T11:31:05.389Z -- n/a -- Rebuild
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1099</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Rebuild up to 3.5.5. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function getFileOfData of the file /filex/read-raw. The manipulation of the argument url leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252456.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Rebuild bis 3.5.5 ausgemacht. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion getFileOfData der Datei /filex/read-raw. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1099|2024-01-31T11:31:05.389Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 11:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>