<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- Rebuild</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/rebuild.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- Rebuild</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1613|2023-10-21T11:11:07.126Z -- n%2Fa -- rebuild
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1613</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Rebuild up to 3.2.3 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /feeds/post/publish. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223744.
In Rebuild bis 3.2.3 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /feeds/post/publish. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1613|2023-10-21T11:11:07.126Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 21:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1612|2023-10-21T11:09:53.927Z -- n%2Fa -- rebuild
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1612</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Rebuild up to 3.2.3. This affects an unknown part of the file /files/list-file. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223743.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Rebuild bis 3.2.3 gefunden. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /files/list-file. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1612|2023-10-21T11:09:53.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 20:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1610|2023-10-21T11:08:40.796Z -- n%2Fa -- rebuild
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1610</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Rebuild up to 3.2.3. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /project/tasks/list. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-223742 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Rebuild bis 3.2.3 entdeckt. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /project/tasks/list. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1610|2023-10-21T11:08:40.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1495|2023-10-21T09:37:41.808Z -- n%2Fa -- rebuild
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1495</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Rebuild up to 3.2.3. Affected by this vulnerability is the function queryListOfConfig of the file /admin/robot/approval/list. The manipulation of the argument q leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is c9474f84e5f376dd2ade2078e3039961a9425da7. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-223381 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Rebuild bis 3.2.3 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Das betrifft die Funktion queryListOfConfig der Datei /admin/robot/approval/list. Durch Manipulation des Arguments q mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Der Patch wird als c9474f84e5f376dd2ade2078e3039961a9425da7 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1495|2023-10-21T09:37:41.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 23:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2474|2023-10-23T05:15:01.327Z -- n%2Fa -- rebuild
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2474</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Rebuild 3.2 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to change the configuration settings. VDB-227866 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Rebuild 3.2 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross-site request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Als bestmögliche Massnahme werden Anpassungen an der Konfiguration empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2474|2023-10-23T05:15:01.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 12:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1098|2024-01-31T11:31:04.316Z -- n%2Fa -- rebuild
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1098</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Rebuild up to 3.5.5 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function QiniuCloud.getStorageFile of the file /filex/proxy-download. The manipulation of the argument url leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252455.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Rebuild bis 3.5.5 gefunden. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion QiniuCloud.getStorageFile der Datei /filex/proxy-download. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1098|2024-01-31T11:31:04.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 11:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1020|2024-01-29T21:31:04.591Z -- n%2Fa -- rebuild
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1020</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Rebuild up to 3.5.5. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getStorageFile of the file /filex/proxy-download. The manipulation of the argument url leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252289 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Rebuild bis 3.5.5 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion getStorageFile der Datei /filex/proxy-download. Durch Manipulation des Arguments url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1020|2024-01-29T21:31:04.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1021|2024-01-29T22:00:08.338Z -- n%2Fa -- rebuild
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1021</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Rebuild up to 3.5.5. Affected by this issue is the function readRawText of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument url leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252290 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Rebuild bis 3.5.5 entdeckt. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion readRawText der Komponente HTTP Request Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine server-side request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1021|2024-01-29T22:00:08.338Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 22:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1099|2024-01-31T11:31:05.389Z -- n%2Fa -- rebuild
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1099</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Rebuild up to 3.5.5. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function getFileOfData of the file /filex/read-raw. The manipulation of the argument url leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252456.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Rebuild bis 3.5.5 ausgemacht. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion getFileOfData der Datei /filex/read-raw. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1099|2024-01-31T11:31:05.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 11:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
