<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- Rockoa</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/rockoa.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- Rockoa</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1501|2023-10-21T09:43:47.764Z -- n%2Fa -- rockoa
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1501</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in RockOA 2.3.2. This affects the function runAction of the file acloudCosAction.php.SQL. The manipulation of the argument fileid leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-223401 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in RockOA 2.3.2 gefunden. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion runAction der Datei acloudCosAction.php.SQL. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments fileid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1501|2023-10-21T09:43:47.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1773|2023-10-21T14:22:09.629Z -- n%2Fa -- rockoa
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1773</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Rockoa 2.3.2. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file webmainConfig.php of the component Configuration File Handler. The manipulation leads to code injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-224674 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Rockoa 2.3.2 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei webmainConfig.php der Komponente Configuration File Handler. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine code injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1773|2023-10-21T14:22:09.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 12:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
