<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- S-CMS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/s-cms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- S-CMS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7190|2024-02-13T07:32:54.442Z -- n%2Fa -- s-cms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-7190</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in S-CMS up to 2.0_build20220529-20231006. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /member/ad.php?action=ad. The manipulation of the argument A_text/A_url/A_contact leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249392. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in S-CMS bis 2.0_build20220529-20231006 entdeckt. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /member/ad.php?action=ad. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments A_text/A_url/A_contact mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7190|2024-02-13T07:32:54.442Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 15:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7191|2024-02-13T07:31:14.975Z -- n%2Fa -- s-cms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-7191</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in S-CMS up to 2.0_build20220529-20231006. This affects an unknown part of the file member/reg.php. The manipulation of the argument M_login/M_email leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249393 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in S-CMS bis 2.0_build20220529-20231006 gefunden. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei member/reg.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments M_login/M_email mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7191|2024-02-13T07:31:14.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7189|2024-02-13T07:28:04.788Z -- n%2Fa -- s-cms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-7189</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in S-CMS up to 2.0_build20220529-20231006. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /s/index.php?action=statistics. The manipulation of the argument lid leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249391. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In S-CMS bis 2.0_build20220529-20231006 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /s/index.php?action=statistics. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments lid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7189|2024-02-13T07:28:04.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 15:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
