<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- samba</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/samba.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- samba</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5568|2024-01-23T01:26:11.228Z -- n%2Fa -- samba
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5568</link>
      <description>A heap-based Buffer Overflow flaw was discovered in Samba. It could allow a remote, authenticated attacker to exploit this vulnerability to cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5568|2024-01-23T01:26:11.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 21:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0614|2023-09-17T08:06:14.183896 -- n%2Fa -- samba
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0614</link>
      <description>The fix in 4.6.16, 4.7.9, 4.8.4 and 4.9.7 for CVE-2018-10919 Confidential attribute disclosure vi LDAP filters was insufficient and an attacker may be able to obtain confidential BitLocker recovery keys from a Samba AD DC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0614|2023-09-17T08:06:14.183896</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0225|2023-09-17T08:06:22.916445 -- n%2Fa -- samba
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0225</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Samba. An incomplete access check on dnsHostName allows authenticated but otherwise unprivileged users to delete this attribute from any object in the directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0225|2023-09-17T08:06:22.916445</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0922|2023-09-17T08:06:29.031505 -- n%2Fa -- samba
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0922</link>
      <description>The Samba AD DC administration tool, when operating against a remote LDAP server, will by default send new or reset passwords over a signed-only connection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0922|2023-09-17T08:06:29.031505</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4154|2024-01-23T01:33:49.736Z -- n%2Fa -- samba
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4154</link>
      <description>A design flaw was found in Samba's DirSync control implementation, which exposes passwords and secrets in Active Directory to privileged users and Read-Only Domain Controllers (RODCs). This flaw allows RODCs and users possessing the GET_CHANGES right to access all attributes, including sensitive secrets and passwords. Even in a default setup, RODC DC accounts, which should only replicate some passwords, can gain access to all domain secrets, including the vital krbtgt, effectively eliminating the RODC / DC distinction. Furthermore, the vulnerability fails to account for error conditions (fail open), like out-of-memory situations, potentially granting access to secret attributes, even under low-privileged attacker influence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4154|2024-01-23T01:33:49.736Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 19:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42670|2024-01-23T02:23:44.541Z -- n%2Fa -- samba
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42670</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Samba. It is susceptible to a vulnerability where multiple incompatible RPC listeners can be initiated, causing disruptions in the AD DC service. When Samba's RPC server experiences a high load or unresponsiveness, servers intended for non-AD DC purposes (for example, NT4-emulation "classic DCs") can erroneously start and compete for the same unix domain sockets. This issue leads to partial query responses from the AD DC, causing issues such as "The procedure number is out of range" when using tools like Active Directory Users. This flaw allows an attacker to disrupt AD DC services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42670|2024-01-23T02:23:44.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 07:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
