<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- SeaCMS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/seacms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- SeaCMS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0960|2023-10-20T21:39:40.042Z -- n%2Fa -- seacms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0960</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SeaCMS 11.6 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /data/config.ftp.php of the component Picture Management. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-221630 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SeaCMS 11.6 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /data/config.ftp.php der Komponente Picture Management. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine deserialization-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0960|2023-10-20T21:39:40.042Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 17:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2926|2023-10-23T07:15:49.167Z -- n%2Fa -- seacms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2926</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SeaCMS 11.6 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file member.php of the component Picture Upload Handler. The manipulation of the argument oldpic leads to denial of service. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-230081 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in SeaCMS 11.6 gefunden. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei member.php der Komponente Picture Upload Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments oldpic mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2926|2023-10-23T07:15:49.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 09:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
