<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- Simple Art Gallery</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/simple%20art%20gallery.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- Simple Art Gallery</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1415|2023-10-21T08:40:20.585Z -- n%2Fa -- simple%20art%20gallery
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1415</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Simple Art Gallery 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function sliderPicSubmit of the file adminHome.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. VDB-223126 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Simple Art Gallery 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft die Funktion sliderPicSubmit der Datei adminHome.php. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1415|2023-10-21T08:40:20.585Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 15:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1416|2023-10-21T08:41:33.718Z -- n%2Fa -- simple%20art%20gallery
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1416</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Simple Art Gallery 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file adminHome.php. The manipulation of the argument social_facebook leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223128.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Simple Art Gallery 1.0 entdeckt. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei adminHome.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments social_facebook mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1416|2023-10-21T08:41:33.718Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 15:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
