<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for n/a -- Smart Office</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/smart%20office.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- Smart Office</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-3735|2024-04-13T13:00:05.571Z -- n/a -- Smart Office
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3735</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Smart Office up to 20240405. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file Main.aspx. The manipulation of the argument New Password/Confirm Password with the input 1 leads to weak password requirements. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-260574 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Smart Office bis 20240405 ausgemacht. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei Main.aspx. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments New Password/Confirm Password mit der Eingabe 1 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine weak password requirements-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie gilt als schwierig auszunutzen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3735|2024-04-13T13:00:05.571Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 13:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>