<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for n/a -- Smsot</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/smsot.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- Smsot</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-0733|2024-02-09T19:12:13.958Z -- n/a -- Smsot
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0733</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Smsot up to 2.12. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument data[sign] leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251556.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Smsot bis 2.12 ausgemacht. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /api.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments data[sign] mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0733|2024-02-09T19:12:13.958Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 20:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0734|2024-02-09T19:12:09.594Z -- n/a -- Smsot
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0734</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Smsot up to 2.12. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /get.php. The manipulation of the argument tid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-251557 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Smsot bis 2.12 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /get.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments tid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0734|2024-02-09T19:12:09.594Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 20:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>