<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for n/a -- Taokeyun</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/taokeyun.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- Taokeyun</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-0480|2024-02-09T19:10:37.484Z -- n/a -- Taokeyun
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0480</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Taokeyun up to 1.0.5. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function index of the file application/index/controller/m/Drs.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument cid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250585 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Taokeyun bis 1.0.5 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Es geht um die Funktion index der Datei application/index/controller/m/Drs.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments cid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0480|2024-02-09T19:10:37.484Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 07:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0479|2024-02-09T19:10:31.666Z -- n/a -- Taokeyun
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0479</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Taokeyun up to 1.0.5. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function login of the file application/index/controller/m/User.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250584.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Taokeyun bis 1.0.5 ausgemacht. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion login der Datei application/index/controller/m/User.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch Manipulation des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0479|2024-02-09T19:10:31.666Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0481|2024-02-09T19:10:43.274Z -- n/a -- Taokeyun
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0481</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Taokeyun up to 1.0.5. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function shopGoods of the file application/index/controller/app/store/Goods.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument keyword leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250586 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Taokeyun bis 1.0.5 ausgemacht. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion shopGoods der Datei application/index/controller/app/store/Goods.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments keyword mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0481|2024-02-09T19:10:43.274Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 09:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0482|2024-02-09T19:10:40.382Z -- n/a -- Taokeyun
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0482</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Taokeyun up to 1.0.5. This affects the function index of the file application/index/controller/app/Video.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument cid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250587.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Taokeyun bis 1.0.5 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um die Funktion index der Datei application/index/controller/app/Video.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments cid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0482|2024-02-09T19:10:40.382Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 09:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0483|2024-02-09T19:10:34.569Z -- n/a -- Taokeyun
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0483</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Taokeyun up to 1.0.5. This vulnerability affects the function index of the file application/index/controller/app/Task.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument cid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250588.
In Taokeyun bis 1.0.5 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um die Funktion index der Datei application/index/controller/app/Task.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments cid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0483|2024-02-09T19:10:34.569Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 10:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>