<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for n/a -- ZZZCMS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/n%2Fa/zzzcms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for n/a -- ZZZCMS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5263|2023-10-24T19:48:43.349Z -- n%2Fa -- zzzcms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5263</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in ZZZCMS 2.1.7 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function restore of the file /admin/save.php of the component Database Backup File Handler. The manipulation leads to permission issues. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-240872.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in ZZZCMS 2.1.7 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion restore der Datei /admin/save.php der Komponente Database Backup File Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine permission issues-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5263|2023-10-24T19:48:43.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 14:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5582|2023-10-14T14:00:06.426Z -- n%2Fa -- zzzcms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5582</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in ZZZCMS 2.2.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Personal Profile Page. The manipulation leads to basic cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-242147.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in ZZZCMS 2.2.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Komponente Personal Profile Page. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine basic cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5582|2023-10-14T14:00:06.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 14:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
