<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for eXo -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/exo/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for eXo -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 06:24:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4902|2024-08-03T01:55:46.060Z -- exo -- chat%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4902</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in eXo Chat Application. Affected is an unknown function of the file application/src/main/webapp/vue-app/components/ExoChatMessageComposer.vue of the component Mention Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 3.3.0-20220417 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 26bf307d3658d1403cfd5c3ad423ce4c4d1cb2dc. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-220212.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in eXo Chat Application entdeckt. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei application/src/main/webapp/vue-app/components/ExoChatMessageComposer.vue der Komponente Mention Handler. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 3.3.0-20220417 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 26bf307d3658d1403cfd5c3ad423ce4c4d1cb2dc bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4902|2024-08-03T01:55:46.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 18:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
