<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for VMware -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/vmware/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for VMware -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5521|2024-08-04T20:01:51.589Z -- vmware -- vmware%20esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5521</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi (6.7 before ESXi670-201904101-SG and 6.5 before ESXi650-201903001), Workstation (15.x before 15.0.3 and 14.x before 14.1.6) and Fusion (11.x before 11.0.3 and 10.x before 10.1.6) contain an out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the pixel shader functionality. Successful exploitation of this issue may lead to information disclosure or may allow attackers with normal user privileges to create a denial-of-service condition on the host. Exploitation of this issue require an attacker to have access to a virtual machine with 3D graphics enabled. It is not enabled by default on ESXi and is enabled by default on Workstation and Fusion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5521|2024-08-04T20:01:51.589Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 18:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5517|2024-08-04T20:01:51.289Z -- vmware -- esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5517</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi (6.7 before ESXi670-201904101-SG and 6.5 before ESXi650-201903001), Workstation (15.x before 15.0.3 and 14.x before 14.1.6), Fusion (11.x before 11.0.3 and 10.x before 10.1.6) contain multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities in the shader translator. Exploitation of these issues requires an attacker to have access to a virtual machine with 3D graphics enabled. Successful exploitation of these issues may lead to information disclosure or may allow attackers with normal user privileges to create a denial-of-service condition on their own VM. The workaround for these issues involves disabling the 3D-acceleration feature. This feature is not enabled by default on ESXi and is enabled by default on Workstation and Fusion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5517|2024-08-04T20:01:51.289Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 17:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3958|2024-08-04T07:52:20.563Z -- vmware -- vmware%20esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3958</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi (6.7 before ESXi670-202004101-SG and 6.5 before ESXi650-202005401-SG), VMware Workstation (15.x before 15.5.2) and VMware Fusion (11.x before 11.5.2) contain a denial-of-service vulnerability in the shader functionality. Successful exploitation of this issue may allow attackers with non-administrative access to a virtual machine to crash the virtual machine's vmx process leading to a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3958|2024-08-04T07:52:20.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 19:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3966|2024-08-04T07:52:20.417Z -- vmware -- vmware%20esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3966</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi (7.0 before ESXi_7.0.0-1.20.16321839, 6.7 before ESXi670-202004101-SG and 6.5 before ESXi650-202005401-SG), Workstation (15.x before 15.5.2), and Fusion (11.x before 11.5.2) contain a heap-overflow due to a race condition issue in the USB 2.0 controller (EHCI). A malicious actor with local access to a virtual machine may be able to exploit this vulnerability to execute code on the hypervisor from a virtual machine. Additional conditions beyond the attacker's control must be present for exploitation to be possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3966|2024-08-04T07:52:20.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 14:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5539|2024-08-04T20:01:51.796Z -- vmware -- vmware%20workstation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5539</link>
      <description>VMware Workstation (15.x prior to 15.5.1) and Horizon View Agent (7.10.x prior to 7.10.1 and 7.5.x prior to 7.5.4) contain a DLL hijacking vulnerability due to insecure loading of a DLL by Cortado Thinprint. Successful exploitation of this issue may allow attackers with normal user privileges to escalate their privileges to administrator on a Windows machine where Workstation or View Agent is installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5539|2024-08-04T20:01:51.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 19:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5518|2024-08-04T20:01:51.546Z -- vmware -- vmware%20esxi%2C%20workstation%2C%20fusion
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5518</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi (6.7 before ESXi670-201903001, 6.5 before ESXi650-201903001, 6.0 before ESXi600-201903001), Workstation (15.x before 15.0.4, 14.x before 14.1.7), Fusion (11.x before 11.0.3, 10.x before 10.1.6) contain an out-of-bounds read/write vulnerability in the virtual USB 1.1 UHCI (Universal Host Controller Interface). Exploitation of this issue requires an attacker to have access to a virtual machine with a virtual USB controller present. This issue may allow a guest to execute code on the host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5518|2024-08-04T20:01:51.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 20:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5528|2024-08-04T20:01:51.756Z -- vmware -- esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5528</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi 6.5 suffers from partial denial of service vulnerability in hostd process. Patch ESXi650-201907201-UG for this issue is available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5528|2024-08-04T20:01:51.756Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 20:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5522|2024-08-04T20:01:51.934Z -- vmware -- vmware%20tools%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5522</link>
      <description>VMware Tools for Windows update addresses an out of bounds read vulnerability in vm3dmp driver which is installed with vmtools in Windows guest machines. This issue is present in versions 10.2.x and 10.3.x prior to 10.3.10. A local attacker with non-administrative access to a Windows guest with VMware Tools installed may be able to leak kernel information or create a denial of service attack on the same Windows guest machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5522|2024-08-04T20:01:51.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 19:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3962|2024-08-04T07:52:20.307Z -- vmware -- vmware%20esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3962</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi (7.0 before ESXi_7.0.0-1.20.16321839, 6.7 before ESXi670-202004101-SG and 6.5 before ESXi650-202005401-SG), Workstation (15.x before 15.5.5), and Fusion (11.x before 11.5.5) contain a use-after-free vulnerability in the SVGA device. A malicious actor with local access to a virtual machine with 3D graphics enabled may be able to exploit this vulnerability to execute code on the hypervisor from a virtual machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3962|2024-08-04T07:52:20.307Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 16:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3941|2024-08-04T07:52:20.398Z -- vmware -- vmware%20tools%20for%20windows%20%28vmware%20tools%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3941</link>
      <description>The repair operation of VMware Tools for Windows 10.x.y has a race condition which may allow for privilege escalation in the Virtual Machine where Tools is installed. This vulnerability is not present in VMware Tools 11.x.y since the affected functionality is not present in VMware Tools 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3941|2024-08-04T07:52:20.398Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 19:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5531|2024-08-04T20:01:51.896Z -- vmware -- vmware%20vsphere%20esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5531</link>
      <description>VMware vSphere ESXi (6.7 prior to ESXi670-201810101-SG, 6.5 prior to ESXi650-201811102-SG, and 6.0 prior to ESXi600-201807103-SG) and VMware vCenter Server (6.7 prior to 6.7 U1b, 6.5 prior to 6.5 U2b, and 6.0 prior to 6.0 U3j) contain an information disclosure vulnerability in clients arising from insufficient session expiration. An attacker with physical access or an ability to mimic a websocket connection to a user’s browser may be able to obtain control of a VM Console after the user has logged out or their session has timed out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5531|2024-08-04T20:01:51.896Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 21:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3970|2024-08-04T07:52:20.563Z -- vmware -- vmware%20esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3970</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi (7.0 before ESXi_7.0.0-1.20.16321839, 6.7 before ESXi670-202004101-SG and 6.5 before ESXi650-202005401-SG), Workstation (15.x before 15.5.5), and Fusion (11.x before 11.5.5) contain an out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the Shader functionality. A malicious actor with non-administrative local access to a virtual machine with 3D graphics enabled may be able to exploit this vulnerability to crash the virtual machine's vmx process leading to a partial denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3970|2024-08-04T07:52:20.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 14:37:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5514|2024-08-04T20:01:52.025Z -- vmware -- vmware%20fusion
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5514</link>
      <description>VMware VMware Fusion (11.x before 11.0.3) contains a security vulnerability due to certain unauthenticated APIs accessible through a web socket. An attacker may exploit this issue by tricking the host user to execute a JavaScript to perform unauthorized functions on the guest machine where VMware Tools is installed. This may further be exploited to execute commands on the guest machines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5514|2024-08-04T20:01:52.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 20:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5523|2024-08-04T20:01:51.415Z -- vmware -- vmware%20vcloud%20director%20for%20service%20providers%20%28vcd%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5523</link>
      <description>VMware vCloud Director for Service Providers 9.5.x prior to 9.5.0.3 update resolves a Remote Session Hijack vulnerability in the Tenant and Provider Portals. Successful exploitation of this issue may allow a malicious actor to access the Tenant or Provider Portals by impersonating a currently logged in session.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5523|2024-08-04T20:01:51.415Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 17:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3969|2024-08-04T07:52:20.611Z -- vmware -- vmware%20esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3969</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi (7.0 before ESXi_7.0.0-1.20.16321839, 6.7 before ESXi670-202004101-SG and 6.5 before ESXi650-202005401-SG), Workstation (15.x before 15.5.5), and Fusion (11.x before 11.5.5) contain an off-by-one heap-overflow vulnerability in the SVGA device. A malicious actor with local access to a virtual machine with 3D graphics enabled may be able to exploit this vulnerability to execute code on the hypervisor from a virtual machine. Additional conditions beyond the attacker's control must be present for exploitation to be possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3969|2024-08-04T07:52:20.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 16:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5541|2024-08-04T20:01:50.794Z -- vmware -- workstation%20and%20fusion
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5541</link>
      <description>VMware Workstation (15.x before 15.5.1) and Fusion (11.x before 11.5.1) contain an out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the e1000e virtual network adapter. Successful exploitation of this issue may lead to code execution on the host from the guest or may allow attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on their own VM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5541|2024-08-04T20:01:50.794Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 15:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3946|2024-08-04T07:52:20.295Z -- vmware -- installbuilder
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3946</link>
      <description>InstallBuilder AutoUpdate tool and regular installers enabling &lt;checkForUpdates&gt; built with versions earlier than 19.11 are vulnerable to Billion laughs attack (denial-of-service).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3946|2024-08-04T07:52:20.295Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 19:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5515|2024-08-04T20:01:51.317Z -- vmware -- vmware%20workstation%20and%20fusion
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5515</link>
      <description>VMware Workstation (15.x before 15.0.3, 14.x before 14.1.6) and Fusion (11.x before 11.0.3, 10.x before 10.1.6) updates address an out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the e1000 and e1000e virtual network adapters. Exploitation of this issue may lead to code execution on the host from the guest but it is more likely to result in a denial of service of the guest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5515|2024-08-04T20:01:51.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 14:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3948|2024-08-04T07:52:20.515Z -- vmware -- workstation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3948</link>
      <description>Linux Guest VMs running on VMware Workstation (15.x before 15.5.2) and Fusion (11.x before 11.5.2) contain a local privilege escalation vulnerability due to improper file permissions in Cortado Thinprint. Local attackers with non-administrative access to a Linux guest VM with virtual printing enabled may exploit this issue to elevate their privileges to root on the same guest VM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3948|2024-08-04T07:52:20.515Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 17:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3971|2024-08-04T07:52:20.541Z -- vmware -- vmware%20esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3971</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi (6.7 before ESXi670-201904101-SG and 6.5 before ESXi650-201907101-SG), Workstation (15.x before 15.0.2), and Fusion (11.x before 11.0.2) contain a heap overflow vulnerability in the vmxnet3 virtual network adapter. A malicious actor with local access to a virtual machine with a vmxnet3 network adapter present may be able to read privileged information contained in physical memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3971|2024-08-04T07:52:20.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 14:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3959|2024-08-04T07:52:20.401Z -- vmware -- vmware%20esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3959</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi (6.7 before ESXi670-202004101-SG and 6.5 before ESXi650-202005401-SG), VMware Workstation (15.x before 15.1.0) and VMware Fusion (11.x before 11.1.0) contain a memory leak vulnerability in the VMCI module. A malicious actor with local non-administrative access to a virtual machine may be able to crash the virtual machine's vmx process leading to a partial denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3959|2024-08-04T07:52:20.401Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 19:49:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3940|2024-08-04T07:52:20.417Z -- vmware -- workspace%20one%20sdk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3940</link>
      <description>VMware Workspace ONE SDK and dependent mobile application updates address sensitive information disclosure vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3940|2024-08-04T07:52:20.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 17:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5519|2024-08-04T20:01:51.426Z -- vmware -- vmware%20esxi%2C%20workstation%2C%20fusion
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5519</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi (6.7 before ESXi670-201903001, 6.5 before ESXi650-201903001, 6.0 before ESXi600-201903001), Workstation (15.x before 15.0.4, 14.x before 14.1.7), Fusion (11.x before 11.0.3, 10.x before 10.1.6) contain a Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) vulnerability in the virtual USB 1.1 UHCI (Universal Host Controller Interface). Exploitation of this issue requires an attacker to have access to a virtual machine with a virtual USB controller present. This issue may allow a guest to execute code on the host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5519|2024-08-04T20:01:51.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 20:39:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5516|2024-08-04T20:01:51.993Z -- vmware -- esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5516</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi (6.7 before ESXi670-201904101-SG and 6.5 before ESXi650-201903001), Workstation (15.x before 15.0.3 and 14.x before 14.1.6), Fusion (11.x before 11.0.3 and 10.x before 10.1.6) updates address an out-of-bounds vulnerability with the vertex shader functionality. Exploitation of this issue requires an attacker to have access to a virtual machine with 3D graphics enabled. Successful exploitation of this issue may lead to information disclosure or may allow attackers with normal user privileges to create a denial-of-service condition on their own VM. The workaround for this issue involves disabling the 3D-acceleration feature. This feature is not enabled by default on ESXi and is enabled by default on Workstation and Fusion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5516|2024-08-04T20:01:51.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5533|2024-08-04T20:01:51.956Z -- vmware -- sd-wan%20by%20velocloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5533</link>
      <description>In VMware SD-WAN by VeloCloud versions 3.x prior to 3.3.0, the VeloCloud Orchestrator parameter authorization check mistakenly allows enterprise users to obtain information of Managed Service Provider accounts. Among the information is username, first and last name, phone numbers and e-mail address if present but no other personal data. VMware has evaluated the severity of this issue to be in the moderate severity range with a maximum CVSSv3 base score of 4.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5533|2024-08-04T20:01:51.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 22:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5542|2024-08-04T20:01:50.748Z -- vmware -- workstation%20and%20fusion
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5542</link>
      <description>VMware Workstation (15.x before 15.5.1) and Fusion (11.x before 11.5.1) contain a denial-of-service vulnerability in the RPC handler. Successful exploitation of this issue may allow attackers with normal user privileges to create a denial-of-service condition on their own VM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5542|2024-08-04T20:01:50.748Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 15:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5540|2024-08-04T20:01:51.413Z -- vmware -- workstation%20and%20fusion
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5540</link>
      <description>VMware Workstation (15.x before 15.5.1) and Fusion (11.x before 11.5.1) contain an information disclosure vulnerability in vmnetdhcp. Successful exploitation of this issue may allow an attacker on a guest VM to disclose sensitive information by leaking memory from the host process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5540|2024-08-04T20:01:51.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 15:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3967|2024-08-04T07:52:20.621Z -- vmware -- vmware%20esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3967</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi (7.0 before ESXi_7.0.0-1.20.16321839, 6.7 before ESXi670-202004101-SG and 6.5 before ESXi650-202005401-SG), Workstation (15.x before 15.5.5), and Fusion (11.x before 11.5.5) contain a heap-overflow vulnerability in the USB 2.0 controller (EHCI). A malicious actor with local access to a virtual machine may be able to exploit this vulnerability to execute code on the hypervisor from a virtual machine. Additional conditions beyond the attacker's control must be present for exploitation to be possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3967|2024-08-04T07:52:20.621Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 14:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5532|2024-08-04T20:01:51.489Z -- vmware -- vcenter%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5532</link>
      <description>VMware vCenter Server (6.7.x prior to 6.7 U3, 6.5 prior to 6.5 U3 and 6.0 prior to 6.0 U3j) contains an information disclosure vulnerability due to the logging of credentials in plain-text for virtual machines deployed through OVF. A malicious user with access to the log files containing vCenter OVF-properties of a virtual machine deployed from an OVF may be able to view the credentials used to deploy the OVF (typically the root account of the virtual machine).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5532|2024-08-04T20:01:51.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 20:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3965|2024-08-04T07:52:20.544Z -- vmware -- vmware%20esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3965</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi (7.0 before ESXi_7.0.0-1.20.16321839, 6.7 before ESXi670-202006401-SG and 6.5 before ESXi650-202005401-SG), Workstation (15.x before 15.5.2), and Fusion (11.x before 11.5.2) contain an information leak in the XHCI USB controller. A malicious actor with local access to a virtual machine may be able to read privileged information contained in hypervisor memory from a virtual machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3965|2024-08-04T07:52:20.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 14:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5525|2024-08-04T20:01:51.689Z -- vmware -- vmware%20workstation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5525</link>
      <description>VMware Workstation (15.x before 15.1.0) contains a use-after-free vulnerability in the Advanced Linux Sound Architecture (ALSA) backend. A malicious user with normal user privileges on the guest machine may exploit this issue in conjunction with other issues to execute code on the Linux host where Workstation is installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5525|2024-08-04T20:01:51.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 19:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3957|2024-08-04T07:52:20.529Z -- vmware -- vmware%20fusion
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3957</link>
      <description>VMware Fusion (11.x before 11.5.5), VMware Remote Console for Mac (11.x and prior) and VMware Horizon Client for Mac (5.x and prior) contain a local privilege escalation vulnerability due to a Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) issue in the service opener. Successful exploitation of this issue may allow attackers with normal user privileges to escalate their privileges to root on the system where Fusion, VMRC and Horizon Client are installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3957|2024-08-04T07:52:20.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 19:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3968|2024-08-04T07:52:20.492Z -- vmware -- vmware%20esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3968</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi (7.0 before ESXi_7.0.0-1.20.16321839, 6.7 before ESXi670-202004101-SG and 6.5 before ESXi650-202005401-SG), Workstation (15.x before 15.5.5), and Fusion (11.x before 11.5.5) contain an out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the USB 3.0 controller (xHCI). A malicious actor with local administrative privileges on a virtual machine may be able to exploit this issue to crash the virtual machine's vmx process leading to a denial of service condition or execute code on the hypervisor from a virtual machine. Additional conditions beyond the attacker's control must be present for exploitation to be possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3968|2024-08-04T07:52:20.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 14:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3955|2024-08-04T07:52:20.472Z -- vmware -- esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3955</link>
      <description>ESXi 6.5 without patch ESXi650-201912104-SG and ESXi 6.7 without patch ESXi670-202004103-SG do not properly neutralize script-related HTML when viewing virtual machines attributes. VMware has evaluated the severity of this issue to be in the Important severity range with a maximum CVSSv3 base score of 8.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3955|2024-08-04T07:52:20.472Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 02:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3963|2024-08-04T07:52:20.479Z -- vmware -- vmware%20esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3963</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi (7.0 before ESXi_7.0.0-1.20.16321839, 6.7 before ESXi670-202006401-SG and 6.5 before ESXi650-202005401-SG), Workstation (15.x before 15.5.2), and Fusion (11.x before 11.5.2) contain a use-after-free vulnerability in PVNVRAM. A malicious actor with local access to a virtual machine may be able to read privileged information contained in physical memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3963|2024-08-04T07:52:20.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 14:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5524|2024-08-04T20:01:51.398Z -- vmware -- vmware%20workstation%2C%20vmware%20fusion
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5524</link>
      <description>VMware Workstation (14.x before 14.1.6) and Fusion (10.x before 10.1.6) contain an out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the e1000 virtual network adapter. This issue may allow a guest to execute code on the host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5524|2024-08-04T20:01:51.398Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 14:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5534|2024-08-04T20:01:51.962Z -- vmware -- vcenter%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5534</link>
      <description>VMware vCenter Server (6.7.x prior to 6.7 U3, 6.5 prior to 6.5 U3 and 6.0 prior to 6.0 U3j) contains an information disclosure vulnerability where Virtual Machines deployed from an OVF could expose login information via the virtual machine's vAppConfig properties. A malicious actor with access to query the vAppConfig properties of a virtual machine deployed from an OVF may be able to view the credentials used to deploy the OVF (typically the root account of the virtual machine).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5534|2024-08-04T20:01:51.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 20:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3944|2024-08-04T07:52:20.339Z -- vmware -- vrealize%20operations%20for%20horizon%20adapter
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3944</link>
      <description>vRealize Operations for Horizon Adapter (6.7.x prior to 6.7.1 and 6.6.x prior to 6.6.1) has an improper trust store configuration leading to authentication bypass. An unauthenticated remote attacker who has network access to vRealize Operations, with the Horizon Adapter running, may be able to bypass Adapter authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3944|2024-08-04T07:52:20.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 20:03:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3943|2024-08-04T07:52:20.381Z -- vmware -- vrealize%20operations%20for%20horizon%20adapter
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3943</link>
      <description>vRealize Operations for Horizon Adapter (6.7.x prior to 6.7.1 and 6.6.x prior to 6.6.1) uses a JMX RMI service which is not securely configured. An unauthenticated remote attacker who has network access to vRealize Operations, with the Horizon Adapter running, may be able to execute arbitrary code in vRealize Operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3943|2024-08-04T07:52:20.381Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 20:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3947|2024-08-04T07:52:20.506Z -- vmware -- workstation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3947</link>
      <description>VMware Workstation (15.x before 15.5.2) and Fusion (11.x before 11.5.2) contain a use-after vulnerability in vmnetdhcp. Successful exploitation of this issue may lead to code execution on the host from the guest or may allow attackers to create a denial-of-service condition of the vmnetdhcp service running on the host machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3947|2024-08-04T07:52:20.506Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 17:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3964|2024-08-04T07:52:20.578Z -- vmware -- vmware%20esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3964</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi (7.0 before ESXi_7.0.0-1.20.16321839, 6.7 before ESXi670-202006401-SG and 6.5 before ESXi650-202005401-SG), Workstation (15.x before 15.5.2), and Fusion (11.x before 11.5.2) contain an information leak in the EHCI USB controller. A malicious actor with local access to a virtual machine may be able to read privileged information contained in the hypervisor's memory. Additional conditions beyond the attacker's control need to be present for exploitation to be possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3964|2024-08-04T07:52:20.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 14:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-3945|2024-08-04T07:52:20.842Z -- vmware -- vrealize%20operations%20for%20horizon%20adapter
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-3945</link>
      <description>vRealize Operations for Horizon Adapter (6.7.x prior to 6.7.1 and 6.6.x prior to 6.6.1) contains an information disclosure vulnerability due to incorrect pairing implementation between the vRealize Operations for Horizon Adapter and Horizon View. An unauthenticated remote attacker who has network access to vRealize Operations, with the Horizon Adapter running, may obtain sensitive information</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-3945|2024-08-04T07:52:20.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 20:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5543|2024-08-04T20:01:51.489Z -- vmware -- vmware%20horizon%20client%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5543</link>
      <description>For VMware Horizon Client for Windows (5.x and prior before 5.3.0), VMware Remote Console for Windows (10.x before 11.0.0), VMware Workstation for Windows (15.x before 15.5.2) the folder containing configuration files for the VMware USB arbitration service was found to be writable by all users. A local user on the system where the software is installed may exploit this issue to run commands as any user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5543|2024-08-04T20:01:51.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 17:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5520|2024-08-04T20:01:51.278Z -- vmware -- esxi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5520</link>
      <description>VMware ESXi (6.7 before ESXi670-201904101-SG and 6.5 before ESXi650-201903001), Workstation (15.x before 15.0.3 and 14.x before 14.1.6), Fusion (11.x before 11.0.3 and 10.x before 10.1.6) updates address an out-of-bounds read vulnerability. Exploitation of this issue requires an attacker to have access to a virtual machine with 3D graphics enabled. Successful exploitation of this issue may lead to information disclosure.The workaround for this issue involves disabling the 3D-acceleration feature. This feature is not enabled by default on ESXi and is enabled by default on Workstation and Fusion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5520|2024-08-04T20:01:51.278Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 17:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22264|2024-08-01T22:43:33.697Z -- vmware -- vmware%20avi%20load%20balancer</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22264</link>
      <description>VMware Avi Load Balancer contains a privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with admin privileges on VMware Avi Load Balancer can create, modify, execute and delete files as a root user on the host system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22264|2024-08-01T22:43:33.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22250|2024-08-01T22:43:33.666Z -- vmware -- vmware%20enhanced%20authentication%20plug-in%20%28eap%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22250</link>
      <description>Session Hijack vulnerability in Deprecated VMware Enhanced Authentication Plug-in could allow a malicious actor with unprivileged local access to a windows operating system can hijack a privileged EAP session when initiated by a privileged domain user on the same system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22250|2024-08-01T22:43:33.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 17:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22280|2024-08-01T22:43:34.225Z -- vmware -- vmware%20aria%20automation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22280</link>
      <description>VMware Aria Automation does not apply correct input validation which allows for SQL-injection in the product. An authenticated malicious user could enter specially crafted SQL queries and perform unauthorised read/write operations in the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22280|2024-08-01T22:43:34.225Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 04:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22232|2024-08-01T22:43:33.697Z -- vmware -- salt%20project</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22232</link>
      <description>A specially crafted url can be created which leads to a directory traversal in the salt file server.
A malicious user can read an arbitrary file from a Salt master’s filesystem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22232|2024-08-01T22:43:33.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22245|2024-08-01T22:43:34.194Z -- vmware -- vmware%20enhanced%20authentication%20plug-in%20%28eap%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22245</link>
      <description>Arbitrary Authentication Relay and Session Hijack vulnerabilities in the deprecated VMware Enhanced Authentication Plug-in (EAP) could allow a malicious actor that could trick a target domain user with EAP installed in their web browser into requesting and relaying service tickets for arbitrary Active Directory Service Principal Names (SPNs).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22245|2024-08-01T22:43:34.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 17:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22231|2024-08-01T22:43:33.678Z -- vmware -- salt%20project</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22231</link>
      <description>Syndic cache directory creation is vulnerable to a directory traversal attack in salt project which can lead a malicious attacker to create an arbitrary directory on a Salt master.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22231|2024-08-01T22:43:33.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22266|2024-08-01T22:43:34.137Z -- vmware -- vmware%20avi%20load%20balancer</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22266</link>
      <description>VMware Avi Load Balancer contains an information disclosure vulnerability. A malicious actor with access to the system logs can view cloud connection credentials in plaintext.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22266|2024-08-01T22:43:34.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22280|2024-07-11T04:39:09.353Z -- vmware -- vmware%20aria%20automation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22280</link>
      <description>VMware Aria Automation does not apply correct input validation which allows for SQL-injection in the product. An authenticated malicious user could enter specially crafted SQL queries and perform unauthorised read/write operations in the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22280|2024-07-11T04:39:09.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 04:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22232|2024-06-27T14:43:01.077Z -- vmware -- salt%20project</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22232</link>
      <description>A specially crafted url can be created which leads to a directory traversal in the salt file server.
A malicious user can read an arbitrary file from a Salt master’s filesystem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22232|2024-06-27T14:43:01.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22264|2024-06-04T17:52:46.529Z -- vmware -- vmware%20avi%20load%20balancer</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22264</link>
      <description>VMware Avi Load Balancer contains a privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with admin privileges on VMware Avi Load Balancer can create, modify, execute and delete files as a root user on the host system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22264|2024-06-04T17:52:46.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22245|2024-02-20T17:35:09.051Z -- vmware -- vmware%20enhanced%20authentication%20plug-in%20%28eap%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22245</link>
      <description>Arbitrary Authentication Relay and Session Hijack vulnerabilities in the deprecated VMware Enhanced Authentication Plug-in (EAP) could allow a malicious actor that could trick a target domain user with EAP installed in their web browser into requesting and relaying service tickets for arbitrary Active Directory Service Principal Names (SPNs).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22245|2024-02-20T17:35:09.051Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 17:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22250|2024-02-20T17:35:23.481Z -- vmware -- vmware%20enhanced%20authentication%20plug-in%20%28eap%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22250</link>
      <description>Session Hijack vulnerability in Deprecated VMware Enhanced Authentication Plug-in could allow a malicious actor with unprivileged local access to a windows operating system can hijack a privileged EAP session when initiated by a privileged domain user on the same system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22250|2024-02-20T17:35:23.481Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 17:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22266|2024-06-04T17:52:37.209Z -- vmware -- vmware%20avi%20load%20balancer</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22266</link>
      <description>VMware Avi Load Balancer contains an information disclosure vulnerability. A malicious actor with access to the system logs can view cloud connection credentials in plaintext.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22266|2024-06-04T17:52:37.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22232|2024-06-27T06:54:08.785Z -- vmware -- salt%20project</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22232</link>
      <description>A specially crafted url can be created which leads to a directory traversal in the salt file server.
A malicious user can read an arbitrary file from a Salt master’s filesystem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22232|2024-06-27T06:54:08.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22231|2024-06-27T06:51:44.428Z -- vmware -- salt%20project</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22231</link>
      <description>Syndic cache directory creation is vulnerable to a directory traversal attack in salt project which can lead a malicious attacker to create an arbitrary directory on a Salt master.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22231|2024-06-27T06:51:44.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22231|2024-07-08T20:00:12.450Z -- vmware -- salt%20project</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22231</link>
      <description>Syndic cache directory creation is vulnerable to a directory traversal attack in salt project which can lead a malicious attacker to create an arbitrary directory on a Salt master.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22231|2024-07-08T20:00:12.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22280|2024-07-12T14:47:28.386Z -- vmware -- vmware%20aria%20automation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22280</link>
      <description>VMware Aria Automation does not apply correct input validation which allows for SQL-injection in the product. An authenticated malicious user could enter specially crafted SQL queries and perform unauthorised read/write operations in the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22280|2024-07-12T14:47:28.386Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 04:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
