<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for nextcloud -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nextcloud/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for nextcloud -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:22:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29438|2024-08-03T22:02:51.929Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloud-dialogs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29438</link>
      <description>The Nextcloud dialogs library (npm package @nextcloud/dialogs) before 3.1.2 insufficiently escaped text input passed to a toast. If your application displays toasts with user-supplied input, this could lead to a XSS vulnerability. The vulnerability has been patched in version 3.1.2 If you need to display HTML in the toast, explicitly pass the `options.isHTML` config flag.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29438|2024-08-03T22:02:51.929Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 18:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24741|2024-08-03T04:20:50.493Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24741</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is an open source, self hosted cloud style services platform. In affected versions an attacker can cause a denial of service by uploading specially crafted files which will cause the server to allocate too much memory / CPU. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 21.0.8 , 22.2.4 or 23.0.1. Users unable to upgrade should disable preview generation with the `'enable_previews'` config flag.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24741|2024-08-03T04:20:50.493Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 21:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29243|2024-08-03T06:17:54.531Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29243</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is the file server software for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. Prior to versions 22.2.7 and 23.0.4, missing input-size validation of new session names allows users to create app passwords with long names. These long names are then loaded into memory on usage, resulting in impacted performance. Versions 22.2.7 and 23.0.4 contain a fix for this issue. There are currently no known workarounds available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29243|2024-08-03T06:17:54.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 16:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39210|2024-08-03T12:00:42.598Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39210</link>
      <description>Nextcloud android is the official Android client for the Nextcloud home server platform. Internal paths to the Nextcloud Android app files are not properly protected. As a result access to internal files of the from within the Nextcloud Android app is possible. This may lead to a leak of sensitive information in some cases. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Android app is upgraded to 3.21.0. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39210|2024-08-03T12:00:42.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 23:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41969|2024-08-03T12:56:39.151Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41969</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is an open source personal cloud server. Prior to versions 23.0.11, 24.0.7, and 25.0.0, there is no password length limit when creating a user as an administrator. An administrator can cause a limited DoS attack against their own server. Versions 23.0.11, 24.0.7, and 25.0.0 contain a fix for the issue. As a workaround, don't create user accounts with long passwords.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41969|2024-08-03T12:56:39.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 20:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31118|2024-08-03T07:11:39.437Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31118</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is an open source personal cloud solution. In affected versions an attacker could brute force to find if federated sharing is being used and potentially try to brute force access tokens for federated shares (`a-zA-Z0-9` ^ 15). It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 22.2.9, 23.0.6 or 24.0.2. Users unable to upgrade may disable federated sharing via the Admin Sharing settings in `index.php/settings/admin/sharing`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31118|2024-08-03T07:11:39.437Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 16:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39364|2024-08-03T12:00:44.215Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39364</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is the file server software for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. In Nextcloud Server prior to versions 23.0.9 and 24.0.5 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server prior to versions 22.2.10.5, 23.0.9, and 24.0.5 an attacker reading `nextcloud.log` may gain knowledge of credentials to connect to a SharePoint service. Nextcloud Server versions 23.0.9 and 24.0.5 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server versions 22.2.10.5, 23.0.9, and 24.0.5 contain a patch for this issue. As a workaround, set `zend.exception_ignore_args = On` as an option in `php.ini`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39364|2024-08-03T12:00:44.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24890|2024-08-03T04:29:00.657Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24890</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Talk is a video and audio conferencing app for Nextcloud. In versions prior to 13.0.5 and 14.0.0, a call moderator can indirectly enable user webcams by granting permissions, if they were enabled before removing the permissions. A patch is available in versions 13.0.5 and 14.0.0. There are currently no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24890|2024-08-03T04:29:00.657Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 19:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39330|2024-08-03T12:00:44.115Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39330</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is the file server software for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. Nextcloud Server prior to versions 23.0.10 and 24.0.6 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server prior to versions 22.2.10, 23.0.10, and 24.0.6 are vulnerable to a logged-in attacker slowing down the system by generating a lot of database/cpu load. Nextcloud Server versions 23.0.10 and 24.0.6 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server versions 22.2.10, 23.0.10, and 24.0.6 contain patches for this issue. As a workaround, disable the Circles app.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39330|2024-08-03T12:00:44.115Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35932|2024-08-03T09:51:59.100Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35932</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Talk is a video and audio conferencing app for Nextcloud. Prior to versions 12.2.7, 13.0.7, and 14.0.3, password protected conversations are susceptible to brute force attacks if the attacker has the link/conversation token. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Talk application is upgraded to 12.2.7, 13.0.7 or 14.0.3. There are currently no known workarounds available apart from not having password protected conversations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35932|2024-08-03T09:51:59.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 15:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24838|2024-08-03T04:20:50.470Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24838</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Calendar is a calendar application for the nextcloud framework. SMTP Command Injection in Appointment Emails via Newlines: as newlines and special characters are not sanitized in the email value in the JSON request, a malicious attacker can inject newlines to break out of the `RCPT TO:&lt;BOOKING USER'S EMAIL&gt; ` SMTP command and begin injecting arbitrary SMTP commands. It is recommended that Calendar is upgraded to 3.2.2. There are no workaround available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24838|2024-08-03T04:20:50.470Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 20:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39331|2024-08-03T12:00:44.041Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39331</link>
      <description>Nexcloud desktop is the Desktop sync client for Nextcloud. An attacker can inject arbitrary HyperText Markup Language into the Desktop Client application in the notifications. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Desktop client is upgraded to 3.6.1. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39331|2024-08-03T12:00:44.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24888|2024-08-03T04:29:01.545Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24888</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is the file server software for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. Prior to versions 20.0.14.4, 21.0.8, 22.2.4, and 23.0.1, it is possible to create files and folders that have leading and trailing \n, \r, \t, and \v characters. The server rejects files and folders that have these characters in the middle of their names, so this might be an opportunity for injection. This issue is fixed in versions 20.0.14.4, 21.0.8, 22.2.4, and 23.0.1. There are currently no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24888|2024-08-03T04:29:01.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 14:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41882|2024-08-03T12:56:38.248Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41882</link>
      <description>The Nextcloud Desktop Client is a tool to synchronize files from Nextcloud Server with your computer. In version 3.6.0, if a user received a malicious file share and has it synced locally or the virtual filesystem enabled and clicked a nc://open/ link it will open the default editor for the file type of the shared file, which on Windows can also sometimes mean that a file depending on the type, e.g. "vbs", is being executed. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Desktop client is upgraded to version 3.6.1. As a workaround, users can block the Nextcloud Desktop client 3.6.0 by setting the `minimum.supported.desktop.version` system config to `3.6.1` on the server, so new files designed to use this attack vector are not downloaded anymore. Already existing files can still be used. Another workaround would be to enforce shares to be accepted by setting the `sharing.force_share_accept` system config to `true` on the server, so new files designed to use this attack vector are not downloaded anymore. Already existing shares can still be abused.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41882|2024-08-03T12:56:38.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41971|2024-08-03T12:56:39.100Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41971</link>
      <description>Nextcould Talk android is a video and audio conferencing app for Nextcloud. Prior to versions 12.2.8, 13.0.10, 14.0.6, and 15.0.0, guests can continue to receive video streams from a call after being removed from a conversation. An attacker would be able to see videos on a call in a public conversation after being removed from that conversation, provided that they were removed while being in the call. Versions 12.2.8, 13.0.10, 14.0.6, and 15.0.0 contain patches for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41971|2024-08-03T12:56:39.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 20:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39339|2024-08-03T12:00:44.166Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39339</link>
      <description>user_oidc is an OpenID Connect user backend for Nextcloud. In versions prior to 1.2.1 sensitive information such as the OIDC client credentials and tokens are sent in plain text of HTTP without TLS. Any malicious actor with access to monitor user traffic may have been able to compromise account security. This issue has been addressed in in user_oidc v1.2.1. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may use https to access Nextcloud. Set an HTTPS discovery URL in the provider settings (in Nextcloud OIDC admin settings).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39339|2024-08-03T12:00:44.166Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24885|2024-08-03T04:29:01.622Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24885</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Android app is the Android client for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. Prior to version 3.19.1, users can bypass a lock on the Nextcloud app on an Android device by repeatedly reopening the app. Version 3.19.1 contains a fix for the problem. There are currently no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24885|2024-08-03T04:29:01.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 13:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31131|2024-08-03T07:11:39.196Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31131</link>
      <description>Nextcloud mail is a Mail app for the Nextcloud home server product. Versions of Nextcloud mail prior to 1.12.2 were found to be missing user account ownership checks when performing tasks related to mail attachments. Attachments may have been exposed to incorrect system users. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Mail app is upgraded to 1.12.2. There are no known workarounds for this issue. ### Workarounds No workaround available ### References * [Pull request](https://github.com/nextcloud/mail/pull/6600) * [HackerOne](https://hackerone.com/reports/1579820) ### For more information If you have any questions or comments about this advisory: * Create a post in [nextcloud/security-advisories](https://github.com/nextcloud/security-advisories/discussions) * Customers: Open a support ticket at [support.nextcloud.com](https://support.nextcloud.com)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31131|2024-08-03T07:11:39.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 17:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39334|2024-08-03T12:00:44.104Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39334</link>
      <description>Nextcloud also ships a CLI utility called nextcloudcmd which is sometimes used for automated scripting and headless servers. Versions of nextcloudcmd prior to 3.6.1 would incorrectly trust invalid TLS certificates, which may enable a Man-in-the-middle attack that exposes sensitive data or credentials to a network attacker. This affects the CLI only. It does not affect the standard GUI desktop Nextcloud clients, and it does not affect the Nextcloud server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39334|2024-08-03T12:00:44.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36074|2024-08-03T09:52:00.462Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36074</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is an open source personal cloud product. Affected versions of this package are vulnerable to Information Exposure which fails to strip the Authorization header on HTTP downgrade. This can lead to account access exposure and compromise. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 23.0.7 or 24.0.3. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 22.2.11, 23.0.7 or 24.0.3. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36074|2024-08-03T09:52:00.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 22:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39346|2024-08-03T12:00:44.115Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39346</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is an open source personal cloud server. Affected versions of nextcloud server did not properly limit user display names which could allow a malicious users to overload the backing database and cause a denial of service. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 22.2.10, 23.0.7 or 24.0.3. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39346|2024-08-03T12:00:44.115Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24906|2024-08-03T04:29:01.616Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24906</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Deck is a Kanban-style project &amp; personal management tool for Nextcloud, similar to Trello. The full path of the application is exposed to unauthorized users. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Deck app is upgraded to 1.2.11, 1.4.6, or 1.5.4. There is no workaround available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24906|2024-08-03T04:29:01.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41970|2024-08-03T12:56:39.097Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41970</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is an open source personal cloud server. Prior to versions 24.0.7 and 25.0.1, disabled download shares still allow download through preview images. Images could be downloaded and previews of documents (first page) can be downloaded without being watermarked. Versions 24.0.7 and 25.0.1 contain a fix for this issue. No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41970|2024-08-03T12:56:39.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 20:54:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39333|2024-08-03T12:00:44.081Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39333</link>
      <description>Nexcloud desktop is the Desktop sync client for Nextcloud. An attacker can inject arbitrary HyperText Markup Language into the Desktop Client application. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Desktop client is upgraded to 3.6.1. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39333|2024-08-03T12:00:44.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39212|2024-08-03T12:00:43.190Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39212</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Talk is an open source chat, video &amp; audio calls client for the Nextcloud platform. In affected versions an attacker could see the last video frame of any participant who has video disabled but a camera selected. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Talk app is upgraded to 13.0.8 or 14.0.4. Users unable to upgrade should select "None" as camera before joining the call.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39212|2024-08-03T12:00:43.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 23:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35931|2024-08-03T09:51:59.040Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35931</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Password Policy is an app that enables a Nextcloud server admin to define certain rules for passwords. Prior to versions 22.2.10, 23.0.7, and 24.0.3 the random password generator may, in very rare cases, generate common passwords that the validator itself would block. Upgrade Nextcloud Server to 22.2.10, 23.0.7 or 24.0.3 to receive a patch for the issue in Password Policy. There are no known workarounds available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35931|2024-08-03T09:51:59.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 18:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31014|2024-08-03T07:03:40.244Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31014</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is an open source personal cloud server. Affected versions were found to be vulnerable to SMTP command injection. The impact varies based on which commands are supported by the backend SMTP server. However, the main risk here is that the attacker can then hijack an already-authenticated SMTP session and run arbitrary SMTP commands as the email user, such as sending emails to other users, changing the FROM user, and so on. As before, this depends on the configuration of the server itself, but newlines should be sanitized to mitigate such arbitrary SMTP command injection. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 22.2.8 , 23.0.5 or 24.0.1. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31014|2024-08-03T07:03:40.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 17:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39338|2024-08-03T12:00:44.112Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39338</link>
      <description>user_oidc is an OpenID Connect user backend for Nextcloud. Versions prior to 1.2.1 did not properly validate discovery urls which may lead to a stored cross site scripting attack vector. The impact is limited due to the restrictive CSP that is applied on this endpoint. Additionally this vulnerability has only been shown to be exploitable in the Safari web browser. This issue has been addressed in version 1.2.1. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should urge their users to avoid using the Safari web browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39338|2024-08-03T12:00:44.112Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39329|2024-08-03T12:00:44.110Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39329</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is the file server software for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. Nextcloud Server and Nextcloud Enterprise Server prior to versions 23.0.9 and 24.0.5 are vulnerable to exposure of information that cannot be controlled by administrators without direct database access. Versions 23.0.9 and 24.0.5 contains patches for this issue. No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39329|2024-08-03T12:00:44.110Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24889|2024-08-03T04:29:01.495Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24889</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is the file server software for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. Prior to versions 21.0.8, 22.2.4, and 23.0.1, it is possible to trick administrators into enabling "recommended" apps for the Nextcloud server that they do not need, thus expanding their attack surface unnecessarily. This issue is fixed in versions 21.0.8 , 22.2.4, and 23.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24889|2024-08-03T04:29:01.495Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 14:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41968|2024-08-03T12:56:39.130Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41968</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is an open source personal cloud server. Prior to versions 23.0.10 and 24.0.5, calendar name lengths are not validated before writing to a database. As a result, an attacker can send unnecessary amounts of data against the database. Version 23.0.10 and 24.0.5 contain patches for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41968|2024-08-03T12:56:39.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 20:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39211|2024-08-03T12:00:43.476Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39211</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is an open source personal cloud platform. In affected versions it was found that locally running webservices can be found and requested erroneously. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 23.0.8 or 24.0.4. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 22.2.10.4, 23.0.8 or 24.0.4. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39211|2024-08-03T12:00:43.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 23:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24886|2024-08-03T04:29:01.649Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24886</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Android app is the Android client for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. In versions prior to 3.19.0, any application with notification permission can access contacts if Nextcloud has access to Contacts without applying for the Contacts permission itself. Version 3.19.0 contains a fix for this issue. There are currently no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24886|2024-08-03T04:29:01.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 13:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24887|2024-08-03T04:29:00.701Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24887</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Talk is a video and audio conferencing app for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. Prior to versions 11.3.4, 12.2.2, and 13.0.0, when sharing a Deck card in conversation, the metaData can be manipulated so users can be tricked into opening arbitrary URLs. This issue is fixed in versions 11.3.4, 12.2.2, and 13.0.0. There are currently no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24887|2024-08-03T04:29:00.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 13:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31120|2024-08-03T07:11:39.406Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31120</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is an open source personal cloud solution. The audit log is used to get a full trail of the actions which has been incompletely populated. In affected versions federated share events were not properly logged which would allow brute force attacks to go unnoticed. This behavior exacerbates the impact of CVE-2022-31118. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 22.2.7, 23.0.4 or 24.0.0. There are no workarounds available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31120|2024-08-03T07:11:39.406Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 17:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29160|2024-08-03T06:10:59.479Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29160</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Android is the Android client for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. Prior to version 3.19.0, sensitive tokens, images, and user related details exist after deletion of a user account. This could result in misuse of the former account holder's information. Nextcloud Android version 3.19.0 contains a patch for this issue. There are no known workarounds available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29160|2024-08-03T06:10:59.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 15:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31024|2024-08-03T07:03:40.286Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31024</link>
      <description>richdocuments is the repository for NextCloud Collabra, the app for Nextcloud Office collaboration. Prior to versions 6.0.0, 5.0.4, and 4.2.6, a user could be tricked into working against a remote Office by sending them a federated share. richdocuments versions 6.0.0, 5.0.4 and 4.2.6 contain a fix for this issue. There are currently no known workarounds available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31024|2024-08-03T07:03:40.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 18:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39332|2024-08-03T12:00:44.115Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39332</link>
      <description>Nexcloud desktop is the Desktop sync client for Nextcloud. An attacker can inject arbitrary HyperText Markup Language into the Desktop Client application via user status and information. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Desktop client is upgraded to 3.6.1. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39332|2024-08-03T12:00:44.115Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41926|2024-08-03T12:56:38.532Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41926</link>
      <description>Nextcould talk android is the android OS implementation of the nextcloud talk chat system. In affected versions the receiver is not protected by broadcastPermission allowing malicious apps to monitor communication. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Talk Android is upgraded to 14.1.0. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41926|2024-08-03T12:56:38.532Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31132|2024-08-03T07:11:39.264Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31132</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Mail is an email application for the nextcloud personal cloud product. Affected versions shipped with a CSS minifier on the path `./vendor/cerdic/css-tidy/css_optimiser.php`. Access to the minifier is unrestricted and access may lead to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF). It is recommendet to upgrade to Mail 1.12.7 or Mail 1.13.6. Users unable to upgrade may manually delete the file located at `./vendor/cerdic/css-tidy/css_optimiser.php`</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31132|2024-08-03T07:11:39.264Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 17:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29163|2024-08-03T06:17:53.907Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29163</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is the file server software for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. Prior to versions 22.2.6 and 23.0.3, a user can create a link that is not password protected even if the administrator requires links to be password protected. Versions 22.2.6 and 23.0.3 contain a patch for this issue. There are currently no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29163|2024-08-03T06:17:53.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 16:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31119|2024-08-03T07:11:39.571Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31119</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Mail is an email application for the nextcloud personal cloud product. Affected versions of Nextcloud mail would log user passwords to disk in the event of a misconfiguration. Should an attacker gain access to the logs complete access to affected accounts would be obtainable. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Mail is upgraded to 1.12.1. Operators should inspect their logs and remove passwords which have been logged. There are no workarounds to prevent logging in the event of a misconfiguration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31119|2024-08-03T07:11:39.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 17:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36075|2024-08-03T09:52:00.295Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36075</link>
      <description>Nextcloud files access control is a nextcloud app to manage access control for files. Users with limited access can see file names in certain cases where they do not have privilege to do so. This issue has been addressed and it is recommended that the Nextcloud Files Access Control app is upgraded to 1.12.2, 1.13.1 or 1.14.1. There are no known workarounds for this issue</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36075|2024-08-03T09:52:00.295Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 21:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29159|2024-08-03T06:10:59.270Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29159</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Deck is a Kanban-style project &amp; personal management tool for Nextcloud. In versions prior to 1.4.8, 1.5.6, and 1.6.1, an authenticated user can move stacks with cards from their own board to a board of another user. The Nextcloud Deck app contains a patch for this issue in versions 1.4.8, 1.5.6, and 1.6.1. There are no known currently-known workarounds available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29159|2024-08-03T06:10:59.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 15:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37316|2024-08-02T03:50:56.106Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37316</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Calendar is a calendar app for Nextcloud. Authenticated users could create an event with manipulated attachment data leading to a bad redirect for participants when clicked. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Calendar App is upgraded to 4.6.8 or 4.7.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37316|2024-08-02T03:50:56.106Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37314|2024-08-02T03:50:56.192Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37314</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Photos is a photo management app. Users can remove photos from the album of registered users. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 25.0.7 or 26.0.2 and the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 25.0.7 or 26.0.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37314|2024-08-02T03:50:56.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37886|2024-08-02T03:57:40.025Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37886</link>
      <description>user_oidc app is an OpenID Connect user backend for Nextcloud. An attacker could potentially trick the app into accepting a request that is not signed by the correct server. It is recommended that the Nextcloud user_oidc app is upgraded to 1.3.5, 2.0.0, 3.0.0, 4.0.0 or 5.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37886|2024-08-02T03:57:40.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37884|2024-08-02T03:57:39.918Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37884</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. A malicious user was able to send delete requests for old versions of files they only got shared with read permissions. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.12 or 27.1.7 or 28.0.3 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 26.0.12 or 27.1.7 or 28.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37884|2024-08-02T03:57:39.918Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37885|2024-08-02T03:57:39.894Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37885</link>
      <description>The Nextcloud Desktop Client is a tool to synchronize files from Nextcloud Server with your computer. A code injection in Nextcloud Desktop Client for macOS allowed to load arbitrary code when starting the client with DYLD_INSERT_LIBRARIES set in the enviroment. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Desktop client is upgraded to 3.12.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37885|2024-08-02T03:57:39.894Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:42:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37312|2024-08-02T03:50:55.709Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37312</link>
      <description>user_oidc app is an OpenID Connect user backend for Nextcloud. Missing access control on the ID4me endpoint allows an attacker to register an account eventually getting access to data that is available to all registered users. It is recommended that the OpenID Connect user backend is upgraded to 3.0.0 (Nextcloud 20-23), 4.0.0 (Nexcloud 24) or 5.0.0 (Nextcloud 25-28).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37312|2024-08-02T03:50:55.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37313|2024-08-02T03:50:56.117Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37313</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is a self hosted personal cloud system. Under some circumstance it was possible to bypass the second factor of 2FA after successfully providing the user credentials. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.13, 27.1.8 or 28.0.4 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 21.0.9.17, 22.2.10.22, 23.0.12.17, 24.0.12.13, 25.0.13.8, 26.0.13, 27.1.8 or 28.0.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37313|2024-08-02T03:50:56.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37317|2024-08-02T03:50:55.961Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37317</link>
      <description>The Nextcloud Notes app is a distraction free notes taking app for Nextcloud. If an attacker managed to share a folder called `Notes/` with a newly created user before they logged in, the Notes app would use that folder store the personal notes. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Notes app is upgraded to 4.9.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37317|2024-08-02T03:50:55.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37315|2024-08-02T03:50:55.709Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37315</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. An attacker with read-only access to a file is able to restore older versions of a document when the files_versions app is enabled. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.12, 27.1.7 or 28.0.3 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 23.0.12.16, 24.0.12.12, 25.0.13.6, 26.0.12, 27.1.7 or 28.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37315|2024-08-02T03:50:55.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37887|2024-08-02T03:57:40.075Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37887</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. Private shared calendar events' recurrence exceptions can be read by sharees. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 27.1.10 or 28.0.6 or 29.0.1 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 27.1.10 or 28.0.6 or 29.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37887|2024-08-02T03:57:40.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37883|2024-08-02T03:57:39.902Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37883</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Deck is a kanban style organization tool aimed at personal planning and project organization for teams integrated with Nextcloud. A user with access to a deck board was able to access comments and attachments of already deleted cards. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Deck app is upgraded to 1.6.6 or 1.7.5 or 1.8.7 or 1.9.6 or 1.11.3 or 1.12.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37883|2024-08-02T03:57:39.902Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37882|2024-08-02T03:57:39.988Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37882</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. A recipient of a share with read&amp;amp;share permissions could reshare the item with more permissions. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.13 or 27.1.8 or 28.0.4 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 26.0.13 or 27.1.8 or 28.0.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37882|2024-08-02T03:57:39.988Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37314|2024-07-30T14:25:26.489Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37314</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Photos is a photo management app. Users can remove photos from the album of registered users. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 25.0.7 or 26.0.2 and the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 25.0.7 or 26.0.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37314|2024-07-30T14:25:26.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37315|2024-06-17T15:13:32.772Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37315</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. An attacker with read-only access to a file is able to restore older versions of a document when the files_versions app is enabled. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.12, 27.1.7 or 28.0.3 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 23.0.12.16, 24.0.12.12, 25.0.13.6, 26.0.12, 27.1.7 or 28.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37315|2024-06-17T15:13:32.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37886|2024-06-15T20:30:30.682Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37886</link>
      <description>user_oidc app is an OpenID Connect user backend for Nextcloud. An attacker could potentially trick the app into accepting a request that is not signed by the correct server. It is recommended that the Nextcloud user_oidc app is upgraded to 1.3.5, 2.0.0, 3.0.0, 4.0.0 or 5.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37886|2024-06-15T20:30:30.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37882|2024-06-14T20:10:15.423Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37882</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. A recipient of a share with read&amp;amp;share permissions could reshare the item with more permissions. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.13 or 27.1.8 or 28.0.4 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 26.0.13 or 27.1.8 or 28.0.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37882|2024-06-14T20:10:15.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37887|2024-06-14T16:56:43.262Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37887</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. Private shared calendar events' recurrence exceptions can be read by sharees. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 27.1.10 or 28.0.6 or 29.0.1 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 27.1.10 or 28.0.6 or 29.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37887|2024-06-14T16:56:43.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37317|2024-06-14T16:57:05.962Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37317</link>
      <description>The Nextcloud Notes app is a distraction free notes taking app for Nextcloud. If an attacker managed to share a folder called `Notes/` with a newly created user before they logged in, the Notes app would use that folder store the personal notes. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Notes app is upgraded to 4.9.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37317|2024-06-14T16:57:05.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37312|2024-06-14T14:43:24.137Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37312</link>
      <description>user_oidc app is an OpenID Connect user backend for Nextcloud. Missing access control on the ID4me endpoint allows an attacker to register an account eventually getting access to data that is available to all registered users. It is recommended that the OpenID Connect user backend is upgraded to 3.0.0 (Nextcloud 20-23), 4.0.0 (Nexcloud 24) or 5.0.0 (Nextcloud 25-28).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37312|2024-06-14T14:43:24.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37313|2024-06-14T14:50:44.035Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37313</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is a self hosted personal cloud system. Under some circumstance it was possible to bypass the second factor of 2FA after successfully providing the user credentials. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.13, 27.1.8 or 28.0.4 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 21.0.9.17, 22.2.10.22, 23.0.12.17, 24.0.12.13, 25.0.13.8, 26.0.13, 27.1.8 or 28.0.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37313|2024-06-14T14:50:44.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30247|2024-03-29T15:57:57.034Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloudpi</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30247</link>
      <description>NextcloudPi is a ready to use image for Virtual Machines, Raspberry Pi, Odroid HC1, Rock64 and other boards. A command injection vulnerability in NextCloudPi allows command execution as the root user via the NextCloudPi web-panel. Due to a security misconfiguration this can be used by anyone with access to NextCloudPi web-panel, no authentication is required. It is recommended that the NextCloudPi is upgraded to 1.53.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30247|2024-03-29T15:57:57.034Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 15:57:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37885|2024-06-14T15:42:42.132Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37885</link>
      <description>The Nextcloud Desktop Client is a tool to synchronize files from Nextcloud Server with your computer. A code injection in Nextcloud Desktop Client for macOS allowed to load arbitrary code when starting the client with DYLD_INSERT_LIBRARIES set in the enviroment. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Desktop client is upgraded to 3.12.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37885|2024-06-14T15:42:42.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:42:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37317|2024-06-14T15:25:24.475Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37317</link>
      <description>The Nextcloud Notes app is a distraction free notes taking app for Nextcloud. If an attacker managed to share a folder called `Notes/` with a newly created user before they logged in, the Notes app would use that folder store the personal notes. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Notes app is upgraded to 4.9.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37317|2024-06-14T15:25:24.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37315|2024-06-14T15:08:54.357Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37315</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. An attacker with read-only access to a file is able to restore older versions of a document when the files_versions app is enabled. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.12, 27.1.7 or 28.0.3 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 23.0.12.16, 24.0.12.12, 25.0.13.6, 26.0.12, 27.1.7 or 28.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37315|2024-06-14T15:08:54.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37884|2024-06-14T15:36:16.181Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37884</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. A malicious user was able to send delete requests for old versions of files they only got shared with read permissions. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.12 or 27.1.7 or 28.0.3 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 26.0.12 or 27.1.7 or 28.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37884|2024-06-14T15:36:16.181Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37313|2024-06-14T15:54:44.089Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37313</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is a self hosted personal cloud system. Under some circumstance it was possible to bypass the second factor of 2FA after successfully providing the user credentials. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.13, 27.1.8 or 28.0.4 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 21.0.9.17, 22.2.10.22, 23.0.12.17, 24.0.12.13, 25.0.13.8, 26.0.13, 27.1.8 or 28.0.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37313|2024-06-14T15:54:44.089Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37882|2024-06-14T15:28:00.462Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37882</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. A recipient of a share with read&amp;amp;share permissions could reshare the item with more permissions. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.13 or 27.1.8 or 28.0.4 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 26.0.13 or 27.1.8 or 28.0.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37882|2024-06-14T15:28:00.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37316|2024-06-14T15:23:12.705Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37316</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Calendar is a calendar app for Nextcloud. Authenticated users could create an event with manipulated attachment data leading to a bad redirect for participants when clicked. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Calendar App is upgraded to 4.6.8 or 4.7.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37316|2024-06-14T15:23:12.705Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37883|2024-06-14T15:33:18.525Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37883</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Deck is a kanban style organization tool aimed at personal planning and project organization for teams integrated with Nextcloud. A user with access to a deck board was able to access comments and attachments of already deleted cards. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Deck app is upgraded to 1.6.6 or 1.7.5 or 1.8.7 or 1.9.6 or 1.11.3 or 1.12.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37883|2024-06-14T15:33:18.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37887|2024-06-14T15:48:11.867Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37887</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. Private shared calendar events' recurrence exceptions can be read by sharees. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 27.1.10 or 28.0.6 or 29.0.1 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 27.1.10 or 28.0.6 or 29.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37887|2024-06-14T15:48:11.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37886|2024-06-14T15:45:12.913Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37886</link>
      <description>user_oidc app is an OpenID Connect user backend for Nextcloud. An attacker could potentially trick the app into accepting a request that is not signed by the correct server. It is recommended that the Nextcloud user_oidc app is upgraded to 1.3.5, 2.0.0, 3.0.0, 4.0.0 or 5.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37886|2024-06-14T15:45:12.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37314|2024-06-14T15:05:48.284Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37314</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Photos is a photo management app. Users can remove photos from the album of registered users. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 25.0.7 or 26.0.2 and the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 25.0.7 or 26.0.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37314|2024-06-14T15:05:48.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37312|2024-06-14T17:15:56.731Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37312</link>
      <description>user_oidc app is an OpenID Connect user backend for Nextcloud. Missing access control on the ID4me endpoint allows an attacker to register an account eventually getting access to data that is available to all registered users. It is recommended that the OpenID Connect user backend is upgraded to 3.0.0 (Nextcloud 20-23), 4.0.0 (Nexcloud 24) or 5.0.0 (Nextcloud 25-28).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37312|2024-06-14T17:15:56.731Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37885|2024-06-14T22:04:41.991Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37885</link>
      <description>The Nextcloud Desktop Client is a tool to synchronize files from Nextcloud Server with your computer. A code injection in Nextcloud Desktop Client for macOS allowed to load arbitrary code when starting the client with DYLD_INSERT_LIBRARIES set in the enviroment. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Desktop client is upgraded to 3.12.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37885|2024-06-14T22:04:41.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:42:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37883|2024-06-17T14:44:36.528Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37883</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Deck is a kanban style organization tool aimed at personal planning and project organization for teams integrated with Nextcloud. A user with access to a deck board was able to access comments and attachments of already deleted cards. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Deck app is upgraded to 1.6.6 or 1.7.5 or 1.8.7 or 1.9.6 or 1.11.3 or 1.12.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37883|2024-06-17T14:44:36.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37316|2024-07-12T19:04:06.344Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37316</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Calendar is a calendar app for Nextcloud. Authenticated users could create an event with manipulated attachment data leading to a bad redirect for participants when clicked. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Calendar App is upgraded to 4.6.8 or 4.7.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37316|2024-07-12T19:04:06.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30247|2024-07-31T20:55:53.041Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloudpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30247</link>
      <description>NextcloudPi is a ready to use image for Virtual Machines, Raspberry Pi, Odroid HC1, Rock64 and other boards. A command injection vulnerability in NextCloudPi allows command execution as the root user via the NextCloudPi web-panel. Due to a security misconfiguration this can be used by anyone with access to NextCloudPi web-panel, no authentication is required. It is recommended that the NextCloudPi is upgraded to 1.53.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30247|2024-07-31T20:55:53.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 15:57:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30247|2024-08-02T01:32:05.394Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloudpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30247</link>
      <description>NextcloudPi is a ready to use image for Virtual Machines, Raspberry Pi, Odroid HC1, Rock64 and other boards. A command injection vulnerability in NextCloudPi allows command execution as the root user via the NextCloudPi web-panel. Due to a security misconfiguration this can be used by anyone with access to NextCloudPi web-panel, no authentication is required. It is recommended that the NextCloudPi is upgraded to 1.53.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30247|2024-08-02T01:32:05.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 15:57:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
