<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Nextcloud -- Nextcloud Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nextcloud/nextcloud%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Nextcloud -- Nextcloud Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 15:23:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0893|2024-08-05T13:18:06.510Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloud%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0893</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server before 9.0.58 and 10.0.5 and 11.0.3 are shipping a vulnerable JavaScript library for sanitizing untrusted user-input which suffered from a XSS vulnerability caused by a behaviour change in Safari 10.1 and 10.2. Note that Nextcloud employs a strict Content-Security-Policy preventing exploitation of this XSS issue on modern web browsers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0893|2024-08-05T13:18:06.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3761|2024-08-05T04:50:30.619Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloud%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3761</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server before 12.0.8 and 13.0.3 suffer from improper authentication on the OAuth2 token endpoint. Missing checks potentially allowed handing out new tokens in case the OAuth2 client was partly compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3761|2024-08-05T04:50:30.619Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0883|2024-08-05T13:18:06.386Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloud%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0883</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server before 9.0.55 and 10.0.2 suffers from a permission increase on re-sharing via OCS API issue. A permission related issue within the OCS sharing API allowed an authenticated adversary to reshare shared files with an increasing permission set. This may allow an attacker to edit files in a share despite having only a 'read' permission set. Note that this only affects folders and files that the adversary has at least read-only permissions for.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0883|2024-08-05T13:18:06.386Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0885|2024-08-05T13:18:06.507Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloud%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0885</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server before 9.0.55 and 10.0.2 suffers from a error message disclosing existence of file in write-only share. Due to an error in the application logic an adversary with access to a write-only share may enumerate the names of existing files and subfolders by comparing the exception messages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0885|2024-08-05T13:18:06.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0884|2024-08-05T13:18:06.462Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloud%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0884</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server before 9.0.55 and 10.0.2 suffers from a creation of folders in read-only folders despite lacking permissions issue. Due to a logical error in the file caching layer an authenticated adversary is able to create empty folders inside a shared folder. Note that this only affects folders and files that the adversary has at least read-only permissions for.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0884|2024-08-05T13:18:06.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0891|2024-08-05T13:18:06.396Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloud%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0891</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server before 9.0.58 and 10.0.5 and 11.0.3 are vulnerable to an inadequate escaping of error messages leading to XSS vulnerabilities in multiple components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0891|2024-08-05T13:18:06.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0887|2024-08-05T13:18:06.509Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloud%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0887</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server before 9.0.55 and 10.0.2 suffers from a bypass in the quota limitation. Due to not properly sanitizing values provided by the `OC-Total-Length` HTTP header an authenticated adversary may be able to exceed their configured user quota. Thus using more space than allowed by the administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0887|2024-08-05T13:18:06.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0886|2024-08-05T13:18:06.533Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloud%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0886</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server before 9.0.55 and 10.0.2 suffers from a Denial of Service attack. Due to an error in the application logic an authenticated adversary may trigger an endless recursion in the application leading to a potential Denial of Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0886|2024-08-05T13:18:06.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0888|2024-08-05T13:18:06.471Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloud%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0888</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server before 9.0.55 and 10.0.2 suffers from a Content-Spoofing vulnerability in the "files" app. The top navigation bar displayed in the files list contained partially user-controllable input leading to a potential misrepresentation of information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0888|2024-08-05T13:18:06.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0936|2024-08-05T13:25:17.066Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloud%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0936</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server before 11.0.7 and 12.0.5 suffers from an Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability. A missing ownership check allowed logged-in users to change the scope of app passwords of other users. Note that the app passwords themselves where neither disclosed nor could the error be misused to identify as another user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0936|2024-08-05T13:25:17.066Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0894|2024-08-05T13:18:06.452Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloud%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0894</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server before 11.0.3 is vulnerable to disclosure of valid share tokens for public calendars due to a logical error. Thus granting an attacker potentially access to publicly shared calendars without knowing the share token.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0894|2024-08-05T13:18:06.452Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0895|2024-08-05T13:25:17.074Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloud%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0895</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server before 10.0.4 and 11.0.2 are vulnerable to disclosure of calendar and addressbook names to other logged-in users. Note that no actual content of the calendar and addressbook has been disclosed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0895|2024-08-05T13:25:17.074Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3762|2024-08-05T04:50:30.641Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloud%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3762</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server before 12.0.8 and 13.0.3 suffers from improper checks of dropped permissions for incoming shares allowing a user to still request previews for files it should not have access to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3762|2024-08-05T04:50:30.641Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0892|2024-08-05T13:18:06.453Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloud%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0892</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server before 11.0.3 is vulnerable to an improper session handling allowed an application specific password without permission to the files access to the users file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0892|2024-08-05T13:18:06.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0890|2024-08-05T13:18:06.510Z -- nextcloud -- nextcloud%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0890</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server before 11.0.3 is vulnerable to an inadequate escaping leading to a XSS vulnerability in the search module. To be exploitable a user has to write or paste malicious content into the search dialogue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0890|2024-08-05T13:18:06.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
