<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nextcloud/security-advisories.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for nextcloud -- security-advisories</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 16:24:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23942|2024-08-02T10:49:08.445Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23942</link>
      <description>The Nextcloud Desktop Client is a tool to synchronize files from a Nextcloud Server with your computer. Versions prior to 3.6.3 are missing sanitisation on qml labels which are used for basic HTML elements such as `strong`, `em` and `head` lines in the UI of the desktop client. The lack of sanitisation may allow for javascript injection. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Desktop Client is upgraded to 3.6.3. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23942|2024-08-02T10:49:08.445Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 20:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33183|2024-08-02T15:39:35.808Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33183</link>
      <description>Calendar app for Nextcloud easily sync events from various devices with your Nextcloud. Some internal paths of the website are disclosed when the SMTP server is unavailable. It is recommended that the Calendar app is updated to 3.5.5 or 4.2.3

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33183|2024-08-02T15:39:35.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 05:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28835|2024-08-02T13:51:38.590Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28835</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is an open source home cloud implementation. In affected versions the generated fallback password when creating a share was using a weak complexity random number generator, so when the sharer did not change it the password could be guessable to an attacker willing to brute force it. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 24.0.10 or 25.0.4. This issue only affects users who do not have a password policy enabled, so enabling a password policy is an effective mitigation for users unable to upgrade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28835|2024-08-02T13:51:38.590Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 18:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28833|2024-08-02T13:51:38.620Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28833</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is an open source home cloud implementation. In affected versions admins of a server were able to upload a logo or a favicon and to provided a file name which was not restricted and could overwrite files in the appdata directory. Administrators may have access to overwrite these files by other means but this method could be exploited by tricking an admin into uploading a maliciously named file. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 24.0.10 or 25.0.4. Users unable to upgrade should avoid ingesting logo files from untrusted sources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28833|2024-08-02T13:51:38.620Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 18:49:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28847|2024-08-02T13:51:38.570Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28847</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is the file server software for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. In Nextcloud Server 24.0.0 prior to 24.0.11 and 25.0.0 prior to 25.0.5; as well as Nextcloud Server Enterprise 23.0.0 prior to 23.0.12.6, 24.0.0 prior to 24.0.11, and 25.0.0 prior to 25.0.5; an attacker is not restricted in verifying passwords of share links so they can just start brute forcing the password. Nextcloud Server 24.0.11 and 25.0.5 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server 23.0.12.6, 24.0.11, and 25.0.5 contain a fix for this issue. No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28847|2024-08-02T13:51:38.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 16:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28644|2024-08-02T13:43:23.667Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28644</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is an open source home cloud implementation. In releases of the 25.0.x branch before 25.0.3 an inefficient fetch operation may impact server performances and/or can lead to a denial of service. This issue has been addressed and it is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 25.0.3. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28644|2024-08-02T13:43:23.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 18:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23944|2024-08-02T10:49:07.951Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23944</link>
      <description>Nextcloud mail is an email app for the nextcloud home server platform. In versions prior to 2.2.2 user's passwords were stored in cleartext in the database during the duration of OAuth2 setup procedure. Any attacker or malicious user with access to the database would have access to these user passwords until the OAuth setup has been completed. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Mail app is upgraded to 2.2.2. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23944|2024-08-02T10:49:07.951Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 19:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25160|2024-08-02T11:18:36.150Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25160</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Mail is an email app for the Nextcloud home server platform. Prior to versions 2.2.1, 1.14.5, 1.12.9, and 1.11.8, an attacker can access the mail box by ID getting the subjects and the first characters of the emails. Users should upgrade to Mail 2.2.1 for Nextcloud 25, Mail 1.14.5 for Nextcloud 22-24, Mail 1.12.9 for Nextcloud 21, or Mail 1.11.8 for Nextcloud 20 to receive a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25160|2024-08-02T11:18:36.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 20:19:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25816|2024-08-02T11:32:12.677Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25816</link>
      <description>Nextcloud is an Open Source private cloud software. Versions 25.0.0 and above, prior to 25.0.3, are subject to Uncontrolled Resource Consumption. A user can configure a very long password, consuming more resources on password validation than desired. This issue is patched in 25.0.3 No workaround is available.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25816|2024-08-02T11:32:12.677Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 23:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32319|2024-08-02T15:10:24.973Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32319</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is an open source personal cloud implementation. Missing brute-force protection on the WebDAV endpoints via the basic auth header allowed to brute-force user credentials when the provided user name was not an email address. Users from version 24.0.0 onward are affected. This issue has been addressed in releases 24.0.11, 25.0.5 and 26.0.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32319|2024-08-02T15:10:24.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 22:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22470|2024-08-02T10:13:48.424Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22470</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Deck is a kanban style organization tool aimed at personal planning and project organization for teams integrated with Nextcloud. A database error can be generated potentially causing a DoS when performed multiple times. There are currently no known workarounds. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 1.6.5 or 1.7.3 or 1.8.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22470|2024-08-02T10:13:48.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 00:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29000|2024-08-02T13:51:38.991Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29000</link>
      <description>The Nextcloud Desktop Client is a tool to synchronize files from Nextcloud Server. Starting with version 3.0.0 and prior to version 3.7.0, by trusting that the server will return a certificate that belongs to the keypair of the user, a malicious server could get the desktop client to encrypt files with a key known to the attacker. This issue is fixed in Nextcloud Desktop 3.7.0. No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29000|2024-08-02T13:51:38.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 12:53:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23943|2024-08-02T10:49:08.130Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23943</link>
      <description>Nextcloud mail is an email app for the nextcloud home server platform. In affected versions the SMTP, IMAP and Sieve host fields allowed to scan for internal services and servers reachable from within the local network of the Nextcloud Server. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Maill app is upgraded to 1.15.0 or 2.2.2. The only known workaround for this issue is to completely disable the nextcloud mail app.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23943|2024-08-02T10:49:08.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 20:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25162|2024-08-02T11:18:35.583Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25162</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is the file server software for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. Nextcloud Server prior to 24.0.8 and 23.0.12 and Nextcloud Enterprise server prior to 24.0.8 and 23.0.12 are vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF). Attackers can leverage enclosed alphanumeric payloads to bypass IP filters and gain SSRF, which would allow an attacker to read crucial metadata if the server is hosted on the AWS platform. Nextcloud Server 24.0.8 and 23.0.2 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server 24.0.8 and 23.0.12 contain a patch for this issue. No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25162|2024-08-02T11:18:35.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 20:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28643|2024-08-02T13:43:23.546Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28643</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is an open source home cloud implementation. In affected versions when a recipient receives 2 shares with the same name, while a memory cache is configured, the second share will replace the first one instead of being renamed to `{name} (2)`. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 25.0.3 or 24.0.9. Users unable to upgrade should avoid sharing 2 folders with the same name to the same user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28643|2024-08-02T13:43:23.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 18:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25821|2024-08-02T11:32:12.640Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25821</link>
      <description>Nextcloud is an Open Source private cloud software. Versions 24.0.4 and above, prior to 24.0.7, and 25.0.0 and above, prior to 25.0.1, contain Improper Access Control. Secure view for internal shares can be circumvented if reshare permissions are also given. This issue is patched in versions 24.0.7 and 25.0.1. No workaround  is available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25821|2024-08-02T11:32:12.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 23:39:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25820|2024-08-02T11:32:12.380Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25820</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is the file server software for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform, and Nextcloud Enterprise Server is the enterprise version of the file server software. In Nextcloud Server versions 25.0.x prior to 25.0.5 and versions 24.0.x prior to 24.0.10 as well as Nextcloud Enterprise Server versions 25.0.x prior to 25.0.4, 24.0.x prior to 24.0.10, 23.0.x prior to 23.0.12.5, 22.x prior to 22.2.0.10, and 21.x prior to 21.0.9.10, when an attacker gets access to an already logged in user session they can then brute force the password on the confirmation endpoint. Nextcloud Server should upgraded to 24.0.10 or 25.0.4 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server should upgraded to 21.0.9.10, 22.2.10.10, 23.0.12.5, 24.0.10, or 25.0.4 to receive a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25820|2024-08-02T11:32:12.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 18:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28999|2024-08-02T13:51:38.979Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28999</link>
      <description>Nextcloud is an open-source productivity platform. In Nextcloud Desktop client 3.0.0 until 3.8.0, Nextcloud Android app 3.13.0 until 3.25.0, and Nextcloud iOS app 3.0.5 until 4.8.0, a malicious server administrator can gain full access to an end-to-end encrypted folder. They can decrypt files, recover the folder structure and add new files.​ This issue is fixed in Nextcloud Desktop 3.8.0, Nextcloud Android 3.25.0, and Nextcloud iOS 4.8.0. No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28999|2024-08-02T13:51:38.979Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 12:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25159|2024-08-02T11:18:35.887Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25159</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is the file server software for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform, and Nextcloud Office is a document collaboration app for the same platform. Nextcloud Server 24.0.x prior to 24.0.8 and 25.0.x prior to 25.0.1, Nextcloud Enterprise Server 24.0.x prior to 24.0.8 and 25.0.x prior to 25.0.1, and Nextcloud Office (Richdocuments) App 6.x prior to 6.3.1 and 7.x prior to 7.0.1 have previews accessible without a watermark. The download should be hidden and the watermark should get applied. This issue is fixed in Nextcloud Server 25.0.1 and 24.0.8, Nextcloud Enterprise Server 25.0.1 and 24.0.8, and  Nextcloud Office (Richdocuments) App 7.0.1 (for 25) and 6.3.1 (for 24). No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25159|2024-08-02T11:18:35.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 16:43:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28647|2024-08-02T13:43:23.742Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28647</link>
      <description>Nextcloud iOS is an ios application used to interface with the nextcloud home cloud ecosystem. In versions prior to 4.7.0 when an attacker has physical access to an unlocked device, they may enable the integration into the iOS Files app and bypass the Nextcloud pin/password protection and gain access to a users files. It is recommended that the Nextcloud iOS app is upgraded to 4.7.0. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28647|2024-08-02T13:43:23.742Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 18:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33184|2024-08-02T15:39:35.928Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33184</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Mail is a mail app in Nextcloud. A blind SSRF attack allowed to send GET requests to services running in the same web server. It is recommended that the Mail app is update to version 3.02, 2.2.5 or 1.15.3.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33184|2024-08-02T15:39:35.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 04:36:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28645|2024-08-02T13:43:23.193Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28645</link>
      <description>Nextcloud richdocuments is a Nextcloud app integrating the office suit Collabora Online. In affected versions the secure view feature of the rich documents app can be bypassed by using unprotected internal API endpoint of the rich documents app. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Office app (richdocuments) is upgraded to 8.0.0-beta.1, 7.0.2 or 6.3.2. Users unable to upgrade may mitigate the issue by taking steps to restrict the ability to download documents. This includes ensuring that the `WOPI configuration` is configured to only serve documents between Nextcloud and Collabora. It is highly recommended to define the list of Collabora server IPs as the allow list within the Office admin settings of Nextcloud.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28645|2024-08-02T13:43:23.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 22:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28845|2024-08-02T13:51:38.693Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28845</link>
      <description>Nextcloud talk is a video &amp; audio conferencing app for Nextcloud. In affected versions the talk app does not properly filter access to a conversations member list. As a result an attacker could use this vulnerability to gain information about the members of a Talk conversation, even if they themselves are not members. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Talk is upgraded to 14.0.9 or 15.0.4. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28845|2024-08-02T13:51:38.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 22:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22469|2024-08-02T10:13:48.353Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22469</link>
      <description>Deck is a kanban style organization tool aimed at personal planning and project organization for teams integrated with Nextcloud. When getting the reference preview for Deck cards the user has no access to, unauthorized user could eventually get the cached data of a user that has access. There are currently no known workarounds. It is recommended that the Nextcloud app Deck is upgraded to 1.8.2.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22469|2024-08-02T10:13:48.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 20:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22472|2024-08-02T10:13:48.521Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22472</link>
      <description>Deck is a kanban style organization tool aimed at personal planning and project organization for teams integrated with Nextcloud. It is possible to make a user send any POST request with an arbitrary body given they click on a malicious deep link on a Windows computer. (e.g. in an email, chat link, etc). There are currently no known workarounds. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Desktop client is upgraded to 3.6.2.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22472|2024-08-02T10:13:48.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 13:54:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25161|2024-08-02T11:18:35.330Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25161</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is the file server software for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. Nextcloud Server and Nextcloud Enterprise Server prior to versions 25.0.1 24.0.8, and 23.0.12 missing rate limiting on password reset functionality. This could result in service slowdown, storage overflow, or cost impact when using external email services. Users should upgrade to Nextcloud Server 25.0.1, 24.0.8, or 23.0.12 or Nextcloud Enterprise Server 25.0.1, 24.0.8, or 23.0.12 to receive a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25161|2024-08-02T11:18:35.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 20:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22473|2024-08-02T10:13:48.470Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22473</link>
      <description>Talk-Android enables users to have video &amp; audio calls through Nextcloud on Android. Due to passcode bypass, an attacker is able to access the user's Nextcloud files and view conversations. To exploit this the attacker needs to have physical access to the target's device. There are currently no known workarounds available. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Talk Android app is upgraded to 15.0.2. 
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22473|2024-08-02T10:13:48.470Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 14:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22471|2024-08-02T10:13:48.519Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22471</link>
      <description>Deck is a kanban style organization tool aimed at personal planning and project organization for teams integrated with Nextcloud. Broken access control allows a user to delete attachments of other users. There are currently no known workarounds. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Deck app is upgraded to 1.6.5 or 1.7.3 or 1.8.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22471|2024-08-02T10:13:48.519Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 00:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28844|2024-08-02T13:51:38.553Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28844</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is an open source home cloud implementation. In affected versions users that should not be able to download a file can still download an older version and use that for uncontrolled distribution. This issue has been addressed in versions 24.0.10 and 25.0.4. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28844|2024-08-02T13:51:38.553Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 22:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25817|2024-08-02T11:32:12.508Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25817</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is an open source, personal cloud implementation. In versions from 24.0.0 and before 24.0.9 a user could escalate their permissions to delete files they were not supposed to deletable but only viewed or downloaded. This issue has been addressed andit is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 24.0.9. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25817|2024-08-02T11:32:12.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 20:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25818|2024-08-02T11:32:12.551Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25818</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is an open source, personal cloud implementation. In affected versions a malicious user could try to reset the password of another user and then brute force the 62^21 combinations for the password reset token. As of commit `704eb3aa` password reset attempts are now throttled. Note that 62^21 combinations would significant compute resources to brute force. None the less it is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 24.0.10 or 25.0.4. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25818|2024-08-02T11:32:12.551Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 20:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32074|2024-08-02T15:03:29.143Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32074</link>
      <description>user_oidc app is an OpenID Connect user backend for Nextcloud. Authentication can be broken/bypassed in user_oidc app. It is recommended that the Nextcloud user_oidc app is upgraded to 1.3.2

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32074|2024-08-02T15:03:29.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 22:59:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32320|2024-08-02T15:10:24.848Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32320</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a data storage system for Nextcloud, a self-hosted productivity platform. When multiple requests are sent in parallel, all of them were executed even if the amount of faulty requests succeeded the limit by the time the response was sent to the client. This allowed someone to send as many requests the server could handle in parallel to bruteforce protected details instead of the configured limit, default 8. Nextcloud Server versions 25.0.7 and 26.0.2 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server versions 21.0.9.12, 22.2.10.12, 23.0.12.7, 24.0.12.2, 25.0.7 and 26.0.2 contain patches for this issue.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32320|2024-08-02T15:10:24.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 20:57:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28998|2024-08-02T13:51:38.943Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28998</link>
      <description>The Nextcloud Desktop Client is a tool to synchronize files from Nextcloud Server. Starting with version 3.0.0 and prior to version 3.6.5, a malicious server administrator can gain full access to an end-to-end encrypted folder. They can decrypt files, recover the folder structure, and add new files.​ Users should upgrade the Nextcloud Desktop client to 3.6.5 to receive a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28998|2024-08-02T13:51:38.943Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 12:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28848|2024-08-02T13:51:38.505Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28848</link>
      <description>user_oidc is the OIDC connect user backend for Nextcloud, an open source collaboration platform. A vulnerability in versions 1.0.0 until 1.3.0 effectively allowed an attacker to bypass the state protection as they could just copy the expected state token from the first request to their second request. Users should upgrade user_oidc to 1.3.0 to receive a patch for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28848|2024-08-02T13:51:38.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 12:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28646|2024-08-02T13:43:23.558Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28646</link>
      <description>Nextcloud android is an android app for interfacing with the nextcloud home server ecosystem. In versions from 3.7.0 and before 3.24.1 an attacker that has access to the unlocked physical device can bypass the Nextcloud Android Pin/passcode protection via a thirdparty app. This allows to see meta information like sharer, sharees and activity of files. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Android app is upgraded to 3.24.1. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28646|2024-08-02T13:43:23.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 18:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25150|2024-08-02T11:18:35.897Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25150</link>
      <description>Nextcloud office/richdocuments is an office suit for the nextcloud server platform. In affected versions the Collabora integration can be tricked to provide access to any file without proper permission validation. As a result any user with access to Collabora can obtain the content of other users files. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Office App (Collabora Integration) is updated to 7.0.2 (Nextcloud 25), 6.3.2 (Nextcloud 24), 5.0.10 (Nextcloud 23), 4.2.9 (Nextcloud 21-22), or 3.8.7 (Nextcloud 15-20). There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25150|2024-08-02T11:18:35.897Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 19:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-30540|2024-08-02T14:28:51.769Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30540</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Talk is a chat, video &amp; audio call extension for Nextcloud. In affected versions a user that was added later to a conversation can use this information to get access to data that was deleted before they were added to the conversation. This issue has been patched in version 15.0.5 and it is recommended that users upgrad to 15.0.5. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-30540|2024-08-02T14:28:51.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 21:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26041|2024-08-02T11:39:06.484Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26041</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Talk is a fully on-premises audio/video and chat communication service. When cron jobs were misconfigured and therefore messages are not expired, the API would still return them while they were then hidden by the frontend code. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Talk is upgraded to 15.0.3. There are no workaround available.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26041|2024-08-02T11:39:06.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 20:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28997|2024-08-02T13:51:38.948Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28997</link>
      <description>The Nextcloud Desktop Client is a tool to synchronize files from Nextcloud Server. Starting with version 3.0.0 and prior to version 3.6.5, a malicious server administrator can recover and modify the contents of end-to-end encrypted files. Users should upgrade the Nextcloud Desktop client to 3.6.5 to receive a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28997|2024-08-02T13:51:38.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 12:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25579|2024-08-02T11:25:19.266Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25579</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is a self hosted home cloud product. In affected versions the `OC\Files\Node\Folder::getFullPath()` function was validating and normalizing the string in the wrong order. The function is used in the `newFile()` and `newFolder()` items, which may allow to creation of paths outside of ones own space and overwriting data from other users with crafted paths. This issue has been addressed in versions 25.0.2, 24.0.8, and 23.0.12. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25579|2024-08-02T11:25:19.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 18:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-30539|2024-08-02T14:28:51.685Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30539</link>
      <description>Nextcloud is a personal home server system. Depending on the set up tags and other workflows this issue can be used to limit access of others or being able to grant them access when there are system tag based files access control or files retention rules. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 24.0.11 or 25.0.5, the Nextcloud Enterprise Server to 21.0.9.11, 22.2.10.11, 23.0.12.6, 24.0.11 or 25.0.5, and the Nextcloud Files automated tagging app to 1.11.1, 1.12.1, 1.13.1, 1.14.2, 1.15.3 or 1.16.1. Users unable to upgrade should disable all workflow related apps. Users are advised to upgrade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-30539|2024-08-02T14:28:51.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 21:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26482|2024-08-02T11:53:53.652Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26482</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is an open source home cloud implementation. In affected versions a missing scope validation allowed users to create workflows which are designed to be only available for administrators. Some workflows are designed to be RCE by invoking defined scripts, in order to generate PDFs, invoking webhooks or running scripts on the server. Due to this combination depending on the available apps the issue can result in a RCE at the end. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 24.0.10 or 25.0.4. Users unable to upgrade should disable app `workflow_scripts` and `workflow_pdf_converter` as a mitigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26482|2024-08-02T11:53:53.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 18:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33182|2024-08-02T15:39:36.162Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33182</link>
      <description>Contacts app for Nextcloud easily syncs contacts from various devices with your Nextcloud and allows editing. The unsanitized SVG is converted to a JavaScript blob (in memory data) that the Avatar can't render. Due to this constellation the missing sanitization does not seem to be exploitable. It is recommended that the Contacts app is upgraded to 5.0.3 or 4.2.4

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33182|2024-08-02T15:39:36.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 04:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28834|2024-08-02T13:51:38.323Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28834</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is an open source personal cloud server. Nextcloud Server 24.0.0 until 24.0.6 and 25.0.0 until 25.0.4, as well as Nextcloud Enterprise Server 23.0.0 until 23.0.11, 24.0.0 until 24.0.6, and 25.0.0 until 25.0.4, have an information disclosure vulnerability. A user was able to get the full data directory path of the Nextcloud server from an API endpoint. By itself this information is not problematic as it can also be guessed for most common setups, but it could speed up other unknown attacks in the future if the information is known. Nextcloud Server 24.0.6 and 25.0.4 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server 23.0.11, 24.0.6, and 25.0.4 contain patches for this issue. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28834|2024-08-02T13:51:38.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 16:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32318|2024-08-02T15:10:24.851Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32318</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server provides a home for data. A regression in the session handling between Nextcloud Server and the Nextcloud Text app prevented a correct destruction of the session on logout if cookies were not cleared manually. After successfully authenticating with any other account the previous session would be continued and the attacker would be authenticated as the previously logged in user. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 25.0.6 or 26.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32318|2024-08-02T15:10:24.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 17:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37316|2024-08-02T03:50:56.106Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37316</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Calendar is a calendar app for Nextcloud. Authenticated users could create an event with manipulated attachment data leading to a bad redirect for participants when clicked. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Calendar App is upgraded to 4.6.8 or 4.7.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37316|2024-08-02T03:50:56.106Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37314|2024-08-02T03:50:56.192Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37314</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Photos is a photo management app. Users can remove photos from the album of registered users. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 25.0.7 or 26.0.2 and the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 25.0.7 or 26.0.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37314|2024-08-02T03:50:56.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37886|2024-08-02T03:57:40.025Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37886</link>
      <description>user_oidc app is an OpenID Connect user backend for Nextcloud. An attacker could potentially trick the app into accepting a request that is not signed by the correct server. It is recommended that the Nextcloud user_oidc app is upgraded to 1.3.5, 2.0.0, 3.0.0, 4.0.0 or 5.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37886|2024-08-02T03:57:40.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37884|2024-08-02T03:57:39.918Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37884</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. A malicious user was able to send delete requests for old versions of files they only got shared with read permissions. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.12 or 27.1.7 or 28.0.3 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 26.0.12 or 27.1.7 or 28.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37884|2024-08-02T03:57:39.918Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37885|2024-08-02T03:57:39.894Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37885</link>
      <description>The Nextcloud Desktop Client is a tool to synchronize files from Nextcloud Server with your computer. A code injection in Nextcloud Desktop Client for macOS allowed to load arbitrary code when starting the client with DYLD_INSERT_LIBRARIES set in the enviroment. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Desktop client is upgraded to 3.12.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37885|2024-08-02T03:57:39.894Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:42:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37312|2024-08-02T03:50:55.709Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37312</link>
      <description>user_oidc app is an OpenID Connect user backend for Nextcloud. Missing access control on the ID4me endpoint allows an attacker to register an account eventually getting access to data that is available to all registered users. It is recommended that the OpenID Connect user backend is upgraded to 3.0.0 (Nextcloud 20-23), 4.0.0 (Nexcloud 24) or 5.0.0 (Nextcloud 25-28).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37312|2024-08-02T03:50:55.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37313|2024-08-02T03:50:56.117Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37313</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is a self hosted personal cloud system. Under some circumstance it was possible to bypass the second factor of 2FA after successfully providing the user credentials. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.13, 27.1.8 or 28.0.4 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 21.0.9.17, 22.2.10.22, 23.0.12.17, 24.0.12.13, 25.0.13.8, 26.0.13, 27.1.8 or 28.0.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37313|2024-08-02T03:50:56.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37317|2024-08-02T03:50:55.961Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37317</link>
      <description>The Nextcloud Notes app is a distraction free notes taking app for Nextcloud. If an attacker managed to share a folder called `Notes/` with a newly created user before they logged in, the Notes app would use that folder store the personal notes. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Notes app is upgraded to 4.9.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37317|2024-08-02T03:50:55.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37315|2024-08-02T03:50:55.709Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37315</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. An attacker with read-only access to a file is able to restore older versions of a document when the files_versions app is enabled. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.12, 27.1.7 or 28.0.3 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 23.0.12.16, 24.0.12.12, 25.0.13.6, 26.0.12, 27.1.7 or 28.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37315|2024-08-02T03:50:55.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37887|2024-08-02T03:57:40.075Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37887</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. Private shared calendar events' recurrence exceptions can be read by sharees. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 27.1.10 or 28.0.6 or 29.0.1 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 27.1.10 or 28.0.6 or 29.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37887|2024-08-02T03:57:40.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37883|2024-08-02T03:57:39.902Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37883</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Deck is a kanban style organization tool aimed at personal planning and project organization for teams integrated with Nextcloud. A user with access to a deck board was able to access comments and attachments of already deleted cards. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Deck app is upgraded to 1.6.6 or 1.7.5 or 1.8.7 or 1.9.6 or 1.11.3 or 1.12.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37883|2024-08-02T03:57:39.902Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37882|2024-08-02T03:57:39.988Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37882</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. A recipient of a share with read&amp;amp;share permissions could reshare the item with more permissions. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.13 or 27.1.8 or 28.0.4 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 26.0.13 or 27.1.8 or 28.0.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37882|2024-08-02T03:57:39.988Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37314|2024-07-30T14:25:26.489Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37314</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Photos is a photo management app. Users can remove photos from the album of registered users. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 25.0.7 or 26.0.2 and the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 25.0.7 or 26.0.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37314|2024-07-30T14:25:26.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37315|2024-06-17T15:13:32.772Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37315</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. An attacker with read-only access to a file is able to restore older versions of a document when the files_versions app is enabled. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.12, 27.1.7 or 28.0.3 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 23.0.12.16, 24.0.12.12, 25.0.13.6, 26.0.12, 27.1.7 or 28.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37315|2024-06-17T15:13:32.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37886|2024-06-15T20:30:30.682Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37886</link>
      <description>user_oidc app is an OpenID Connect user backend for Nextcloud. An attacker could potentially trick the app into accepting a request that is not signed by the correct server. It is recommended that the Nextcloud user_oidc app is upgraded to 1.3.5, 2.0.0, 3.0.0, 4.0.0 or 5.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37886|2024-06-15T20:30:30.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37882|2024-06-14T20:10:15.423Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37882</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. A recipient of a share with read&amp;amp;share permissions could reshare the item with more permissions. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.13 or 27.1.8 or 28.0.4 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 26.0.13 or 27.1.8 or 28.0.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37882|2024-06-14T20:10:15.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37887|2024-06-14T16:56:43.262Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37887</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. Private shared calendar events' recurrence exceptions can be read by sharees. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 27.1.10 or 28.0.6 or 29.0.1 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 27.1.10 or 28.0.6 or 29.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37887|2024-06-14T16:56:43.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37317|2024-06-14T16:57:05.962Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37317</link>
      <description>The Nextcloud Notes app is a distraction free notes taking app for Nextcloud. If an attacker managed to share a folder called `Notes/` with a newly created user before they logged in, the Notes app would use that folder store the personal notes. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Notes app is upgraded to 4.9.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37317|2024-06-14T16:57:05.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37312|2024-06-14T14:43:24.137Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37312</link>
      <description>user_oidc app is an OpenID Connect user backend for Nextcloud. Missing access control on the ID4me endpoint allows an attacker to register an account eventually getting access to data that is available to all registered users. It is recommended that the OpenID Connect user backend is upgraded to 3.0.0 (Nextcloud 20-23), 4.0.0 (Nexcloud 24) or 5.0.0 (Nextcloud 25-28).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37312|2024-06-14T14:43:24.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37313|2024-06-14T14:50:44.035Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37313</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is a self hosted personal cloud system. Under some circumstance it was possible to bypass the second factor of 2FA after successfully providing the user credentials. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.13, 27.1.8 or 28.0.4 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 21.0.9.17, 22.2.10.22, 23.0.12.17, 24.0.12.13, 25.0.13.8, 26.0.13, 27.1.8 or 28.0.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37313|2024-06-14T14:50:44.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37885|2024-06-14T15:42:42.132Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37885</link>
      <description>The Nextcloud Desktop Client is a tool to synchronize files from Nextcloud Server with your computer. A code injection in Nextcloud Desktop Client for macOS allowed to load arbitrary code when starting the client with DYLD_INSERT_LIBRARIES set in the enviroment. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Desktop client is upgraded to 3.12.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37885|2024-06-14T15:42:42.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:42:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37317|2024-06-14T15:25:24.475Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37317</link>
      <description>The Nextcloud Notes app is a distraction free notes taking app for Nextcloud. If an attacker managed to share a folder called `Notes/` with a newly created user before they logged in, the Notes app would use that folder store the personal notes. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Notes app is upgraded to 4.9.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37317|2024-06-14T15:25:24.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37315|2024-06-14T15:08:54.357Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37315</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. An attacker with read-only access to a file is able to restore older versions of a document when the files_versions app is enabled. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.12, 27.1.7 or 28.0.3 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 23.0.12.16, 24.0.12.12, 25.0.13.6, 26.0.12, 27.1.7 or 28.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37315|2024-06-14T15:08:54.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37884|2024-06-14T15:36:16.181Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37884</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. A malicious user was able to send delete requests for old versions of files they only got shared with read permissions. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.12 or 27.1.7 or 28.0.3 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 26.0.12 or 27.1.7 or 28.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37884|2024-06-14T15:36:16.181Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37313|2024-06-14T15:54:44.089Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37313</link>
      <description>Nextcloud server is a self hosted personal cloud system. Under some circumstance it was possible to bypass the second factor of 2FA after successfully providing the user credentials. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.13, 27.1.8 or 28.0.4 and Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 21.0.9.17, 22.2.10.22, 23.0.12.17, 24.0.12.13, 25.0.13.8, 26.0.13, 27.1.8 or 28.0.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37313|2024-06-14T15:54:44.089Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37882|2024-06-14T15:28:00.462Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37882</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. A recipient of a share with read&amp;amp;share permissions could reshare the item with more permissions. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 26.0.13 or 27.1.8 or 28.0.4 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 26.0.13 or 27.1.8 or 28.0.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37882|2024-06-14T15:28:00.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37316|2024-06-14T15:23:12.705Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37316</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Calendar is a calendar app for Nextcloud. Authenticated users could create an event with manipulated attachment data leading to a bad redirect for participants when clicked. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Calendar App is upgraded to 4.6.8 or 4.7.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37316|2024-06-14T15:23:12.705Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37883|2024-06-14T15:33:18.525Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37883</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Deck is a kanban style organization tool aimed at personal planning and project organization for teams integrated with Nextcloud. A user with access to a deck board was able to access comments and attachments of already deleted cards. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Deck app is upgraded to 1.6.6 or 1.7.5 or 1.8.7 or 1.9.6 or 1.11.3 or 1.12.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37883|2024-06-14T15:33:18.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37887|2024-06-14T15:48:11.867Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37887</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Server is a self hosted personal cloud system. Private shared calendar events' recurrence exceptions can be read by sharees. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 27.1.10 or 28.0.6 or 29.0.1 and that the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 27.1.10 or 28.0.6 or 29.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37887|2024-06-14T15:48:11.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37886|2024-06-14T15:45:12.913Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37886</link>
      <description>user_oidc app is an OpenID Connect user backend for Nextcloud. An attacker could potentially trick the app into accepting a request that is not signed by the correct server. It is recommended that the Nextcloud user_oidc app is upgraded to 1.3.5, 2.0.0, 3.0.0, 4.0.0 or 5.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37886|2024-06-14T15:45:12.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37314|2024-06-14T15:05:48.284Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37314</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Photos is a photo management app. Users can remove photos from the album of registered users. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Server is upgraded to 25.0.7 or 26.0.2 and the Nextcloud Enterprise Server is upgraded to 25.0.7 or 26.0.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37314|2024-06-14T15:05:48.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37312|2024-06-14T17:15:56.731Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37312</link>
      <description>user_oidc app is an OpenID Connect user backend for Nextcloud. Missing access control on the ID4me endpoint allows an attacker to register an account eventually getting access to data that is available to all registered users. It is recommended that the OpenID Connect user backend is upgraded to 3.0.0 (Nextcloud 20-23), 4.0.0 (Nexcloud 24) or 5.0.0 (Nextcloud 25-28).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37312|2024-06-14T17:15:56.731Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37885|2024-06-14T22:04:41.991Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37885</link>
      <description>The Nextcloud Desktop Client is a tool to synchronize files from Nextcloud Server with your computer. A code injection in Nextcloud Desktop Client for macOS allowed to load arbitrary code when starting the client with DYLD_INSERT_LIBRARIES set in the enviroment. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Desktop client is upgraded to 3.12.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37885|2024-06-14T22:04:41.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:42:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37883|2024-06-17T14:44:36.528Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37883</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Deck is a kanban style organization tool aimed at personal planning and project organization for teams integrated with Nextcloud. A user with access to a deck board was able to access comments and attachments of already deleted cards. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Deck app is upgraded to 1.6.6 or 1.7.5 or 1.8.7 or 1.9.6 or 1.11.3 or 1.12.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37883|2024-06-17T14:44:36.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37316|2024-07-12T19:04:06.344Z -- nextcloud -- security-advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37316</link>
      <description>Nextcloud Calendar is a calendar app for Nextcloud. Authenticated users could create an event with manipulated attachment data leading to a bad redirect for participants when clicked. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Calendar App is upgraded to 4.6.8 or 4.7.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37316|2024-07-12T19:04:06.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
