<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for CMS Made Simple -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cms%20made%20simple/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for CMS Made Simple -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1527|2024-03-12T15:22:47.649Z -- CMS Made Simple -- CMS Made Simple
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1527</link><description>Unrestricted file upload vulnerability in CMS Made Simple, affecting version 2.2.14. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to bypass the security measures of the upload functionality and potentially create a remote execution of commands via webshell.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1527|2024-03-12T15:22:47.649Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 15:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1529|2024-03-12T15:25:56.200Z -- CMS Made Simple -- CMS Made Simple
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1529</link><description>Vulnerability in CMS Made Simple 2.2.14, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability through /admin/adduser.php, in multiple parameters. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted JavaScript payload to an authenticated user and partially take over their browser session.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1529|2024-03-12T15:25:56.200Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 15:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1528|2024-03-12T15:23:06.887Z -- CMS Made Simple -- CMS Made Simple
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1528</link><description>CMS Made Simple version 2.2.14, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability through /admin/moduleinterface.php, in multiple parameters. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted JavaScript payload to an authenticated user and partially hijack their browser session.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1528|2024-03-12T15:23:06.887Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 15:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>