<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for NA -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/na/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for NA -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:22:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23005|2024-08-03T03:28:42.818Z -- na -- na
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23005</link>
      <description>Western Digital has identified a weakness in the UFS standard that could result in a security vulnerability. This vulnerability may exist in some systems where the Host boot ROM code implements the UFS Boot feature to boot from UFS compliant storage devices. The UFS Boot feature, as specified in the UFS standard, is provided by UFS devices to support platforms that need to download the system boot loader from external non-volatile storage locations. Several scenarios have been identified in which adversaries may disable the boot capability, or revert to an old boot loader code, if the host boot ROM code is improperly implemented. UFS Host Boot ROM implementers may be impacted by this vulnerability. UFS devices are only impacted when connected to a vulnerable UFS Host and are not independently impacted by this vulnerability. When present, the vulnerability is in the UFS Host implementation and is not a vulnerability in Western Digital UFS Devices. Western Digital has provided details of the vulnerability to the JEDEC standards body, multiple vendors of host processors, and software solutions providers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23005|2024-08-03T03:28:42.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22267|2024-06-04T17:52:36.236Z -- na -- vmware%20workstation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22267</link>
      <description>VMware Workstation and Fusion contain a use-after-free vulnerability in the vbluetooth device. A malicious actor with local administrative privileges on a virtual machine may exploit this issue to execute code as the virtual machine's VMX process running on the host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22267|2024-06-04T17:52:36.236Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 12:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22267|2024-08-01T22:43:34.527Z -- na -- vmware%20workstation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22267</link>
      <description>VMware Workstation and Fusion contain a use-after-free vulnerability in the vbluetooth device. A malicious actor with local administrative privileges on a virtual machine may exploit this issue to execute code as the virtual machine's VMX process running on the host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22267|2024-08-01T22:43:34.527Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 12:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
