<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for litonice13 -- Master Addons – Free Widgets, Hover Effects, Toggle, Conditions, Animations for Elementor</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/litonice13/master%20addons%20%E2%80%93%20free%20widgets%2C%20hover%20effects%2C%20toggle%2C%20conditions%2C%20animations%20for%20elementor.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for litonice13 -- Master Addons – Free Widgets, Hover Effects, Toggle, Conditions, Animations for Elementor</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-4580|2024-05-16T11:33:32.957Z -- litonice13 -- Master Addons – Free Widgets, Hover Effects, Toggle, Conditions, Animations for Elementor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4580</link><description>The Master Addons – Free Widgets, Hover Effects, Toggle, Conditions, Animations for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters in versions up to, and including, 2.0.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4580|2024-05-16T11:33:32.957Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4265|2024-05-02T16:52:29.292Z -- litonice13 -- Master Addons – Free Widgets, Hover Effects, Toggle, Conditions, Animations for Elementor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4265</link><description>The Master Addons – Free Widgets, Hover Effects, Toggle, Conditions, Animations for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 2.0.5.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4265|2024-05-02T16:52:29.292Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3134|2024-05-16T21:30:55.964Z -- litonice13 -- Master Addons – Free Widgets, Hover Effects, Toggle, Conditions, Animations for Elementor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3134</link><description>The Master Addons – Free Widgets, Hover Effects, Toggle, Conditions, Animations for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the title_html_tag attribute in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3134|2024-05-16T21:30:55.964Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 21:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2139|2024-03-27T01:56:46.912Z -- litonice13 -- Master Addons – Free Widgets, Hover Effects, Toggle, Conditions, Animations for Elementor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2139</link><description>The Master Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Pricing Table widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.5.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2139|2024-03-27T01:56:46.912Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 01:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>