<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18814|2024-08-05T11:23:08.427Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18814</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Spotfire authentication component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains a vulnerability in the handling of the authentication that theoretically may allow an attacker to gain full access to a target account, independent of configured authentication mechanisms. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions up to and including 10.0.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions up to and including 7.10.1; 7.11.0; 7.11.1; 7.12.0; 7.13.0; 7.14.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18814|2024-08-05T11:23:08.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18810|2024-08-05T11:23:08.355Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20managed%20file%20transfer%20command%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18810</link>
      <description>The Administrator Service component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center, and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server contains vulnerabilities where an authenticated user with specific privileges can gain access to credentials to other systems. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center: versions up to and including 7.3.2; 8.0.0; 8.0.1; 8.0.2; 8.1.0, and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server: versions up to and including 7.3.2; 8.0.0; 8.0.1; 8.0.2; 8.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18810|2024-08-05T11:23:08.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5533|2024-08-05T15:04:15.360Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5533</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the server content cache of TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a vulnerability which fails to prevent remote access to all the contents of the web application, including key configuration files. Affected releases are TIBCO JasperReports Server 6.4.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition 6.4.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM 6.4.0, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy 6.4.0, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS 6.4.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5533|2024-08-05T15:04:15.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5437|2024-08-05T05:33:44.438Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analyst
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5437</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Spotfire Client and TIBCO Spotfire Web Player Client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, and TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs contain multiple vulnerabilities that may allow for unauthorized information disclosure. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0; 7.9.1; 7.10.0; 7.10.1; 7.11.0; 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions up to and including 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0;7.9.1;7.10.0;7.10.1;7.11.0; 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0; 7.9.1; 7.10.0; 7.10.1; 7.11.0;7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0; 7.9.1; 7.10.0; 7.10.1; 7.11.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5437|2024-08-05T05:33:44.438Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5528|2024-08-05T15:04:14.869Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5528</link>
      <description>Multiple JasperReports Server components contain vulnerabilities which may allow authorized users to perform cross-site scripting (XSS) and cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks.  The impact of this vulnerability includes the theoretical disclosure of sensitive information.  Affects TIBCO JasperReports Server (versions 6.1.1 and below, 6.2.0, 6.2.1, and 6.3.0), TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition (versions 6.3.0 and below), TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM (versions 6.2.0 and below), TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy (versions 6.2.0 and below), and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS (versions 6.2.0 and below).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5528|2024-08-05T15:04:14.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5433|2024-08-05T05:33:44.236Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20administrator%20-%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5433</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Administrator server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, and TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux contains vulnerabilities wherein a malicious user could perform XML external entity expansion (XXE) attacks to disclose host machine information. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions up to and including 5.10.0, and TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions up to and including 5.9.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5433|2024-08-05T05:33:44.236Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18808|2024-08-05T11:23:08.199Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18808</link>
      <description>The domain management component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a race-condition vulnerability that may allow any users with domain save privileges to gain superuser privileges. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.3.4; 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.3; 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 7.1.0, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 7.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18808|2024-08-05T11:23:08.199Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12411|2024-08-05T08:38:05.058Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activespaces%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12411</link>
      <description>The administrative daemon (tibdgadmind) of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition, and TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability which may allow an attacker to perform cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition: 3.3.0; 3.4.0; 3.5.0, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition: 3.0.0; 3.1.0; 3.3.0; 3.4.0; 3.5.0, and TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition: 3.0.0; 3.1.0; 3.2.0; 3.3.0; 3.4.0; 3.5.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12411|2024-08-05T08:38:05.058Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17330|2024-08-05T01:40:14.511Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17330</link>
      <description>The Web server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX contains multiple vulnerabilities that theoretically allow authenticated users to perform stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks, and unauthenticated users to perform reflected cross-site scripting attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions up to and including 5.8.1.fixR, versions 5.9.3, 5.9.4, 5.9.5, and 5.9.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17330|2024-08-05T01:40:14.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5535|2024-08-05T15:04:15.350Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20datasynapse%20gridserver%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5535</link>
      <description>The GridServer Broker, GridServer Driver, and GridServer Engine components of TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO DataSynapse GridServer Manager contain vulnerabilities related to both the improper use of encryption mechanisms and the use of weak ciphers. A malicious actor could theoretically compromise the traffic between any of the components. Affected releases include TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO DataSynapse GridServer Manager: versions up to and including 5.1.3; 6.0.0; 6.0.1; 6.0.2; 6.1.0; 6.1.1; and 6.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5535|2024-08-05T15:04:15.350Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5534|2024-08-05T15:04:15.296Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibbr%20community
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5534</link>
      <description>The tibbr user profiles components of tibbr Community, and tibbr Enterprise expose a weakness in an improperly sandboxed third-party component. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. tibbr Community 5.2.1 and below; 6.0.0; 6.0.1; 7.0.0, tibbr Enterprise 5.2.1 and below; 6.0.0; 6.0.1; 7.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5534|2024-08-05T15:04:15.296Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18812|2024-08-05T11:23:08.100Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18812</link>
      <description>The Spotfire Library component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains a vulnerability that might theoretically fail to restrict users with read-only access from modifying files stored in the Spotfire Library, only when the Spotfire Library is configured to use external storage. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace versions up to and including 10.0.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Server versions up to and including 7.10.1; 7.11.0; 7.11.1; 7.12.0; 7.13.0; 7.14.0; 10.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18812|2024-08-05T11:23:08.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5531|2024-08-05T15:04:15.327Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20managed%20file%20transfer%20command%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5531</link>
      <description>Deployments of TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center versions 8.0.0 and 8.0.1 and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server versions 8.0.0 and 8.0.1 that enable the Administrator Service may be affected by a vulnerability which may allow any authenticated user to gain administrative control of Managed File Transfer web applications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5531|2024-08-05T15:04:15.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17335|2024-08-05T01:40:14.503Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17335</link>
      <description>The Data access layer component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains multiple vulnerabilities that theoretically allow an attacker access to data cached from a data source, or a portion of a data source, that the attacker should not have access to. The attacker would need privileges to save a Spotfire file to the library. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: version 10.6.0 and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 7.11.7 and below, versions 7.12.0, 7.13.0, 7.14.0, 10.0.0, 10.0.1, 10.1.0, 10.2.0, 10.2.1, 10.3.0, 10.3.1, 10.3.2, 10.3.3, and 10.3.4, versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, and 10.6.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17335|2024-08-05T01:40:14.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17337|2024-08-05T01:40:14.494Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17337</link>
      <description>The Spotfire library component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an attacker to perform a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attack. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: version 10.6.0 and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 7.11.7 and below, versions 7.12.0, 7.13.0, 7.14.0, 10.0.0, 10.0.1, 10.1.0, 10.2.0, 10.2.1, 10.3.0, 10.3.1, 10.3.2, 10.3.3, and 10.3.4, versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, and 10.6.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17337|2024-08-05T01:40:14.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12413|2024-08-05T08:38:04.943Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20messaging%20-%20apache%20kafka%20distribution%20-%20schema%20repository%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12413</link>
      <description>The Schema repository server (tibschemad) component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Messaging - Apache Kafka Distribution - Schema Repository - Community Edition, and TIBCO Messaging - Apache Kafka Distribution - Schema Repository - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability which may allow an attacker to perform cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO Messaging - Apache Kafka Distribution - Schema Repository - Community Edition: 1.0.0, and TIBCO Messaging - Apache Kafka Distribution - Schema Repository - Enterprise Edition: 1.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12413|2024-08-05T08:38:04.943Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17332|2024-08-05T01:40:15.251Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx%20add-ons
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17332</link>
      <description>The Digital Asset Manager Web Interface component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows authenticated users to perform stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions up to and including 3.20.13, versions 4.1.0, 4.2.0, 4.2.1, and 4.2.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17332|2024-08-05T01:40:15.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18809|2024-08-05T11:23:08.387Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20library
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18809</link>
      <description>The default server implementation of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Library, TIBCO JasperReports Library Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a directory-traversal vulnerability that may theoretically allow web server users to access contents of the host system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Library: versions up to and including 6.3.4; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.21; 7.1.0; 7.2.0, TIBCO JasperReports Library Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.7.0, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.21, TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.3.4; 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.3; 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.3; 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 7.1.0, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 7.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18809|2024-08-05T11:23:08.387Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5532|2024-08-05T15:04:15.302Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5532</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the report renderer component of TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO JasperReports Library, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio for ActiveMatrix BPM may allow a subset of authorized users to perform persistent cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO JasperReports Server 6.2.3 and below; 6.3.0; 6.3.1; 6.3.2; 6.4.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition 6.4.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM 6.4.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Library 6.2.3 and below; 6.3.0; 6.3.1; 6.3.2; 6.4.0; 6.4.1, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM 6.4.1 and below, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy 6.4.0 and below, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS 6.4.0 and below, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio 6.2.3 and below; 6.3.0; 6.3.1; 6.3.2; 6.4.0, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio for ActiveMatrix BPM 6.4.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5532|2024-08-05T15:04:15.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5428|2024-08-05T05:33:44.342Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20virtualization
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5428</link>
      <description>The version control adapters component of TIBCO Data Virtualization (formerly known as Cisco Information Server) contains vulnerabilities that may allow for arbitrary command execution. Affected releases are TIBCO Data Virtualization: 7.0.5; 7.0.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5428|2024-08-05T05:33:44.342Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18807|2024-08-05T11:23:08.197Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20statistica%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18807</link>
      <description>The web application of the TIBCO Statistica component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Statistica Server contains vulnerabilities which may allow an authenticated user to perform cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Statistica Server versions up to and including 13.4.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18807|2024-08-05T11:23:08.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18816|2024-08-05T11:23:08.207Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18816</link>
      <description>The repository component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a persistent cross site scripting vulnerability. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.3.4; 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.3; 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi- Tenancy versions up to and including 7.1.0, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 7.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18816|2024-08-05T11:23:08.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17331|2024-08-05T01:40:14.487Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx%20add-ons
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17331</link>
      <description>The Data Exchange Web Interface component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows authenticated users to perform stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions up to and including 3.20.13, version 4.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17331|2024-08-05T01:40:14.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17339|2024-08-05T01:40:14.516Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20silver%20fabric
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17339</link>
      <description>The VirtualRouter component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Silver Fabric contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an attacker to inject scripts via URLs. The attacker could theoretically social engineer an authenticated user into submitting the URL, thus executing the script on the affected system with the privileges of the user. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 6.0.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17339|2024-08-05T01:40:14.516Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12408|2024-08-05T08:38:04.839Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activematrix%20businessworks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12408</link>
      <description>The BusinessWorks engine component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks, TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks for z/Linux, and TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric contains a vulnerability that may allow XML eXternal Entity (XXE) attacks via incoming network messages, and may disclose the contents of files accessible to a running BusinessWorks engine Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks: versions up to and including 5.13.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks for z/Linux: versions up to and including 5.13.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions up to and including 5.13.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12408|2024-08-05T08:38:04.839Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5432|2024-08-05T05:33:44.377Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20administrator%20-%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5432</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Administrator server component of of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, and TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux contains multiple vulnerabilities wherein a malicious user could theoretically perform cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks by way of manipulating artifacts prior to uploading them. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions up to and including 5.10.0, and TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions up to and including 5.9.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5432|2024-08-05T05:33:44.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18815|2024-08-05T11:23:07.855Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18815</link>
      <description>The REST API component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows unauthenticated users to bypass authorization checks for portions of the HTTP interface to the JasperReports Server. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.3; 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 7.1.0, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 7.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18815|2024-08-05T11:23:07.855Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12412|2024-08-05T08:38:05.116Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12412</link>
      <description>The realm server (tibrealmserver) component of TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability which may allow an attacker to perform cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions up to and including 5.4.0, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions up to and including 5.4.0, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions up to and including 5.4.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12412|2024-08-05T08:38:05.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5536|2024-08-05T15:04:15.331Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20datasynapse%20gridserver%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5536</link>
      <description>The GridServer Broker, and GridServer Director components of TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO DataSynapse GridServer Manager contain vulnerabilities which may allow an authenticated user to perform cross-site scripting (XSS). In addition, an authenticated user could be a victim of a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack. Affected releases include TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO DataSynapse GridServer Manager: versions up to and including 5.1.3; 6.0.0; 6.0.1; 6.0.2; 6.1.0; 6.1.1; and 6.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5536|2024-08-05T15:04:15.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5435|2024-08-05T05:33:44.385Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analyst
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5435</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Spotfire Client and TIBCO Spotfire Web Player Client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, and TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs contain multiple vulnerabilities that may allow for remote code execution. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0; 7.9.1; 7.10.0; 7.10.1; 7.11.0; 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions up to and including 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0;7.9.1;7.10.0;7.10.1;7.11.0; 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0; 7.9.1; 7.10.0; 7.10.1; 7.11.0;7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0; 7.9.1; 7.10.0; 7.10.1; 7.11.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5435|2024-08-05T05:33:44.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17338|2024-08-05T01:40:14.472Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20patterns%20-%20search
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17338</link>
      <description>The user interface component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Patterns - Search contains multiple vulnerabilities that theoretically allow authenticated users to perform persistent cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Patterns - Search: versions 5.4.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17338|2024-08-05T01:40:14.472Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5430|2024-08-05T05:33:44.336Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5430</link>
      <description>The Spring web flows of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contain a vulnerability which may allow any authenticated user read-only access to the contents of the web application, including key configuration files. Affected releases include TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2; 6.3.3;6.4.0; 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5430|2024-08-05T05:33:44.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5436|2024-08-05T05:33:44.366Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5436</link>
      <description>The Spotfire server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contain multiple vulnerabilities that may allow for the disclosure of information, including user and data source credentials. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions up to and including 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions up to and including 7.8.1; 7.9.0; 7.10.0; 7.11.0; 7.12.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5436|2024-08-05T05:33:44.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5431|2024-08-05T05:33:44.377Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5431</link>
      <description>The domain designer component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a vulnerability which may allow, in the context of a non-default permissions configuration, persisted cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases include TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2; 6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5431|2024-08-05T05:33:44.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17336|2024-08-05T01:40:14.527Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17336</link>
      <description>The Data access layer component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains multiple vulnerabilities that theoretically allow an attacker access to information that can lead to obtaining credentials used to access Spotfire data sources. The attacker would need privileges to save a Spotfire file to the library, and only applies in a situation where NTLM credentials, or a credentials profile is in use. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: version 10.6.0 and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 7.11.7 and below, versions 7.12.0, 7.13.0, 7.14.0, 10.0.0, 10.0.1, 10.1.0, 10.2.0, 10.2.1, 10.3.0, 10.3.1, 10.3.2, 10.3.3, and 10.3.4, versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, and 10.6.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17336|2024-08-05T01:40:14.527Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12415|2024-08-05T08:38:05.049Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20enterprise%20message%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12415</link>
      <description>The Central Administration server (emsca) component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Message Service, TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Community Edition, and TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Developer Edition contains a vulnerability which may allow an attacker to perform cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Message Service: versions 8.4.0 and below, TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Community Edition: versions 8.4.0 and below, and TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Developer Edition: versions 8.4.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12415|2024-08-05T08:38:05.049Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5529|2024-08-05T15:04:15.353Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20library%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5529</link>
      <description>JasperReports library components contain an information disclosure vulnerability. This vulnerability includes the theoretical disclosure of any accessible information from the host file system. Affects TIBCO JasperReports Library Community Edition (versions 6.4.0 and below), TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM (versions 6.2.0 and below), TIBCO JasperReports Professional (versions 6.2.1 and below, and 6.3.0), TIBCO JasperReports Server (versions 6.1.1 and below, 6.2.0, 6.2.1, 6.3.0), TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition (versions 6.3.0 and below), TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM (versions 6.2.0 and below), TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy (versions 6.3.0 and below), TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS (versions 6.3.0 and below), and TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio for ActiveMatrix BPM (versions 6.2.0 and below).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5529|2024-08-05T15:04:15.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5434|2024-08-05T05:33:44.337Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20runtime%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5434</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Designer component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Runtime Agent, and TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux contains vulnerabilities wherein a malicious user could perform XML external entity expansion (XXE) attacks to disclose host machine information. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Runtime Agent: versions up to and including 5.10.0, and TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux: versions up to and including 5.9.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5434|2024-08-05T05:33:44.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17333|2024-08-05T01:40:14.487Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17333</link>
      <description>The Web server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows authenticated users to perform stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions 5.8.1.fixS and below, versions 5.9.3, 5.9.4, 5.9.5, 5.9.6, and 5.9.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17333|2024-08-05T01:40:14.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12414|2024-08-05T08:38:05.517Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20rendezvous
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12414</link>
      <description>The Rendezvous Routing Daemon (rvrd), Rendezvous Secure Routing Daemon (rvrsd), Rendezvous Secure Daemon (rvsd), Rendezvous Cache (rvcache), and Rendezvous Daemon Manager (rvdm) components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Rendezvous, TIBCO Rendezvous Developer Edition, TIBCO Rendezvous for z/Linux, TIBCO Rendezvous for z/OS, TIBCO Rendezvous Network Server, TIBCO Substation ES contain vulnerabilities which may allow an attacker to perform cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Rendezvous: versions up to and including 8.4.5, TIBCO Rendezvous Developer Edition: versions up to and including 8.4.5, TIBCO Rendezvous for z/Linux: versions up to and including 8.4.5, TIBCO Rendezvous for z/OS: versions up to and including 8.4.5, TIBCO Rendezvous Network Server: versions up to and including 1.1.2, and TIBCO Substation ES: versions up to and including 2.12.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12414|2024-08-05T08:38:05.517Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18813|2024-08-05T11:23:07.973Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18813</link>
      <description>The Spotfire web server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains multiple vulnerabilities that may allow persistent and reflected cross-site scripting attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions up to and including 10.0.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions up to and including 7.10.1; 7.11.0; 7.11.1; 7.12.0; 7.13.0; 7.14.0; 10.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18813|2024-08-05T11:23:07.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12416|2024-08-05T08:38:04.959Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20datasynapse%20gridserver%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12416</link>
      <description>The GridServer Broker and GridServer Director components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO DataSynapse GridServer Manager contain vulnerabilities which may allow an unauthenticated user to perform cross-site request forgery (CSRF). Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO DataSynapse GridServer Manager: versions up to and including 5.2.0; 6.0.0; 6.0.1; 6.0.2; 6.1.0; 6.1.1; 6.2.0; 6.3.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12416|2024-08-05T08:38:04.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5530|2024-08-05T15:04:15.347Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibbr%20community
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5530</link>
      <description>The tibbr web server components of tibbr Community, and tibbr Enterprise contain SAML protocol handling errors which may allow authorized users to impersonate other users, and therefore escalate their access privileges. Affected releases are tibbr Community 5.2.1 and below; 6.0.0; 6.0.1; 7.0.0, tibbr Enterprise 5.2.1 and below; 6.0.0; 6.0.1; 7.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5530|2024-08-05T15:04:15.347Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12410|2024-08-05T08:38:05.137Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20statistics%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12410</link>
      <description>The web server component of TIBCO Software Inc's Spotfire Statistics Services contains multiple vulnerabilities that may allow the remote execution of code. Without needing to authenticate, an attacker may be able to remotely execute code with the permissions of the system account used to run the web server component. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services versions up to and including 7.11.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12410|2024-08-05T08:38:05.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5527|2024-08-05T15:04:15.132Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5527</link>
      <description>TIBCO Spotfire Server 7.0.X before 7.0.2, 7.5.x before 7.5.1, 7.6.x before 7.6.1, 7.7.x before 7.7.1, and 7.8.x before 7.8.1 and Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace 7.8.0 and earlier contain multiple vulnerabilities which may allow authorized users to perform SQL injection attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5527|2024-08-05T15:04:15.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17334|2024-08-05T01:40:14.457Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analyst
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17334</link>
      <description>The Visualizations component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, and TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an attacker with permission to write DXP files to the Spotfire library to remotely execute code of their choice on the user account of other users who access the affected system. This attack is a risk only when the attacker has write access to a network file system shared with the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions 7.11.1 and below, versions 7.12.0, 7.13.0, 7.14.0, 10.0.0, 10.1.0, 10.2.0, 10.3.0, 10.3.1, and 10.3.2, versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, and 10.6.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: version 10.6.0, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit: versions 7.11.1 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions 7.11.1 and below, versions 7.12.0, 7.13.0, 7.14.0, 10.0.0, 10.1.0, 10.2.0, 10.3.0, 10.3.1, and 10.3.2, versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, and 10.6.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs: versions 7.11.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17334|2024-08-05T01:40:14.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5429|2024-08-05T05:33:44.416Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5429</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the report scripting component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO JasperReports Library, TIBCO JasperReports Library Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio Community Edition, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio for ActiveMatrix BPM may allow analytic reports that contain scripting to perform arbitrary code execution. Affected releases include TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2;6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Library: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2; 6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Library Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2; 6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5429|2024-08-05T05:33:44.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1137|2024-06-04T18:00:30.306Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activespaces%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1137</link>
      <description>The Proxy and Client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows an Active Spaces client to passively observe data traffic to other clients. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition: versions 4.4.0 through 4.9.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1137|2024-06-04T18:00:30.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 17:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1138|2024-03-12T17:30:15.100Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1138</link>
      <description>The FTL Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a privilege escalation on the affected ftlserver. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.10.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1138|2024-03-12T17:30:15.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 17:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1137|2024-08-01T18:26:30.510Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activespaces%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1137</link>
      <description>The Proxy and Client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows an Active Spaces client to passively observe data traffic to other clients. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition: versions 4.4.0 through 4.9.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1137|2024-08-01T18:26:30.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 17:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1138|2024-08-01T18:26:30.563Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1138</link>
      <description>The FTL Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a privilege escalation on the affected ftlserver. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.10.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1138|2024-08-01T18:26:30.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 17:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
