<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 11:20:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9415|2024-08-04T10:26:16.248Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20virtualization
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9415</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Data Virtualization Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a malicious authenticated user to download any arbitrary file from the affected system. The user must be authenticated and have privileges required to monitor the server in an operational capacity. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization: versions 7.0.8 and below, versions 8.0.0, 8.1.0, 8.1.1, and 8.2.0 and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.2.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9415|2024-08-04T10:26:16.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35500|2024-08-04T00:40:46.397Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20virtualization
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35500</link>
      <description>The Data Virtualization Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization, TIBCO Data Virtualization, TIBCO Data Virtualization, and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with local access to download arbitrary files outside of the scope of the user's permissions on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization: versions 8.3.0 and below, TIBCO Data Virtualization: version 8.4.0, TIBCO Data Virtualization: version 8.5.0, and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35500|2024-08-04T00:40:46.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9409|2024-08-04T10:26:16.088Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9409</link>
      <description>The administrative UI component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an unauthenticated attacker to obtain the permissions of a JasperReports Server "superuser" for the affected systems. The attacker can theoretically exploit the vulnerability consistently, remotely, and without authenticating. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.1.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.1.1 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.1.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9409|2024-08-04T10:26:16.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43053|2024-08-04T03:47:13.205Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43053</link>
      <description>The Realm Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to obtain the cluster secret of another application connected to the realm server. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43053|2024-08-04T03:47:13.205Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9410|2024-08-04T10:26:16.100Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20library
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9410</link>
      <description>The report generator component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Library, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an attacker to exploit HTML injection to gain full control of a web interface containing the output of the report generator component with the privileges of any user that views the affected report(s). The attacker can theoretically exploit this vulnerability when other users view a maliciously generated report, where those reports use Fusion Charts and a data source with contents controlled by the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Library: versions 7.1.1 and below, versions 7.2.0 and 7.2.1, version 7.3.0, version 7.5.0, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.1.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.1.1 and below, version 7.2.0, version 7.5.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.5.0 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.1.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9410|2024-08-04T10:26:16.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9413|2024-08-04T10:26:16.111Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20managed%20file%20transfer%20command%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9413</link>
      <description>The MFT Browser file transfer client and MFT Browser admin client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows an attacker to craft an URL that will execute arbitrary commands on the affected system. If the attacker convinces an authenticated user with a currently active session to enter or click on the URL the commands will be executed on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center: versions 8.2.1 and below and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server: versions 8.2.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9413|2024-08-04T10:26:16.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43048|2024-08-04T03:47:13.219Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20partnerexpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43048</link>
      <description>The Interior Server and Gateway Server components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute a clickjacking attack on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability does not require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress: versions 6.2.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43048|2024-08-04T03:47:13.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43047|2024-08-04T03:47:13.246Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20partnerexpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43047</link>
      <description>The Interior Server and Gateway Server components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress contain easily exploitable Stored and Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow a low privileged attacker to social engineer a legitimate user with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress: versions 6.2.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43047|2024-08-04T03:47:13.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43054|2024-08-04T03:47:13.223Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20eftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43054</link>
      <description>The eFTL Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to generate API tokens that can access any other channel with arbitrary permissions. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43054|2024-08-04T03:47:13.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35495|2024-08-04T00:40:46.345Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35495</link>
      <description>The Scheduler Connection component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker with network access to obtain FTP server passwords for other users of the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.2.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.5.0 and 7.5.1, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.8.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.9.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 7.8.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.9.0 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 7.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35495|2024-08-04T00:40:46.345Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43046|2024-08-04T03:47:13.158Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20partnerexpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43046</link>
      <description>The Interior Server and Gateway Server components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress contain an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to obtain session tokens for the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress: versions 6.2.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43046|2024-08-04T03:47:13.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9411|2024-08-04T10:26:16.111Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20managed%20file%20transfer%20platform%20server%20for%20ibm%20i
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9411</link>
      <description>The file transfer component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for IBM i contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an attacker to perform unauthorized network file transfers to and from the file system accessible to the affected component. This vulnerability is exploitable when the configuration option 'Require Node Resp' is set to 'No'. In the event of a successful exploit, the attacker could theoretically read and write any file on the file system accessible to the affected component, thus fully affecting the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the operating system hosting the deployment of the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for IBM i: versions 7.1.0 and below, version 8.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9411|2024-08-04T10:26:16.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35499|2024-08-04T00:40:46.808Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20nimbus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35499</link>
      <description>The Web Reporting component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Nimbus contains easily exploitable Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow a low privileged attacker to social engineer a legitimate user with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Nimbus: versions 10.4.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35499|2024-08-04T00:40:46.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9408|2024-08-04T10:26:16.100Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9408</link>
      <description>The Spotfire library component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an attacker with write permissions to the Spotfire Library, but not "Script Author" group permission, to modify attributes of files and objects saved to the library such that the system treats them as trusted. This could allow an attacker to cause the Spotfire Web Player, Analyst clients, and TERR Service into executing arbitrary code with the privileges of the system account that started those processes. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions 10.8.0 and below and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 7.11.9 and below, versions 7.12.0, 7.13.0, 7.14.0, 10.0.0, 10.0.1, 10.1.0, 10.2.0, 10.3.0, 10.3.1, 10.3.2, 10.3.3, 10.3.4, 10.3.5, and 10.3.6, versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, 10.6.0, 10.6.1, 10.7.0, and 10.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9408|2024-08-04T10:26:16.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35494|2024-08-04T00:40:46.445Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35494</link>
      <description>The Rest API component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contain a race condition that allows a low privileged authenticated attacker via the REST API to obtain read access to temporary objects created by other users on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.2.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.5.0 and 7.5.1, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.8.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.9.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 7.8.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.9.0 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 7.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35494|2024-08-04T00:40:46.445Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43055|2024-08-04T03:47:13.230Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20eftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43055</link>
      <description>The eFTL Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows clients to inherit the permissions of the client that initially connected on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43055|2024-08-04T03:47:13.230Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9412|2024-08-04T10:26:16.380Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20managed%20file%20transfer%20platform%20server%20for%20ibm%20i
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9412</link>
      <description>The file transfer component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for IBM i contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows execution of arbitrary commands at the privilege level of the affected system following a failed file transfer. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for IBM i: versions 7.1.0 and below, version 8.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9412|2024-08-04T10:26:16.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43052|2024-08-04T03:47:13.437Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43052</link>
      <description>The Realm Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows authentication bypass due to a hard coded secret used in the default realm server of the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43052|2024-08-04T03:47:13.437Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9416|2024-08-04T10:26:16.103Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analyst
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9416</link>
      <description>The Spotfire client component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a legitimate user to inject scripts. If executed by a victim authenticated to the affected system these scripts will be executed at the privileges of the victim. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions 10.7.0, 10.8.0, 10.9.0, and 10.10.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions 10.7.0, 10.8.0, 10.8.1, 10.9.0, 10.10.0, and 10.10.1, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions 10.7.0, 10.8.0, 10.9.0, and 10.10.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 10.7.0, 10.8.0, 10.8.1, 10.9.0, 10.10.0, and 10.10.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9416|2024-08-04T10:26:16.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43049|2024-08-04T03:47:13.252Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20businessconnect%20container%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43049</link>
      <description>The Database component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Container Edition contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to obtain the usernames and passwords of users of the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Container Edition: versions 1.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43049|2024-08-04T03:47:13.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9414|2024-08-04T10:26:16.102Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20managed%20file%20transfer%20command%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9414</link>
      <description>The MFT admin service component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an authenticated user with specific permissions to obtain the session identifier of another user. The session identifier when replayed could provide administrative rights or file transfer permissions to the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center: versions 8.2.1 and below and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server: versions 8.2.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9414|2024-08-04T10:26:16.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43050|2024-08-04T03:47:13.628Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20businessconnect%20container%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43050</link>
      <description>The Auth Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Container Edition contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with local access to obtain administrative usernames and passwords for the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Container Edition: versions 1.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43050|2024-08-04T03:47:13.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35493|2024-08-04T00:40:46.614Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20webfocus%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35493</link>
      <description>The WebFOCUS Reporting Server and WebFOCUS Client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO WebFOCUS Client, TIBCO WebFOCUS Installer, and TIBCO WebFOCUS Reporting Server contain easily exploitable Stored and Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow a low privileged attacker to social engineer a legitimate user with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO WebFOCUS Client: versions 8207.27.0 and below, TIBCO WebFOCUS Installer: versions 8207.27.0 and below, and TIBCO WebFOCUS Reporting Server: versions 8207.27.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35493|2024-08-04T00:40:46.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43051|2024-08-04T03:47:13.411Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43051</link>
      <description>The Spotfire Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Server, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows malicious custom API clients with network access to execute internal API operations outside of the scope of those granted to it. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 10.10.6 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 11.0.0, 11.1.0, 11.2.0, 11.3.0, 11.4.0, and 11.4.1, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 11.5.0 and 11.6.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43051|2024-08-04T03:47:13.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9417|2024-08-04T10:26:16.118Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20foresight%20archive%20and%20retrieval%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9417</link>
      <description>The Transaction Insight reporting component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Foresight Archive and Retrieval System, TIBCO Foresight Archive and Retrieval System Healthcare Edition, TIBCO Foresight Operational Monitor, TIBCO Foresight Operational Monitor Healthcare Edition, TIBCO Foresight Transaction Insight, and TIBCO Foresight Transaction Insight Healthcare Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an authenticated attacker to perform SQL injection. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Foresight Archive and Retrieval System: versions 5.1.0 and below, version 5.2.0, TIBCO Foresight Archive and Retrieval System Healthcare Edition: versions 5.1.0 and below, version 5.2.0, TIBCO Foresight Operational Monitor: versions 5.1.0 and below, version 5.2.0, TIBCO Foresight Operational Monitor Healthcare Edition: versions 5.1.0 and below, version 5.2.0, TIBCO Foresight Transaction Insight: versions 5.1.0 and below, version 5.2.0, and TIBCO Foresight Transaction Insight Healthcare Edition: versions 5.1.0 and below, version 5.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9417|2024-08-04T10:26:16.118Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35496|2024-08-04T00:40:46.364Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35496</link>
      <description>The XMLA Connections component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to interfere with XML processing in the affected component. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.2.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.5.0 and 7.5.1, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.8.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.9.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 7.8.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.9.0 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 7.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35496|2024-08-04T00:40:46.364Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35498|2024-08-04T00:40:46.830Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35498</link>
      <description>The TIBCO EBX Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX, TIBCO EBX, TIBCO EBX, and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX contains a vulnerability that under certain specific conditions allows an attacker to enter a password other than the legitimate password and it will be accepted as valid. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions 5.8.123 and below, TIBCO EBX: versions 5.9.3, 5.9.4, 5.9.5, 5.9.6, 5.9.7, 5.9.8, 5.9.9, 5.9.10, 5.9.11, 5.9.12, 5.9.13, and 5.9.14, TIBCO EBX: versions 6.0.0 and 6.0.1, and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX: version 1.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35498|2024-08-04T00:40:46.830Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35497|2024-08-04T00:40:47.272Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activespaces%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35497</link>
      <description>The FTL Server (tibftlserver) and Docker images containing tibftlserver components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows a non-administrative, authenticated FTL user to trick the affected components into creating illegitimate certificates. These maliciously generated certificates can be used to enable man-in-the-middle attacks or to escalate privileges so that the malicious user has administrative privileges. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition: versions 4.3.0, 4.4.0, 4.5.0, 4.6.0, 4.6.1, and 4.6.2, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition: versions 4.3.0, 4.4.0, 4.5.0, 4.6.0, 4.6.1, and 4.6.2, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition: versions 4.3.0, 4.4.0, 4.5.0, 4.6.0, 4.6.1, and 4.6.2, TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.2.0, 6.3.0, 6.3.1, 6.4.0, 6.5.0, 6.6.0, 6.6.1, and 6.7.0, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.2.0, 6.3.0, 6.3.1, 6.4.0, 6.5.0, 6.6.0, 6.6.1, and 6.7.0, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.2.0, 6.3.0, 6.3.1, 6.4.0, 6.5.0, 6.6.0, 6.6.1, and 6.7.0, TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition: versions 6.2.0, 6.3.0, 6.3.1, 6.4.0, 6.5.0, 6.6.0, 6.6.1, and 6.7.0, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.2.0, 6.3.0, 6.3.1, 6.4.0, 6.5.0, 6.6.0, 6.6.1, and 6.7.0, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.2.0, 6.3.0, 6.3.1, 6.4.0, 6.5.0, 6.6.0, 6.6.1, and 6.7.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35497|2024-08-04T00:40:47.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1137|2024-06-04T18:00:30.306Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activespaces%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1137</link>
      <description>The Proxy and Client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows an Active Spaces client to passively observe data traffic to other clients. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition: versions 4.4.0 through 4.9.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1137|2024-06-04T18:00:30.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 17:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1138|2024-03-12T17:30:15.100Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1138</link>
      <description>The FTL Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a privilege escalation on the affected ftlserver. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.10.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1138|2024-03-12T17:30:15.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 17:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1137|2024-08-01T18:26:30.510Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activespaces%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1137</link>
      <description>The Proxy and Client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows an Active Spaces client to passively observe data traffic to other clients. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition: versions 4.4.0 through 4.9.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1137|2024-08-01T18:26:30.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 17:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1138|2024-08-01T18:26:30.563Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1138</link>
      <description>The FTL Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a privilege escalation on the affected ftlserver. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.10.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1138|2024-08-01T18:26:30.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 17:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
