<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30574|2024-08-03T06:56:12.980Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30574</link>
      <description>The ftlserver component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with local access to obtain user credentials to the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.8.0, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.0.1 through 6.8.0, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.7.3, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: version 6.8.0, TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.8.0, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.0.1 through 6.8.0, TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.7.3, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition: version 6.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30574|2024-08-03T06:56:12.980Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22777|2024-08-03T03:21:49.131Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20businessconnect%20trading%20community%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22777</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management contains easily exploitable Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management: versions 6.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22777|2024-08-03T03:21:49.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22769|2024-08-03T03:21:49.075Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22769</link>
      <description>The Web server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX, TIBCO EBX, TIBCO EBX, TIBCO EBX Add-ons, TIBCO EBX Add-ons, TIBCO EBX Add-ons, and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions 5.8.124 and below, TIBCO EBX: versions 5.9.3, 5.9.4, 5.9.5, 5.9.6, 5.9.7, 5.9.8, 5.9.9, 5.9.10, 5.9.11, 5.9.12, 5.9.13, 5.9.14, and 5.9.15, TIBCO EBX: versions 6.0.0, 6.0.1, 6.0.2, and 6.0.3, TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions 3.20.18 and below, TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions 4.1.0, 4.2.0, 4.2.1, 4.2.2, 4.3.0, 4.3.1, 4.3.2, 4.3.3, 4.3.4, 4.4.0, 4.4.1, 4.4.2, 4.4.3, 4.5.0, 4.5.1, 4.5.2, 4.5.3, 4.5.4, 4.5.5, and 4.5.6, TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions 5.0.0, 5.0.1, 5.1.0, 5.1.1, and 5.2.0, and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX: versions 1.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22769|2024-08-03T03:21:49.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41562|2024-08-03T12:49:41.887Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41562</link>
      <description>The HTML escaping component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a privileged/administrative attacker with network access to execute an XSS attack on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 8.0.2 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 8.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 8.1.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 8.1.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.0.2 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: version 8.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: versions 8.0.2 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 8.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41562|2024-08-03T12:49:41.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23273|2024-08-03T19:05:55.402Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analyst
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23273</link>
      <description>The Spotfire client component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) attack on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions 10.3.3 and below, versions 10.10.0, 10.10.1, and 10.10.2, versions 10.7.0, 10.8.0, 10.9.0, 11.0.0, and 11.1.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions 11.1.0 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions 10.3.3 and below, versions 10.10.0, 10.10.1, and 10.10.2, versions 10.7.0, 10.8.0, 10.9.0, 11.0.0, and 11.1.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 10.3.11 and below, versions 10.10.0, 10.10.1, 10.10.2, and 10.10.3, versions 10.7.0, 10.8.0, 10.8.1, 10.9.0, 11.0.0, and 11.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23273|2024-08-03T19:05:55.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22771|2024-08-03T03:21:49.119Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20library
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22771</link>
      <description>The Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Library, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains a directory-traversal vulnerability that may theoretically allow web server users to access contents of the host system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Library: version 7.9.0, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM: version 7.9.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.9.0 and 7.9.1, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.9.0 and 7.9.1, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.9.0 and 7.9.1, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 7.9.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22771|2024-08-03T03:21:49.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23271|2024-08-03T19:05:54.516Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23271</link>
      <description>The TIBCO EBX Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) attack on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions 5.9.12 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23271|2024-08-03T19:05:54.516Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23275|2024-08-03T19:05:55.635Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20enterprise%20runtime%20for%20r%20-%20server%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23275</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services, and TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition: versions 1.2.4 and below, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition: versions 1.3.0 and 1.3.1, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition: versions 1.4.0, 1.5.0, and 1.6.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions 11.3.0 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 10.3.12 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, 10.6.0, 10.6.1, 10.7.0, 10.8.0, 10.8.1, 10.9.0, 10.10.0, 10.10.1, 10.10.2, 10.10.3, and 10.10.4, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 11.0.0, 11.1.0, 11.2.0, and 11.3.0, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services: versions 10.3.0 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services: versions 10.10.0, 10.10.1, and 10.10.2, and TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services: versions 11.1.0, 11.2.0, and 11.3.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23275|2024-08-03T19:05:55.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30577|2024-08-03T06:56:12.860Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30577</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions 6.0.0 through 6.0.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30577|2024-08-03T06:56:12.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28830|2024-08-03T21:55:11.597Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20enterprise%20runtime%20for%20r%20-%20server%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28830</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Spotfire Server and TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services, and TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from the affected component searching for run-time artifacts outside of the installation hierarchy. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition: versions 1.2.4 and below, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition: versions 1.3.0 and 1.3.1, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition: versions 1.4.0, 1.5.0, and 1.6.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions 11.3.0 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 10.3.12 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, 10.6.0, 10.6.1, 10.7.0, 10.8.0, 10.8.1, 10.9.0, 10.10.0, 10.10.1, 10.10.2, 10.10.3, and 10.10.4, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 11.0.0, 11.1.0, 11.2.0, and 11.3.0, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services: versions 10.3.0 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services: versions 10.10.0, 10.10.1, and 10.10.2, and TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services: versions 11.1.0, 11.2.0, and 11.3.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28830|2024-08-03T21:55:11.597Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28828|2024-08-03T21:55:11.793Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20administrator%20-%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28828</link>
      <description>The Administration GUI component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux, and TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a SQL injection attack on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions 5.10.2 and below, and TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28828|2024-08-03T21:55:11.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28817|2024-08-03T21:55:11.598Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20rendezvous
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28817</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Rendezvous and TIBCO Rendezvous Developer Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Rendezvous: versions 8.5.1 and below and TIBCO Rendezvous Developer Edition: versions 8.5.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28817|2024-08-03T21:55:11.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28827|2024-08-03T21:55:12.093Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20administrator%20-%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28827</link>
      <description>The Administration GUI component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux, TIBCO Runtime Agent, TIBCO Runtime Agent, TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux, and TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker to social engineer a legitimate user with network access to execute a Stored XSS attack targeting the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Runtime Agent: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Runtime Agent: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux: versions 5.10.2 and below, and TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28827|2024-08-03T21:55:12.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28823|2024-08-03T21:55:11.579Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20eftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28823</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28823|2024-08-03T21:55:11.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28824|2024-08-03T21:55:11.744Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activespaces%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28824</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition, and TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition: versions 4.5.0 and below, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition: versions 4.5.0 and below, and TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition: versions 4.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28824|2024-08-03T21:55:11.744Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28822|2024-08-03T21:55:11.567Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20enterprise%20message%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28822</link>
      <description>The Enterprise Message Service Server (tibemsd), Enterprise Message Service Central Administration (tibemsca), Enterprise Message Service JSON configuration generator (tibemsconf2json), and Enterprise Message Service C API components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Message Service, TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Community Edition, and TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Developer Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from the affected component searching for run-time artifacts outside of the installation hierarchy. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Message Service: versions 8.5.1 and below, TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Community Edition: versions 8.5.1 and below, and TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Developer Edition: versions 8.5.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28822|2024-08-03T21:55:11.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28821|2024-08-03T21:55:11.558Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20enterprise%20message%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28821</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Message Service, TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Community Edition, and TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Developer Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Message Service: versions 8.5.1 and below, TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Community Edition: versions 8.5.1 and below, and TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Developer Edition: versions 8.5.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28821|2024-08-03T21:55:11.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28826|2024-08-03T21:55:11.911Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20messaging%20-%20eclipse%20mosquitto%20distribution%20-%20bridge%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28826</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Messaging - Eclipse Mosquitto Distribution - Bridge - Community Edition and TIBCO Messaging - Eclipse Mosquitto Distribution - Bridge - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Messaging - Eclipse Mosquitto Distribution - Bridge - Community Edition: versions 1.3.0 and below and TIBCO Messaging - Eclipse Mosquitto Distribution - Bridge - Enterprise Edition: versions 1.3.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28826|2024-08-03T21:55:11.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22772|2024-08-03T03:21:49.168Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20managed%20file%20transfer%20platform%20server%20for%20unix
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22772</link>
      <description>The cfsend, cfrecv, and CyberResp components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for UNIX and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for z/Linux contain a difficult to exploit Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute arbitrary code on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for UNIX: versions 8.1.0 and below and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for z/Linux: versions 8.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22772|2024-08-03T03:21:49.168Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41561|2024-08-03T12:49:41.895Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41561</link>
      <description>The JNDI Data Sources component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a privileged/administrative attacker with network access to execute Remote Code Execution to obtain a reverse shell on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 8.0.2 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 8.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 8.1.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 8.1.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.0.2 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: version 8.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: versions 8.0.2 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 8.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41561|2024-08-03T12:49:41.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22774|2024-08-03T03:21:49.107Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20managed%20file%20transfer%20command%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22774</link>
      <description>The DOM XML parser and SAX XML parser components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center, TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center, TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server, and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute XML External Entity (XXE) attacks on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center: versions 8.3.1 and below, TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center: versions 8.4.0 and 8.4.1, TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server: versions 8.3.1 and below, and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server: versions 8.4.0 and 8.4.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22774|2024-08-03T03:21:49.107Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41567|2024-08-03T12:49:41.904Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20businessconnect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41567</link>
      <description>The BusinessConnect UI component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect: versions 7.3.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41567|2024-08-03T12:49:41.904Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22770|2024-08-03T03:21:49.164Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20auditsafe
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22770</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO AuditSafe contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute API methods on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO AuditSafe: versions 1.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22770|2024-08-03T03:21:49.164Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22778|2024-08-03T03:21:49.163Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20businessconnect%20trading%20community%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22778</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management: versions 6.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22778|2024-08-03T03:21:49.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28829|2024-08-03T21:55:11.764Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20administrator%20-%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28829</link>
      <description>The Administration GUI component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux, and TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a persistent CSV injection attack from the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions 5.10.2 and below, and TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28829|2024-08-03T21:55:11.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28825|2024-08-03T21:55:11.826Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20messaging%20-%20eclipse%20mosquitto%20distribution%20-%20core%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28825</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Messaging - Eclipse Mosquitto Distribution - Core - Community Edition and TIBCO Messaging - Eclipse Mosquitto Distribution - Core - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Messaging - Eclipse Mosquitto Distribution - Core - Community Edition: versions 1.3.0 and below and TIBCO Messaging - Eclipse Mosquitto Distribution - Core - Enterprise Edition: versions 1.3.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28825|2024-08-03T21:55:11.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41564|2024-08-03T12:49:43.251Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20hawk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41564</link>
      <description>The Hawk Console component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Hawk and TIBCO Operational Intelligence Hawk RedTail contains a vulnerability that will return the EMS transport password and EMS SSL password to a privileged user. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Hawk: versions 6.1.0 through 6.2.1 and TIBCO Operational Intelligence Hawk RedTail: versions 7.0.0 through 7.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41564|2024-08-03T12:49:43.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30579|2024-08-03T06:56:12.867Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30579</link>
      <description>The Web Player component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute blind Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: version 12.0.0 and TIBCO Spotfire Server: version 12.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30579|2024-08-03T06:56:12.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41558|2024-08-03T12:42:46.398Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analyst
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41558</link>
      <description>The Visualizations component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Server, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions 11.4.4 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions 11.5.0, 11.6.0, 11.7.0, 11.8.0, 12.0.0, and 12.0.1, TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: version 12.1.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions 12.1.0 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions 11.4.4 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions 11.5.0, 11.6.0, 11.7.0, 11.8.0, 12.0.0, and 12.0.1, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: version 12.1.0, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 11.4.8 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 11.5.0, 11.6.0, 11.6.1, 11.6.2, 11.6.3, 11.7.0, 11.8.0, 11.8.1, 12.0.0, and 12.0.1, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: version 12.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41558|2024-08-03T12:42:46.398Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30570|2024-08-03T06:56:13.013Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20virtualization
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30570</link>
      <description>The Column Based Security component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to obtain read access to application information on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization: versions 8.5.2 and below and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.5.2 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30570|2024-08-03T06:56:13.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41565|2024-08-03T12:49:43.191Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41565</link>
      <description>The Web Application component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a stored XSS on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions 5.9.21 and below, versions 6.0.11 and below and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX: versions 1.2.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41565|2024-08-03T12:49:43.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41566|2024-08-03T12:49:41.888Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx%20add-ons
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41566</link>
      <description>The server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute stored XSS on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions 5.6.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41566|2024-08-03T12:49:41.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30575|2024-08-03T06:56:12.974Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20science%20-%20workbench
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30575</link>
      <description>The Web Console component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science - Workbench, TIBCO Statistica, TIBCO Statistica - Estore Edition, and TIBCO Statistica Trial contains easily exploitable Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow a low privileged attacker with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science - Workbench: versions 14.0.0 and below, TIBCO Statistica: versions 14.0.0 and below, TIBCO Statistica - Estore Edition: versions 14.0.0 and below, and TIBCO Statistica Trial: versions 14.0.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30575|2024-08-03T06:56:12.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41559|2024-08-03T12:42:46.254Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20nimbus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41559</link>
      <description>The Web Client component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Nimbus contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to exploit an open redirect on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Nimbus: version 10.5.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41559|2024-08-03T12:42:46.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22775|2024-08-03T03:21:49.170Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20bpm%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22775</link>
      <description>The Workspace client component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BPM Enterprise and TIBCO BPM Enterprise Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric contains difficult to exploit Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow low privileged attackers with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BPM Enterprise: versions 4.3.1 and below and TIBCO BPM Enterprise Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 4.3.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22775|2024-08-03T03:21:49.170Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30573|2024-08-03T06:56:12.870Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30573</link>
      <description>The ftlserver component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a privilege escalation on the affected ftlserver. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.8.0, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.0.1 through 6.8.0, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.7.3, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: version 6.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30573|2024-08-03T06:56:12.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41560|2024-08-03T12:42:46.392Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20nimbus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41560</link>
      <description>The Statement Set Upload via the Web Client component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Nimbus contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a Denial of Service Attack on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Nimbus: version 10.5.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41560|2024-08-03T12:42:46.392Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41563|2024-08-03T12:49:41.886Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41563</link>
      <description>The Dashboard component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 8.0.2 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 8.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 8.1.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.0.2 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: version 8.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: versions 8.0.2 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 8.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41563|2024-08-03T12:49:41.886Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30571|2024-08-03T06:56:13.169Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20iway%20service%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30571</link>
      <description>The iWay Service Manager Console component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO iWay Service Manager contains easily exploitable Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow a low privileged attacker with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO iWay Service Manager: versions 8.0.6 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30571|2024-08-03T06:56:13.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28819|2024-08-03T21:55:11.563Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28819</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28819|2024-08-03T21:55:11.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30572|2024-08-03T06:56:12.712Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20iway%20service%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30572</link>
      <description>The iWay Service Manager Console component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO iWay Service Manager contains an easily exploitable Directory Traversal vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to read arbitrary resources on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO iWay Service Manager: versions 8.0.6 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30572|2024-08-03T06:56:12.712Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28818|2024-08-03T21:55:11.852Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20rendezvous
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28818</link>
      <description>The Rendezvous Routing Daemon (rvrd), Rendezvous Secure Routing Daemon (rvrsd), Rendezvous Secure Daemon (rvsd), Rendezvous Cache (rvcache), Rendezvous Secure C API, Rendezvous Java API, and Rendezvous .Net API components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Rendezvous and TIBCO Rendezvous Developer Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from the affected component searching for run-time artifacts outside of the installation hierarchy. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Rendezvous: versions 8.5.1 and below and TIBCO Rendezvous Developer Edition: versions 8.5.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28818|2024-08-03T21:55:11.852Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30578|2024-08-03T06:56:13.099Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx%20add-ons
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30578</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions 5.4.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30578|2024-08-03T06:56:13.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28820|2024-08-03T21:55:11.578Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28820</link>
      <description>The FTL Server (tibftlserver), FTL C API, FTL Golang API, FTL Java API, and FTL .Net API components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from the affected component searching for run-time artifacts outside of the installation hierarchy. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28820|2024-08-03T21:55:11.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23274|2024-08-03T19:05:55.616Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20api%20exchange%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23274</link>
      <description>The Config UI component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO API Exchange Gateway and TIBCO API Exchange Gateway Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute a clickjacking attack on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability does not require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO API Exchange Gateway: versions 2.3.3 and below and TIBCO API Exchange Gateway Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 2.3.3 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23274|2024-08-03T19:05:55.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23272|2024-08-03T19:05:55.489Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20bpm%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23272</link>
      <description>The Application Development Clients component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BPM Enterprise and TIBCO BPM Enterprise Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) attack on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BPM Enterprise: versions 4.3.0 and below and TIBCO BPM Enterprise Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 4.3.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23272|2024-08-03T19:05:55.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22776|2024-08-03T03:21:49.157Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20businessconnect%20trading%20community%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22776</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management contains easily exploitable vulnerabilities that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the affected system. A successful attack using these vulnerabilities requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management: versions 6.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22776|2024-08-03T03:21:49.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30576|2024-08-03T06:56:12.927Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20science%20-%20workbench
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30576</link>
      <description>The Web Console component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science - Workbench, TIBCO Statistica, TIBCO Statistica - Estore Edition, and TIBCO Statistica Trial contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science - Workbench: versions 14.0.0 and below, TIBCO Statistica: versions 14.0.0 and below, TIBCO Statistica - Estore Edition: versions 14.0.0 and below, and TIBCO Statistica Trial: versions 14.0.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30576|2024-08-03T06:56:12.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22773|2024-08-03T03:21:49.160Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22773</link>
      <description>The REST API component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains difficult to exploit Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow a low privileged attacker with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 8.0.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 8.0.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 8.0.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.0.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.9.2 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: versions 8.0.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22773|2024-08-03T03:21:49.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1137|2024-06-04T18:00:30.306Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activespaces%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1137</link>
      <description>The Proxy and Client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows an Active Spaces client to passively observe data traffic to other clients. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition: versions 4.4.0 through 4.9.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1137|2024-06-04T18:00:30.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 17:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1138|2024-03-12T17:30:15.100Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1138</link>
      <description>The FTL Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a privilege escalation on the affected ftlserver. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.10.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1138|2024-03-12T17:30:15.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 17:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1137|2024-08-01T18:26:30.510Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activespaces%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1137</link>
      <description>The Proxy and Client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows an Active Spaces client to passively observe data traffic to other clients. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition: versions 4.4.0 through 4.9.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1137|2024-08-01T18:26:30.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 17:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1138|2024-08-01T18:26:30.563Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1138</link>
      <description>The FTL Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a privilege escalation on the affected ftlserver. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.10.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1138|2024-08-01T18:26:30.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 17:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
