<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 19:20:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43053|2024-09-16T18:08:27.215Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43053</link>
      <description>The Realm Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to obtain the cluster secret of another application connected to the realm server. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43053|2024-09-16T18:08:27.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 18:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18816|2024-09-16T17:58:45.349Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18816</link>
      <description>The repository component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a persistent cross site scripting vulnerability. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.3.4; 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.3; 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi- Tenancy versions up to and including 7.1.0, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 7.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18816|2024-09-16T17:58:45.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28828|2024-09-16T18:54:24.252Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20administrator%20-%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28828</link>
      <description>The Administration GUI component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux, and TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a SQL injection attack on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions 5.10.2 and below, and TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28828|2024-09-16T18:54:24.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 18:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41558|2024-09-16T18:14:31.299Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analyst
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41558</link>
      <description>The Visualizations component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Server, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions 11.4.4 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions 11.5.0, 11.6.0, 11.7.0, 11.8.0, 12.0.0, and 12.0.1, TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: version 12.1.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions 12.1.0 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions 11.4.4 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions 11.5.0, 11.6.0, 11.7.0, 11.8.0, 12.0.0, and 12.0.1, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: version 12.1.0, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 11.4.8 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 11.5.0, 11.6.0, 11.6.1, 11.6.2, 11.6.3, 11.7.0, 11.8.0, 11.8.1, 12.0.0, and 12.0.1, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: version 12.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41558|2024-09-16T18:14:31.299Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 18:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5428|2024-09-16T17:48:24.850Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20virtualization
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5428</link>
      <description>The version control adapters component of TIBCO Data Virtualization (formerly known as Cisco Information Server) contains vulnerabilities that may allow for arbitrary command execution. Affected releases are TIBCO Data Virtualization: 7.0.5; 7.0.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5428|2024-09-16T17:48:24.850Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12411|2024-09-16T18:03:18.833Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activespaces%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12411</link>
      <description>The administrative daemon (tibdgadmind) of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition, and TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability which may allow an attacker to perform cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition: 3.3.0; 3.4.0; 3.5.0, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition: 3.0.0; 3.1.0; 3.3.0; 3.4.0; 3.5.0, and TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition: 3.0.0; 3.1.0; 3.2.0; 3.3.0; 3.4.0; 3.5.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12411|2024-09-16T18:03:18.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12410|2024-09-16T17:04:15.928Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20statistics%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12410</link>
      <description>The web server component of TIBCO Software Inc's Spotfire Statistics Services contains multiple vulnerabilities that may allow the remote execution of code. Without needing to authenticate, an attacker may be able to remotely execute code with the permissions of the system account used to run the web server component. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services versions up to and including 7.11.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12410|2024-09-16T17:04:15.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41559|2024-09-16T16:38:27.617Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20nimbus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41559</link>
      <description>The Web Client component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Nimbus contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to exploit an open redirect on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Nimbus: version 10.5.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41559|2024-09-16T16:38:27.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 01:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28827|2024-09-16T16:32:29.141Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20administrator%20-%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28827</link>
      <description>The Administration GUI component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux, TIBCO Runtime Agent, TIBCO Runtime Agent, TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux, and TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker to social engineer a legitimate user with network access to execute a Stored XSS attack targeting the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Runtime Agent: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Runtime Agent: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux: versions 5.10.2 and below, and TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28827|2024-09-16T16:32:29.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 18:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22777|2024-09-16T16:49:14.776Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20businessconnect%20trading%20community%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22777</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management contains easily exploitable Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management: versions 6.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22777|2024-09-16T16:49:14.776Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27148|2024-09-16T16:22:54.482Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx%20add-ons
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27148</link>
      <description>The TIBCO EBX Add-on for Oracle Hyperion EPM, TIBCO EBX Data Exchange Add-on, and TIBCO EBX Insight Add-on components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute an XML External Entity (XXE) attack. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions 4.4.2 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27148|2024-09-16T16:22:54.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 18:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43046|2024-09-16T18:54:31.908Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20partnerexpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43046</link>
      <description>The Interior Server and Gateway Server components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress contain an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to obtain session tokens for the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress: versions 6.2.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43046|2024-09-16T18:54:31.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 17:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11206|2024-09-16T18:13:40.717Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11206</link>
      <description>The Spotfire library component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains vulnerabilities that theoretically allow a malicious user to undermine the integrity of comments and bookmarks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions up to and including 10.2.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions up to and including 7.11.2; 7.12.0; 7.13.0; 7.14.0; 10.0.0; 10.0.1; 10.1.0; and 10.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11206|2024-09-16T18:13:40.717Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 19:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5528|2024-09-16T16:58:24.595Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5528</link>
      <description>Multiple JasperReports Server components contain vulnerabilities which may allow authorized users to perform cross-site scripting (XSS) and cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks.  The impact of this vulnerability includes the theoretical disclosure of sensitive information.  Affects TIBCO JasperReports Server (versions 6.1.1 and below, 6.2.0, 6.2.1, and 6.3.0), TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition (versions 6.3.0 and below), TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM (versions 6.2.0 and below), TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy (versions 6.2.0 and below), and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS (versions 6.2.0 and below).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5528|2024-09-16T16:58:24.595Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5530|2024-09-16T17:39:02.481Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibbr%20community
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5530</link>
      <description>The tibbr web server components of tibbr Community, and tibbr Enterprise contain SAML protocol handling errors which may allow authorized users to impersonate other users, and therefore escalate their access privileges. Affected releases are tibbr Community 5.2.1 and below; 6.0.0; 6.0.1; 7.0.0, tibbr Enterprise 5.2.1 and below; 6.0.0; 6.0.1; 7.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5530|2024-09-16T17:39:02.481Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22778|2024-09-16T18:24:03.196Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20businessconnect%20trading%20community%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22778</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management: versions 6.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22778|2024-09-16T18:24:03.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 17:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30573|2024-09-16T16:48:53.136Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30573</link>
      <description>The ftlserver component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a privilege escalation on the affected ftlserver. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.8.0, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.0.1 through 6.8.0, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.7.3, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: version 6.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30573|2024-09-16T16:48:53.136Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 17:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9415|2024-09-16T17:04:04.831Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20virtualization
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9415</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Data Virtualization Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a malicious authenticated user to download any arbitrary file from the affected system. The user must be authenticated and have privileges required to monitor the server in an operational capacity. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization: versions 7.0.8 and below, versions 8.0.0, 8.1.0, 8.1.1, and 8.2.0 and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.2.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9415|2024-09-16T17:04:04.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 18:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30570|2024-09-16T18:18:20.062Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20virtualization
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30570</link>
      <description>The Column Based Security component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to obtain read access to application information on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization: versions 8.5.2 and below and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.5.2 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30570|2024-09-16T18:18:20.062Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 17:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18815|2024-09-16T16:12:36.076Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18815</link>
      <description>The REST API component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows unauthenticated users to bypass authorization checks for portions of the HTTP interface to the JasperReports Server. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.3; 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 7.1.0, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 7.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18815|2024-09-16T16:12:36.076Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28823|2024-09-16T18:08:48.731Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20eftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28823</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28823|2024-09-16T18:08:48.731Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 20:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35495|2024-09-16T18:12:56.880Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35495</link>
      <description>The Scheduler Connection component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker with network access to obtain FTP server passwords for other users of the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.2.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.5.0 and 7.5.1, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.8.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.9.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 7.8.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.9.0 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 7.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35495|2024-09-16T18:12:56.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 17:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30575|2024-09-16T17:29:00.246Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20science%20-%20workbench
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30575</link>
      <description>The Web Console component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science - Workbench, TIBCO Statistica, TIBCO Statistica - Estore Edition, and TIBCO Statistica Trial contains easily exploitable Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow a low privileged attacker with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science - Workbench: versions 14.0.0 and below, TIBCO Statistica: versions 14.0.0 and below, TIBCO Statistica - Estore Edition: versions 14.0.0 and below, and TIBCO Statistica Trial: versions 14.0.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30575|2024-09-16T17:29:00.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 17:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17334|2024-09-16T18:39:10.409Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analyst
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17334</link>
      <description>The Visualizations component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, and TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an attacker with permission to write DXP files to the Spotfire library to remotely execute code of their choice on the user account of other users who access the affected system. This attack is a risk only when the attacker has write access to a network file system shared with the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions 7.11.1 and below, versions 7.12.0, 7.13.0, 7.14.0, 10.0.0, 10.1.0, 10.2.0, 10.3.0, 10.3.1, and 10.3.2, versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, and 10.6.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: version 10.6.0, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit: versions 7.11.1 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions 7.11.1 and below, versions 7.12.0, 7.13.0, 7.14.0, 10.0.0, 10.1.0, 10.2.0, 10.3.0, 10.3.1, and 10.3.2, versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, and 10.6.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs: versions 7.11.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17334|2024-09-16T18:39:10.409Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 20:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28824|2024-09-16T17:08:34.597Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activespaces%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28824</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition, and TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition: versions 4.5.0 and below, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition: versions 4.5.0 and below, and TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition: versions 4.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28824|2024-09-16T17:08:34.597Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 20:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35500|2024-09-16T16:18:36.002Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20virtualization
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35500</link>
      <description>The Data Virtualization Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization, TIBCO Data Virtualization, TIBCO Data Virtualization, and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with local access to download arbitrary files outside of the scope of the user's permissions on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization: versions 8.3.0 and below, TIBCO Data Virtualization: version 8.4.0, TIBCO Data Virtualization: version 8.5.0, and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35500|2024-09-16T16:18:36.002Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 18:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30574|2024-09-16T18:49:54.765Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30574</link>
      <description>The ftlserver component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with local access to obtain user credentials to the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.8.0, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.0.1 through 6.8.0, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.7.3, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: version 6.8.0, TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.8.0, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.0.1 through 6.8.0, TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.7.3, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition: version 6.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30574|2024-09-16T18:49:54.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 17:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8987|2024-09-16T16:22:55.424Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20science%20for%20aws
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8987</link>
      <description>The application server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science for AWS, and TIBCO Spotfire Data Science contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that theoretically allows an authenticated user to gain access to all the capabilities of the web interface available to more privileged users. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Data Science: versions up to and including 6.4.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8987|2024-09-16T16:22:55.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 17:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35498|2024-09-16T17:32:55.642Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35498</link>
      <description>The TIBCO EBX Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX, TIBCO EBX, TIBCO EBX, and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX contains a vulnerability that under certain specific conditions allows an attacker to enter a password other than the legitimate password and it will be accepted as valid. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions 5.8.123 and below, TIBCO EBX: versions 5.9.3, 5.9.4, 5.9.5, 5.9.6, 5.9.7, 5.9.8, 5.9.9, 5.9.10, 5.9.11, 5.9.12, 5.9.13, and 5.9.14, TIBCO EBX: versions 6.0.0 and 6.0.1, and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX: version 1.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35498|2024-09-16T17:32:55.642Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 16:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23272|2024-09-16T17:38:34.192Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20bpm%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23272</link>
      <description>The Application Development Clients component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BPM Enterprise and TIBCO BPM Enterprise Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) attack on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BPM Enterprise: versions 4.3.0 and below and TIBCO BPM Enterprise Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 4.3.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23272|2024-09-16T17:38:34.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 18:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8990|2024-09-16T17:03:00.302Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activematrix%20businessworks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8990</link>
      <description>The HTTP Connector component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows unauthenticated HTTP requests to be processed by the BusinessWorks engine even when authentication is required. This possibility is restricted to circumstances where HTTP "Basic Authentication" policy is used in conjunction with an XML Authentication resource. The BusinessWorks engine might instead use credentials from a prior HTTP request for authorization purposes. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks: versions up to and including 6.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8990|2024-09-16T17:03:00.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 17:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11204|2024-09-16T17:53:03.664Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20statistics%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11204</link>
      <description>The web interface component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services contains a vulnerability that might theoretically allow an authenticated user to access sensitive information needed by the Spotfire Statistics Services server. The sensitive information that might be affected includes database, JMX, LDAP, Windows service account, and user credentials. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services: versions up to and including 7.11.1; 10.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11204|2024-09-16T17:53:03.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 19:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8991|2024-09-16T18:39:49.437Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activematrix%20bpm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8991</link>
      <description>The administrator web interface of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Policy Director, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Bus, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Grid, TIBCO Silver Fabric Enabler for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO Silver Fabric Enabler for ActiveMatrix Service Grid contains multiple vulnerabilities that may allow for cross-site scripting (XSS) and cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 4.2.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions up to and including 4.2.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Policy Director: versions up to and including 1.1.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Bus: versions up to and including 3.3.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Grid: versions up to and including 3.3.1, TIBCO Silver Fabric Enabler for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 1.4.1, and TIBCO Silver Fabric Enabler for ActiveMatrix Service Grid: versions up to and including 1.3.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8991|2024-09-16T18:39:49.437Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 20:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
