<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 02:30:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35500|2024-08-04T00:40:46.397Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20virtualization
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35500</link>
      <description>The Data Virtualization Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization, TIBCO Data Virtualization, TIBCO Data Virtualization, and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with local access to download arbitrary files outside of the scope of the user's permissions on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization: versions 8.3.0 and below, TIBCO Data Virtualization: version 8.4.0, TIBCO Data Virtualization: version 8.5.0, and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35500|2024-08-04T00:40:46.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35495|2024-08-04T00:40:46.345Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35495</link>
      <description>The Scheduler Connection component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker with network access to obtain FTP server passwords for other users of the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.2.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.5.0 and 7.5.1, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.8.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.9.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 7.8.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.9.0 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 7.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35495|2024-08-04T00:40:46.345Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35499|2024-08-04T00:40:46.808Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20nimbus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35499</link>
      <description>The Web Reporting component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Nimbus contains easily exploitable Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow a low privileged attacker to social engineer a legitimate user with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Nimbus: versions 10.4.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35499|2024-08-04T00:40:46.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35494|2024-08-04T00:40:46.445Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35494</link>
      <description>The Rest API component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contain a race condition that allows a low privileged authenticated attacker via the REST API to obtain read access to temporary objects created by other users on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.2.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.5.0 and 7.5.1, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.8.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.9.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 7.8.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.9.0 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 7.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35494|2024-08-04T00:40:46.445Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35493|2024-08-04T00:40:46.614Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20webfocus%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35493</link>
      <description>The WebFOCUS Reporting Server and WebFOCUS Client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO WebFOCUS Client, TIBCO WebFOCUS Installer, and TIBCO WebFOCUS Reporting Server contain easily exploitable Stored and Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow a low privileged attacker to social engineer a legitimate user with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO WebFOCUS Client: versions 8207.27.0 and below, TIBCO WebFOCUS Installer: versions 8207.27.0 and below, and TIBCO WebFOCUS Reporting Server: versions 8207.27.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35493|2024-08-04T00:40:46.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35496|2024-08-04T00:40:46.364Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35496</link>
      <description>The XMLA Connections component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to interfere with XML processing in the affected component. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.2.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.5.0 and 7.5.1, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.8.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.9.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 7.8.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.9.0 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 7.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35496|2024-08-04T00:40:46.364Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35498|2024-08-04T00:40:46.830Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35498</link>
      <description>The TIBCO EBX Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX, TIBCO EBX, TIBCO EBX, and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX contains a vulnerability that under certain specific conditions allows an attacker to enter a password other than the legitimate password and it will be accepted as valid. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions 5.8.123 and below, TIBCO EBX: versions 5.9.3, 5.9.4, 5.9.5, 5.9.6, 5.9.7, 5.9.8, 5.9.9, 5.9.10, 5.9.11, 5.9.12, 5.9.13, and 5.9.14, TIBCO EBX: versions 6.0.0 and 6.0.1, and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX: version 1.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35498|2024-08-04T00:40:46.830Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35497|2024-08-04T00:40:47.272Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activespaces%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35497</link>
      <description>The FTL Server (tibftlserver) and Docker images containing tibftlserver components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows a non-administrative, authenticated FTL user to trick the affected components into creating illegitimate certificates. These maliciously generated certificates can be used to enable man-in-the-middle attacks or to escalate privileges so that the malicious user has administrative privileges. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition: versions 4.3.0, 4.4.0, 4.5.0, 4.6.0, 4.6.1, and 4.6.2, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition: versions 4.3.0, 4.4.0, 4.5.0, 4.6.0, 4.6.1, and 4.6.2, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition: versions 4.3.0, 4.4.0, 4.5.0, 4.6.0, 4.6.1, and 4.6.2, TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.2.0, 6.3.0, 6.3.1, 6.4.0, 6.5.0, 6.6.0, 6.6.1, and 6.7.0, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.2.0, 6.3.0, 6.3.1, 6.4.0, 6.5.0, 6.6.0, 6.6.1, and 6.7.0, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.2.0, 6.3.0, 6.3.1, 6.4.0, 6.5.0, 6.6.0, 6.6.1, and 6.7.0, TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition: versions 6.2.0, 6.3.0, 6.3.1, 6.4.0, 6.5.0, 6.6.0, 6.6.1, and 6.7.0, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.2.0, 6.3.0, 6.3.1, 6.4.0, 6.5.0, 6.6.0, 6.6.1, and 6.7.0, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.2.0, 6.3.0, 6.3.1, 6.4.0, 6.5.0, 6.6.0, 6.6.1, and 6.7.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35497|2024-08-04T00:40:47.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1138|2024-08-01T18:26:30.563Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1138</link>
      <description>The FTL Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a privilege escalation on the affected ftlserver. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.10.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1138|2024-08-01T18:26:30.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 17:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1137|2024-08-01T18:26:30.510Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activespaces%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1137</link>
      <description>The Proxy and Client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows an Active Spaces client to passively observe data traffic to other clients. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition: versions 4.4.0 through 4.9.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1137|2024-08-01T18:26:30.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 17:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1138|2024-03-12T17:30:15.100Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1138</link>
      <description>The FTL Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a privilege escalation on the affected ftlserver. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.10.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1138|2024-03-12T17:30:15.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 17:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1137|2024-06-04T18:00:30.306Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activespaces%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1137</link>
      <description>The Proxy and Client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows an Active Spaces client to passively observe data traffic to other clients. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition: versions 4.4.0 through 4.9.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1137|2024-06-04T18:00:30.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 17:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
