<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 17:22:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41559|2024-09-16T16:38:27.617Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20nimbus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41559</link>
      <description>The Web Client component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Nimbus contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to exploit an open redirect on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Nimbus: version 10.5.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41559|2024-09-16T16:38:27.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 01:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28827|2024-09-16T16:32:29.141Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20administrator%20-%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28827</link>
      <description>The Administration GUI component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux, TIBCO Runtime Agent, TIBCO Runtime Agent, TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux, and TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker to social engineer a legitimate user with network access to execute a Stored XSS attack targeting the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Runtime Agent: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Runtime Agent: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux: versions 5.10.2 and below, and TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28827|2024-09-16T16:32:29.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 18:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22777|2024-09-16T16:49:14.776Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20businessconnect%20trading%20community%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22777</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management contains easily exploitable Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management: versions 6.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22777|2024-09-16T16:49:14.776Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27148|2024-09-16T16:22:54.482Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx%20add-ons
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27148</link>
      <description>The TIBCO EBX Add-on for Oracle Hyperion EPM, TIBCO EBX Data Exchange Add-on, and TIBCO EBX Insight Add-on components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute an XML External Entity (XXE) attack. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions 4.4.2 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27148|2024-09-16T16:22:54.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 18:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5528|2024-09-16T16:58:24.595Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5528</link>
      <description>Multiple JasperReports Server components contain vulnerabilities which may allow authorized users to perform cross-site scripting (XSS) and cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks.  The impact of this vulnerability includes the theoretical disclosure of sensitive information.  Affects TIBCO JasperReports Server (versions 6.1.1 and below, 6.2.0, 6.2.1, and 6.3.0), TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition (versions 6.3.0 and below), TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM (versions 6.2.0 and below), TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy (versions 6.2.0 and below), and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS (versions 6.2.0 and below).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5528|2024-09-16T16:58:24.595Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30573|2024-09-16T16:48:53.136Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30573</link>
      <description>The ftlserver component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a privilege escalation on the affected ftlserver. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.8.0, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.0.1 through 6.8.0, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.7.3, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: version 6.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30573|2024-09-16T16:48:53.136Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 17:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18815|2024-09-16T16:12:36.076Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18815</link>
      <description>The REST API component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows unauthenticated users to bypass authorization checks for portions of the HTTP interface to the JasperReports Server. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.3; 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 7.1.0, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 7.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18815|2024-09-16T16:12:36.076Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35500|2024-09-16T16:18:36.002Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20virtualization
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35500</link>
      <description>The Data Virtualization Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization, TIBCO Data Virtualization, TIBCO Data Virtualization, and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with local access to download arbitrary files outside of the scope of the user's permissions on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization: versions 8.3.0 and below, TIBCO Data Virtualization: version 8.4.0, TIBCO Data Virtualization: version 8.5.0, and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35500|2024-09-16T16:18:36.002Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 18:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8987|2024-09-16T16:22:55.424Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20science%20for%20aws
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8987</link>
      <description>The application server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science for AWS, and TIBCO Spotfire Data Science contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that theoretically allows an authenticated user to gain access to all the capabilities of the web interface available to more privileged users. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Data Science: versions up to and including 6.4.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8987|2024-09-16T16:22:55.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 17:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
