<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:24:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17333|2024-09-17T03:52:40.294Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17333</link>
      <description>The Web server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows authenticated users to perform stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions 5.8.1.fixS and below, versions 5.9.3, 5.9.4, 5.9.5, 5.9.6, and 5.9.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17333|2024-09-17T03:52:40.294Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 18:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5536|2024-09-17T03:38:41.007Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20datasynapse%20gridserver%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5536</link>
      <description>The GridServer Broker, and GridServer Director components of TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO DataSynapse GridServer Manager contain vulnerabilities which may allow an authenticated user to perform cross-site scripting (XSS). In addition, an authenticated user could be a victim of a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack. Affected releases include TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO DataSynapse GridServer Manager: versions up to and including 5.1.3; 6.0.0; 6.0.1; 6.0.2; 6.1.0; 6.1.1; and 6.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5536|2024-09-17T03:38:41.007Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11205|2024-09-17T00:05:43.567Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11205</link>
      <description>The web server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains vulnerabilities that theoretically allow reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: 7.14.0; 7.14.1; 10.0.0; 10.0.1; 10.1.0; 10.2.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: 7.14.0; 10.0.0; 10.0.1; 10.1.0; 10.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11205|2024-09-17T00:05:43.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 19:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18810|2024-09-17T01:32:00.588Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20managed%20file%20transfer%20command%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18810</link>
      <description>The Administrator Service component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center, and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server contains vulnerabilities where an authenticated user with specific privileges can gain access to credentials to other systems. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center: versions up to and including 7.3.2; 8.0.0; 8.0.1; 8.0.2; 8.1.0, and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server: versions up to and including 7.3.2; 8.0.0; 8.0.1; 8.0.2; 8.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18810|2024-09-17T01:32:00.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35496|2024-09-17T03:43:38.702Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35496</link>
      <description>The XMLA Connections component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to interfere with XML processing in the affected component. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.2.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.5.0 and 7.5.1, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.8.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.9.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 7.8.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.9.0 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 7.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35496|2024-09-17T03:43:38.702Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 17:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11211|2024-09-17T03:34:08.098Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20enterprise%20runtime%20for%20r%20-%20server%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11211</link>
      <description>The server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition, and TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an authenticated user to trigger remote code execution in certain circumstances. When the affected component runs with the containerized TERR service on Linux the host can theoretically be tricked into running malicious code. This issue affects: TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition version 1.2.0 and below, and TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace 10.4.0; 10.5.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11211|2024-09-17T03:34:08.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 22:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8986|2024-09-17T03:37:40.244Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8986</link>
      <description>The SOAP API component vulnerability of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM contains a vulnerability that may allow a malicious authenticated user to copy text files from the host operating system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.3.4; 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.3, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8986|2024-09-17T03:37:40.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30576|2024-09-17T00:40:59.946Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20science%20-%20workbench
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30576</link>
      <description>The Web Console component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science - Workbench, TIBCO Statistica, TIBCO Statistica - Estore Edition, and TIBCO Statistica Trial contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science - Workbench: versions 14.0.0 and below, TIBCO Statistica: versions 14.0.0 and below, TIBCO Statistica - Estore Edition: versions 14.0.0 and below, and TIBCO Statistica Trial: versions 14.0.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30576|2024-09-17T00:40:59.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 17:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12412|2024-09-17T02:06:27.359Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12412</link>
      <description>The realm server (tibrealmserver) component of TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability which may allow an attacker to perform cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions up to and including 5.4.0, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions up to and including 5.4.0, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions up to and including 5.4.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12412|2024-09-17T02:06:27.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28820|2024-09-17T03:18:44.039Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28820</link>
      <description>The FTL Server (tibftlserver), FTL C API, FTL Golang API, FTL Java API, and FTL .Net API components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from the affected component searching for run-time artifacts outside of the installation hierarchy. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28820|2024-09-17T03:18:44.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 20:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18814|2024-09-17T01:20:31.366Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18814</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Spotfire authentication component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains a vulnerability in the handling of the authentication that theoretically may allow an attacker to gain full access to a target account, independent of configured authentication mechanisms. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions up to and including 10.0.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions up to and including 7.10.1; 7.11.0; 7.11.1; 7.12.0; 7.13.0; 7.14.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18814|2024-09-17T01:20:31.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5437|2024-09-17T01:25:43.883Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analyst
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5437</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Spotfire Client and TIBCO Spotfire Web Player Client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, and TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs contain multiple vulnerabilities that may allow for unauthorized information disclosure. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0; 7.9.1; 7.10.0; 7.10.1; 7.11.0; 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions up to and including 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0;7.9.1;7.10.0;7.10.1;7.11.0; 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0; 7.9.1; 7.10.0; 7.10.1; 7.11.0;7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0; 7.9.1; 7.10.0; 7.10.1; 7.11.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5437|2024-09-17T01:25:43.883Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28822|2024-09-17T03:47:42.618Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20enterprise%20message%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28822</link>
      <description>The Enterprise Message Service Server (tibemsd), Enterprise Message Service Central Administration (tibemsca), Enterprise Message Service JSON configuration generator (tibemsconf2json), and Enterprise Message Service C API components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Message Service, TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Community Edition, and TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Developer Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from the affected component searching for run-time artifacts outside of the installation hierarchy. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Message Service: versions 8.5.1 and below, TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Community Edition: versions 8.5.1 and below, and TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Developer Edition: versions 8.5.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28822|2024-09-17T03:47:42.618Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 20:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35499|2024-09-17T01:27:09.136Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20nimbus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35499</link>
      <description>The Web Reporting component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Nimbus contains easily exploitable Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow a low privileged attacker to social engineer a legitimate user with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Nimbus: versions 10.4.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35499|2024-09-17T01:27:09.136Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 16:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17339|2024-09-17T00:45:44.564Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20silver%20fabric
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17339</link>
      <description>The VirtualRouter component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Silver Fabric contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an attacker to inject scripts via URLs. The attacker could theoretically social engineer an authenticated user into submitting the URL, thus executing the script on the affected system with the privileges of the user. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 6.0.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17339|2024-09-17T00:45:44.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 19:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43048|2024-09-17T03:27:29.314Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20partnerexpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43048</link>
      <description>The Interior Server and Gateway Server components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute a clickjacking attack on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability does not require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress: versions 6.2.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43048|2024-09-17T03:27:29.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 17:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5433|2024-09-17T01:26:56.135Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20administrator%20-%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5433</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Administrator server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, and TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux contains vulnerabilities wherein a malicious user could perform XML external entity expansion (XXE) attacks to disclose host machine information. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions up to and including 5.10.0, and TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions up to and including 5.9.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5433|2024-09-17T01:26:56.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5429|2024-09-17T00:32:19.534Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5429</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the report scripting component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO JasperReports Library, TIBCO JasperReports Library Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio Community Edition, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio for ActiveMatrix BPM may allow analytic reports that contain scripting to perform arbitrary code execution. Affected releases include TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2;6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Library: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2; 6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Library Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2; 6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5429|2024-09-17T00:32:19.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5529|2024-09-17T02:52:33.674Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20library%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5529</link>
      <description>JasperReports library components contain an information disclosure vulnerability. This vulnerability includes the theoretical disclosure of any accessible information from the host file system. Affects TIBCO JasperReports Library Community Edition (versions 6.4.0 and below), TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM (versions 6.2.0 and below), TIBCO JasperReports Professional (versions 6.2.1 and below, and 6.3.0), TIBCO JasperReports Server (versions 6.1.1 and below, 6.2.0, 6.2.1, 6.3.0), TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition (versions 6.3.0 and below), TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM (versions 6.2.0 and below), TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy (versions 6.3.0 and below), TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS (versions 6.3.0 and below), and TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio for ActiveMatrix BPM (versions 6.2.0 and below).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5529|2024-09-17T02:52:33.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22771|2024-09-17T02:57:15.084Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20library
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22771</link>
      <description>The Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Library, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains a directory-traversal vulnerability that may theoretically allow web server users to access contents of the host system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Library: version 7.9.0, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM: version 7.9.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.9.0 and 7.9.1, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.9.0 and 7.9.1, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.9.0 and 7.9.1, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 7.9.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22771|2024-09-17T02:57:15.084Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 17:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35493|2024-09-17T03:14:29.776Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20webfocus%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35493</link>
      <description>The WebFOCUS Reporting Server and WebFOCUS Client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO WebFOCUS Client, TIBCO WebFOCUS Installer, and TIBCO WebFOCUS Reporting Server contain easily exploitable Stored and Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow a low privileged attacker to social engineer a legitimate user with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO WebFOCUS Client: versions 8207.27.0 and below, TIBCO WebFOCUS Installer: versions 8207.27.0 and below, and TIBCO WebFOCUS Reporting Server: versions 8207.27.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35493|2024-09-17T03:14:29.776Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 17:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12413|2024-09-17T00:11:42.949Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20messaging%20-%20apache%20kafka%20distribution%20-%20schema%20repository%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12413</link>
      <description>The Schema repository server (tibschemad) component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Messaging - Apache Kafka Distribution - Schema Repository - Community Edition, and TIBCO Messaging - Apache Kafka Distribution - Schema Repository - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability which may allow an attacker to perform cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO Messaging - Apache Kafka Distribution - Schema Repository - Community Edition: 1.0.0, and TIBCO Messaging - Apache Kafka Distribution - Schema Repository - Enterprise Edition: 1.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12413|2024-09-17T00:11:42.949Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8988|2024-09-17T00:26:21.220Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20science%20for%20aws
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8988</link>
      <description>The application server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science for AWS, and TIBCO Spotfire Data Science contains a persistent cross-site contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a user to escalate their privileges on the affected system, in a way that may allow for data modifications and deletions that should be denied. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Data Science: versions up to and including 6.4.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8988|2024-09-17T00:26:21.220Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 17:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5432|2024-09-17T02:05:57.067Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20administrator%20-%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5432</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Administrator server component of of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, and TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux contains multiple vulnerabilities wherein a malicious user could theoretically perform cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks by way of manipulating artifacts prior to uploading them. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions up to and including 5.10.0, and TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions up to and including 5.9.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5432|2024-09-17T02:05:57.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8992|2024-09-17T03:23:24.223Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activematrix%20bpm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8992</link>
      <description>The administrative server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Policy Director, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Bus, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Grid, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Grid Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO Silver Fabric Enabler for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO Silver Fabric Enabler for ActiveMatrix Service Grid contains a vulnerability wherein a user without privileges to upload distributed application archives ("Upload DAA" permission) can theoretically upload arbitrary code, and in some circumstances then execute that code on ActiveMatrix Service Grid nodes. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 4.2.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions up to and including 4.2.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Policy Director: versions up to and including 1.1.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Bus: versions up to and including 3.3.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Grid: versions up to and including 3.3.1, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Grid Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions up to and including 3.3.0, TIBCO Silver Fabric Enabler for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 1.4.1, and TIBCO Silver Fabric Enabler for ActiveMatrix Service Grid: versions up to and including 1.3.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8992|2024-09-17T03:23:24.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 20:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9413|2024-09-17T01:07:05.625Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20managed%20file%20transfer%20command%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9413</link>
      <description>The MFT Browser file transfer client and MFT Browser admin client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows an attacker to craft an URL that will execute arbitrary commands on the affected system. If the attacker convinces an authenticated user with a currently active session to enter or click on the URL the commands will be executed on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center: versions 8.2.1 and below and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server: versions 8.2.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9413|2024-09-17T01:07:05.625Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 19:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5436|2024-09-17T01:26:22.747Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5436</link>
      <description>The Spotfire server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contain multiple vulnerabilities that may allow for the disclosure of information, including user and data source credentials. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions up to and including 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions up to and including 7.8.1; 7.9.0; 7.10.0; 7.11.0; 7.12.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5436|2024-09-17T01:26:22.747Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17331|2024-09-17T00:11:11.551Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx%20add-ons
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17331</link>
      <description>The Data Exchange Web Interface component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows authenticated users to perform stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions up to and including 3.20.13, version 4.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17331|2024-09-17T00:11:11.551Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 19:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17338|2024-09-17T01:36:54.758Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20patterns%20-%20search
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17338</link>
      <description>The user interface component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Patterns - Search contains multiple vulnerabilities that theoretically allow authenticated users to perform persistent cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Patterns - Search: versions 5.4.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17338|2024-09-17T01:36:54.758Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 18:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18812|2024-09-17T01:46:57.774Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18812</link>
      <description>The Spotfire Library component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains a vulnerability that might theoretically fail to restrict users with read-only access from modifying files stored in the Spotfire Library, only when the Spotfire Library is configured to use external storage. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace versions up to and including 10.0.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Server versions up to and including 7.10.1; 7.11.0; 7.11.1; 7.12.0; 7.13.0; 7.14.0; 10.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18812|2024-09-17T01:46:57.774Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17336|2024-09-17T02:06:23.402Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17336</link>
      <description>The Data access layer component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains multiple vulnerabilities that theoretically allow an attacker access to information that can lead to obtaining credentials used to access Spotfire data sources. The attacker would need privileges to save a Spotfire file to the library, and only applies in a situation where NTLM credentials, or a credentials profile is in use. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: version 10.6.0 and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 7.11.7 and below, versions 7.12.0, 7.13.0, 7.14.0, 10.0.0, 10.0.1, 10.1.0, 10.2.0, 10.2.1, 10.3.0, 10.3.1, 10.3.2, 10.3.3, and 10.3.4, versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, and 10.6.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17336|2024-09-17T02:06:23.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 20:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9414|2024-09-17T01:41:47.701Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20managed%20file%20transfer%20command%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9414</link>
      <description>The MFT admin service component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an authenticated user with specific permissions to obtain the session identifier of another user. The session identifier when replayed could provide administrative rights or file transfer permissions to the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center: versions 8.2.1 and below and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server: versions 8.2.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9414|2024-09-17T01:41:47.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 19:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30572|2024-09-17T02:47:18.987Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20iway%20service%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30572</link>
      <description>The iWay Service Manager Console component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO iWay Service Manager contains an easily exploitable Directory Traversal vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to read arbitrary resources on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO iWay Service Manager: versions 8.0.6 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30572|2024-09-17T02:47:18.987Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 16:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11207|2024-09-17T02:00:41.276Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20loglogic%20enterprise%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11207</link>
      <description>The web server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO LogLogic Enterprise Virtual Appliance, and TIBCO LogLogic Log Management Intelligence contains multiple vulnerabilities that theoretically allow persistent and reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks, as well as cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks. This issue affects: TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO LogLogic Enterprise Virtual Appliance version 6.2.1 and prior versions. TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO LogLogic Log Management Intelligence 6.2.1. TIBCO LogLogic LX825 Appliance 0.0.004, TIBCO LogLogic LX1025 Appliance 0.0.004, TIBCO LogLogic LX4025 Appliance 0.0.004, TIBCO LogLogic MX3025 Appliance 0.0.004, TIBCO LogLogic MX4025 Appliance 0.0.004, TIBCO LogLogic ST1025 Appliance 0.0.004, TIBCO LogLogic ST2025-SAN Appliance 0.0.004, and TIBCO LogLogic ST4025 Appliance 0.0.004 using TIBCO LogLogic Log Management Intelligence versions 6.2.1 and below. TIBCO LogLogic LX1035 Appliance 0.0.005, TIBCO LogLogic LX1025R1 Appliance 0.0.004, TIBCO LogLogic LX1025R2 Appliance 0.0.004, TIBCO LogLogic LX4025R1 Appliance 0.0.004, TIBCO LogLogic LX4025R2 Appliance 0.0.004, TIBCO LogLogic LX4035 Appliance 0.0.005, TIBCO LogLogic ST2025-SANR1 Appliance 0.0.004, TIBCO LogLogic ST2025-SANR2 Appliance 0.0.004, TIBCO LogLogic ST2035-SAN Appliance 0.0.005, TIBCO LogLogic ST4025R1 Appliance 0.0.004, TIBCO LogLogic ST4025R2 Appliance 0.0.004, and TIBCO LogLogic ST4035 Appliance 0.0.005 using TIBCO LogLogic Log Management Intelligence versions 6.2.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11207|2024-09-17T02:00:41.276Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 20:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9412|2024-09-17T00:35:28.475Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20managed%20file%20transfer%20platform%20server%20for%20ibm%20i
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9412</link>
      <description>The file transfer component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for IBM i contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows execution of arbitrary commands at the privilege level of the affected system following a failed file transfer. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for IBM i: versions 7.1.0 and below, version 8.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9412|2024-09-17T00:35:28.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 17:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43052|2024-09-17T00:10:54.268Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43052</link>
      <description>The Realm Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows authentication bypass due to a hard coded secret used in the default realm server of the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43052|2024-09-17T00:10:54.268Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 18:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9417|2024-09-17T03:02:27.461Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20foresight%20archive%20and%20retrieval%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9417</link>
      <description>The Transaction Insight reporting component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Foresight Archive and Retrieval System, TIBCO Foresight Archive and Retrieval System Healthcare Edition, TIBCO Foresight Operational Monitor, TIBCO Foresight Operational Monitor Healthcare Edition, TIBCO Foresight Transaction Insight, and TIBCO Foresight Transaction Insight Healthcare Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an authenticated attacker to perform SQL injection. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Foresight Archive and Retrieval System: versions 5.1.0 and below, version 5.2.0, TIBCO Foresight Archive and Retrieval System Healthcare Edition: versions 5.1.0 and below, version 5.2.0, TIBCO Foresight Operational Monitor: versions 5.1.0 and below, version 5.2.0, TIBCO Foresight Operational Monitor Healthcare Edition: versions 5.1.0 and below, version 5.2.0, TIBCO Foresight Transaction Insight: versions 5.1.0 and below, version 5.2.0, and TIBCO Foresight Transaction Insight Healthcare Edition: versions 5.1.0 and below, version 5.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9417|2024-09-17T03:02:27.461Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 21:13:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43050|2024-09-17T00:06:19.636Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20businessconnect%20container%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43050</link>
      <description>The Auth Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Container Edition contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with local access to obtain administrative usernames and passwords for the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Container Edition: versions 1.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43050|2024-09-17T00:06:19.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 17:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5431|2024-09-17T01:56:35.755Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5431</link>
      <description>The domain designer component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a vulnerability which may allow, in the context of a non-default permissions configuration, persisted cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases include TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2; 6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5431|2024-09-17T01:56:35.755Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27146|2024-09-17T04:08:46.251Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20iprocess%20workspace%20%28browser%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27146</link>
      <description>The Core component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO iProcess Workspace (Browser) contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute a Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from an authenticated user other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO iProcess Workspace (Browser): versions 11.6.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27146|2024-09-17T04:08:46.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 17:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41561|2024-09-17T02:05:41.937Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41561</link>
      <description>The JNDI Data Sources component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a privileged/administrative attacker with network access to execute Remote Code Execution to obtain a reverse shell on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 8.0.2 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 8.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 8.1.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 8.1.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.0.2 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: version 8.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: versions 8.0.2 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 8.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41561|2024-09-17T02:05:41.937Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 03:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18813|2024-09-17T00:51:13.618Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18813</link>
      <description>The Spotfire web server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains multiple vulnerabilities that may allow persistent and reflected cross-site scripting attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions up to and including 10.0.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions up to and including 7.10.1; 7.11.0; 7.11.1; 7.12.0; 7.13.0; 7.14.0; 10.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18813|2024-09-17T00:51:13.618Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8989|2024-09-17T01:21:17.066Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20science%20for%20aws
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8989</link>
      <description>The application server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science for AWS, and TIBCO Spotfire Data Science contains a vulnerability that theoretically enables a user to spoof their account to look like a different user in the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Data Science: versions up to and including 6.4.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8989|2024-09-17T01:21:17.066Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 17:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35494|2024-09-17T00:51:58.556Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35494</link>
      <description>The Rest API component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contain a race condition that allows a low privileged authenticated attacker via the REST API to obtain read access to temporary objects created by other users on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.2.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.5.0 and 7.5.1, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.8.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.9.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 7.8.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.9.0 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 7.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35494|2024-09-17T00:51:58.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 17:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22769|2024-09-17T00:16:09.810Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22769</link>
      <description>The Web server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX, TIBCO EBX, TIBCO EBX, TIBCO EBX Add-ons, TIBCO EBX Add-ons, TIBCO EBX Add-ons, and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions 5.8.124 and below, TIBCO EBX: versions 5.9.3, 5.9.4, 5.9.5, 5.9.6, 5.9.7, 5.9.8, 5.9.9, 5.9.10, 5.9.11, 5.9.12, 5.9.13, 5.9.14, and 5.9.15, TIBCO EBX: versions 6.0.0, 6.0.1, 6.0.2, and 6.0.3, TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions 3.20.18 and below, TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions 4.1.0, 4.2.0, 4.2.1, 4.2.2, 4.3.0, 4.3.1, 4.3.2, 4.3.3, 4.3.4, 4.4.0, 4.4.1, 4.4.2, 4.4.3, 4.5.0, 4.5.1, 4.5.2, 4.5.3, 4.5.4, 4.5.5, and 4.5.6, TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions 5.0.0, 5.0.1, 5.1.0, 5.1.1, and 5.2.0, and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX: versions 1.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22769|2024-09-17T00:16:09.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 19:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18809|2024-09-17T00:10:56.155Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20library
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18809</link>
      <description>The default server implementation of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Library, TIBCO JasperReports Library Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a directory-traversal vulnerability that may theoretically allow web server users to access contents of the host system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Library: versions up to and including 6.3.4; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.21; 7.1.0; 7.2.0, TIBCO JasperReports Library Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.7.0, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.21, TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.3.4; 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.3; 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.3; 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 7.1.0, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 7.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18809|2024-09-17T00:10:56.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22775|2024-09-17T03:37:44.649Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20bpm%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22775</link>
      <description>The Workspace client component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BPM Enterprise and TIBCO BPM Enterprise Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric contains difficult to exploit Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow low privileged attackers with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BPM Enterprise: versions 4.3.1 and below and TIBCO BPM Enterprise Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 4.3.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22775|2024-09-17T03:37:44.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 17:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43054|2024-09-17T02:11:55.506Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20eftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43054</link>
      <description>The eFTL Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to generate API tokens that can access any other channel with arbitrary permissions. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43054|2024-09-17T02:11:55.506Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 18:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5535|2024-09-17T03:47:43.629Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20datasynapse%20gridserver%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5535</link>
      <description>The GridServer Broker, GridServer Driver, and GridServer Engine components of TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO DataSynapse GridServer Manager contain vulnerabilities related to both the improper use of encryption mechanisms and the use of weak ciphers. A malicious actor could theoretically compromise the traffic between any of the components. Affected releases include TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO DataSynapse GridServer Manager: versions up to and including 5.1.3; 6.0.0; 6.0.1; 6.0.2; 6.1.0; 6.1.1; and 6.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5535|2024-09-17T03:47:43.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28817|2024-09-17T00:51:51.446Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20rendezvous
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28817</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Rendezvous and TIBCO Rendezvous Developer Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Rendezvous: versions 8.5.1 and below and TIBCO Rendezvous Developer Edition: versions 8.5.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28817|2024-09-17T00:51:51.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 20:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43049|2024-09-17T01:40:32.611Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20businessconnect%20container%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43049</link>
      <description>The Database component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Container Edition contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to obtain the usernames and passwords of users of the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Container Edition: versions 1.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43049|2024-09-17T01:40:32.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 17:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9409|2024-09-17T01:16:13.966Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9409</link>
      <description>The administrative UI component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an unauthenticated attacker to obtain the permissions of a JasperReports Server "superuser" for the affected systems. The attacker can theoretically exploit the vulnerability consistently, remotely, and without authenticating. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.1.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.1.1 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.1.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9409|2024-09-17T01:16:13.966Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 12:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12408|2024-09-17T02:56:30.441Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activematrix%20businessworks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12408</link>
      <description>The BusinessWorks engine component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks, TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks for z/Linux, and TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric contains a vulnerability that may allow XML eXternal Entity (XXE) attacks via incoming network messages, and may disclose the contents of files accessible to a running BusinessWorks engine Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks: versions up to and including 5.13.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks for z/Linux: versions up to and including 5.13.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions up to and including 5.13.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12408|2024-09-17T02:56:30.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11208|2024-09-17T02:53:22.304Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20api%20exchange%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11208</link>
      <description>The authorization component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO API Exchange Gateway, and TIBCO API Exchange Gateway Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric contains a vulnerability that theoretically processes OAuth authorization incorrectly, leading to potential escalation of privileges for the specific customer endpoint, when the implementation uses multiple scopes. This issue affects: TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO API Exchange Gateway version 2.3.1 and prior versions, and TIBCO API Exchange Gateway Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric version 2.3.1 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11208|2024-09-17T02:53:22.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 15:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28818|2024-09-17T00:55:50.824Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20rendezvous
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28818</link>
      <description>The Rendezvous Routing Daemon (rvrd), Rendezvous Secure Routing Daemon (rvrsd), Rendezvous Secure Daemon (rvsd), Rendezvous Cache (rvcache), Rendezvous Secure C API, Rendezvous Java API, and Rendezvous .Net API components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Rendezvous and TIBCO Rendezvous Developer Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from the affected component searching for run-time artifacts outside of the installation hierarchy. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Rendezvous: versions 8.5.1 and below and TIBCO Rendezvous Developer Edition: versions 8.5.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28818|2024-09-17T00:55:50.824Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 20:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
