<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:21:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43053|2024-09-16T18:08:27.215Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43053</link>
      <description>The Realm Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to obtain the cluster secret of another application connected to the realm server. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43053|2024-09-16T18:08:27.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 18:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22774|2024-09-16T20:43:11.558Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20managed%20file%20transfer%20command%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22774</link>
      <description>The DOM XML parser and SAX XML parser components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center, TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center, TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server, and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute XML External Entity (XXE) attacks on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center: versions 8.3.1 and below, TIBCO Managed File Transfer Command Center: versions 8.4.0 and 8.4.1, TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server: versions 8.3.1 and below, and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Internet Server: versions 8.4.0 and 8.4.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22774|2024-09-16T20:43:11.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 17:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22770|2024-09-16T22:36:51.954Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20auditsafe
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22770</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO AuditSafe contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute API methods on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO AuditSafe: versions 1.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22770|2024-09-16T22:36:51.954Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 18:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11203|2024-09-16T20:28:07.150Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activematrix%20bpm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11203</link>
      <description>The workspace client, openspace client, app development client, and REST API of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, and TIBCO Silver Fabric Enabler for ActiveMatrix BPM contain cross site scripting (XSS) and cross-site request forgery vulnerabilities. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 4.2.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions up to and including 4.2.0, and TIBCO Silver Fabric Enabler for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 1.4.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11203|2024-09-16T20:28:07.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 20:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22773|2024-09-16T20:36:15.644Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22773</link>
      <description>The REST API component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains difficult to exploit Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow a low privileged attacker with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 8.0.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 8.0.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 8.0.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.0.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.9.2 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: versions 8.0.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22773|2024-09-16T20:36:15.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 17:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30571|2024-09-16T20:07:14.375Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20iway%20service%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30571</link>
      <description>The iWay Service Manager Console component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO iWay Service Manager contains easily exploitable Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow a low privileged attacker with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO iWay Service Manager: versions 8.0.6 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30571|2024-09-16T20:07:14.375Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 16:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18816|2024-09-16T17:58:45.349Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18816</link>
      <description>The repository component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a persistent cross site scripting vulnerability. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.3.4; 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.3; 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi- Tenancy versions up to and including 7.1.0, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 7.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18816|2024-09-16T17:58:45.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28828|2024-09-16T18:54:24.252Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20administrator%20-%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28828</link>
      <description>The Administration GUI component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux, and TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a SQL injection attack on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions 5.10.2 and below, and TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28828|2024-09-16T18:54:24.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 18:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11209|2024-09-16T22:50:25.564Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11209</link>
      <description>The realm configuration component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL Community Edition, TIBCO FTL Developer Edition, TIBCO FTL Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically fails to properly enforce access controls. This issue affects TIBCO FTL Community Edition 6.0.0; 6.0.1; 6.1.0, TIBCO FTL Developer Edition 6.0.1; 6.1.0, and TIBCO FTL Enterprise Edition 6.0.0; 6.0.1; 6.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11209|2024-09-16T22:50:25.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 17:23:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5534|2024-09-16T22:30:39.860Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibbr%20community
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5534</link>
      <description>The tibbr user profiles components of tibbr Community, and tibbr Enterprise expose a weakness in an improperly sandboxed third-party component. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. tibbr Community 5.2.1 and below; 6.0.0; 6.0.1; 7.0.0, tibbr Enterprise 5.2.1 and below; 6.0.0; 6.0.1; 7.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5534|2024-09-16T22:30:39.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17330|2024-09-16T20:16:20.848Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17330</link>
      <description>The Web server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX contains multiple vulnerabilities that theoretically allow authenticated users to perform stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks, and unauthenticated users to perform reflected cross-site scripting attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions up to and including 5.8.1.fixR, versions 5.9.3, 5.9.4, 5.9.5, and 5.9.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17330|2024-09-16T20:16:20.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 19:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41558|2024-09-16T18:14:31.299Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analyst
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41558</link>
      <description>The Visualizations component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Server, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions 11.4.4 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions 11.5.0, 11.6.0, 11.7.0, 11.8.0, 12.0.0, and 12.0.1, TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: version 12.1.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions 12.1.0 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions 11.4.4 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions 11.5.0, 11.6.0, 11.7.0, 11.8.0, 12.0.0, and 12.0.1, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: version 12.1.0, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 11.4.8 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 11.5.0, 11.6.0, 11.6.1, 11.6.2, 11.6.3, 11.7.0, 11.8.0, 11.8.1, 12.0.0, and 12.0.1, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: version 12.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41558|2024-09-16T18:14:31.299Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 18:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43051|2024-09-16T21:09:03.934Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43051</link>
      <description>The Spotfire Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Server, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows malicious custom API clients with network access to execute internal API operations outside of the scope of those granted to it. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 10.10.6 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 11.0.0, 11.1.0, 11.2.0, 11.3.0, 11.4.0, and 11.4.1, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 11.5.0 and 11.6.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43051|2024-09-16T21:09:03.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 19:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41563|2024-09-16T19:36:24.781Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41563</link>
      <description>The Dashboard component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 8.0.2 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 8.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 8.1.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.0.2 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: version 8.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: versions 8.0.2 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 8.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41563|2024-09-16T19:36:24.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 03:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41562|2024-09-16T22:01:43.407Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41562</link>
      <description>The HTML escaping component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a privileged/administrative attacker with network access to execute an XSS attack on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 8.0.2 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 8.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 8.1.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 8.1.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.0.2 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: version 8.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: versions 8.0.2 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 8.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41562|2024-09-16T22:01:43.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 03:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28821|2024-09-16T22:36:09.372Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20enterprise%20message%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28821</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Message Service, TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Community Edition, and TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Developer Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Message Service: versions 8.5.1 and below, TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Community Edition: versions 8.5.1 and below, and TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Developer Edition: versions 8.5.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28821|2024-09-16T22:36:09.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 20:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5428|2024-09-16T17:48:24.850Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20virtualization
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5428</link>
      <description>The version control adapters component of TIBCO Data Virtualization (formerly known as Cisco Information Server) contains vulnerabilities that may allow for arbitrary command execution. Affected releases are TIBCO Data Virtualization: 7.0.5; 7.0.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5428|2024-09-16T17:48:24.850Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12411|2024-09-16T18:03:18.833Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activespaces%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12411</link>
      <description>The administrative daemon (tibdgadmind) of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition, and TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability which may allow an attacker to perform cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition: 3.3.0; 3.4.0; 3.5.0, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition: 3.0.0; 3.1.0; 3.3.0; 3.4.0; 3.5.0, and TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition: 3.0.0; 3.1.0; 3.2.0; 3.3.0; 3.4.0; 3.5.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12411|2024-09-16T18:03:18.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23274|2024-09-16T21:58:25.614Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20api%20exchange%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23274</link>
      <description>The Config UI component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO API Exchange Gateway and TIBCO API Exchange Gateway Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute a clickjacking attack on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability does not require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO API Exchange Gateway: versions 2.3.3 and below and TIBCO API Exchange Gateway Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 2.3.3 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23274|2024-09-16T21:58:25.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 16:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5435|2024-09-16T19:51:48.227Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analyst
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5435</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Spotfire Client and TIBCO Spotfire Web Player Client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, and TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs contain multiple vulnerabilities that may allow for remote code execution. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0; 7.9.1; 7.10.0; 7.10.1; 7.11.0; 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions up to and including 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0;7.9.1;7.10.0;7.10.1;7.11.0; 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0; 7.9.1; 7.10.0; 7.10.1; 7.11.0;7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0; 7.9.1; 7.10.0; 7.10.1; 7.11.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5435|2024-09-16T19:51:48.227Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12410|2024-09-16T17:04:15.928Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20statistics%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12410</link>
      <description>The web server component of TIBCO Software Inc's Spotfire Statistics Services contains multiple vulnerabilities that may allow the remote execution of code. Without needing to authenticate, an attacker may be able to remotely execute code with the permissions of the system account used to run the web server component. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services versions up to and including 7.11.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12410|2024-09-16T17:04:15.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43055|2024-09-16T20:03:47.637Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20eftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43055</link>
      <description>The eFTL Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows clients to inherit the permissions of the client that initially connected on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43055|2024-09-16T20:03:47.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 18:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41559|2024-09-16T16:38:27.617Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20nimbus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41559</link>
      <description>The Web Client component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Nimbus contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to exploit an open redirect on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Nimbus: version 10.5.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41559|2024-09-16T16:38:27.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 01:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23271|2024-09-16T20:07:21.003Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23271</link>
      <description>The TIBCO EBX Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) attack on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions 5.9.12 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23271|2024-09-16T20:07:21.003Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 18:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30577|2024-09-16T21:57:36.958Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30577</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions 6.0.0 through 6.0.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30577|2024-09-16T21:57:36.958Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 17:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17337|2024-09-16T21:02:56.222Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17337</link>
      <description>The Spotfire library component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an attacker to perform a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attack. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: version 10.6.0 and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 7.11.7 and below, versions 7.12.0, 7.13.0, 7.14.0, 10.0.0, 10.0.1, 10.1.0, 10.2.0, 10.2.1, 10.3.0, 10.3.1, 10.3.2, 10.3.3, and 10.3.4, versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, and 10.6.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17337|2024-09-16T21:02:56.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 20:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28827|2024-09-16T16:32:29.141Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20administrator%20-%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28827</link>
      <description>The Administration GUI component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux, TIBCO Runtime Agent, TIBCO Runtime Agent, TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux, and TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker to social engineer a legitimate user with network access to execute a Stored XSS attack targeting the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Administrator - Enterprise Edition for z/Linux: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Runtime Agent: versions 5.10.2 and below, TIBCO Runtime Agent: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1, TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux: versions 5.10.2 and below, and TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux: versions 5.11.0 and 5.11.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28827|2024-09-16T16:32:29.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 18:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22777|2024-09-16T16:49:14.776Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20businessconnect%20trading%20community%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22777</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management contains easily exploitable Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management: versions 6.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22777|2024-09-16T16:49:14.776Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12416|2024-09-16T20:51:58.488Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20datasynapse%20gridserver%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12416</link>
      <description>The GridServer Broker and GridServer Director components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO DataSynapse GridServer Manager contain vulnerabilities which may allow an unauthenticated user to perform cross-site request forgery (CSRF). Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO DataSynapse GridServer Manager: versions up to and including 5.2.0; 6.0.0; 6.0.1; 6.0.2; 6.1.0; 6.1.1; 6.2.0; 6.3.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12416|2024-09-16T20:51:58.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5434|2024-09-16T20:31:50.987Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20runtime%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5434</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Designer component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Runtime Agent, and TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux contains vulnerabilities wherein a malicious user could perform XML external entity expansion (XXE) attacks to disclose host machine information. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Runtime Agent: versions up to and including 5.10.0, and TIBCO Runtime Agent for z/Linux: versions up to and including 5.9.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5434|2024-09-16T20:31:50.987Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27148|2024-09-16T16:22:54.482Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx%20add-ons
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27148</link>
      <description>The TIBCO EBX Add-on for Oracle Hyperion EPM, TIBCO EBX Data Exchange Add-on, and TIBCO EBX Insight Add-on components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute an XML External Entity (XXE) attack. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions 4.4.2 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27148|2024-09-16T16:22:54.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 18:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17332|2024-09-16T20:37:36.265Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx%20add-ons
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17332</link>
      <description>The Digital Asset Manager Web Interface component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows authenticated users to perform stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions up to and including 3.20.13, versions 4.1.0, 4.2.0, 4.2.1, and 4.2.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17332|2024-09-16T20:37:36.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 19:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43046|2024-09-16T18:54:31.908Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20partnerexpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43046</link>
      <description>The Interior Server and Gateway Server components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress contain an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to obtain session tokens for the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress: versions 6.2.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43046|2024-09-16T18:54:31.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 17:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11212|2024-09-16T19:41:44.955Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20mdm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11212</link>
      <description>The MDM server component of TIBCO Software Inc's TIBCO MDM contains multiple vulnerabilities that theoretically allow an authenticated user with specific roles to perform cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. This issue affects TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO MDM version 9.0.1 and prior versions; version 9.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11212|2024-09-16T19:41:44.955Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 14:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11206|2024-09-16T18:13:40.717Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11206</link>
      <description>The Spotfire library component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains vulnerabilities that theoretically allow a malicious user to undermine the integrity of comments and bookmarks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions up to and including 10.2.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions up to and including 7.11.2; 7.12.0; 7.13.0; 7.14.0; 10.0.0; 10.0.1; 10.1.0; and 10.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11206|2024-09-16T18:13:40.717Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 19:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5528|2024-09-16T16:58:24.595Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5528</link>
      <description>Multiple JasperReports Server components contain vulnerabilities which may allow authorized users to perform cross-site scripting (XSS) and cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks.  The impact of this vulnerability includes the theoretical disclosure of sensitive information.  Affects TIBCO JasperReports Server (versions 6.1.1 and below, 6.2.0, 6.2.1, and 6.3.0), TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition (versions 6.3.0 and below), TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM (versions 6.2.0 and below), TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy (versions 6.2.0 and below), and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS (versions 6.2.0 and below).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5528|2024-09-16T16:58:24.595Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30579|2024-09-16T20:38:01.508Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30579</link>
      <description>The Web Player component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute blind Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: version 12.0.0 and TIBCO Spotfire Server: version 12.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30579|2024-09-16T20:38:01.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 18:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17335|2024-09-16T20:58:01.616Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17335</link>
      <description>The Data access layer component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains multiple vulnerabilities that theoretically allow an attacker access to data cached from a data source, or a portion of a data source, that the attacker should not have access to. The attacker would need privileges to save a Spotfire file to the library. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: version 10.6.0 and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 7.11.7 and below, versions 7.12.0, 7.13.0, 7.14.0, 10.0.0, 10.0.1, 10.1.0, 10.2.0, 10.2.1, 10.3.0, 10.3.1, 10.3.2, 10.3.3, and 10.3.4, versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, and 10.6.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17335|2024-09-16T20:58:01.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 20:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12414|2024-09-16T21:04:22.688Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20rendezvous
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12414</link>
      <description>The Rendezvous Routing Daemon (rvrd), Rendezvous Secure Routing Daemon (rvrsd), Rendezvous Secure Daemon (rvsd), Rendezvous Cache (rvcache), and Rendezvous Daemon Manager (rvdm) components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Rendezvous, TIBCO Rendezvous Developer Edition, TIBCO Rendezvous for z/Linux, TIBCO Rendezvous for z/OS, TIBCO Rendezvous Network Server, TIBCO Substation ES contain vulnerabilities which may allow an attacker to perform cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Rendezvous: versions up to and including 8.4.5, TIBCO Rendezvous Developer Edition: versions up to and including 8.4.5, TIBCO Rendezvous for z/Linux: versions up to and including 8.4.5, TIBCO Rendezvous for z/OS: versions up to and including 8.4.5, TIBCO Rendezvous Network Server: versions up to and including 1.1.2, and TIBCO Substation ES: versions up to and including 2.12.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12414|2024-09-16T21:04:22.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11210|2024-09-16T19:20:22.104Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20enterprise%20runtime%20for%20r%20-%20server%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11210</link>
      <description>The server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition, and TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an unauthenticated user to bypass access controls and remotely execute code using the operating system account hosting the affected component. This issue affects: TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition versions 1.2.0 and below, and TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace versions 10.4.0 and 10.5.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11210|2024-09-16T19:20:22.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 22:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5530|2024-09-16T17:39:02.481Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibbr%20community
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5530</link>
      <description>The tibbr web server components of tibbr Community, and tibbr Enterprise contain SAML protocol handling errors which may allow authorized users to impersonate other users, and therefore escalate their access privileges. Affected releases are tibbr Community 5.2.1 and below; 6.0.0; 6.0.1; 7.0.0, tibbr Enterprise 5.2.1 and below; 6.0.0; 6.0.1; 7.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5530|2024-09-16T17:39:02.481Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28819|2024-09-16T22:20:44.364Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28819</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28819|2024-09-16T22:20:44.364Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 20:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28826|2024-09-16T19:15:38.507Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20messaging%20-%20eclipse%20mosquitto%20distribution%20-%20bridge%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28826</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Messaging - Eclipse Mosquitto Distribution - Bridge - Community Edition and TIBCO Messaging - Eclipse Mosquitto Distribution - Bridge - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Messaging - Eclipse Mosquitto Distribution - Bridge - Community Edition: versions 1.3.0 and below and TIBCO Messaging - Eclipse Mosquitto Distribution - Bridge - Enterprise Edition: versions 1.3.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28826|2024-09-16T19:15:38.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 16:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22778|2024-09-16T18:24:03.196Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20businessconnect%20trading%20community%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22778</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management: versions 6.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22778|2024-09-16T18:24:03.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 17:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30573|2024-09-16T16:48:53.136Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30573</link>
      <description>The ftlserver component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a privilege escalation on the affected ftlserver. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.8.0, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.0.1 through 6.8.0, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.7.3, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: version 6.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30573|2024-09-16T16:48:53.136Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 17:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12415|2024-09-16T20:22:46.057Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20enterprise%20message%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12415</link>
      <description>The Central Administration server (emsca) component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Message Service, TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Community Edition, and TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Developer Edition contains a vulnerability which may allow an attacker to perform cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Message Service: versions 8.4.0 and below, TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Community Edition: versions 8.4.0 and below, and TIBCO Enterprise Message Service - Developer Edition: versions 8.4.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12415|2024-09-16T20:22:46.057Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9415|2024-09-16T17:04:04.831Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20virtualization
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9415</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Data Virtualization Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a malicious authenticated user to download any arbitrary file from the affected system. The user must be authenticated and have privileges required to monitor the server in an operational capacity. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization: versions 7.0.8 and below, versions 8.0.0, 8.1.0, 8.1.1, and 8.2.0 and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.2.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9415|2024-09-16T17:04:04.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 18:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30578|2024-09-16T20:21:52.794Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx%20add-ons
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30578</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions 5.4.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30578|2024-09-16T20:21:52.794Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 17:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23275|2024-09-16T20:53:10.445Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20enterprise%20runtime%20for%20r%20-%20server%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23275</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services, and TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition: versions 1.2.4 and below, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition: versions 1.3.0 and 1.3.1, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition: versions 1.4.0, 1.5.0, and 1.6.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions 11.3.0 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 10.3.12 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, 10.6.0, 10.6.1, 10.7.0, 10.8.0, 10.8.1, 10.9.0, 10.10.0, 10.10.1, 10.10.2, 10.10.3, and 10.10.4, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 11.0.0, 11.1.0, 11.2.0, and 11.3.0, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services: versions 10.3.0 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services: versions 10.10.0, 10.10.1, and 10.10.2, and TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services: versions 11.1.0, 11.2.0, and 11.3.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23275|2024-09-16T20:53:10.445Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 17:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5527|2024-09-16T19:46:16.352Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5527</link>
      <description>TIBCO Spotfire Server 7.0.X before 7.0.2, 7.5.x before 7.5.1, 7.6.x before 7.6.1, 7.7.x before 7.7.1, and 7.8.x before 7.8.1 and Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace 7.8.0 and earlier contain multiple vulnerabilities which may allow authorized users to perform SQL injection attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5527|2024-09-16T19:46:16.352Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27147|2024-09-16T19:40:52.297Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20partnerexpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27147</link>
      <description>The REST API component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to obtain an authenticated login URL for the affected system via a REST API. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress: version 6.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27147|2024-09-16T19:40:52.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 17:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9408|2024-09-16T22:30:59.464Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9408</link>
      <description>The Spotfire library component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an attacker with write permissions to the Spotfire Library, but not "Script Author" group permission, to modify attributes of files and objects saved to the library such that the system treats them as trusted. This could allow an attacker to cause the Spotfire Web Player, Analyst clients, and TERR Service into executing arbitrary code with the privileges of the system account that started those processes. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions 10.8.0 and below and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 7.11.9 and below, versions 7.12.0, 7.13.0, 7.14.0, 10.0.0, 10.0.1, 10.1.0, 10.2.0, 10.3.0, 10.3.1, 10.3.2, 10.3.3, 10.3.4, 10.3.5, and 10.3.6, versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, 10.6.0, 10.6.1, 10.7.0, and 10.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9408|2024-09-16T22:30:59.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 19:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30570|2024-09-16T18:18:20.062Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20virtualization
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30570</link>
      <description>The Column Based Security component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to obtain read access to application information on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization: versions 8.5.2 and below and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.5.2 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30570|2024-09-16T18:18:20.062Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 17:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18815|2024-09-16T16:12:36.076Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18815</link>
      <description>The REST API component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows unauthenticated users to bypass authorization checks for portions of the HTTP interface to the JasperReports Server. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.3; 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 7.1.0, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 7.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18815|2024-09-16T16:12:36.076Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22776|2024-09-16T19:05:25.021Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20businessconnect%20trading%20community%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22776</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management contains easily exploitable vulnerabilities that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the affected system. A successful attack using these vulnerabilities requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management: versions 6.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22776|2024-09-16T19:05:25.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28825|2024-09-16T20:37:10.067Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20messaging%20-%20eclipse%20mosquitto%20distribution%20-%20core%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28825</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Messaging - Eclipse Mosquitto Distribution - Core - Community Edition and TIBCO Messaging - Eclipse Mosquitto Distribution - Core - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Messaging - Eclipse Mosquitto Distribution - Core - Community Edition: versions 1.3.0 and below and TIBCO Messaging - Eclipse Mosquitto Distribution - Core - Enterprise Edition: versions 1.3.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28825|2024-09-16T20:37:10.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 16:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28823|2024-09-16T18:08:48.731Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20eftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28823</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28823|2024-09-16T18:08:48.731Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 20:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35495|2024-09-16T18:12:56.880Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35495</link>
      <description>The Scheduler Connection component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker with network access to obtain FTP server passwords for other users of the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.2.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.5.0 and 7.5.1, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.8.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.9.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 7.8.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.9.0 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 7.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35495|2024-09-16T18:12:56.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 17:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30575|2024-09-16T17:29:00.246Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20science%20-%20workbench
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30575</link>
      <description>The Web Console component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science - Workbench, TIBCO Statistica, TIBCO Statistica - Estore Edition, and TIBCO Statistica Trial contains easily exploitable Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow a low privileged attacker with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science - Workbench: versions 14.0.0 and below, TIBCO Statistica: versions 14.0.0 and below, TIBCO Statistica - Estore Edition: versions 14.0.0 and below, and TIBCO Statistica Trial: versions 14.0.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30575|2024-09-16T17:29:00.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 17:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9410|2024-09-16T19:24:39.249Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20library
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9410</link>
      <description>The report generator component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Library, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an attacker to exploit HTML injection to gain full control of a web interface containing the output of the report generator component with the privileges of any user that views the affected report(s). The attacker can theoretically exploit this vulnerability when other users view a maliciously generated report, where those reports use Fusion Charts and a data source with contents controlled by the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Library: versions 7.1.1 and below, versions 7.2.0 and 7.2.1, version 7.3.0, version 7.5.0, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.1.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.1.1 and below, version 7.2.0, version 7.5.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.5.0 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.1.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9410|2024-09-16T19:24:39.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 12:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17334|2024-09-16T18:39:10.409Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analyst
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17334</link>
      <description>The Visualizations component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, and TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an attacker with permission to write DXP files to the Spotfire library to remotely execute code of their choice on the user account of other users who access the affected system. This attack is a risk only when the attacker has write access to a network file system shared with the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions 7.11.1 and below, versions 7.12.0, 7.13.0, 7.14.0, 10.0.0, 10.1.0, 10.2.0, 10.3.0, 10.3.1, and 10.3.2, versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, and 10.6.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: version 10.6.0, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit: versions 7.11.1 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions 7.11.1 and below, versions 7.12.0, 7.13.0, 7.14.0, 10.0.0, 10.1.0, 10.2.0, 10.3.0, 10.3.1, and 10.3.2, versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, and 10.6.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs: versions 7.11.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17334|2024-09-16T18:39:10.409Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 20:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28824|2024-09-16T17:08:34.597Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activespaces%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28824</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition, and TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition: versions 4.5.0 and below, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition: versions 4.5.0 and below, and TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition: versions 4.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28824|2024-09-16T17:08:34.597Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 20:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18807|2024-09-16T19:51:25.569Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20statistica%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18807</link>
      <description>The web application of the TIBCO Statistica component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Statistica Server contains vulnerabilities which may allow an authenticated user to perform cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Statistica Server versions up to and including 13.4.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18807|2024-09-16T19:51:25.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35500|2024-09-16T16:18:36.002Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20virtualization
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35500</link>
      <description>The Data Virtualization Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization, TIBCO Data Virtualization, TIBCO Data Virtualization, and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with local access to download arbitrary files outside of the scope of the user's permissions on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Virtualization: versions 8.3.0 and below, TIBCO Data Virtualization: version 8.4.0, TIBCO Data Virtualization: version 8.5.0, and TIBCO Data Virtualization for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35500|2024-09-16T16:18:36.002Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 18:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9416|2024-09-16T19:20:42.329Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analyst
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9416</link>
      <description>The Spotfire client component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a legitimate user to inject scripts. If executed by a victim authenticated to the affected system these scripts will be executed at the privileges of the victim. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions 10.7.0, 10.8.0, 10.9.0, and 10.10.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions 10.7.0, 10.8.0, 10.8.1, 10.9.0, 10.10.0, and 10.10.1, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions 10.7.0, 10.8.0, 10.9.0, and 10.10.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 10.7.0, 10.8.0, 10.8.1, 10.9.0, 10.10.0, and 10.10.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9416|2024-09-16T19:20:42.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 18:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30574|2024-09-16T18:49:54.765Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30574</link>
      <description>The ftlserver component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with local access to obtain user credentials to the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.8.0, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.0.1 through 6.8.0, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.7.3, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: version 6.8.0, TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.8.0, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.0.1 through 6.8.0, TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.7.3, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition: version 6.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30574|2024-09-16T18:49:54.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 17:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8987|2024-09-16T16:22:55.424Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20data%20science%20for%20aws
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8987</link>
      <description>The application server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science for AWS, and TIBCO Spotfire Data Science contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that theoretically allows an authenticated user to gain access to all the capabilities of the web interface available to more privileged users. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Data Science for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Data Science: versions up to and including 6.4.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8987|2024-09-16T16:22:55.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 17:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35498|2024-09-16T17:32:55.642Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35498</link>
      <description>The TIBCO EBX Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX, TIBCO EBX, TIBCO EBX, and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX contains a vulnerability that under certain specific conditions allows an attacker to enter a password other than the legitimate password and it will be accepted as valid. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions 5.8.123 and below, TIBCO EBX: versions 5.9.3, 5.9.4, 5.9.5, 5.9.6, 5.9.7, 5.9.8, 5.9.9, 5.9.10, 5.9.11, 5.9.12, 5.9.13, and 5.9.14, TIBCO EBX: versions 6.0.0 and 6.0.1, and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX: version 1.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35498|2024-09-16T17:32:55.642Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 16:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23272|2024-09-16T17:38:34.192Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20bpm%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23272</link>
      <description>The Application Development Clients component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BPM Enterprise and TIBCO BPM Enterprise Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) attack on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BPM Enterprise: versions 4.3.0 and below and TIBCO BPM Enterprise Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions 4.3.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23272|2024-09-16T17:38:34.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 18:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5532|2024-09-16T20:48:07.136Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5532</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the report renderer component of TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO JasperReports Library, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio for ActiveMatrix BPM may allow a subset of authorized users to perform persistent cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO JasperReports Server 6.2.3 and below; 6.3.0; 6.3.1; 6.3.2; 6.4.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition 6.4.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM 6.4.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Library 6.2.3 and below; 6.3.0; 6.3.1; 6.3.2; 6.4.0; 6.4.1, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM 6.4.1 and below, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy 6.4.0 and below, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS 6.4.0 and below, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio 6.2.3 and below; 6.3.0; 6.3.1; 6.3.2; 6.4.0, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio for ActiveMatrix BPM 6.4.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5532|2024-09-16T20:48:07.136Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8990|2024-09-16T17:03:00.302Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activematrix%20businessworks
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8990</link>
      <description>The HTTP Connector component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows unauthenticated HTTP requests to be processed by the BusinessWorks engine even when authentication is required. This possibility is restricted to circumstances where HTTP "Basic Authentication" policy is used in conjunction with an XML Authentication resource. The BusinessWorks engine might instead use credentials from a prior HTTP request for authorization purposes. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks: versions up to and including 6.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8990|2024-09-16T17:03:00.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 17:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11204|2024-09-16T17:53:03.664Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20statistics%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11204</link>
      <description>The web interface component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services contains a vulnerability that might theoretically allow an authenticated user to access sensitive information needed by the Spotfire Statistics Services server. The sensitive information that might be affected includes database, JMX, LDAP, Windows service account, and user credentials. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services: versions up to and including 7.11.1; 10.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11204|2024-09-16T17:53:03.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 19:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22772|2024-09-16T21:08:01.606Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20managed%20file%20transfer%20platform%20server%20for%20unix
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22772</link>
      <description>The cfsend, cfrecv, and CyberResp components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for UNIX and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for z/Linux contain a difficult to exploit Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute arbitrary code on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for UNIX: versions 8.1.0 and below and TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for z/Linux: versions 8.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22772|2024-09-16T21:08:01.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 16:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8991|2024-09-16T18:39:49.437Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activematrix%20bpm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8991</link>
      <description>The administrator web interface of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Policy Director, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Bus, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Grid, TIBCO Silver Fabric Enabler for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO Silver Fabric Enabler for ActiveMatrix Service Grid contains multiple vulnerabilities that may allow for cross-site scripting (XSS) and cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 4.2.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions up to and including 4.2.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Policy Director: versions up to and including 1.1.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Bus: versions up to and including 3.3.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Grid: versions up to and including 3.3.1, TIBCO Silver Fabric Enabler for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 1.4.1, and TIBCO Silver Fabric Enabler for ActiveMatrix Service Grid: versions up to and including 1.3.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8991|2024-09-16T18:39:49.437Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 20:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18808|2024-09-16T19:46:17.061Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18808</link>
      <description>The domain management component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a race-condition vulnerability that may allow any users with domain save privileges to gain superuser privileges. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.3.4; 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.3; 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 7.1.0, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 7.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18808|2024-09-16T19:46:17.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8993|2024-09-16T19:46:19.863Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activematrix%20bpm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8993</link>
      <description>The administrative web server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Policy Director, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Bus, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Grid, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Grid Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric, TIBCO Silver Fabric Enabler for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO Silver Fabric Enabler for ActiveMatrix Service Grid contains a vulnerability that could theoretically allow an unauthenticated user to download a file with credentials information. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 4.2.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix BPM Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions up to and including 4.2.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Policy Director: versions up to and including 1.1.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Bus: versions up to and including 3.3.0, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Grid: versions up to and including 3.3.1, TIBCO ActiveMatrix Service Grid Distribution for TIBCO Silver Fabric: versions up to and including 3.3.0, TIBCO Silver Fabric Enabler for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 1.4.1, and TIBCO Silver Fabric Enabler for ActiveMatrix Service Grid: versions up to and including 1.3.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8993|2024-09-16T19:46:19.863Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 20:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41560|2024-09-16T20:02:37.195Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20nimbus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41560</link>
      <description>The Statement Set Upload via the Web Client component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Nimbus contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a Denial of Service Attack on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Nimbus: version 10.5.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41560|2024-09-16T20:02:37.195Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 01:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
