<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for IBM i</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./tibco%20managed%20file%20transfer%20platform%20server%20for%20ibm%20i.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for IBM i</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 12:25:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9411|2024-08-04T10:26:16.111Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20managed%20file%20transfer%20platform%20server%20for%20ibm%20i
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9411</link>
      <description>The file transfer component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for IBM i contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an attacker to perform unauthorized network file transfers to and from the file system accessible to the affected component. This vulnerability is exploitable when the configuration option 'Require Node Resp' is set to 'No'. In the event of a successful exploit, the attacker could theoretically read and write any file on the file system accessible to the affected component, thus fully affecting the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the operating system hosting the deployment of the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for IBM i: versions 7.1.0 and below, version 8.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9411|2024-08-04T10:26:16.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9412|2024-08-04T10:26:16.380Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20managed%20file%20transfer%20platform%20server%20for%20ibm%20i
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9412</link>
      <description>The file transfer component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for IBM i contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows execution of arbitrary commands at the privilege level of the affected system following a failed file transfer. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Managed File Transfer Platform Server for IBM i: versions 7.1.0 and below, version 8.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9412|2024-08-04T10:26:16.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
