<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./tibco%20enterprise%20runtime%20for%20r%20-%20server%20edition.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23275|2024-08-03T19:05:55.635Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20enterprise%20runtime%20for%20r%20-%20server%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23275</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services, and TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition: versions 1.2.4 and below, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition: versions 1.3.0 and 1.3.1, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition: versions 1.4.0, 1.5.0, and 1.6.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions 11.3.0 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 10.3.12 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, 10.6.0, 10.6.1, 10.7.0, 10.8.0, 10.8.1, 10.9.0, 10.10.0, 10.10.1, 10.10.2, 10.10.3, and 10.10.4, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 11.0.0, 11.1.0, 11.2.0, and 11.3.0, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services: versions 10.3.0 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services: versions 10.10.0, 10.10.1, and 10.10.2, and TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services: versions 11.1.0, 11.2.0, and 11.3.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23275|2024-08-03T19:05:55.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28830|2024-08-03T21:55:11.597Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20enterprise%20runtime%20for%20r%20-%20server%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28830</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Spotfire Server and TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Server, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services, and TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from the affected component searching for run-time artifacts outside of the installation hierarchy. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition: versions 1.2.4 and below, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition: versions 1.3.0 and 1.3.1, TIBCO Enterprise Runtime for R - Server Edition: versions 1.4.0, 1.5.0, and 1.6.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions 11.3.0 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 10.3.12 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, 10.6.0, 10.6.1, 10.7.0, 10.8.0, 10.8.1, 10.9.0, 10.10.0, 10.10.1, 10.10.2, 10.10.3, and 10.10.4, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 11.0.0, 11.1.0, 11.2.0, and 11.3.0, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services: versions 10.3.0 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services: versions 10.10.0, 10.10.1, and 10.10.2, and TIBCO Spotfire Statistics Services: versions 11.1.0, 11.2.0, and 11.3.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28830|2024-08-03T21:55:11.597Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
