<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO Rendezvous</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./tibco%20rendezvous.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO Rendezvous</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:25:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28817|2024-09-17T00:51:51.446Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20rendezvous
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28817</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Rendezvous and TIBCO Rendezvous Developer Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Rendezvous: versions 8.5.1 and below and TIBCO Rendezvous Developer Edition: versions 8.5.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28817|2024-09-17T00:51:51.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 20:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28818|2024-09-17T00:55:50.824Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20rendezvous
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28818</link>
      <description>The Rendezvous Routing Daemon (rvrd), Rendezvous Secure Routing Daemon (rvrsd), Rendezvous Secure Daemon (rvsd), Rendezvous Cache (rvcache), Rendezvous Secure C API, Rendezvous Java API, and Rendezvous .Net API components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Rendezvous and TIBCO Rendezvous Developer Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from the affected component searching for run-time artifacts outside of the installation hierarchy. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Rendezvous: versions 8.5.1 and below and TIBCO Rendezvous Developer Edition: versions 8.5.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28818|2024-09-17T00:55:50.824Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 20:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
