<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO EBX</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./tibco%20ebx.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO EBX</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22769|2024-08-03T03:21:49.075Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22769</link>
      <description>The Web server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX, TIBCO EBX, TIBCO EBX, TIBCO EBX Add-ons, TIBCO EBX Add-ons, TIBCO EBX Add-ons, and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions 5.8.124 and below, TIBCO EBX: versions 5.9.3, 5.9.4, 5.9.5, 5.9.6, 5.9.7, 5.9.8, 5.9.9, 5.9.10, 5.9.11, 5.9.12, 5.9.13, 5.9.14, and 5.9.15, TIBCO EBX: versions 6.0.0, 6.0.1, 6.0.2, and 6.0.3, TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions 3.20.18 and below, TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions 4.1.0, 4.2.0, 4.2.1, 4.2.2, 4.3.0, 4.3.1, 4.3.2, 4.3.3, 4.3.4, 4.4.0, 4.4.1, 4.4.2, 4.4.3, 4.5.0, 4.5.1, 4.5.2, 4.5.3, 4.5.4, 4.5.5, and 4.5.6, TIBCO EBX Add-ons: versions 5.0.0, 5.0.1, 5.1.0, 5.1.1, and 5.2.0, and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX: versions 1.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22769|2024-08-03T03:21:49.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23271|2024-08-03T19:05:54.516Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23271</link>
      <description>The TIBCO EBX Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) attack on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions 5.9.12 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23271|2024-08-03T19:05:54.516Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30577|2024-08-03T06:56:12.860Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30577</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions 6.0.0 through 6.0.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30577|2024-08-03T06:56:12.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41565|2024-08-03T12:49:43.191Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ebx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41565</link>
      <description>The Web Application component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a stored XSS on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions 5.9.21 and below, versions 6.0.11 and below and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX: versions 1.2.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41565|2024-08-03T12:49:43.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
