<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11206|2024-08-04T22:48:09.021Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11206</link>
      <description>The Spotfire library component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains vulnerabilities that theoretically allow a malicious user to undermine the integrity of comments and bookmarks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions up to and including 10.2.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions up to and including 7.11.2; 7.12.0; 7.13.0; 7.14.0; 10.0.0; 10.0.1; 10.1.0; and 10.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11206|2024-08-04T22:48:09.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11205|2024-08-04T22:48:08.367Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11205</link>
      <description>The web server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains vulnerabilities that theoretically allow reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: 7.14.0; 7.14.1; 10.0.0; 10.0.1; 10.1.0; 10.2.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: 7.14.0; 10.0.0; 10.0.1; 10.1.0; 10.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11205|2024-08-04T22:48:08.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9408|2024-08-04T10:26:16.100Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9408</link>
      <description>The Spotfire library component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an attacker with write permissions to the Spotfire Library, but not "Script Author" group permission, to modify attributes of files and objects saved to the library such that the system treats them as trusted. This could allow an attacker to cause the Spotfire Web Player, Analyst clients, and TERR Service into executing arbitrary code with the privileges of the system account that started those processes. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions 10.8.0 and below and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 7.11.9 and below, versions 7.12.0, 7.13.0, 7.14.0, 10.0.0, 10.0.1, 10.1.0, 10.2.0, 10.3.0, 10.3.1, 10.3.2, 10.3.3, 10.3.4, 10.3.5, and 10.3.6, versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, 10.6.0, 10.6.1, 10.7.0, and 10.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9408|2024-08-04T10:26:16.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
