<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 23:24:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11205|2024-09-17T00:05:43.567Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11205</link>
      <description>The web server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains vulnerabilities that theoretically allow reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: 7.14.0; 7.14.1; 10.0.0; 10.0.1; 10.1.0; 10.2.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: 7.14.0; 10.0.0; 10.0.1; 10.1.0; 10.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11205|2024-09-17T00:05:43.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 19:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18814|2024-09-17T01:20:31.366Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18814</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Spotfire authentication component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains a vulnerability in the handling of the authentication that theoretically may allow an attacker to gain full access to a target account, independent of configured authentication mechanisms. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions up to and including 10.0.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions up to and including 7.10.1; 7.11.0; 7.11.1; 7.12.0; 7.13.0; 7.14.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18814|2024-09-17T01:20:31.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5436|2024-09-17T01:26:22.747Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5436</link>
      <description>The Spotfire server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contain multiple vulnerabilities that may allow for the disclosure of information, including user and data source credentials. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions up to and including 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions up to and including 7.8.1; 7.9.0; 7.10.0; 7.11.0; 7.12.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5436|2024-09-17T01:26:22.747Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18812|2024-09-17T01:46:57.774Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18812</link>
      <description>The Spotfire Library component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains a vulnerability that might theoretically fail to restrict users with read-only access from modifying files stored in the Spotfire Library, only when the Spotfire Library is configured to use external storage. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace versions up to and including 10.0.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Server versions up to and including 7.10.1; 7.11.0; 7.11.1; 7.12.0; 7.13.0; 7.14.0; 10.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18812|2024-09-17T01:46:57.774Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17336|2024-09-17T02:06:23.402Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17336</link>
      <description>The Data access layer component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains multiple vulnerabilities that theoretically allow an attacker access to information that can lead to obtaining credentials used to access Spotfire data sources. The attacker would need privileges to save a Spotfire file to the library, and only applies in a situation where NTLM credentials, or a credentials profile is in use. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: version 10.6.0 and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions 7.11.7 and below, versions 7.12.0, 7.13.0, 7.14.0, 10.0.0, 10.0.1, 10.1.0, 10.2.0, 10.2.1, 10.3.0, 10.3.1, 10.3.2, 10.3.3, and 10.3.4, versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, and 10.6.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17336|2024-09-17T02:06:23.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 20:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18813|2024-09-17T00:51:13.618Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analytics%20platform%20for%20aws%20marketplace
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18813</link>
      <description>The Spotfire web server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO Spotfire Server contains multiple vulnerabilities that may allow persistent and reflected cross-site scripting attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions up to and including 10.0.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Server: versions up to and including 7.10.1; 7.11.0; 7.11.1; 7.12.0; 7.13.0; 7.14.0; 10.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18813|2024-09-17T00:51:13.618Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
