<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO Spotfire Analyst</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./tibco%20spotfire%20analyst.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO Spotfire Analyst</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:22:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5437|2024-08-05T05:33:44.438Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analyst
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5437</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Spotfire Client and TIBCO Spotfire Web Player Client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, and TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs contain multiple vulnerabilities that may allow for unauthorized information disclosure. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0; 7.9.1; 7.10.0; 7.10.1; 7.11.0; 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions up to and including 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0;7.9.1;7.10.0;7.10.1;7.11.0; 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0; 7.9.1; 7.10.0; 7.10.1; 7.11.0;7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0; 7.9.1; 7.10.0; 7.10.1; 7.11.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5437|2024-08-05T05:33:44.438Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5435|2024-08-05T05:33:44.385Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analyst
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5435</link>
      <description>The TIBCO Spotfire Client and TIBCO Spotfire Web Player Client components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, and TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs contain multiple vulnerabilities that may allow for remote code execution. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0; 7.9.1; 7.10.0; 7.10.1; 7.11.0; 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: versions up to and including 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0;7.9.1;7.10.0;7.10.1;7.11.0; 7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0; 7.9.1; 7.10.0; 7.10.1; 7.11.0;7.12.0, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs: versions up to and including 7.8.0; 7.9.0; 7.9.1; 7.10.0; 7.10.1; 7.11.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5435|2024-08-05T05:33:44.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17334|2024-08-05T01:40:14.457Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20spotfire%20analyst
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17334</link>
      <description>The Visualizations component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop, and TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an attacker with permission to write DXP files to the Spotfire library to remotely execute code of their choice on the user account of other users who access the affected system. This attack is a risk only when the attacker has write access to a network file system shared with the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO Spotfire Analyst: versions 7.11.1 and below, versions 7.12.0, 7.13.0, 7.14.0, 10.0.0, 10.1.0, 10.2.0, 10.3.0, 10.3.1, and 10.3.2, versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, and 10.6.0, TIBCO Spotfire Analytics Platform for AWS Marketplace: version 10.6.0, TIBCO Spotfire Deployment Kit: versions 7.11.1 and below, TIBCO Spotfire Desktop: versions 7.11.1 and below, versions 7.12.0, 7.13.0, 7.14.0, 10.0.0, 10.1.0, 10.2.0, 10.3.0, 10.3.1, and 10.3.2, versions 10.4.0, 10.5.0, and 10.6.0, and TIBCO Spotfire Desktop Language Packs: versions 7.11.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17334|2024-08-05T01:40:14.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
